Nope. Nope. Nope.
Nope. Nope. Nope!
Nope.
Huh?
Found it!
The tent!
This doesn't seem right.
It's so cold!
I can't camp with this.
Mount Fuji...
It's Saitou-san!
I think Rin's camping here today
Onee-chan!
Are you taking the car?
I am, but what's with all the stuff?
Can you give me a ride?
Thanks, Onee-chan!
Isn't that the check-in over there?
Be right back.
Onee-chan...
It costs money.
Hup!
Rin-chan!
Let's make hot pot!
ma
Open
window
and,
ta
ra
ah
bright
Open
light
window
ta
and,
ra
ah
bright
light
ya
Bathe
sa
shii
in
hi
the
za
light
shi
sun's
ip
gentle
pai
Bathe
rays
shii
the
hi
za
sun's
shi
ip
gentle
pai
ni
a
bi
rays
su
Wonderful
te
expectations,
Wonderful
expectations,
bit,
mu
fill
heart
bit,
mu
fill
heart
Push
wa
ra
open
na
i
the
hi
door
Push
bi
of
no
ka
unchanging
to
bi
days
open
door
bi
no
of
to
unchanging
bi
ra
wo
a
days
once
no
your
mu
eyes
kou
adjust
light
once
ka
ri
your
no
eyes
mu
adjust
kou
ma
to
the
light
right
Right
now
de
ha
we're
ji
ma
taking
ri
our
Right
no
first
i
ppo
step
right
now
ha
ji
we're
ma
ri
no
taking
i
our
first
step
ppo
shi
Shiny
ny
days
a
blow
ta
ra
in
Shiny
shii
with
ka
ze
a
new
wind
shi
days
ny
blow
days
a
in
ta
ra
with
shii
a
new
ka
wind
ha
Bounce
skip
na
step
along
Bounce
fun
the
de
trail
skip
you
na
along
step
the
fun
trail
feel
su
the
ki
too
clear
ru
Can
skies?
so
ra
you
can
feel
the
su
ki
clear
too
ru
skies?
excitement
hearts
re
te
mu
will
ku
na
take
excitement
brand
us
new
to
world
sa
a
brand
new
wa
world
in
gi
our
ga
hearts
tsu
re
will
take
brand
new
world
Li
sten
sten
-off
dy
e
echoes
whistling
-off
bu
echoes
e
hi
of
bi
whistling
leap
sou
into
mi
ra
the
i
future
e
And
to
bi
leap
da
sou
mi
into
ra
i
the
future
e
Episode 3
Mount Fuji and Relaxed Hot Pot Camp
Hot pot?
Yep!
Gyoza hot pot.
Nothing beats hot pot in the winter.
I bet it's even better when you eat it outside!
Napa cabbage, green onions,
garlic chives, tofu,
bean sprouts, gyoza...
Do you need any help?
Nope, I'm good! Just relax.
But...
Don't worry.
It's just cut, dump, and boil!
Now I am worried.
Hey, you didn't bike here, did you?
We're 40 kilometers from Nanbu.
Nah.
My sister drove me here.
Oh, the kiwi lady.
I'm staying overnight this time
and camping for real.
I don't have a tent though,
so I'm sleeping in the car.
I brought a futon and everything.
Really?
Hold on,
am I still camping for real if I sleep in the car?
Probably.
You'll just be like those people.
A lot of RV campers sleep in their vehicles.
Oh, you're right.
Wait, what about your sister?
She went to Fujinomiya.
Going to hang out with her friends.
She should be back around nine—
It's pretty cold, huh?
I have some stick-on heat pads. Want one?
Thanks—
F-Fifteen hundred yen?
Forget about that already.
Use as many as you want.
You're making me hot pot, after all.
Can I?
Thanks!
But the cooking is to return the favor
from last time.
Last time?
The curry noodles.
Don't peek until it's done.
“Nadeshiko's Return of a Favor.”
Hey, Rin-chan, where are you
supposed to stick these?
Your eyes.
Heat pads are best applied to the base of the neck,
the pit of the stomach,
between the shoulder blades...
Thank you.
...or anywhere else with thick veins.
Wear a scarf and down jacket on top
for optimal results.
Can I lie down for a few minutes?
I don't think that's a good idea.
Kawamoto Liquors  Minobu Branch
P-Please and thank you!
Sure thing.
Actually, one of our regulars just quit,
so this is perfect.
You can show up in the evenings, right?
Uh, yes!
Do you live close by?
Have a seat on that box over there.
R-Roger!
Hey, you're from Motosu High School?
I went there too.
Oh, reall—
Was that on purpose?
No.
Kawamoto Liquors  Minobu Branch
Would you give me a hand, please?
Took you a while, huh?
Kawamoto Liquors
I'm so tired.
Did the interview go badly?
I got the job.
Me too.
D
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Looks like we'll have enough money
for club activities now.
Yeah.
We have a new member now, too,
so let's really go camping this winter!
Yeah!
Well, well, it should be about done, right?
It's bright red.
Dandan gyoza hot pot!
Don't worry. It's not really that spicy.
It looks hot, but it isn't.
A mildly hot pot, miss.
It's delicious.
Hawking samples at the supermarket, are you?
Here you are.
Dig in, dearie.
A country grandma, are you?
All right, let's eat!
Let's eat.
It's good.
Yes!
How's it? Warms you up good, don't it?
She likes the country grandma bit, huh?
Although...
The chili pepper really does have a pleasant kick.
It makes me all warm and cozy from the inside.
Warm and cozy...
It's hot!
As contents are fresh,
please consume as soon as possible
Outlet Store
Manufacturer Direct Sales
50 Pieces
Maruju Market
Did you happen to put in all of the gyoza?
Yep, I did!
Aren't Hamamatsu gyoza delicious?
I forgot to bring rice to finish with!
I can't eat that much.
She really does make it look good.
Hey...
Hm?
Sorry about the other day.
The other day?
Which one?
You invited me into your club, but I, well...
I sort of made a face.
I kind of got carried away, too.
Sorry for being so pushy.
Aoi-chan told me afterward...
“Rin-chan probably doesn't like camping
in a noisy group
as much as camping quietly alone.”
Well yeah, I suppose...
Then let's do this again.
A relaxed hot pot camp!
And if you ever feel like it,
we can camp with the others too.
All right, fine.
Although there are tons of supplies and stuff
that we need to stock up on first.
Wait, she finished all of it!
I brought potato chips. Want some?
You're still eating?
Mount Fuji's so nice at night, isn't it?
This area tends to get pretty foggy
in the early morning.
I've heard it makes Mount Fuji look dreamlike.
Although the fog only really appears
in the spring and summer...
Mount Fuji in the fog, huh?
I want to see that.
When's sunrise?
Around six, I think.
I don't know if I can get up for that.
I'll probably be asleep.
Want to try setting an alarm?
To see Mount Fuji.
No, I'd rather sleep.
You better not wake me up.
That was our last song of the night.
How did you like it?
Sunny skies across the country tomorrow,
but it'll be a chilly morning,
so remember to dress warmly when going out.
And with that, have a good weekend.
This is Itou, signing off.
Goodnight.
Nadeshiko, wake up.
Aren't you watching the sunrise?
I'm awake.
Yeah, I'm awake.
I'm going to get breakfast
from the convenience store.
What do you want?
Fried rice with fried meat, pudding,
fried chicken, potato chips,
baumkuchen, ice cream, and tonkotsu salt ramen.
Rice balls and tea, yeah?
It's wet.
So bright.
Well, whatever.
What are you smiling about?
N-Nothing.
Oh, now I know it was something.
I see, I see.
You went camping with Nadeshiko-chan, huh?
Weren't you the one behind it?
Now, now, it's all good.
You only go camping
during this time of year, right?
Yeah, and?
What's so good about camping in the winter?
It's way cold.
No bugs.
No sweating.
No other campers. It's quiet.
Campfires and hot springs feel good.
You can see clearly into the distance.
Soups taste good...
Those sorts of things.
Hot pot's good this time of year, isn't it?
I wish I could've tried some of Nadeshiko's cooking.
She ended up eating most of it herself.
Maybe I'll take Chikuwa and
come with you guys next time.
It's so cold, though.
I'll probably wait until it gets a little warmer.
It'll be another six months, then.
Hey, where are you going next?
Stare...
C'mon... I won't tell Nadeshiko-chan, okay?
Get up already.
I'm already awake, Rin-chan.
Wake up,
Nadeshiko.
The fresh air brushes across my brow
hitai ni kanjiru sunda kuuki
Each breath I blow is white
haku iki ga hazumu
Put one foot in front of the other and don't stop walking
tomaru koto mo naku aruki tsudzuketeita no
Turning back I finally see the first beams of light
koko de furikaeru mou sugu da yo
The sun rises
asahi ga noboru
I am on a journey
watashi wa tabi suru
To breathe in the freedom that comes with a new day
atarashii hi ni jiyuu wo suikondara
Let's sit down and huddle around a warm fire
atatakai hi wo kakonde suwarou
Chatting about all the silly things that come to mind
tawaimonai koto hanashi nagara
Room Camp
Room Camp!
Guys, check it out!
I got pictures of Mount Fuji!
Hey, isn't that Shimarin?
You two went together, huh?
Fuji
Fumoto Campgrounds
The view of Mount Fuji
from this campsite was so awesome!
Fuji
Fumoto Campgrounds
And this ice cream I had while viewing
Mount Fuji from the station was so good!
I even ended up buying a Mount Fuji T-shirt and mascot!
Mount Fuji
Is Love
You're all about Mount Fuji, aren't you?
Why not try climbing it if you like it so much?
No way, no way!
There's no way I could climb Mount Fuji!
Just watching it from afar is enough.
You sound like a girl with a crush.
You're all Fuji this, Fuji that.
From now on, you're “The Fuji Kid”.
The Fuji Kid?!
Sure!
Seriously?
Next Episode
The Outdoors Club and the Solo Camping Girl
When camping...
Always mind the campsite and facility rules.
Don't forget to clean up fires and take your trash!
It gets cold during the winter.
Stay warm and be well-prepared!!
Outdoor Activities Club