Come to think of it, I see this place on travel shows occasionally.
Well, it is a pretty famous hot spring.
Especially for opening early enough
that you can watch the sunrise while bathing.
The sunrise, huh?
That sounds nice!
The shower's so warm!
Aoi-chan, let's go to the outdoor baths.
Sure, let's go!
40 kilometers to go.
Maybe this was a little too ambitious
for my first trip.
It's cold.
Speaking of, didn't Nadeshiko say
she was going to visit a hot spring?
Hot springs...
Once I arrive, I'm definitely hitting one too!
Hot spring, hot spring,
hot spring!
ma
Open
window
and,
ta
ra
ah
bright
Open
light
window
ta
and,
ra
ah
bright
light
ya
Bathe
sa
shii
in
hi
the
za
light
shi
sun's
ip
gentle
pai
Bathe
rays
shii
the
hi
za
sun's
shi
ip
gentle
pai
ni
a
bi
rays
su
Wonderful
te
expectations,
Wonderful
expectations,
bit,
mu
fill
heart
bit,
mu
fill
heart
Push
wa
ra
open
na
i
the
hi
door
Push
bi
of
no
ka
unchanging
to
bi
days
open
door
bi
no
of
to
unchanging
bi
ra
wo
a
days
once
no
your
mu
eyes
kou
adjust
light
once
ka
ri
your
no
eyes
mu
adjust
kou
ma
to
the
light
right
Right
now
de
ha
we're
ji
ma
taking
ri
our
Right
no
first
i
ppo
step
right
now
ha
ji
we're
ma
ri
no
taking
i
our
first
step
ppo
shi
Shiny
ny
days
a
blow
ta
ra
in
Shiny
shii
with
ka
ze
a
new
wind
shi
days
ny
blow
days
a
in
ta
ra
with
shii
a
new
ka
wind
ha
Bounce
skip
na
step
along
Bounce
fun
the
de
trail
skip
you
na
along
step
the
fun
trail
feel
su
the
ki
too
clear
ru
Can
skies?
so
ra
you
can
feel
the
su
ki
clear
too
ru
skies?
excitement
hearts
re
te
mu
will
ku
na
take
excitement
brand
us
new
to
world
sa
a
brand
new
wa
world
in
gi
our
ga
hearts
tsu
re
will
take
brand
new
world
Li
sten
sten
-off
dy
e
echoes
whistling
-off
bu
echoes
e
hi
of
bi
whistling
leap
sou
into
mi
ra
the
i
future
e
And
to
bi
leap
da
sou
mi
into
ra
i
the
future
e
It's such a nice view...
Episode 5
The Two Camps, The Two's Views
Isn't it?
Hot springs are so nice in the winter.
Aki-chan, how much farther is it
to the campground?
About a kilometer, I think.
I told the manager that we'd arrive after noon,
so we've still got plenty of time here.
Oh, okay!
Oh no, that's the devil on your shoulder talking.
I wonder what Rin-chan's doing right now.
So cold!
Current
Temp.
I'm in heaven.
Restrooms
That was a good bath.
I don't even need my jumper anymore.
It looks like they serve real food here too.
Deep-Fried Hot Spring Eggs
White
Peach
Soft
Serve
Mildly
Sweet Milk
Soft
Serve
White
Peach
Soft
Serve
So it does.
Meal Ticket
Houtou requires about
20 minutes.
Thank you for your
understanding.
Houtou requires about
20 minutes.
Thank you for your
understanding.
Houtou takes
20 minutes!!
Houtou requires about
20 minutes.
Thank you for your
understanding.
Tsukimi soba for me.
I'll have the tsukimi udon.
I'll have...
Wait, we won't be able to eat
our camp food if we eat here!
Huh?!
Deep-Fried Hot Spring Eggs
The hot spring was so nice, our brains shut off.
You're right.
We must fear the hot spring.
Deep-Fried Hot Spring Eggs
Tasty deep-fried hot spring eggs.
Buy some?
Just some deep-fried eggs and that's it!
Yeah!
Time to eat!
Yummm!
How does just deep-frying an egg
make it this good?
The yolk's all runny!
This stuff is devastating to have right out of a bath.
Yeah, super devastating.
Just devastating.
Absolutely devastating.
I'm finally here.
The super scenic area known only to a few,
Takabocchi Highlands.
Apparently, you can see Matsumoto, Lake Suwa,
and even Mount Fuji all at once from the peak.
All right.
Only nine kilometers to the top!
I made it.
I rode 150 kilometers!
I'm beat
It's so peaceful.
There's nothing here.
I wonder if there are cows or something
in the summer.
It's freezing!
Now, then...
Let's head to the hot spring.
It should be just up ahead.
Takabocchi Mineral Springs
Still six more kilometers.
Curses!
Takabocchi Mineral Springs
Hi-yah!
Whoa, close one.
Hot spring, hot spring, hot spring!
Takabocchi Mineral Springs
Events
Rock Baths
Lodging
Day Use
Outdoor Baths
Relaxation
I'm here! The hot spring!
Clothes and a towel...
It's time to wash away
this cold and tiredness with a bath.
We are closed
as of October.
Takabocchi Mineral Springs
What? Seriously?
Hot... spring...
Hot spring...!
Takabocchi Highlands
Quasi-National Park
Japanese Alps
Panoramic Lookout
Matsumoto City.
Takabocchi Highlands
Quasi-National Park
Japanese Alps
Panoramic Lookout
Can't see a single thing whatsoever
through these clouds.
Talk about adding insult to injury.
Sniffle.
Might as well hike up since I'm here.
TL Note: Bocchi is slang for alone.
Taking on Takabocchi alone.
The hot spring was closed, the view was blocked...
I should've just camped closer to home.
Yatsugatake-Chuushin
Highlands
Quasi
National
Park
Mount
Takabocchi
1664.9 m
I reached the peak pretty quick.
Come on, you've got a perfect view right here.
It's so pretty.
I'll just visit a hot spring on the way back.
Besides, today's real goal was to make
some hot camp food! Let's go!
All right, where should I cook?
It's still too early to go to the campgrounds.
The vending machine's busted.
How about here?
No, let's look around a little more.
There's a pasture over here.
Here seems good.
First, the table and chair.
There.
I'll start with something simple.
Mega Tasty Milk
Tonight's meal is a pasta soup that can be made
with a single camping pot.
It leaves no extra broth,
making it ideal for camping and hiking.
Onions
Bacon
Asparagus
Mushrooms
Onions
Bacon
Asparagus
Mushrooms
Take your previously chopped ingredients,
Onions
Bacon
Asparagus
Mushrooms
Onions
Bacon
Asparagus
Mushrooms
Onions
Bacon
Asparagus
Mushrooms
Onions
Bacon
Asparagus
Mushrooms
Onions
Bacon
Asparagus
Mushrooms
and fry them in olive oil and chopped garlic.
Mix in 150 millilitres of water,
add one cube of consommé, and bring to a boil.
Then add the pasta,
breaking it in half first so it can all fit.
As the boiling point is lower at high altitudes,
even boiling water may not
cook the pasta through.
If that's the case, use quick cook pasta.
The water level will fall as the pasta absorbs liquid.
Once that occurs, add 200 millilitres of milk and two pieces
of sliced cheese, and simmer for a bit longer.
Top with black pepper and parsley to taste,
and you're done.
I did it.
My first real camp meal.
Time to eat.
Yum!
Pasta soup up on Mount Bocchi,
Yumm
Rin-chan made pasta soup, huh?
It looks good.
Aki-chan, Aoi-chan! It's already past four!
We totally overslept!
Devastating.
Just devastating.
Hey, Aki, is this really the right way?
We've been going downhill for a while.
Uh, the map says so, but...
I'm not so good with dark woods.
That's, like, every forest campsite.
Hey, isn't that it?
East wood Ca
“...mpgrounds”?
Yeah, “...mpgrounds”.
East wood Ca
Sorry we're late.
Don't worry about it.
Checkout's tomorrow at noon.
I'll bring you some water later.
He's wearing a monk's robe.
How reserved.
Isn't he cold?
East Wood
Camp  Garden
His living space is really nice in contrast, though.
Can you believe it?
This is the kind of place I'd want to retire to.
You should think about getting a job first
before thinking about retiring from one.
Hey, Aki-chan, where are we setting up the tents?
Oh, over here.
I reserved a good spot.
Here we are!
This is great!
I thought the view would be better higher up,
so I chose the second level.
All right, let's set up the tents before it gets dark.
Yeah!
All done!
I'll just leave the water here, okay?
Sure, thank you.
Drinking water and a watering can
for dousing the fire.
Make sure you use water to put the fire out
completely before you go to bed.
Lastly, you're free to use
as much firewood as you like,
but no bonfires, please. Keep them small.
Oh, yeah!
Since we have these, we should make log candles!
Log candles?
A log candle is what you call it when...
you make cuts in a log, fill it with kindling,
and then burn it like a candle.
They're also called Swedish torches
and lumberjack candles.
Just tie the firewood together,
stuff in kindling, and...
Done!
It's got a different feel from normal campfires.
It's nice.
You can even put a pot on top to cook with.
That's amazing.
Although it'd end up black with soot
like our club's pot.
That's true.
I wonder why watching a campfire is so relaxing.
Beats me.
Ah, yikes!
What just happened?
This wire's just made of thin aluminum.
It must've snapped from the heat.
See?!
Aren't you glad we didn't put a pot on it?
Don't you “see?!” me!
UFO Encounter Files
All right!
It's cooking time!
Potato
Carrot
Onion
Okra
Eggplant
Garlic
Pork
Take your previously chopped and fried ingredients
and throw them into hot water with curry roux.
Potato
Carrot
Onion
Okra
Eggplant
Garlic
Pork
Potato
Carrot
Onion
Okra
Eggplant
Garlic
Pork
Potato
Carrot
Onion
Okra
Eggplant
Garlic
Pork
Potato
Carrot
Onion
Okra
Eggplant
Garlic
Pork
Potato
Carrot
Onion
Okra
Eggplant
Garlic
Pork
Potato
Carrot
Onion
Okra
Eggplant
Garlic
Pork
Potato
Carrot
Onion
Okra
Eggplant
Garlic
Pork
It's no ordinary curry. It's stewed curry!
So it was curry.
Looks so good!
Time to eat!
Delicious!
It's really good.
Eating good food outdoors,
gazing at such a pretty view...
It's the best part of camping.
It's good, but there's some kind of mysterious flavor.
I'm glad you noticed.
Ta-da!
The secret ingredient's tonkotsu ramen powder.
Like the tonkotsu curry you get at ramen shops, huh?
Yep!
I make this a lot using leftover soup base.
It's too salty by itself,
so I dilute it with flour and water.
So it's like a transformed curry.
My family makes leftover meat
and potatoes into curry the next day.
Mine does oden curry.
What, oden?
The Japanese-style broth
goes really well with the curry.
We put beef tendon in, too.
Wow! I'll try that out next time!
Soft Marshmallows
This tent's too small!
I don't think three's doable.
But it's kind of lonely sleeping alone.
Well, I guess...
Okay, let's make it fair.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Sniffle.
Oh, yeah... I wonder what Rin-chan's up to.
Rin-chan, are you still up?
Sleeping
That was fast!
How are things over there?
Super cold. I'm a caterpillar right now
I'm a caterpillar right now, too ( * ´w` * )
Winter sleeping bags are so warm
Put some heat pads by your feet. It's even warmer
I'm a caterpillar right now, too ( * ´w` * )
Winter sleeping bags are so warm
Put some heat pads by your feet. It's even warmer
I'm a caterpillar right now, too ( * ´w` * )
Winter sleeping bags are so warm
Put some heat pads by your feet. It's even warmer
I'm a caterpillar right now, too ( * ´w` * )
Winter sleeping bags are so warm
Put some heat pads by your feet. It's even warmer
Really? I'll try it right now
Heat pad, heat pad...
By the way, I went to a hot spring
and it was out of business . . .
I'm absolutely getting in one tomorrow !
Totally getting in !
and it was out of business . . .
I'm absolutely getting in one tomorrow !
Totally getting in !
I totally believe in you !
Rin-chan !
The stars and night view here
are amazing
Night view, huh?
Rin-chan, stay up for a bit longer ! !
Hmm? 'Kay
Aki-chan, Aoi-chan, are you guys asleep?
They're asleep already, huh?
Oh, well.
I'll go by myself.
This is so scary!
I made it past the dark part.
Better hurry. Rin-chan's waiting.
Made it.
All right.
Finally.
What does she even want?
Hold on a sec
So cold!
In return
Thanks ( ＞ v ＜ )ノシ
It's so pretty.
The fresh air brushes across my brow
hitai ni kanjiru sunda kuuki
Each breath I blow is white
haku iki ga hazumu
Put one foot in front of the other and don't stop walking
tomaru koto mo naku aruki tsudzuketeita no
Turning back I finally see the first beams of light
koko de furikaeru mou sugu da yo
The sun rises
asahi ga noboru
I am on a journey
watashi wa tabi suru
To breathe in the freedom that comes with a new day
atarashii hi ni jiyuu wo suikondara
Let's sit down and huddle around a warm fire
atatakai hi wo kakonde suwarou
Chatting about all the silly things that come to mind
tawaimonai koto hanashi nagara
Room Camp
Room Camp!
That Outdoors Club trip was so fun!
Sure was.
Guys, look!
Huh?
I got my sister to print these out so that
we could see all our fun memories right away!
Ooh!
I'm going to post these all up on the wall!
Good idea!
I've already started with the ones from Fumoto.
Huh?
Where are they?
Over there!
Let's take lots more and put them all up!
She totally wants to cover
the whole wall from end to end.
Next Episode
Meat and Fall Colors and The Mystery Lake
When camping...
Always mind the campsite and facility rules.
Don't forget to clean up fires and take your trash!
It gets cold during the winter.
Stay warm and be well-prepared!!
Outdoor Activities Club