Library
It's about time to close the library...
But this heat has taken me hostage.
Only about a month left in the year.
Nagano sure was nice.
I visited all sorts of places,
and the hot spring was great.
I was planning on giving this to her today,
but school ended before I knew it.
I know we're in different classes,
but I was hoping I'd run into her anyway.
What's this?
Did I bring this with me?
Rin, aren't you having breakfast?
Not today. I'm running late.
All right, then.
Here, your lunch.
Thanks.
Also, you got a package of some kind.
See you later.
Have a nice day at school!
I guess I just brought it along with me after I got it.
Why'd she give it to me on my way out?
What is it, anyway?
Oh, it's this!
I remember ordering it before going to Nagano.
It's smaller than I thought it'd be.
About the size of a book?
Compact campfire grill.
Look what I scored!
ma
Open
window
and,
ta
ra
ah
bright
Open
light
window
ta
and,
ra
ah
bright
light
ya
Bathe
sa
shii
in
hi
the
za
light
shi
sun's
ip
gentle
pai
Bathe
rays
shii
the
hi
za
sun's
shi
ip
gentle
pai
ni
a
bi
rays
su
Wonderful
te
expectations,
Wonderful
expectations,
bit,
mu
fill
heart
bit,
mu
fill
heart
Push
wa
ra
open
na
i
the
hi
door
Push
bi
of
no
ka
unchanging
to
bi
days
open
door
bi
no
of
to
unchanging
bi
ra
wo
a
days
once
no
your
mu
eyes
kou
adjust
light
once
ka
ri
your
no
eyes
mu
adjust
kou
ma
to
the
light
right
Right
now
de
ha
we're
ji
ma
taking
ri
our
Right
no
first
i
ppo
step
right
now
ha
ji
we're
ma
ri
no
taking
i
our
first
step
ppo
shi
Shiny
ny
days
a
blow
ta
ra
in
Shiny
shii
with
ka
ze
a
new
wind
shi
days
ny
blow
days
a
in
ta
ra
with
shii
a
new
ka
wind
ha
Bounce
skip
na
step
along
Bounce
fun
the
de
trail
skip
you
na
along
step
the
fun
trail
feel
su
the
ki
too
clear
ru
Can
skies?
so
ra
you
can
feel
the
su
ki
clear
too
ru
skies?
excitement
hearts
re
te
mu
will
ku
na
take
excitement
brand
us
new
to
world
sa
a
brand
new
wa
world
in
gi
our
ga
hearts
tsu
re
will
take
brand
new
world
Li
sten
sten
-off
dy
e
echoes
whistling
-off
bu
echoes
e
hi
of
bi
whistling
leap
sou
into
mi
ra
the
i
future
e
And
to
bi
leap
da
sou
mi
into
ra
i
the
future
e
Now I have a stand for those campsites
that require them,
and I can cook tasty food with charcoal too.
Outdoor
Cooking
Meat Dishes
Meat...
Grilled meat while camping...
Oh, you're grinning again.
Hmm? What's this?
A metal donation box?
Not even close.
Episode 6
Meat and Fall Colors and The Mystery Lake
So you can use this for campfires, huh?
This one's on the smaller side, though.
Sometimes I see this kind of thing
at barbecue places.
Really?
Actually, I think you're supposed to
be able to grill meat on this top part.
Oh, so I was right.
Grilling meat outdoors by yourself, huh?
What would you make first, Rin?
I'd probably start with salt beef tongue.
Oh, good choice!
I'd do pork ribs after that,
also salt-flavored.
I think I'd go with salt pork jowl, maybe.
Oh, that sounds good too.
I'd eat rice while grilling the kalbi,
and use sauce for the ribeye and skirt.
Oh, man!
Could try offal, too!
In that case, I'd do stuffed intestines.
Give the grill a light cleaning...
And follow it up with some more salt meats.
Yep, yep!
And finally, wash it down with soup.
There's ice cream, too.
That'll be 35,000 yen.
That's too much.
What could possibly cost that much
at a barbecue place?
You still haven't given that to Nadeshiko-chan?
Ganache Manju
I haven't run into her today.
Wouldn't she still be in the club room?
I don't really mix well with them all.
Yeah, I know.
Saitou, would you go give it to her?
Uh-uh, not gonna happen.
You bought that all the way out in Nagano, right?
You should give it to her yourself.
She'd probably be happier that way.
I'll do it by the end of the year.
You sure it won't expire first?
Anyway, I'm going to head home.
See you, Rin.
'Kay.
For lunch tomorrow, bring that along
and let's grill meat here.
That's a recipe for disaster.
You'd better give Nadeshiko-chan her gift soon!
Ganache Manju
Maybe I should've gotten cookies,
since those last longer.
Well, you two looked like you were having
so much fun, that I didn't want to interrupt.
What were you talking about?
This. A souvenir from Nagano.
Huh? A souvenir? For me?
They'll expire soon, so eat them quickly.
Thanks, Rin-chan!
I'll cherish them forever!
No, eat them.
Chocolate manju!
Sounds good!
They'd be good with hot cocoa.
And of course milk, too.
Or I could be mature with coffee milk.
But I can't just ignore tea!
I'm Japanese, after all!
Rin-chan, can I open it?
Let's have them together.
Sure.
What's this?
A mini donation box?
You too?
Wow, it can do campfires, cooking,
and even barbecue?
Oh wow!
Look how small it gets!
Hey, want to try grilling meat
with that sometime?
Oh man, I do!
Let's do it!
Barbecue camping!
Um, I didn't mean while camp–
I know!
Rin-chan, are you free this weekend?
Well, I'm not working...
I'll find us the campground this time.
In the name of the Outdoors Club!
S-Sure.
All right, let's do it!
What kind of meat should we have?
Does she know we have finals coming up?
Well, whatever.
She's finished almost all of them.
Rin-chan, is this everything?
No, there's still the firewood and charcoal.
Got it!
Use the back seats if you can't
fit everything in the trunk.
Okay.
Thank you for driving my girl.
No problem.
I'll be borrowing your daughter!
We're all set, Onee-chan.
Yeah, yeah.
See you later.
Be careful, okay?
Okay.
All right, let's go!
Hey, Rin-chan, where are we buying the groceries?
There's a supermarket called Zebra up ahead.
Okay, let's go there.
Where's that, exactly?
Along Route 52?
Yes.
Take a right onto the 52,
and it's about five minutes out.
Got it.
Cars are so comfy.
And Nadeshiko's sister is so pretty.
GUMMIES
Though this one here's less so.
By the way, I'm surprised you know about
Lake Shibire Campgrounds.
Oh, actually...
Huh? You're going camping with Shimarin this week?
That's two weeks in a row, too.
Pretty hardcore, aren't you?
Aki-chan, Aoi-chan, do you know
any good campgrounds?
Hmm...
Because of Mount Fuji and the Five Lakes,
there are a ton of good places around here.
That's true.
What kinds of campgrounds are there?
Well, in general...
First, forest campgrounds.
Forest Campgrounds
Seaside Campgrounds
Then, seaside campgrounds.
Field Campgrounds
Field campgrounds,
Lookout Campgrounds
and also lookout campgrounds.
Riverside or Lakeshore Campgrounds
Finally, riverside and lakeshore campgrounds.
Most of the Fuji Five Lakes campgrounds
are this last kind.
Speaking of the Five Lakes,
did you kids know that
they used to be the Eight Lakes?
What's this, an urban legend?
No, it's true.
Apparently one of them
even has a campground nearby.
And that lake's named... Shibire.
“Electroshock” Lake?
TL Note: A common meaning for shibire is electrical stunning.
Are there electric eels or something?
Nay!
Doggy
Lake Shibire
It's written like this!
Even the local residents don't know much about it.
It's said that a giant, mysterious fish
lives in the lake,
and that the management building may or may not
serve ridiculously good barbecue!
Ridiculously good?!
I've been meaning to investigate,
but there are too many mysteries to solve alone...
Private Kagamihara, can I leave this one to you?
Yes, Captain!
Why the skit?
Lake Shibire's pretty famous for its fall colors.
Really?
We're almost at the supermarket.
Oh.
Nadeshiko, can you get me a can of coffee?
A sweet one.
Yeah, sure thing.
Exercise      Caution
Zebra
Rin-chan, what kinds of meat should we get?
Let's see...
Exercise      Caution
Zebra
Pork ribs, kalbi, pork jowl, offal,
skirt, tongue, pork loin...
Oh, I like pork jowl a lot!
This time we'll be grilling over charcoal, too.
And with the eating-outside effect
tripling the taste,
it's for real gonna be amazing!
Hearty
Assorted Grilling Meats
PORK RIB
Only ribs...
KALBI
...and kalbi.
Hearty
Assorted Grilling Meats
PORK RIB
KALBI
PORK LOIN
Well, I guess barbecue is usually a summer thing, so right now...
I'm being oppressed!
A-Are you crying, Rin-chan?
Look, they have pork skewers!
CHICKEN AND GREEN ONION SKEWERS
PORK SKEWERS
Chicken, too.
Chicken skewers?
Yeah, chicken skewers!
Skewers are great chargrilled!
That's right, if we're chargrilling,
we can do Hamburg steak too.
Totally, Rin-chan!
It's not what I was planning,
but this should do it for meat.
Nadeshiko, what kind of sauce do you want?
Fresh out of the fryer!
Croquettes
Mince Cutlets
The freshly fried food trap!
The just fried meat cutlet looked so good
that I just couldn't help myself.
Oh, and I'm thinking of making mini hot pot, too.
Is there anything you don't like?
I'm not a big fan of shellfish.
Okay, got it.
I'll make something with fish and vegetables, then.
Please come again!
Huh?
Aoi-chan!
Welcome.
I didn't know you worked here!
Well, I just started last week.
Are you guys going to Lake Shibire now?
Yep!
I'll send you lots of pictures!
Please do.
Thank you very much.
Take care now.
Yeah, see you, Aoi-chan!
Good luck at work, Inuyama-san.
Thanks.
Have fun camping, Shima-san.
O-Onee-chan, it's cold!
The smell from that fried minced meat cutlet
is taking over the car.
Aoi-chan, are you done for the day?
Yes.
I'll be heading home now.
Good work.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Sure.
I'm at the campgrounds!
Aki's already there.
How is it?
Pretty wide open !
Lots of campsites, too !
Scope them out well
Leave it to me !
Nice!
This is a strong candidate
for the next Outdoors Club trip.
A seasoned one-pole tent,
a campfire stand, and a wooden low chair.
It looks straight out of a coffee commercial
or something.
That meat looks so good!
Skillet cooking's great, isn't it?
The food looks five times as good,
and it's kind of cool, too.
Want some meat?
May I?
Thank you.
Oh man!
That was one classy grandpa.
The meat was crazy good, too.
I think I'll buy a skillet.
CAUTION
Welcome to Lake Shibire, Seiun Lodge
Mountain Retreat
Kiake Lodge
Campgrounds, Lodging... etc
Which way?
Um...
Right, I think.
Campgrounds, Lodging... etc
Kiake Lodge
Doggy dash.
So this is Lake Shibire!
Wow.
It's all yellow.
Are you here to camp?
Oh, yes!
Our reservation's under “Kagamihara”.
Hello.
Good afternoon.
Please head to the reception desk over there.
Are you both staying in tents?
Yes, we are.
The sites are on the opposite shore.
You won't be able to get there by car,
so you'll have to walk around the lake.
They're near that white tent over there.
Feel free to use the carts
by the entrance if you need to.
Sure, thank you!
Hup.
Can you fit all our stuff in yours?
Just barely.
Okay, see you, Onee-chan.
Yeah, have fun.
I'll be back around noon tomorrow,
so you'd better be awake.
I know.
It'll get cold at night, so be careful, Rin-chan.
Oh, yes.
Thank you.
See you!
The leaves are so pretty, Rin-chan.
I'll have to thank Aki-chan for telling me about this.
Looks like it's just the right time, too.
Your sister's so nice, Nadeshiko.
It's a pretty long trip,
but she drove us the whole way.
Yeah!
She likes driving a lot.
She looked like she was having fun
during the trip, too.
Really?
Yeah.
She was, huh?
Chai
Tasty!
Excuse me, can I get a hot chai, please?
This is good.
By the way, apart from the fall colors,
this place is famous for a story
about a cow ghost, too.
Gh-gh-gh-gh-gh-gh-gh-ghost?
Here?
Are you afraid of ghosts?
The fresh air brushes across my brow
hitai ni kanjiru sunda kuuki
Each breath I blow is white
haku iki ga hazumu
Put one foot in front of the other and don't stop walking
tomaru koto mo naku aruki tsudzuketeita no
Turning back I finally see the first beams of light
koko de furikaeru mou sugu da yo
The sun rises
asahi ga noboru
I am on a journey
watashi wa tabi suru
To breathe in the freedom that comes with a new day
atarashii hi ni jiyuu wo suikondara
Let's sit down and huddle around a warm fire
atatakai hi wo kakonde suwarou
Chatting about all the silly things that come to mind
tawaimonai koto hanashi nagara
Room Camp
Room Camp!
Hey, Aki-chan,
there are a ton of shops selling soba
and udon in the mountains, right?
Why is that?
Now that you mention it...
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
In 1 km
SOBAUDON
Nozawa Noodle House
Maybe it's because noodles don't take too
much to make, or the water there's good.
Nope, that's not it.
Those places don't actually sell soba and udon,
but rather sobau don.
Sobau  don
.
The “u” in “sobau” is the character for “cormorant”.
CORMORANT
They cook cormorants that have been fed soba
SOBA
and serve them in a sweet and sour sauce
on top of rice.
It's the specialty of some mountain village.
SOBAUDON
That's what sobau don is.
SPECIALTY
SOBAU DON
But people kept miscalling it “soba udon”,
SPECIALTY
SOBAU DON
Handmade
SOBA UDON
and sobau don soon vanished
from the history books.
SOBA UDON
FAMOUS
R-Really?
Nah, not at all.
Next Episode
Night by the Lakeshore and Campers of All Sorts
When camping...
Always mind the campsite and facility rules.
Don't forget to clean up fires and take your trash!
It gets cold during the winter.
Stay warm and be well-prepared!!
Outdoor Activities Club