So wide open!
Asagiri Highlands Campgrounds
Sensei, we've chosen a spot for our tent.
All right, I'll carry the equipment over.
Could you two check in at reception?
Roger that!
Oh, by the way, you bought a huge
pack of bacon on the way here, right?
Will that accompany your drinking today?
What?! No, I'm just going to drink a little, at night!
Wait, you were watching?
There's no need to hold back because of us.
You should have your fun too, Sensei.
Girls...
We're off to reception!
Not too windy, either. What nice weather.
One night for six people, is that right?
Episode 11
Campmas!
Then if you would, please fill in your names
and contact information here.
Let's see...
Oogaki Chiaki, Inuyama Aoi,
Kagamihara Nadeshiko, Toba Sensei...
That's not her name.
What's Saitou's first name again?
Ena.
What about Shimarin's family name?
It's literally half of what you just said.
We were supposed to meet up at two,
but it looks like we're a little early.
SUNDAY, DECEMBER 24
You were the one who suddenly said
you wanted to get going already.
But I just couldn't wait to see
Mount Fuji, you know!
Cut it with the Nadeshiko-chan impression.
What should we do until two?
Oh, yeah. Isn't there some “Woodlands Ranch”
place right nearby?
Woodlands        Ranch
Base of Mount Fuji
Asagiri Highlands
Entrance
Ranch
Cheesecake
Wanna get some dairy desserts there?
Woodlands Ranch
Soft Serve
Oh, sounds good!
Let's ask Sensei for a ride.
Sh-She's already gotten started...
See you later!
FUJINOMIYA
SUNDAY, DECEMBER 24
I got here earlier than I expected.
Well, I guess I'll read a bit and take it easy.
Huh?
They're already here?
Yes, two of them came to check in.
Two of them?
Oogaki and Inuyama-san?
Yuummm!
Ice cream in a warm shop...
Woodlands Ranch
So good!
Ahh... I don't want to go anywhere anymore.
They aren't over here.
That's... not them either.
I don't see them anywhere.
It's a bit early, but I'm at the campsite .
I heard you already checked in,
but where'd you guys go ?
Kids...
What a great place this is, though.
The view's nice, too.
I guess I'll just set my tent up here for now.
That's number four.
We're almost there.
All right.
Hey!
Rin-chan!
Ah, there's our little bundle of energy.
I just couldn't wait until two!
We should have picked twelve instead.
Right?
Keep warm at night, you two. Don't catch a cold.
Okay, got it.
Right.
See you tomorrow, Onee-chan!
Inuyama-san
They replied.
We're having dairy desserts
at the Woodlands Ranch
We're having dairy desserts at the Woodlands Ranch!
We're having dairy desserts
at the Woodlands Ranch
So that's why they're not around.
Lucky!
It looks so good!
Since it's right nearby, want to walk over?
I'm running out of allowance for this month,
so I'll try and resist.
A-And I just had lunch a minute ago...
She has to be raising something in her stomach.
In that case, want to just have a light snack here?
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Fluffy
White
Marshmallows
Yay!
Toasted marshmallows are so tasty!
We did this on the last Outdoors Club trip too.
Well, we're not done just yet.
Sandwich the toasted marshmallow
between some chocolate biscuits, and...
There, done.
Apparently they're called s'mores.
S'mores!
They look good!
Yum!
Wha' are 'hese 'hings, Rin-shan? 'hey're sho good!
As usual, she makes the food look great.
Ahh... this place is so great!
You can see Mount Fuji, and the grass feels nice.
I'm so glad we asked you, Rin-chan!
Don't thank me.
It was my grandpa who knew about this place.
The one who gave you camping gear?
Yeah.
He's been camping all over for ages.
Since he knows a lot about the area
around Mount Fuji, I asked him for help.
Oh, really?
I want to meet him!
The camping grandpa...
He's a weird one.
By the way, Inuyama-san's going to make dinner
with some amazing meat, right?
Do you know what it'll be?
Nope.
But I'm really excited!
I've never had A5 grade meat before.
You're doing breakfast tomorrow, right?
Yeah!
Japanese breakfast!
Japanese?
Look forward to it, okay?
Okay, I'll look forward to it.
Bundled firewood  300 yen each
Payment at
the.crepe.shop
They're selling firewood out here?
300 yen a bundle?
Pretty cheap.
Bundled firewood  300 yen each
Payment at
the.crepe.shop
All right, let's get some here.
Ah, but it's gonna be a pain to carry it back.
Well, if we call Sensei and ask for a ride...
...nothing will happen.
Man, sorry about this!
I already told you I don't mind.
Oh, and I'll pay for these.
S-Seriously?!
I'm getting a free dinner, after all.
Thanks, Shima-san.
Captain!
I'm gonna take this home and treasure it forever!
We'll be burning it soon.
So heavy!
Man, not only did you pay for it,
but you're carrying it for us, too.
I'm getting teary-eyed.
Huh?
Hey Shimarin, you forgot one!
It'd be too heavy, so you're in charge of that one.
Huh?
You guys bought so much!
I have to carry those to the campsite.
Can you help me out?
Okie-dokie!
Toba-sensei.
She's totally conked out.
Come on, you'll catch a cold sleeping here, Sensei.
But...
To think that that lady we met at Lake Shibire
would turn out to be Toba-sensei...
booze
Hey, you've made her look like a monster.
But her head would be cold otherwise.
It sounds like she's suffocating.
Hm. Okay, then...
Don't go thinking you'll get to enjoy
your comfy camp trip forever .
I've sent an assassin
to your dumb campsite
Party's . . . over ! !
An . . . assassin . . .
Rin-chan, look!
A bunny!
A bunny's coming our way!
No...
That's no bunny.
That's...
Chikuwa!
Chikuwa...
Hey!
Rin!
Nadeshiko-chan!
Morning!
Decided to reveal yourself, bunny-dog master?
Where are the other two girls?
They should be arriving soon.
Hey, everyone's here.
Oh, there you are.
Morning, guys.
Morning.
You sure brought a ton of stuff, Saitou-san.
Heh, maybe a bit.
What are you doing, Nadeshiko?
Chikuwa won't come out.
Chikuwa?
You're right.
He's all curled up.
He really likes tight spaces.
Hang on a sec.
Holy Smokes
Chicken Sausage
Barkin'
good!!
Chicken Sausage
Holy Smokes
For all breeds
Chicken Sausage
Holy Smokes
Barkin'
good!!
For all breeds
Holy Smokes
Chicken Sausage
Barkin'
good!!
For all breeds
Holy Smokes
Chicken Sausage
Barkin'
good!!
For all breeds
Chikuwa, here boy.
It's snack time.
Oh, he came out!
Bunny ears!
Nadeshiko-chan, hold this.
Huh? Sure.
Now run for your life!
Wha? Uh... S-Sure...
Eat or be eaten.
It's a dog-eat-dog world, Nadeshiko-chan.
Looks like fun.
All right, while Nadeshiko's dog-eat-dogging,
let's set up the tent.
Aye!
What about you, Shimarin?
Oh, right. I've already set my tent up over there.
I'll go get it.
Isn't it going to be a pain to set it up again?
Well, I guess...
Why don't we move there, then?
Good idea.
Oh, but we would need a car for all this stuff...
I only need the tent to sleep in,
so I'll go get my other stuff later.
We're getting pretty good at setting these up!
Eh? Oogaki, you've got a cast iron skillet?
Heh heh, sure do.
Saitou-san, is that the sleeping bag
you mentioned earlier?
Yeah, it is.
Whoa, it's so warm!
It's nothing like ours.
So this is what a 45,000 yen sleeping bag's like.
Lucky.
Oh yeah, you should show us your gear too.
I wanna see! I wanna see!
Fine, but it's all normal stuff.
Yay!
How far did Nadeshiko go, anyway?
Whoa! It's one of those nice tents that are
easy enough to set up even by moonlight!
And this chair's that super light one
that's really compact.
She's even got one of these portable stoves.
Lucky.
Oh, Nadeshiko-chan's back.
Wait up, Chikuwa!
Oh, he got the sausage.
Give it back!
There's more of them now.
Looks like fun.
All right, let's take this and get in there too.
Thanks for helping me carry all this stuff.
No problem.
We got some free cookies.
They said they were homemade.
Let's have them with tea.
Agreed!
Here.
Thanks.
Everyone's here, huh?
Oh, Sensei! Good morning!
Sensei, would you like some hot cocoa?
Thanks, I would.
Wh-What are you putting in it, Sensei?!
Rum goes surprisingly well with cocoa.
Warms you right up!
Right after waking up...
So this is Chuggsie.
When we first met her at Lake Shibire,
she was like this too.
Yeah.
Hey, look!
Red Fuji!
So pretty!
Sure is.
Okay, let's start prepping dinner
before it gets dark.
Inuko-han, tonight, what're you making
with that good meat, eh?
Well, since we're being Christmassy today...
Grilled Tofu
Famed
Sukiyaki.
First, coat the pot with beef fat,
and lightly fry the meat.
Add sugar, soy sauce, and sake
before bringing to a simmer.
Shiitake, enoki, green onions,
grilled tofu, konjak noodles, and chrysanthemum greens follow
before the lid is closed to cook.
That's a pretty orthodox sukiyaki recipe.
It's Kansai-style.
Aki, can you fry these onions in your skillet?
With olive oil and garlic.
Huh?
Are you making another dish or something?
Well, something like that.
But man, is it ever getting cold.
You can thank the plateau for that.
It says it's around zero right now!
My dears, you'll be quite warm like this.
Oh dear, the blankiemonster's back.
The ever-expanding Secret Society BLANKET.
Secret
Society BLANKET
Big Boss
General Chikuwa
It should be about done now.
Dinner's ready!
Wow!
Now then...
Time to eat!
First, the enoki and green onions.
Yup, it's absorbed the flavor of the beef really well.
It's good.
Next is grilled tofu.
This is good, too!
With its great texture,
grilled tofu's a must for sukiyaki.
And finally...
the beef.
Garnish with some greens...
Good meat, come to me.
The superbly tender, juicy beef,
combined with the subtle bitterness
of the stewed greens,
all covered in the mellow taste of the egg...
Delicious.
Thank you, cow.
moo
The meat's super good!
It's really tasty, Aoi-chan!
You're welcome!
Their reactions split perfectly.
Silently Savoring Type
Entirely Expressive Type
Wh-What's wrong, Sensei?
I forgot to bring sake that matches sukiyaki!
Oh, I see.
Hey, Inuko, why are we having sukiyaki for dinner?
Well, actually...
Beef and Tomato Stew
Beef and tomato stew...
Beef Stroganoff
Beef and Tomato Stew
Beef stroganoff looks good, too.
Beef Stroganoff
Beef and Tomato Stew
You've never made anything like this, right?
Sure you can do it?
With a recipe, anyone can do it.
Aoi, if you want to appreciate the meat,
have sukiyaki.
Eh? But that's not Christmassy enough, Grandma.
That's not true.
Christmas is a special day, isn't it?
Yeah...
And isn't sukiyaki something you have on special days
with the people you cherish?
Now that she mentions it, that's right!
More or less.
Your grandma talked you into it, huh?
I really like sitting around a pot like this.
It's nice how it feels just like a Japanese New Year.
Sure does.
Oh yeah, I forgot!
I brought some Christmassy stuff along with me.
Yuletide Warriors...
Yuletide Warriors
Santa Rangers
I brought a mini tree too.
Reindeer Chikuwa's so cute!
Now we're in the Christmas spirit!
It's...
kind of like we're a bunch of mall Santas
getting together after work.
Oh, should we add some more stuff to the pot?
Nope, we're done with this one.
Huh? But there's still this much meat.
Next up's...
a makeover using this.
We'll take the onions that Aki prepared
and fry them a bit more with some tomatoes and basil.
Add them to the pot we just finished with,
simmer, and...
We've made ourselves some tomato sukiyaki!
Tomato sukiyaki?!
Yumm!
The tomatoes are so good!
The beef and appetite-whetting acidity
of the tomato
match perfectly with the broth,
reborn in Western style.
Oh man, this should be illegal!
This would go so well with wine! So well!
Yes, yes, you forgot to bring any, right?
I'm so full.
I ate so much!
Thank you, Inuyama-san.
It was really delicious.
You're too kind.
But you know, we're not finished just yet.
We still have to finish the tomato sukiyaki...
with cheese pasta!
Ready in 9 min
Fettuccine
Ch-Cheese pasta?!
Who's up for one more round?
Me!
You amaze me...
I'll just have a bite.
Me too.
Oh dear, we're out of gas.
Nadeshiko-chan, do you have another one?
I forgot to bring any.
Couldn't we take the one
from the burner Sensei brought?
Really?
Nice, is it on?!
Nope, this one's out too.
No way!
Sensei, is there any more gas?
Nah, ther' isn'!
If we can't use the stove anymore...
I won't be able to make breakfast tomorrow either!
How many cans of gas do we need?
There should be a convenience store nearby.
I'll go buy some.
Rin-chan!
Thank you!
Don't cry.
Oh, that's right! Aoi-chan, is there
any meat or broth left?
Yeah, just a little bit.
Rin-chan! I'll pay you back, so can you get
two cans and some grated ginger?
Got it.
And some sake for me!
I'm a minor, so I can't.
See you!
Man, it's really cold.
You might like camping alone more,
but isn't there a different kind of fun to be had
camping in a group?
Yeah, yeah.
The fresh air brushes across my brow
hitai ni kanjiru sunda kuuki
Each breath I blow is white
haku iki ga hazumu
Put one foot in front of the other and don't stop walking
tomaru koto mo naku aruki tsudzuketeita no
Turning back I finally see the first beams of light
koko de furikaeru mou sugu da yo
The sun rises
asahi ga noboru
I am on a journey
watashi wa tabi suru
To breathe in the freedom that comes with a new day
atarashii hi ni jiyuu wo suikondara
Let's sit down and huddle around a warm fire
atatakai hi wo kakonde suwarou
Chatting about all the silly things that come to mind
tawaimonai koto hanashi nagara
Next Episode
Mount Fuji and the Yuru Camp Girls
When camping...
Always mind the campsite and facility rules.
Don't forget to clean up fires and take your trash!
It gets cold during the winter.
Stay warm and be well-prepared!!
Outdoor Activities Club