An enemy in the real world?
Is that an enemy?
What is that?
Something like that...
With this, everyone here
will be able to become one
with Shinjyu-sama.
We will be accepted as the people of God.
What a fortunate thing.
This is your last duty.
Hold back the attacks
until the Shinkon is complete.
We'll do it. But we'll also take Yuna back!
We won't let her go through with the Shinkon!
Yuki Yuna is a Hero -Hero Chapter-
FINAL EPISODE
ONLY YOU CAN MAKE ME HAPPY
Oh, no!
The god above...
If my life is going to end soon,
if I can use my life to save everyone,
I'm not scared.
That thing is crazy.
-Fu!
-Karin!
You guys, go to where Yuna is!
I'll keep this thing busy!
-Keep it busy!?
-Don't underestimate me...
I still have my Mankai left!
Karin!
I have to apologize to Yuna.
And go back together.
The unparalleled, Karin Miyoshi!
Thoroughly watch my
once-in-a-lifetime rampage!
This...
Fu, I...
Itsuki, can I ask you to handle this?
Yes. Go to Yuna, Fu.
Yes. I'll bring Yuna back!
-Please stay safe.
-Yeah.
Get on, Fu-senpai!
Togo!
All right! Let's go to where Yuna is!
I'll head there full speed!
A barrier?
This is the reason...
Don't mess with me!
You!
Sonoko!
Don't go ahead too much, Nibosshi!
-Itsuki!
-Let's protect it together.
This place, Yuna will come back to.
Togo! Look!
Towards Shinjyu-sama...
Yuna is up ahead!
What is that?
One after another!
Fu-senpai.
Abandon ship!
Togo...
We're being blocked by Shinjyu-sama.
Who cares?!
Even if it's Shinjyu-sama,
I won't yield this time!
The road is...
This is...
Togo, can you do it?
Without fail.
Then I will...
create the...
path!
Where...
is this?
Will I be able to return with the power of the Spirit?
Yuna!
Ms. Togo? Why?
Yuna, let's go back home!
I came to take you back!
You really don't want
to give her up, do you?
Yuna! I'm going to save you right now!
But, I...
I have to do this...
otherwise the world will disappear.
Someone has to do this.
So I will...
Yuna!
No one has to do this!
I don't want to
lose any more
important people in my life!
I just have to endure this...
-and it'll be okay.
-Yuna!
Please say the truth.
If you're scared...
please tell me.
If we're really friends,
please ask me for help!
I don't want to...
I'm scared...
But I can't say that.
But I...
I don't want to die.
I don't want to be apart
from everyone!
Yuna...
We were
doing our best.
But why?
I don't want this.
I want to...
I want to stay with everyone!
Yuna! Reach your hand out!
Ms. Togo! Please save me!
Yuna!
Ms. Togo!
No... Why is it still getting in the way?
Ms. Togo...
Please save me...
Yuna!
Ms. Togo...
No!
This can't be...
We...
shouldn't be doing this...
I am thankful...
But...
It's fine.
I don't want a world
you can only gain
by sacrificing my friends and other people.
I don't want...
a world like that.
That is...
Shinjyu-sama.
There are...
many kinds of people.
But if you
really intend to save them.
Please...
put your trust in people!
We...
will choose the path of a human.
Yuna!
Ms. Togo?
Ms. Togo.
Ms. Togo!
I'm sorry, I...
-said too much.
-I...
I'm also sorry.
I said some horrible things to you
and everyone.
It's fine. It's all fine now.
What do we do? The world!
The world is going to end now!
That's not your fault, Yuna.
Even if the world were to end now...
it's all out of our control.
Gyuki.
-What are you...?
-It's okay.
It's so warm.
I...
We...
will fight as humans.
We want to live!
Heroes are unyielding.
We'll get right back up no matter
how many times we go down!
Go! Yuna!
For Ms. Yuna's happiness!
You're likely to succeed...
If you try!
Hero club...
Fight on!
A hero
has guts!
Hero...
Punch!
The flames are...
This...
Is different from usual.
Gyuki, you are...
Thank you.
Goodbye.
We made it back.
The world...
Still exists.
What about Shinjyu-sama?
He's gone.
Did he perish?
It's the usual sky.
What's wrong, Yuna? Are you not feeling well?
It's gone.
Are the markings gone?
Everyone...
I'm so sorry, everyone.
Me too.
I'm sorry.
Karin!
Welcome back, Yuna.
I'm back.
The large-scale fire stretching across the city...
-In one week,
-The prolonged shelter living has...
-has spread to 10,000 Hectare.
-Many of the citizens are fatigued.
-So the Amnesty was aware of what
-The Amnesty's role in the future will be discussed.
-was beyond the wall?
-Please take a look!
-The headquarters are completely abandoned!
-People will have to figure out
-There is no sign of anyone!
-a way to survive on limited resources.
There is a theory that the
flowing oil field is the remains
-of the world of trees.
-The children are not at fault.
The god on land has perished.
Losing its protection, humanity must learn
to survive on limited resources.
There will be chaos.
But this is fine.
I am proud of the decision the girls made.
The new era
will be for the children.
The adults will have to take the responsibilities.
This is how it must be.
The Hero club is back in its original form!
Fu-senpai has been accepted into high school.
And Itsuki has been chosen
as the next club leader!
Let's do our best today.
Of course, without pushing yourself too hard.
That way, the future will be wonderful.
So you can look back,
and see everything as something great.
With everyone here.
Because everyone was here.
Because I care about everyone.
I...
I'm glad I was in the Hero club.
I see...
So this is...
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR
GRADUATION, FU-SENPAI.
CONGRATS ON BECOMING
A NEXT LEADER, ITSUKI!
SANSHU MIDDLE SCHOOL
HERO CLUB WILL LIVE ON FOREVER
I HOPE YOUR DAYS ARE PEACEFUL
HERO CHAPTER