SHINJYU
Ah, finally out of the hospital!
The fresh air feels so great!
That's great you were able
to leave the hospital so quick.
Even though we've already
entered the new year.
Isn't that something good?
It means I'm getting another year older.
And not to mention,
I also graduate in March.
You know you can stay another year.
No, I can't.
Hey, I want to drink some sweet sake
That sounds good!
Let's all get a cup!
SWEET SAKE
You guys just downed it.
It's non-alcoholic, right?
Why are you drunk?
We're not drunk!
My golden middle school years are coming to an end!
What's up with them?
This is an important record.
Do you not want any, Yuna?
It's too hot...
Oh, no, Wasshi!
We have to cool it down for her!
Thank you.
Togo-senpai!
Let's take a picture!
My youth!
Let's take one with everyone.
Are you guys ready?
Haha!
Yuki Yuna is a Hero -Hero Chapter-
EPISODE 4
UNSPOKEN INTENTIONS
Fu-senpai, you can just act natural.
Sorry, I can't help it...
You've been rolling your camera
so diligently recently.
Since you're graduating soon
it's important that we have a record
of the things we do together.
Well,
I'll probably still hang out here
after I graduate.
You're going to hang out here?
I predicted that would happen.
You say that, but you look so happy, Karin.
What's that reaction?
Watching them makes me
want to create things!
Right, Sancho?
That's right, Sonoko.
He talks?
Fumin-senpai and Nibosshi
made my imagination run wild.
I'm going to write a book
about them when I get home.
-Huh?
-What!?
See you tomorrow!
See you.
See you later, Sonocchi.
Wait a minute!
Anyway, where should we go
for my graduation trip?
Especially since you couldn't
go anywhere during the new year's holiday.
That's right.
Should we go to an onsen
with the amnesty money?
Well, we've already been to the onsen.
So maybe we can go somewhere else?
The mountains might be nice.
Lost kitty, lost kitty, where are you?
How about over there?
We can't find him anywhere.
Itsuki, could you try calling for him in cat language?
What!? Me-- Meow.
Meow! Meow!
More! Become more animal-like!
That's good! Ittsun, that's really good!
Please stop taking photos of this!
Oh! There he is.
Come here. Let's go home.
There. There.
Good job finding him, Yuna.
I scared him.
We found the cat so the request
has been completed.
Now, senpai, let's take a photo
to commemorate this moment.
Good idea!
KARAOKE
Somewhere beyond
We can meet again
Nice! You guys sing so well.
You guys were perfectly in sync.
Should we also sing something, Yuna?
-Yeah, let's finish our homework.
-Huh?
You must be half asleep.
-Nibosshi, please sing with me!
-Oh, okay.
-Yuna.
-Oh?
Karin.
Can I talk to you about something?
What is it, Karin?
Do you mind walking a little?
It's been a while since we've been
on this side.
The last time we came here
was to save Ms. Togo.
Yuna, umm...
Before you continue, can I say something?
Are you not cold, Karin?
Sorry, I didn't think about that!
Should we go somewhere else?
No, this is fine.
We just have to do this.
So warm!
The other day, when Fu was saying
that even after she graduated
she wanted to come and hang out, right?
Yeah.
I was
a little happy when I heard that.
Just a little?
Just a little!
But, actually, maybe a little more...
It's happy news.
Yeah.
So anyway,
I am able to express how I feel now.
So, Yuna, you should say how you feel.
Yuna, you've been acting weird
since the end of last year.
Something is definitely wrong, right?
I want to help you.
Please talk to me.
Yuna?
Nothing's wrong.
It's okay!
No matter what it is, I'll be there for you!
If it's for you, Yuna!
Karin.
I'll be there for you.
I'll do anything for you!
I'm so happy that I have a friend
I can feel that way for.
You and everyone made me
feel this way.
Karin.
What happened, Yuna?
Uh...
Um.
It really is nothing.
I see.
Karin.
When we have trouble,
we talk about it, right?
I...
wanted to help my friends.
Karin, wait!
Karin!
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
As I thought,
Yuna has been acting weird recently.
Oh! I got "great luck."
Awesome!
Something's not right.
If she got "great luck"
she would have been more excited.
But why does she look so sad?
There must be something wrong
she can't tell us about.
If so...
I'll get to the bottom of it.
THE TARGET IS ASLEEP.
YOU MAY ENTER.
UNDERSTOOD. STAND BY.
GO INSIDE, AND OPEN THE LOCK.
COPY THAT.
Yuna...
With all the lights on.
Sorry for sneaking in.
Any clues?
Oh, is that...?
When Yuna entered middle school,
on April 3rd, her parents bought
her these encyclopedias.
She said she never used them,
but one of them is slightly out of place.
Hero Records?
Why does she have this?
HERO RECORDS
Could it be? No,
this is definitely a clue.
But...
I'm sorry, Yuna.
I'm going to borrow this.
So Yuna wrote this?
Yuna has been acting really weirdly recently.
I think the reasons behind her behavior
are written in this.
Who knew it would be something like this.
Can I also say something?
Sonocchi.
I was also worried about Yu-yu,
so I looked into it.
I've been leaving earlier
than everyone recently, right?
-I've actually been going to the amnesty.
-The amnesty?
In conclusion,
the reason why Yu-yu has been
acting weird is
because Yu-yu is being tormented
by the Curse from God.
Sonocchi, that's...
Listen to me, Wasshi.
I read at the amnesty that if Yu-yu
speaks or writes about this,
the curse will spread.
That's what I found out.
So,
this book is very dangerous.
Do you still want to look inside?
I do.
I'm worried about Yuna.
Then let's read it.
Yu-yu's Hero Records.
Yuki Yuna is a Hero -Hero Chapter-
It began at the end of last year
when the people from the amnesty
noticed the change
and came to my house.
They said they figured out the truth
through their research.
Since they wanted to keep
an authentic record of it,
they made me keep this journal.
I hope I can keep it up.
Why has this happened?
Apparently, I pushed myself too far
during the big battle.
It ended up damaging my whole body.
Also, by touching the enemy's spirit,
my own spirit was consumed by it.
When I came to my senses,
I was at the same place we went
to save Ms. Togo.
An ever-expanding world.
I tried my best to break out of it.
But the world kept going and going,
expanding forever.
Everyone...
Please save me.
Even when they were all alone,
the hero...
The hero
never gave up fighting.
Ms. Togo?
As long as they didn't give up...
Ms. Togo.
hope was never lost.
-Ms. Togo.
-No matter what they lose.
Even then...
Ms. Togo! Ms. Togo! Ms. Togo!
I don't want to
lose my
best friend!
-Ms. Togo is crying.
-I don't want to.
I am...
I am
a hero.
A hero would never
leave a crying friend behind.
A hero has guts!
I'm going home no matter what!
A crow?
I felt like the crow
was telling me to follow him.
So I...
headed towards the light
and kept going.
That's how I was able to return.
But my body was different.
It seemed like we all recovered
from our injuries.
But it seems like we weren't able
to get back everything we sacrificed.
Our working, healed bodies
were something Shinjyu-sama created.
So it took my body some time
to accept it.
Since I got damaged doing such a forceful Mankai.
To heal,
Shinjyu-sama had to create
a whole new body for me.
At the amnesty,
they said they call me a Misugata.
MISUGATA
In a positive light, a Misugata
is seen as a very sacred figure.
So they are favored by God.
So I...
What I wished for,
by taking my friend's place,
helped restore the balance
of the world.
Afterwards, the amnesty
noticed the change
and figured out what was happening.
What they found was that
as long as the world of flames existed,
there is no chance that my body
would heal.
And that I
probably won't make it till spring.
I'm feeling very scared
and guilty about Fu-senpai,
who got injured because of me.
I just
feel like I'm stuck in a tunnel.
January 7th,
I'm so happy Fu-senpai was released
from the hospital.
I feel more energetic
when I'm with everyone,
but I have to be careful not to spread it.
So I try to talk less.
I didn't have an appetite,
but the sweet sake was delicious.
So my throat was very happy.
But I threw it all up at home.
January 9th,
I felt very nauseous but
being in the club room
made my heart feel very warm.
Lately, I really like hearing the words,
"See you tomorrow."
I feel like if I promise it,
tomorrow will really come.
I wish I could stay here forever.
Fu-senpai mentioned going on an onsen trip.
But if they saw my current naked body,
they would be shocked.
So I'm sorry, but I couldn't possibly go
on that trip.
January 11th,
I'm feeling really good today.
Maybe all the resting helped.
I was so happy to move my body around.
Maybe with some willpower
I can keep up this good feeling.
I'll try doing some other things
that'll be good for my body.
January 13th,
my chest hurt really bad
and I was really dizzy.
I feel like
I was probably not making sense.
I thought my body was getting better.
January 14th,
I have to sleep a lot
and try to heal my body.
But I'm scared to sleep with the lights off.
The darkness scares me.
I feel like the darkness will swallow me up.
January 16th.
Today I hurt Karin.
But I can't tell her.
I'm sorry.
It's so painful.
My body hurts. My heart hurts.
I'm so messed up.
I'm going crazy.
I just...
wanted to spend my days with everyone.
I can't give up. I can't be weak.
I'm a hero.
I should have been prepared for this.
I won't cry anymore. I can do it!
Yuna Yuki!
A hero never gives up!
I want to make up with Karin.
But I can't tell her the truth.
What should I do?
I'll write it all out here.
Karin, I...
I like you so much, Karin.
Karin,
I'm so sorry.
This can't be.
What do you mean, she won't get better?
She won't make it till spring?
What?
Wait, Wasshi!
Please don't stop me!
This is all my fault!
God's anger wasn't subsided!
That was a curse I should have gotten!
It was in her journal.
Even if you got it,
she would still be cursed.
It can't be.
The amnesty
kept another huge secret from us.
To put it simply,
she couldn't tell us because she was afraid
of spreading the curse.
I was also the same.
I found out about the details
of the curse
just a moment ago.
Ms. Karin...
Yuna was in so much pain,
But I...
I LIKE YOU SO MUCH, KARIN
I said such horrible things.
I said such awful things to her.
Even after learning the truth,
there was nothing we could do.
Good morning.
Which made me feel frustrated.
Yes?
Good morning, Yuna.
Good morning, Ms. Togo.
You're up early.
Yes, I woke up early.
But it's so cold, I don't want to get out of bed.
What's wrong, Yuna?
Ms. Togo, you don't look too well.
Are you okay?
Ms. Togo?
When I was feeling unsure,
Yuna always hugged me
just like this.
Yuna.
Now,
it's my turn to save you.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
I don't want to sacrifice
anyone anymore!
That's not fair.
Yuna did nothing wrong!
Don't fight...
What's the right thing to do?
Yuna Yuki will get married.
NEXT EPISODE
INCORRUPTIBLE HEART