Look. Christmas decorations
are already up everywhere.
We are such a tolerant nation
-to embrace foreign festivities without hesitation.
-You sound like a politician.
How do you think we should decorate
our Christmas tree?
-I'm so glad.
-What?
It looks like I'll be able to celebrate
this year's Christmas with you.
Of course we will, unless you disappear.
Oh, stop it.
How about me?
Sonocchi.
This may be our first time
celebrating Christmas together.
Let's do it together. It should be fun.
-Yeah!
Yeah.
Christmas!
Yuki Yuna is a Hero -Hero Chapter-
EPISODE 3
MY HEART HURTS WHEN I THINK OF YOU
PREPARATION ROOM
HERO CLUB'S CLUB ROOM
Hey, Yuna, isn't it a little crooked?
-Let's see. It's fine.
-Itsuki, you check it too. It's a little more to the right...
-What's with those glasses?
-I hear her vision's gotten worse.
Even studying for the entrance exam
in the club room? I feel bad for her.
I had a tough week and found no time to study.
I must make up for it.
-I apologize.
-I didn't mean to blame you.
It's not your fault.
Of course, Black Hole is more urgent
than the entrance exam.
I guess so.
I apologize.
Correct. Correct. Correct.
Good. Even the last one is correct too.
Fumin-senpai got a perfect score.
Good. Am I a genius or what?
-Bonus chance.
-What is that?
If you answer correctly,
you'll become twice as attractive.
-I will do it.
-Is it still for the entrance exam?
I was just kidding.
But I want to become more attractive!
You did well, so you will be fine. I'm impressed.
Thank you, Nogi. I couldn't do it without your help.
Next week I will be busy with Itsuki's show.
I see. That's why you are studying so hard this week.
Fu, it's not my show.
It's a community Christmas event.
It's the school chorus.
Impressive. You are selected to represent our school.
Ms. Yuna, thank you for your help.
You are just talented. That's all.
Your voice is exceptional.
I'm so proud of you. Go beat the other schools, okay?
That's not what this event is all about.
Don't catch a cold.
You must be on top of your health.
Be healthy. Be healthy. Be healthy.
You are making me nervous.
-Do you want a supplement?
-Give me an effective one.
-Can I sell your merchandise?
-Stop it!
What's up with you? Is something bothering you?
What? Well, nothing really bothers me.
Nothing? Really?
Don't you feel sick or something?
What? Yuna feels sick?
Be healthy. Be healthy.
-No way it works.
-I'm getting warm.
No way. You must be kidding.
-Be healthy. Be healthy.
-Stop it.
I'm getting warm.
-Wait. What are you doing to my body?
-Be healthy. Be healthy.
IF TROUBLED, ALWAYS TALK ABOUT IT!
Fu.
Help us decorate the tree if you finished studying.
You are almost done anyway.
Listen, everyone.
Well...
I give you a riddle.
A grasshopper shoulders the debt of an ant secretly.
Now what kind of problem will they face?
-What in the world are you talking about?
-I have no idea...
-Some kind of empirical question for social studies?
-Well...
I'm thinking about a riddle for our class newspaper.
-I see.
-But it's not a riddle at all.
An ant has debt? That's too unrealistic.
-Then maybe...
-She is talking nonsense again.
To tell you the truth, I was...
A riddle about shouldering someone's debt?
Let's use the story about the red ogre
who sacrifices himself for the blue ogre
to come up with a new riddle.
When I saved Ms. Togo,
I took over "the duty."
If Ms. Togo finds out, she will be shocked.
Finally we are all together, having fun. I can't ruin it.
-"Christmas" sounds too foreign to me.
-How about "The Festival of Pine Trees?
-That doesn't sound too appealing...
-Are you stupid?
-That's a little...
-Wasshi, you never change!
I detest my lack in writing skills!!
I...
I am being kept alive.
That's why I can stay on this side.
I can't believe it. Why did our AC
break on such a cold day?
We also had a power outage yesterday.
It was terrible.
-You two had a rough day, huh?
-What a mishap.
That's nothing, compared to my troubles.
Yesterday, Itsuki lost the keys,
and we couldn't get in the house.
-On such a cold night.
-Please, don't bring it up.
We just went to a convenience store.
It turned into a disaster.
You are so careless.
I thought you were becoming dependable.
Sonoko is here.
What happened to your hand?
It's nothing. Don't worry.
If I put my Sancho on it, you don't see it.
It's biting your hand!
What happened?
I burned it with a hot kettle this morning.
-I'm glad it's nothing serious.
-Not at all.
What an end of the year.
Everyone's got some bad luck.
All Hero Club members should get exorcised.
Stop it. Don't say things like that.
-But wait. Maybe we need it.
-Don't take it seriously.
Yuna, have you had anything bad happen to you?
-No. I'm fine.
-Glad to hear that.
If you had, it would mean that we were all cursed.
Amnesty!
No, no, no way.
You are right.
We are becoming too suspicious.
Okay. Listen, everyone. Get back to work.
Okay.
Excuse me, Fu-senpai.
You have a minute?
What's the matter? Are you troubled?
Well... Well...
Is it about your love life?
Wait. That would upset Togo.
-She wouldn't be upset.
-I don't know about that.
Then tell me.
What is it?
To tell you the truth, the other day...
-The other day? When?
-Well...
The day I got my smartphone back.
Something happened on that day?
Believe it or not, Ms. Togo...
What?
Well, nothing...
All our pictures were gone from the phone.
I see. But you can't do anything about that.
Amnesty's inspection may have erased them.
But I feel bad for my friends.
Were there embarrassing pictures of you two?
Wait a second.
Now I get it. No wonder you came to me.
But seriously, how embarrassing was it?
No, nothing like that!
The same one...
It was on Fu-senpai.
It sounds great.
Don't practice too much. You may hurt your voice.
I can't wait to see your event.
-I will be cheering for you.
-It's not my event.
But...
Thank you for your support.
That's the way to go.
Let's cook something hot today.
-Let's stop by at the supermarket.
-Yes, ma'am.
Fu!
YUKI
AT THE HOSPITAL RIGHT NOW.
FU GOT HIT BY A CAR.
What?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
CALM DOWN, ITSUKI. WE'RE ON OUR WAY.
-I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
-I JUST LEFT.
-Guys...
-Yuna...
How is Fu-senpai doing?
EMERGENCY ROOM
She is still in there.
Fu.
Well, it was unfortunate... Ouch.
-Fu.
-Fu-senpai.
I'm fine.
Can you believe it? The car didn't stop at all.
-Who runs a red light?
-But...
Itsuki...
Thank you for coming, everyone.
Come on. You always make us worry.
Can't you be nice to me a little?
So it's not life-threatening, right?
Of course not. Don't be so serious.
But this may ruin your chance
at the entrance exam.
Don't say that. I will take the exam, no matter what.
-You have to stay in the hospital, right?
-Just for a couple of weeks!
This is a hospital. Please, be quiet.
-Are you her sister?
-Yes, I am.
I need you to fill out the forms.
-Can you come with me?
-Sure.
I have to go now. Thank you for coming.
-Be quiet.
-Please, Fu.
That was a relief, right?
You guys take care of yourselves. Don't get hurt.
It's time for alpha waves.
-Forget about it.
-Sorry.
Anyone that violates road traffic laws
should never be forgiven.
The good news is that she is going to be fine.
I wonder what the Spirit was doing.
If something happens to any of you,
I will lose my mind.
Togo...
No more National Defense Mask. No more Black Hole.
Stop it. I mean it.
-You too, Yuna.
-Me too?
-Please, be careful not to hurt yourself.
-Sure.
It's green now. See you.
-See you.
-Bye.
Bye.
Whenever I tried to talk to someone,
something bad happened to them.
I tried to discuss the issue with Fu-senpai,
and she got in an accident.
Heaven has power to influence our world.
Whatever I try to do, there will be a ripple effect.
That's how the world keeps balance.
What's happening to me
needs to be kept to myself.
If I break the rule,
an unfortunate event occurs to everyone.
Our battle is over.
Nobody needs to suffer.
If I keep quiet, nothing will change.
We can enjoy Hero Club every day.
I must not get anyone involved.
If I keep it to myself,
it's going to be fine.
Itsuki, you have the important event today.
It doesn't matter.
-It does.
-You got hurt.
I cannot have fun while you are here.
Don't make me feel bad.
You shouldn't worry about me.
If you are not having fun, I can't have fun.
So I will skip today's event.
Don't worry. I got someone to take my place.
Jeez.
You must rest to recover.
Have you been eating?
You can order delivery if you want.
Of course. I've been cooking.
Well, I mostly eat store-bought food.
-You couldn't even cook rice before.
-That was a long time ago.
I'm okay. Don't worry about me.
-Have you been getting up every morning?
-Yes.
I have not been late for school at all.
Don't worry about me.
Sounds like you are the big sister.
You think so? Yay!
Don't get too excited.
Whatever.
But thank you.
Let's do something fun together
when you are discharged.
-Sure. I can't wait for New Year's Day.
-Me too.
It has been an eventful year.
Let's make the new year a better one.
With a lot of fun.
We tried so hard. We deserve it.
We all deserve to be happy...
I mean, Itsuki, Togo, Karin, Sonoko, and Yuna.
You are all good girls.
The president of Hero Club is very lucky.
Look.
-White Christmas.
-Yes, indeed.
-Hey, victim.
-Sorry we are late.
You don't need to come so often.
Wait, why are you dressed like that?
We thought you might be lonely
that you're in a hospital on Christmas Eve.
I'm not lonely at all. Absolutely not.
Please, forgive her. She is very happy to see you.
Come on, Itsuki!
Wait. Where is Yuna?
I thought she would be here.
YUKI
Thanks to the accident,
-you will fail the entrance exam for sure.
-Shut up. It's not over yet.
I wonder what happened to Yuna.
I may have figured it out.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
Meow! Meow!
-This is an important record.
-I scared them.
-How did this turn up...?
-Wait, Wasshi!
I wanted to help my friends. I'm sorry.
EPISODE 4
UNSPOKEN INTENTIONS