Togo-san is gone.
SCHOOL FESTIVAL ENDED
ON A HIGH NOTE!!
She's gone from the photos too.
What's going on?
At any rate, let's go find Togo-san.
Yup.
I promised that I'll never forget about Togo-san.
And yet...
Yuki Yuna is a Hero -Hero Chapter-
EPISODE 1
SPECTACULAR DAYS
SANSHU
No one has any leads.
It's as if Togo-san never existed.
Even her desk is gone from the classroom.
The support messages I got from you guys...
TO ITSUKI-CHAN
This part has been erased,
but Togo-senpai wrote that everyone's a pumpkin.
This is what vicious bullying would look like.
The amnesty would probably
know something about it.
But they told me they don't know anything about it.
I got the same answer from them.
Does this mean the amnesty is playing dumb again?
The amnesty really doesn't
seem to know anything about it.
Nogi, where have you been?
The amnesty's headquarters.
I've asked about Wasshi to the priests of the shrine
in a rank whom I could talk to,
but they just trembled
and said they don't know about it.
Even the amnesty doesn't know what's going on.
Togo-san...
I guess this is our only way.
Is this...?
The Hero System.
The people at the amnesty brought it out
when I got angry,
and told them to give it to me.
Let's go find her with this.
Find her?
We can still transform, right?
That's right, Nibosshi.
Look, Wasshi's phone is gone.
But Wasshi hasn't appeared
on the radar on my phone.
YUNA YUKI, SONOKO NOGI,
KARIN MIYOSHI, INUBOZAKI FU, ITSUKI
Maybe Wasshi is somewhere
that's really unexpected.
That means, in other words...
-She might be beyond the wall?
-That's right.
That's possible, since Togo's insane.
So I'm thinking of transforming
into a hero, and going there.
The spirit.
If we become heroes,
will there be a price for its power like before?
They said it's a new version this time,
and we won't lose our body functions.
It sounds too good to be true...
She's right.
Even if they tell us that it's a new system,
we could end up...
It's natural to be scared.
I understand.
All right. If it's to save Togo-san, I'll...
-Wait.
-But...
It's different from the first time.
As the club president, I don't want
to let you guys transform so easily.
Don't do this on impulse.
Yes.
Nogi, you too.
Yup, thanks.
We certainly did have terrible experiences,
but the world would have been destroyed
if the heroes didn't fight by offering their bodies.
There was no choice.
The amnesty just did it in a bad way,
but it wasn't anyone's fault.
The amnesty said they won't keep any secrets
about the Hero System anymore.
I was told that in person,
and decided to believe them.
So it's different from before.
This time I'm doing it after fully understanding it,
so I'm going to go.
I'll believe too.
Yuna...
I'm not sure about the people at the amnesty,
but I'll believe it
because you believe them, Sono-chan.
Yu-yu...
Fu-senpai.
I thought this through. I'm going to go.
Jeez.
Don't leave the club president behind.
Fu-senpai.
I do trust you guys, Yuna and Nogi.
Well, since a member of the Hero Club is missing,
the members of the same club should look for her.
Karin-chan.
I'll go too.
Itsuki...
You guys.
Beyond the wall, huh?
We don't know what could happen.
Itsuki, for now, you should take this supplement.
-Wait--
-I'll take some this time.
-Itsuki?
-Thank you.
Don't!
You guys have wonderful friends.
You too, Sono-chan.
The Mankai gauge is full to begin with,
in the new Hero System.
The spirit will protect you with its barrier,
but each time you use the barrier,
you'll consume your Mankai gauge.
The gauge won't get restored.
You can use Mankai if the gauge is full,
but if you use it,
the gauge will become empty at once.
When the gauge is empty,
the spirit won't be able to put up a barrier.
If you get attacked in that situation,
it'll be a matter of life or death.
This is the new Hero System,
which won't make us lose our body functions.
All in all, it's better to have it all explained like this.
You're right. Now we can be prepared.
Sounds like it'll be a lot of work to clean.
Inugami.
Gyuki, long time no see.
Looking forward to working together again.
Hey, I can't see.
Just as I thought, Inugami is my sister's great friend.
I get it, so get off me!
-How have you been?
-You brute.
You haven't changed a bit.
The impermanence of all things.
-I'm sorry!
-Excuse us!
It'll get fierce beyond this point, so be careful.
I'll lead, so you support from the back, Sonoko.
Nibosshi, make sure you don't go too far ahead.
Okay.
Itsuki, I'll make you special udon tonight.
Yup. I'll be looking forward to it, sis.
All right, let's go.
-It's as fierce as ever.
-No matter how many times you look at it,
it doesn't look like a scene from this world.
Oh, it appeared on the radar.
What? Where?
MIMORI TOGO
-Here.
-Oh, it's Togo-san.
Just as we'd expected,
Togo-san was beyond the wall.
-Seems like it's going to be all right, Yuna.
-Yes.
She seems to be surprisingly close.
This direction should be right--
-Oh, my god!
-What is that?
-Over there, right?
-Yeah.
It seems like Wasshi is in there.
Togo-san...
Togo-san turned into a black hole.
I don't know anyone else that's turned into a black hole
after not seeing them for a while.
Sis...
There are Vertex around it.
-Let's go.
-But...
How?
This would happen at a time like this.
Thanks, Itsuki.
You did great, Sonoko.
Yay, I got complemented.
But at this rate, they'll beat us.
How should we get to where Togo is?
I think we can go there on a ship.
A ship? Sonoko?
Mankai!
You're using Mankai already?
You won't be able to have the help of the spirit.
There never used to be a barrier, so it's no problem.
-What do you mean, "It's no problem"?
-Come on.
This is the ship that can take us to Wasshi.
Get on.
Jeez, I guess we have no choice.
-Excuse us.
-What a cool ship.
I think Togo and you guys are cunning.
Mine is the coolest.
You're amazing, Sono-chan.
Thanks, Yu-yu.
Now...
We're off!
We'll be there, Togo-san.
Yuki Yuna is a Hero -Hero Chapter-
You guys, do you have any motion sickness?
Never mind the motion sickness,
this is just plain dangerous.
I wonder what's going on in there.
Togo-san...
They're launching an attack.
Could they be protecting this place?
We're surrounded.
I'll go to where Togo-san is.
Yuna.
I'll come back with her at any cost.
Yu-yu...
Hey, are you going to be okay?
Sheesh, make sure to come back, Yuna.
That's an order.
We'll beat the ones that interfere.
Anything could happen in a place like that.
-Put your spirit into it.
-Yup.
Yu-yu...
Take care of Wasshi.
You can count on me, Sono-chan.
All right.
Right, we'll go there without stopping!
MIMORI TOGO
I won't let you get in the way of Yu-yu!
-Yu-yu, now.
-Yup.
See you guys later.
I have to get there.
Togo-san...
Out-of-body experience?
Could this mean that if I fall apart,
my body would stay like this forever?
Togo-san?
After a while since Sonocchi came
to our middle school,
something that the amnesty
hadn't expected was happening.
Because I broke a part of the sacred boundary,
the outside flames were activated.
At this rate, the flames from the outside
will eat up the world.
They needed to shut down the crime plan
that the amnesty had planned,
and defuse the current situation.
Did I just see Togo-san's memory?
Togo-san, just as I thought, you are in there.
What else?
The only way to suppress the flames
is to beg for forgiveness from God
by offering a shrine maiden
who can hear God's voice
to the outside flames.
They said it's a ritual sacrifice
which was also done at the end of the Christian Era.
A couple of the shrine maidens
who are currently serving at the amnesty
were chosen to be the sacrifices.
But they said I can also take their places.
Apparently, I was the one and only existence
who was qualified to be a hero,
while also having the power of a shrine maiden.
I didn't even have to think about it.
I was the one who made a hole
in the sacred boundary. I have to pay for it.
If Yuna-chan and everyone would be safe...
If it's only myself...
If I disappear...
Yuna-chan and the others will probably look for me.
Shinjyu-sama, please, don't let that happen.
Yuna-chan...
Togo-san always does things in haste.
She made it seem like she didn't exist.
But I promised that I won't leave Togo-san alone.
So I'll save her over and over again!
What's going on?!
I've been here before.
I knew it.
This is the place from that time.
Togo-san.
What is this?
Togo-san!
This is horrible.
I'll save you now.
I don't care! Let go of Togo-san!
Let's go home, Togo-san!
Yes. Now we can...
What's going on?
Yes, she's awake. Togo-san.
Wasshi.
You guys, where am I?
You've been sleeping for a couple of days.
You saved me?
-Yup.
-But...
But the fire will destroy the world at this rate.
I heard your story.
The power of the fire has been stabilized already,
so they don't need a sacrifice anymore.
-Don't tell me someone had to replace me.
-Nope.
Togo. Apparently, you had a fatal amount
of life force taken from you.
So your job was done, because of that.
But you're tough, so you were still alive.
And we made it in time.
That's what happened.
It was a good thing that you trained a lot.
Apparently, you're in good condition.
Have I really been spared?
That's right. You're safe now.
Good job. Well, you'll probably have to stay
at the hospital for a bit longer.
Now everyone in the Hero Club
is here again together.
You guys...
I'm sorry, Togo-san.
Even though I promised I'll never forget about you,
I did for couple of days.
I'm the one who's sorry.
I made you worry so much.
You had no choice.
I probably would have done the same.
Make sure to tell us everything next time.
Yes.
Well, I think we're both to blame.
We did forget too.
Still, you guys all remembered about me.
This isn't a dream, is it?
That's right, Togo-san.
Thanks.
There, there.
-Case closed, right?
-Yup.
All right. We can all celebrate
Christmas, New Year's Eve,
and New Year together.
You're only thinking about playing.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
-Way to go!
-How cruel!
-What a mishap.
-I may have figured it out.
Please be careful not to hurt yourself.
We must not get anyone involved.
Fu!
EPISODE 3
MY HEART HURTS WHEN I THINK OF YOU