So I tried putting some ramune in.
-How was it?
-It was so-so.
-It's starting to get warm.
-Yes.
-It'll be spring soon.
-Ms. Togo, I...
-Yes?
I'm going to get married.
Yes.
Huh!?
This may be sudden,
but Yuna Yuki will get married.
Wha... What are you saying, Yuna!?
You're in middle school!
Who are you getting married to!?
To Shinjyu-sama.
What?
Yuki Yuna is a Hero -Hero Chapter-
EPISODE 5
INCORRUPTIBLE HEART
Please raise your head.
Today...
How can I help you today?
There is something
we must tell you in haste, Ms. Yuna.
We have already received
approval from your parents.
What is it?
Shinjyu-sama, who has been
protecting us for 300 years,
is approaching the end of his life.
Once Shinjyu-sama withers away,
we will no longer have the barrier
that protects us from the flames outside.
The world we live in will be engulfed in flames
and disappear.
Disappear?
-Unfortunately.
-Wait! Wait!
This is all too sudden.
It'll disappear? That can't happen.
Exactly.
We cannot let the human race
be wiped out.
We have found a solution to avoid
the destruction of the human race.
Um, shouldn't everyone
from the Hero Club listen to this?
We would like to talk to you about this first.
-The only way for everyone to survive...
-Huh?
Is for a chosen person
to get married to Shinjyu-sama.
Get married? Married...
Like really get married?
Yes.
From the ancient times, we have called
the act of marrying god a Shinkon.
A union between a god and a saintly maiden.
A ceremony to maintain peace in the world.
That is a Shinkon.
If...
If I do that, will everyone be saved?
Yes.
Be saved...
By performing the Shinkon,
people will acquire a new power
that will help them
become the people of god.
And they will all be able to
live with Shinjyu-sama eternally.
Do you understand?
I don't understand.
But I don't want the human race wiped out.
We also feel the same way.
Once the Shinkon is complete,
the body of the chosen girl
will be moved to the world of god.
And you will no longer be able
get in contact with the outside world.
What?
Meaning the girl chosen for the Shinkon
must die.
Shinjyu-sama has chosen
you, Ms. Yuna,
as his bride for the Shinkon.
Why... Why did he choose me?
Because both your body
and soul are the closest to god.
Because you are a Misugata.
I believe it is similar to the reason why god
chose you as a sacrifice.
So I have to go through with the Shinkon?
All of us at the amnesty
have worked hard trying to figure out
different ways to save the human race.
And we've come
to the conclusion that the Shinkon
is the only choice we have left.
Um...
I'm sorry.
I can't answer right away.
My mind hasn't been able to
keep up with everything.
You already have the wrath of god
on your shoulders.
So this must be very difficult for you.
Unable to tell anyone, because of the curse.
Even if I couldn't talk about it,
I'm sure there would have been
other ways I could have told people.
But I...
hurt my friend's feelings.
Your heart that holds compassion for everyone.
I believe that you are a great hero.
That's not true.
Yuna, you are the only person
who has the power to
save your friend and the human race.
So if I were to do this Shinkon,
what do you mean by they would live eternally
as the people of god?
It means just that.
We will have Shinjyu-sama manage all of us.
In a kind world.
When people die,
that is the end for them.
But if we can live as people of god
alongside Shinjyu-sama,
we may have hope.
Would everyone still be human?
We would be able to exist
under the god's care.
The ones with stronger faith will
be with Shinjyu-sama.
Everyone with Shinjyu-sama.
Please,
help us save the human race.
Please make a merciful decision.
After the curse,
now I have to get married?
What a shock, huh, Gyuki?
Mom and Dad were crying but...
They said they would let me decide.
My body...
My life is already...
I wonder what happens when I die for the Shinkon?
Would it be less painful than dying from the curse?
It's not good, I'm only thinking about myself.
I am a hero.
I have to do what a hero would do.
I can't let the world be engulfed by the flames.
Hero club 5 clauses.
Things will work out if you try.
That's right. It's not the time
for me to be unsure or scared.
I have to do it.
I'm a hero!
If this life will perish with the curse,
I want to use this life for everyone.
I'm not scared.
I'm not scared!
How beautiful.
I've decided.
PREPARATION ROOM
HERO CLUB'S CLUB ROOM
There's something wrong!
What have you taken on!
Yu-yu, I don't think that's right.
Everyone...
You can tell by our reactions, right?
That your decision is wrong.
Ms. Togo...
Those amnesty people!
Yuna, we'll go with you.
Let's go turn it down!
You don't need to go through with the Shinkon!
Sonoko, can you contact the amnesty right now?
I can't hold back any longer.
Let's go.
It might be a good thing to take them down.
Wait!
I decided...
To accept the Shinkon.
You don't have to do this!
This would kill you, right?
That makes no sense.
It's the same as a sacrifice.
Also living alongside Shinjyu-sama.
What does that mean?
It makes me shiver.
It couldn't possibly be something good.
But if I don't do the Shinkon,
Shinjyu-sama will wither away,
and the world will end.
I understand why Shinjyu-sama
would wither away,
but that doesn't mean you have to do this!
Fu-senpai,
the hero club
is a club that does things for other people, right?
-Yuna, this is not the same!
-But!
I think this is also part of the hero club.
No one is at fault.
If there is nothing else left to do
to save the world...
If this is the only way, as a hero I have to...
Yuna!
Go and calm yourself.
Yu-yu, let's not see that as the only way.
Before Shinjyu-sama withers away,
let's try to come up with something else.
That's right!
We can't.
Even if we were to think together,
I don't have much time left anymore.
Yuna?
We know.
That your body is weak from the curse
god gave you.
Please don't talk about it!
I never told you anything!
Yuna, it's okay.
Including all that, we'll definitely solve this.
It's not right!
Why is this all happening just to Ms. Yuna?!
But, Itsuki...
I don't like
that someone could get hurt
or go through something painful.
So this time,
-the burden has to be on me only.
-No!
If Yuna dies,
do you know how much pain
that will cause all of us here!
I tried to imagine it,
but I'll probably stab my stomach and follow you.
But even you, Ms. Togo,
you went to the sea of flames to save everyone.
You also thought you could sacrifice
yourself to save the world, right?
I did!
But it was my fault
for breaking the wall in the first place.
You did nothing wrong!
I'm against it! I'll stab myself!
That's not fair.
I'm like this, because I took your place...
Took my place? What does that mean?
Ms. Yuna.
If heroes are like what you say,
I feel like they need
to work to make everyone happy.
I know, that's why I'm working so hard.
B... but...
When we say everyone,
you are also included, Yuna!
I am... very happy.
If everyone can be saved.
-That's a lie!
-The hero club five clauses.
Try your best to not give up.
I'm betting on a future where everyone is safe.
But you've given up on surviving!
Hero club five clauses!
Things will work out if you try!
Nothing will happen if you don't try!
Yuna! Don't use the clauses like that!
I want to do everything I can
with the time I have left!
Which is why I came here to discuss it with you!
This is just an announcement.
-We have to discuss it more.
-I am!
Yuna, anyway
-don't push yourself too hard.
-I'm not!
-I'm sorry.
-I am hero like,
just like I always am!
-Wait...
-Yuna!
You still don't understand what we're saying?
There are no other options left!
-So we have to do this!
-Wait.
Why is it like this?
Don't fight...
Itsuki...
Itsuki.
I...
I really
don't have any time left.
-Yuna!
-Yu-yu!
What is the right answer in situations like these?
I can't find her.
Did she hide somewhere?
I checked the terminal,
and there is a reaction from Yuna's home.
-Let's go!
-Yes.
If we talk at once,
Yu-yu will be overwhelmed.
So let's talk to her calmly.
That's true.
Yuna?
The radar was reacting to this?
It has today's date.
Where did she go, leaving her terminal?
SORRY ABOUT EVERYHING.
I AM GOING.
It can't be.
THE AMNESTY'S HEADQUARTERS
Yuki Yuna is a Hero -Hero Chapter-
My highest respects to the heroes.
Please stop.
This is where all the previous
heroes and shrine maidens lie.
Is Yuna here?
It can't be!
Ms. Yuna is not here.
I just thought this was a good place to talk.
We came here to see Yuna!
Where is Ms. Yuna?
She is at the amnesty.
-Then we'll break in there.
-Yes.
So you've heard everything from Ms. Yuna.
The only way to save the world
is for her to do the Shinkon.
Yes, she told us!
Are you aware of the reason
behind the hurry?
Ms. Yuna only has a short time to live.
Is there really no way we can get rid of Yuna's curse?
We tried to find a way.
A way to save Ms. Yuna.
But we couldn't find anything.
As long as the flames outside exist,
Ms. Yuna will be cursed.
Then is there anything we can
do about the flames outside?
We did have a few plans.
-Then we can do those!
-But...
We realized they were impossible to do.
Why did you decide that?!
There isn't enough time.
Ms. Yuna will be doing the Shinkon ceremony shortly.
Don't mess around! We'll stop it!
Many of the previous heroes
lost their lives fulfilling their duties.
Gin Minowa gave her life
two years ago to protect humanity.
Ms. Gin
fought hard and long for humanity,
and fulfilled her duties,
and became an eternal spirit.
Ms. Yuna,
though the circumstance is different
she too will be sacrificing herself for the greater good.
Understanding that, that is what a hero must do.
So you want us
to be understanding?
Previous heroes and shrine maidens.
So they were all around the same age as us.
So you've always survived
by sacrificing the lives of children.
How can a world like that exist?
If this is the only way,
it must be done to protect everyone's lives.
This is how people exist in this world.
It must be done?
Yes.
You hated bell peppers. Right?
You were strict.
But I really liked the charming side
you sometimes showed.
But now...
You're no longer that Aki-sensei.
You mourned Gin's death with us.
If you know that pain,
you wouldn't sacrifice any more people!
You classmates,
their friends,
and family
are excitedly waiting for spring to come.
Eating udon at home.
Sleeping in their warm futons.
They are leading peaceful lives.
With a small sacrifice,
we've been able to help
the majority of the people live happy lives.
If that's the case...
If that's the case!
Then you should all sacrifice yourselves!
We would, if that were possible.
But Shinjyu-sama will not accept us.
Maybe he accepts you
for the anger you feel for things like this.
This is...
It's already here.
Wait... What is this?!
It's your turn.
The god above
was angered by how close
the humans got to his powers.
So it is said that he sent down his judgement.
A Shinkon would be out of the question.
The Vertex is coming.
No.
What is this?
What's going on?
What?
An enemy in the real world?
Is that... an enemy?
What is that?
Something like that...
A Shinkon is realized
when Ms. Yuna goes to where Shinjyu-sama is,
and becomes the sacrifice for the people's wishes.
Once the Shinkon is realized,
humans will become the people of god.
No longer being humans,
they will not be attacked anymore.
So everyone will be able to
live in peace with Shinjyu-sama.
This is your last duty.
Hold back the attacks until the Shinkon is complete.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
-Don't mess with us!
-I can't forgive this!
-For Yuna's happiness!
-Please believe in humanity.
-We want to...
live!
FINAL EPISODE
ONLY YOU CAN MAKE ME HAPPY