I have a big gun
I took it from my lord
Sick with justice
I just wanna feel you
I'm your angel
Only a ring away
You make me violate you
No matter who you are
It's all up to you
No one lives forever
Been burn in the hell
By all those pigs out there
It's always been hell
From when I was born
They make me violate them
No matter who they are
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
Weapon . . . I have it all
Your face suddenly changed, Mr. Rock.
I'm making this face because I have...
another favor to ask of you.
There's still another one?
Yes. It's not something I can talk about with a plain face.
The two of us are quite alike in nature aside from a minuscule difference:
the people we happened upon along the way. That's all it is.
So there's a chance...
There are no chances. The way things work never changes,
just like how your legwork can never defeat a gun.
That's the law of nature. Listen.
Coercive power decides the winner.
That's all there is to it.
So I'll be using this and...
Indeed.
And, with that, I will win the game.
You snicker contemptuously at people a lot. Do you ever look yourself in the mirror?
Your grins resemble those of the skulls in the Day of the Dead festival.
Yes, exactly!
I'm impressed you noticed it, little lady.
We came here carrying guns all the way from the Netherworld!
My team, your chief, those soldiers—everyone did.
So, little lady, offer some marigolds
and tequila when you visit our graves.
If you do, after you meet your pathetic fate here in the outskirts of Asia,
I'll at least offer some chocolate.
Here it goes! Take my oiler's cock!
Grab it and get ready for the sucking!
I talked with the Japanese man.
I did so with the gunslinger.
I'm tired of getting pushed around by them.
Yes...
Um, Young Master?
Young Master?
This feels great!
What are you saying, Young Master?
Please come here.
Fabiola, you too!
Young Master!
Take that!
W-Wait!
Ah, geez.
The kids are fooling around.
By the way, never mind Rock, but where's Revy?
Oh, I thought she was having a chat with the small maid,
but then she shut herself in a bow cabin.
Don't worry, Fabiola.
About what?
I bet you thought I went insane.
No, not at all!
I won't hesitate anymore.
I'm sick of everyone pushing me around.
Fabiola, you also met Roberta, didn't you?
Chief was, well...
It hurts me to say it,
but even if she successfully brings down the enemies,
I doubt she will remember for what reason and for whom she killed.
Indeed, she is in a state of confusion,
but Roberta's ultimate motive is to atone for her sins.
Chief is so earnest yet uncouth, dismissing the compromised morality of murder as hypocrisy.
Fabiola, listen carefully. This is important.
I will save her at all costs. This is my own will.
The Japanese man might be manipulating me, but if it helps me achieve my goal, I will do it.
You're free to return to Venezuela before me.
Even if I'm left alone, I will save Roberta and make it back.
I will become her cane and walk with her forever.
Young Master!
Young Master, I'm taking this talk beyond our master-
servant relationship. Listen with that in mind.
Chief will probably stay that way. Actually,
it may have become a whole lot worse by now.
This is serious! Even if we manage to
return together, the suffering will remain.
That won't stop me, Fabiola.
I see. You're really determined.
To be honest, I thought you'd have given up already.
You saw how badly Chief broke down, after all.
You may be good-natured and diligent, but you're still a spoiled little boy.
I thought you couldn't handle this one.
But you're still going to do it, aren't you?
Yes. I won't let her die a dog's death in their hands!
All right. Let's do it!
We can do it! I'm sure we can!
Definitely. May the Lord bless us.
May the Lord bless us.
Damn her!
Family love? She's got her head in the clouds.
You fucking brat!
No one was ever there to protect me when I grew up.
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it. What the hell? Damn it. Damn it. Damn it.
Fuck you. Die. Die.
Damn you. Just die. Damn it! Damn it!
Fucker. Damn it!
Becky, I need alcohol so get your ass—
Fuck you!
Fuck this. What a terrible flashback.
We entered the Mekong Delta on schedule.
We'd see the blue water had changed
to brown if the sun were up.
Hmph! This stench reminds me of my U.S. brown-water navy days.
Still, I'd rather pass by this place
in the dead of night like this.
Benny.
Yeah.
The GPS and the echo sounder are
all we can depend on from here.
One more.
Right now, I'm looking through the latest survey data of a mining company.
I'm also worried that we can't travel
as fast in this shallow water.
The maid is rapidly catching up to us this very second. Keep that in mind.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ, I'm fucking anxious!
The Japanese man told me you were waiting here.
Major.
This is something you gave me.
Your eyes tell me that you won't forget what I've done, that you'll never forgive me.
Are you going to shoot me?
If you think that way, Major,
please listen to me for the sake
of the justice you believe in.
I see.
I understand.
However, the responsibility for what happened to you, your father, and your maid falls only on me.
My men will engage in battle ordinarily
and protect themselves. Will that be fine?
You...
What did you infuse in Young Master's mind?
Well...
I'll tell you half of it.
Attention!
Gentlemen, we will reach the area of operation tonight.
However, expect the woman that came after us in Roanapur to be there. This is for certain.
Destroy all obstacles in the way.
Shane.
Isn't that woman related to this boy?
Yes, but I alone will bear that responsibility.
Give your all for the mission and for justice. That is all.
That's just impossible!
Then let me ask you instead.
Can we overcome this situation without betting anything?
So you were looking ahead to all of this.
Yes. I'm eliminating every factor other than luck.
This is a standard gambling tactic.
The gamble is at its finest when winning is a matter of trying one's luck at the very last moment.
You...
You are...
Ridiculous.
We're here, sirs, right in the center
of the border of three countries,
the area of a three-way standoff that no one dares break.
This is the Golden Triangle.
Many thanks.
No need. I already got paid in full for the job.
Now, please leave!
I apologize for acting rather unfriendly.
Good hunting! And try not to drag us into your mess.
Did Garcia leave with the Major?
Yeah, they left.
Yes.
Yes, good.
Yes!
I'm definitely going to hit the jackpot!
Benny, he's going to lose!
Mr. Chang is going to lose!
Echo to Alpha. We've reached the sentry location.
Situation OK. No coordinate changes.
Alpha, roger. Standby for orders.
This is Delta. Two hundred yards to sentry location.
Alpha, roger. All squads, complete closure by 0230 hours.
Delta, roger.
Echo, roger.
Good. Let's hurry to the designated point.
Major, Major!
This is Delta. We found unusual
objects right in front of the village.
What are the unusual objects? Describe.
Poles.
Many cylindrical poles, about thirty
inches long, are mounted on our path.
Charlie, Echo, anything unusual
in the area? About thirty inches—
This is Echo. We see a few dozen of them.
Simple cylindrical objects with nothing attached, about three feet apart from one another.
We do not see any explosives or wires.
This is Charlie.
There are poles by this entrance of the village as well!
What are those? It's as if they form a barrier.
Shane!
What are those poles for?
Could they be religious objects for the Shan or the Va?
Never heard of it.
Young Master.
I know. She is already here.
Echo to Alpha. Major, please respond.
This is Alpha.
We've reached the surveillance point.
But something is strange.
There are no signs of people.
So the place is deserted?
Yes, Major.
Alpha to Charlie. How does it look from the east side?
This is Charlie. No movement in sight.
There's a plant in view, but no one is...
It's a corpse!
Echo to Alpha!
We also see the corpse!
There are multiple corpses near the gate!
There's light to the south end!
Ray, we're the farthest from there. Let's hurry.
Right.
It's Package Romeo!
We confirm Package Romeo!
Everyone, listen. The illegal drug plant has already been neutralized.
It's only us and Package Romeo here.
Package Romeo running at 10 o'clock!
Target is going to the jungle!
Delta to Alpha. She's approaching.
She's stopped right in front of us.
Target seems to be holding a hostage!
Now she's disappeared into the forest!
What's the matter, Deckard?
Target is holding a hostage, and she sliced off his ear!
The hostage screamed, so he must be alive.
Who's the hostage?
It's Shue Yan. She's using him to lure us out.
Is Delta the closest?
Yes.
All right. Pursue the target.
But do not approach her.
Only capture the location of the target.
Delta, roger!
All other squads, provide backup for Delta.
Delta to Alpha. We can't locate the target!
Alpha to Echo. Do you see her?
This is Echo. Hold for a moment.
We have her in sight!
Oh, damn it!
Do you copy, Delta? Respond!
I swear on the name of Santa Maria...
to counter every injustice with an iron hammer!
We lost Murdoch and Garraty!
Sniper team, report!
Lost target, but one shot hit her!
Damn it!
She's aiming for our heads instead of our armored body!
All squads, do you copy? Everyone except
squad captains, take off your night vision device.
Put on a face mask and prepare for close-range combat!
Quickly equip your face masks!
We need to go back up Delta!
Let's hurry!
Echo to Alpha.
Echo, report.
We've located Package Drug Vault inside the jungle.
Be careful. She most likely set a booby trap.
I have fought on filthy Vietnamese
battlefields many, many times.
I have quite a bit of experience fighting in the jungle.
If we were in Guadalcanal, I'd use a mortar,
or, if we were in Vietnam, napalm bombs, to burn down the whole forest...
along with your dearest.
Echo to Alpha. We've located a detonator.
It seems we need to input a numeral code.
Is Package Romeo telling us we need to capture her for the unlock code?
No. Wait, Gardner. That is a trap itself.
Evacuate immediately!
Understood. All Squad Echo members, immediately—
Lieutenant Gardner, there's something over here!
This is Squad E Captain. Wright is dead!
The enemy bullet pierced the bulletproof vest!
Package Romeo's weapon is flechettes!
She's using a musket to fire those poles!
She came with an antique weapon to hunt us down.
We saw the muzzle blast!
Good! We've got her! Let's go!
She mounted the numerous poles as a silent declaration that she won't let any of us return alive.
All squads, retreat slowly and exit the forest.
Do not let your guards down.
Sanchez, get ready.
This is the sniper team. We're
now in retreat support position.
Damn it.
We can't move because of all these traps in the forest!
Understood. Stay and prepare for enemy attack.
The squad immobilized in the forest is like a trapped rat.
She can attack them from anywhere.
Sniper team, watch out! You'll get assaulted first.
Damn it!
I got a shot in.
I went for her leg to avoid giving her a fatal injury, but she ran away!
All right!
That would...
only make her fiercer, like a wounded tiger.
Let's go!
All right? We will evacuate as soon as Squad Alpha takes support position!
Hold out until then!
Damn it.
It's hopeless! Goddamn it!
Damn it!
Sanchez, where are you? Respond.
Join up with the main unit immediately!
They're going to keep dying.
Your little foxes, that is.
Until I skin all the foxes in the forest,
my hunt won't end!
Major.
I know.
Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it all!
Roberta.
Roberta!
Do you hear me?
I've finally caught up, Roberta.
I'll tell you where to come, so listen carefully.
And...
make sure you come.
I'll be waiting for you.
Fuck it!
Fine, I get it!
I get what kind of person I am.
Hey, Revy.
Just a little longer.
Just a little longer and everything will be over.
I don't care.
Jesus, I keep remembering things
I don't need to. I can't stand this.
This is your fault.
Why is that?
Never mind that. Everything is playing into my hands, Revy.
I'm talking about the fate of everyone living in the town.
What the hell happened to you?
Jesus Christ. It's just like what that fucking midget said.
Rock, you've been living in that town for too long.
You've immersed yourself in Roanapur too much.
As soon as this case is over, get out.
What are you saying, Revy? The conclusion is in sight.
As I said, just a little longer.
I don't get you at all.
Young Master.
Yes, Fabiola. To be honest,
I'm scared of what's going to happen.
I don't know what that Japanese man told you,
but I do know you can do it, Young Master.
The Lord does not save anyone. People like you do.
I'm sure you can do it.
Thanks.
The sun is about to rise.
The matter will come to light when the
Opium Army soldiers start their morning patrol.
However, things will be settled before that.
What settlement, Rock? Do you have a real sense of what you're doing?
Yes. I'm betting on that split second
that will decide everything.
Rock, do you realize you're—
Revy.
I know. I can see what lies ahead.
Young Master.
Why is he here?
Young Master, at this point, I can't even tell whether you are real.
I can't make out what time it is,
and a dead man keeps talking to me!
I can't even be sure whether I'm alive or dead.
But it's all right!
Once I finish the revenge, I can return
to that mansion where the orchids bloom!
Roberta!
Revenge never mattered to me.
Even though I kept defying his orders,
Chang let me leave the town with the kids.
Why did he?
And Balalaika, upon understanding Chang's intentions,
didn't finish off Roberta and instead let her escape very easily.
Why did she?
Revy, Chang's goal is not only to keep Roanapur hidden from the public eye,
but also to use Roberta to ruin the U.S. Army's plans.
This is a major site of drug production, and Roanapur is its export port.
By having Roberta attack the U.S. Army,
Chang intended to keep the U.S. judicial
authority away from the Golden Triangle.
However, that cannot be allowed to happen.
Rock, so tell me.
What is your goal?
It does matter!
They killed your dad and caused you grief, trying to take away everything from me!
That's why I cannot forgive that—
Roberta, you got it wrong.
No matter who you judge and punish, you won't be redeemed of your sins.
That is why...
you aren't going to end this.
No!
That can't be! You can't do that!
Well, this ends everything.
No! Young Master would never say such a thing!
It can't end this way!
No one will be rewarded this way!
You are not Young Master!
Is this your revenge to Roanapur?
That town led many people to ruin, yet I never saved any.
Are you still feeling sorry about that Tokyo girl—
However,
this time I will put an end to the
misfortune that befalls the town.
I've been thinking for a long time, Roberta, about what I should say when I find you.
But words can't convey anything. That was my conclusion.
Young Master!
I'll bet everything on this.
Do you understand, Roberta?
If you believe, my bullet will not kill you.
You will not die,
no matter what.
This gamble will bring
this long dance of death,
this chain of miserable revenge,
to an end, at last.
Here it goes, Roberta.
So what about us? What about yourself?
You can't return to your peaceful homeland anymore.
Let me ask one thing.
Why did you leave the twilight to join us in the dark night?
This was the only way to settle it.
Still, I'm glad I did. I learned one thing.
Revy, I now understand how you guys feel every day.
Don't act like you know everything!
Young Master!
I can't control my hands anymore!
I didn't mean to fire back! Young Master!
Roberta, look.
You are still alive...
even though my bullet should have pierced through.
Roberta,
so this is the end.
Young Master, you're bleeding!
It's all right.
Young Master!
Young Master, you were hit by my bullet!
Let your gun down, Ray.
It was so realistic I almost fired a shot.
The impact was far greater than I imagined.
Hey! Snap out of it and give first aid to Young Master!
Why is he...
Why is he alive? Damn you!
He...
He died once at my bullet.
So did you, and so did I.
No one here is a winner. Only the sinners remain.
I will share your burden.
From now on, I will support you, and we'll live together.
Young Master!
Oh, geez, what now?
Hey, Rock, they're back.
Let's see.
Did the Americans capture their target?
Seems so. I see three stretchers.
All right!
This is undoubtedly the optimal result.
I knew you could do it, Garcia.
I'm glad I could save somebody at last.
Mr. Rock.
Really...
we just got really lucky.
And...
you too.
You're a fucker who manipulated Young Master to play "Cambodian roulette," all under the pretense of kindness!
Look. I fired a blank,
a hollow brass counterfeit just like your specious magic!
I will never see someone like you or that town again.
Enjoy your waltz with the dead until the Lord gets tired of it.
Still, I have definitely attained something unique.
Um, Cathy, put a lot of sugar and milk in my coffee, enough for a pancake.
Boss, how's your blood sugar level been recently?
Just bring it. We only live once, you know.
Well, the secretary had a private lunch meeting with the National Security Advisor.
We'll draw a clear line in the next Security Council meeting.
By the way, Shue Yan's custody and rights will be transferred to us.
And yes, in front of the President.
That would have surely infuriated the other party.
It was a cavalcade of four-letter words in a voice you'd hear ringing out in a French restaurant.
That's amazing!
Isn't it?
I wonder who they thought they were up against.
No kidding.
What a mess.
It's from Chang.
I got a belated bonus.
Why now?
Many months have passed since then,
but Roanapur hasn't changed in the slightest.
Money and guns decide the worth of everything. That's one fact that won't easily change.
Though my body is worn out and weak
Somewhere on this planet, someone outdid me.
I can't save anyone.
Though the strength that I once had is gone
Now my eyes have learned to cry heavy tears
Now my heart is beating with yours
In the midst of the night I survived
Where the moon and stars could not be found
Now I see the brightest light on my way
In this moment I exist
In this moment I live
All because of the grace you bestowed on me
Is it painful to keep looking at that town through the eyes of a living man?
Either way, that's the path you chose yourself.
The only other option is to die for real.
Bang!
Still, you could reach that point once.
Yes, certainly.
But not now, Revy. Sometime, eventually.