I have a big gun
I took it from my lord
Sick with justice
I just wanna feel you
I'm your angel
Only a ring away
You make me violate you
No matter who you are
It's all up to you
No one lives forever
Been burn in the hell
By all those pigs out there
It's always been hell
From when I was born
They make me violate them
No matter who they are
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
Weapon . . . I have it all
Sergeant Major Horner, what happened?
We heard gunshots and advanced to capture the enemy. A child was there.
I'm very sorry, sir!
This'll be extra trouble.
This is Burrows!
The kid would have died had we not rescued him.
...here and now.
I believe Sergeant Major made the right choice!
All right, abort the pincer. We're switching to maneuver warfare.
The rendezvous is at Dagger 6.
Sergeant Major, the situation
has become even more severe.
Still...
we'd never leave a child to die.
Well done.
Shane...
Now, gentlemen, the situation has changed.
Are you up to the challenge?
Sir, yes, sir!
Young Master...
is gone.
He's gone!
This is all because of the foxes.
The stench of blood is gettin' stronger.
Be careful, Shenhua!
It'll be really bad if we let our source of income run away.
Stop, gal!
Chief!
Don't! She's gone crazy!
Let me go!
Chief, it's me, Fabiola!
I have come to greet you on Young Master's strong request.
Chief, Young Master is...
Fabiola?
Did you finish cleaning the living room?
Master is looking for his newspaper.
I have to go to the plantation and pick up Young Master before it starts raining.
That bridge is no good. The enemy could ambush us there.
But it's the only road out of town.
Calm down, kid. We're on your side.
Kid, how are you feeling?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
We're American soldiers. We saved you from the shootout.
We'll protect you until we reach a safe location.
I don't break my promises, so trust me and relax.
Roberta has taken too many drugs.
It is uncertain whether she will recognize Garcia at all.
I've made my bet on that uncertainty.
If Garcia fails to bring Roberta back,
his role will change dramatically.
I need you to understand, Garcia.
Are you all right?
Would you like some water?
What are you doing, Sergeant Major?
You scared out another child, didn't you?
That's nonsense!
I'm Sanchez, a First Sergeant. 'Sup.
Despite his looks, Sergeant Major Horner has a seven-year-old daughter—
Hey!
and is actually a really sweet daddy.
That was unnecessary!
Burrows, do you have any chocolate bars?
I don't have any.
Oh, LG might.
Oh, right. He has a sweet tooth.
If only...
If only you did not exist...
If only... If only you did not exist...
In case Garcia successfully makes it through,
the problem is what comes next.
I spent two days to let people in town know about my business.
I don't know who it is,
but that person won't be able to overlook this situation and should definitely contact me.
Still, he's late.
LG, notify Bravo and Charlie of the new ORP.
Yes, sir!
Hey!
Stop!
Kid!
Why?
Don't point your gun at the kid!
However, Major, he...
Horner, you put it down, too.
Kid...
Why did you?
Who are you? You weren't there by coincidence.
C-Coincidence? It's no coincidence!
You took away everything.
You're the ones who messed up our lives!
We are...
in a much worse situation than I thought.
Who are you?
You should know.
Last October, in Barinas, Venezuela,
ten people were killed at a political gathering.
One of them was my... my father!
That was...
...Non-Departmental Presidential Directive 114!
You took away my father.
And another important person to me
will never come back!
Kid...
you have the right to take revenge upon me.
Don't, Shane!
You are a boy.
You should be able to decide what to do on your own.
What is so difficult? Let me see.
Apparently four things are hidden inside that picture.
But no matter how hard I look, it's just a picture of a hunt in a forest.
Certainly.
Emilione came here and boasted about it, but I bet she lied.
You shouldn't be so fast to call someone a liar.
That's the back side.
Well, it is important to examine it from different angles.
And when you do...
here's the horned owl,
and here's the angel.
And look here!
It's Jesus Christ! You're right!
Why didn't I see it earlier?
You were probably only looking at it from the one angle.
In order to see things correctly, you must
approach the matter from all possible directions.
Shane, stop!
Put your guns down!
That's an order!
Oh, it's just you.
That was a bit rude. Who have you been waiting for?
Well...
As for the stuff you ordered over the phone this morning,
it's been delivered to the specified location.
Thanks.
So how's it going? Are things going to settle down soon?
No, it won't end just yet.
I won't let it end.
On my way here, I saw some Ivans sprinting on rooftops.
We located the main U.S. Army unit.
Man your battle stations immediately.
That part of the bet should be fine.
Come on. The proud Visotoniki is making an appearance before their old enemy.
If he shoots you, he'll be considered
an enemy as per the rules of engagement!
Didn't you hear my orders?
Major! We're picking up a strange signal on our radios!
It's in Russian!
We found the enemy!
Gray Fox! Do you hear me, Major?
She is right above you. Get ready.
I have caught up.
Run away farther, little fox.
Shane!
Major!
If you don't...
you'll be skinned!
Who is this woman?
Don't point your guns at her!
Kid...
She is another person you broke down!
Young Master...
Is that you, Young Master?
As soon as the hunt is over,
I shall prepare some tea for you.
Please wait just a little longer.
The enemy has been repelled.
Good work, Corporal Zachamin.
Who are you and that unit on the rooftop?
I belong to the Soviet VDV.
My name is, yes, Captain Jane Doe.
Major, the Bloodhound is still close by.
Evacuate immediately.
Rather than take on the U.S. Army and wipe each other out,
Balalaika will choose to settle the matter between her and Chang.
The Hong Kong Triad and Hotel Moscow
once fought each other for the
stranglehold of power in this town.
However, to this day, neither side has claimed victory.
In their last duel before the ceasefire, Chang's bullet pierced through Balalaika's body.
And she feels heavily indebted to Dutch for saving her from that predicament
because he gave her another chance to strike back at Chang.
Chang is giving Balalaika deliberate openings so that she'll...
You've already won that part of the gamble.
Military radio messages we've been tapping said something along those lines.
So? What are you going to set up next?
The American soldiers had their
ground plan greatly compromised.
Even if they wish to return to their original mission, they lack the means to do so.
And I will be there to provide for them.
But what if they give up and call off the operation?
In that case...
You're on the right track, Rock.
It's a matter of honor for the U.S. military.
They'll go ahead with the operation no matter what.
Then, if all goes well, I'll have every game card
other than Roberta in my hand.
And that's when the stuff you ordered from us will prove useful.
The U.S. government and a wealthy
South American are both there to pay.
It's a guaranteed payment.
I smell a bonanza, Rock!
Eda!
Is that really all you will take?
You...
Personally,
I'd prefer to have the Hong Kong Triads pay you as well.
I see where you're going. You need a backer.
The Mafias may be promoting coexistence and co-prosperity,
but Chang is the one who holds the real power here.
Well, yeah.
But Chang...
has a backer.
Regardless of how big the Hong Kong gangsters act, this town can only exist in collusion with the Man!
So what?
I am looking for someone who can move Chang,
the true overlord of Roanapur that pulls the strings behind Chang's back, the—
Enough, Rock.
There's no need to look for Leviathan in the ocean's depths.
Also...
did you know, Rock? Not all gods are on good terms!
Isn't it fine that way?
It's best to just call him yourself!
They're covering us from above perfectly. That's impressive.
Still, it's a bit rude.
Shane, are they really Soviet soldiers?
The Soviet Union no longer exists.
And she introduced herself as "Jane Doe,"
a placeholder name for unidentified corpses.
Ray!
My only wish is to leave this town of madness as soon as possible.
Yeah.
I agree.
Mr. Rock...
You told me to read this when I feel lost.
Mr. Rock, do you understand who exactly I'm dealing with?
Oh, Rock. The boss is pissed.
You shouldn't get too emotional with him.
Is it Rock?
Yeah. I'll finish up now.
As your friend, I don't want to see you leave.
Do a good job!
It's me.
I'm so worried about what you're trying to pull off that I can't sleep.
Dutch, first of all, let me apologize.
You're polite all right, but you should've taken note of the dress code!
You're not wrong,
but this is no longer about me alone.
You're talking big, Rock.
Will you be bringing Perry Mason as your attorney or something?
We've been commissioned for work, Dutch.
A U.S. government agency is the client.
It's a legitimate job for the Lagoon Company.
This town passed the turning point long ago.
Our job is to get rid of the troublemakers at the very last moment.
If we take them out as a courier,
another troublemaker will leave the town as well.
I get what you're saying, Rock.
But this is pathetic. Right now you're just like a—
Dutch.
Someone gets to put an end to all this turmoil,
and we'll be the only ones enjoying it.
Hang up!
What did he say exactly?
Now there's another person that needs to see a doctor, aside from the maid.
Hello.
Tell him that's never going to happen.
Oh, it's not him.
It's Mr. Chang of the Triads.
He wants to commission us for work.
Do you see them, Goth girl?
Quiet. Isn't that Garcia?
Oh gosh! Our client's with the U.S. army soldiers now.
That kid is being a fucking pain in the ass.
There are only a few of them right now. We can take them on.
How are your weapons?
This is all I have.
That's perfect.
Good. It didn't penetrate. When were you shot?
It was when that monster woman jumped down.
The kid was in danger.
Good.
The big one in the middle can't move.
I'll get the black guy.
You take care of the captain guy, okay?
All right.
We'll get them after my countdown.
Ready...
Three!
Two!
One!
Fuck!
I make a living thanks to these arms. You fuckers shot them both!
Two Hand!
This is a message from our captain!
The war tonight is solely ours!
No one else shall interfere!
We will aim for your head or neck next time. That's all!
Damn it!
Young Master.
Mister!
Take a look at this.
No trace of booby traps!
Engine turned on!
We just followed the boy's map.
We didn't expect to see you here, Will.
We utilized our intelligence agents to find the town's broker agency.
And, this might surprise you, but the cathedral on the hill was the one.
At this point, nothing really surprises me.
We also procured a ship that'll take you to the site of the operation.
Squad B will now merge.
Good!
Unfortunately, this operation cannot be canceled.
Squad C will now merge.
Good!
Complete the roll call quickly, then have everyone board the vehicle!
This isn't too pleasing, but let's accept it and move on.
Shane!
We have two kids now.
Yeah.
We'll bring both of them along.
Despite all that shooting, not a single policeman showed up.
The business district is flourishing as usual five blocks down.
Major.
Oh, Captain Jane Doe.
Thank you for the assistance thus far.
It has been our pleasure, Major.
However, frankly speaking,
we wish we had a chance to exchange fire with your troops.
Ever since that time we were still living in the human world,
ever since we were writhing on the sands of Afghanistan,
we have been eagerly looking forward to this war.
So you were in Afghanistan, eh? Vietnam was our marsh.
We may differ in nationality or in locations we served at,
but my unit has seen and fought in the same war!
However, we have fallen to the point where our hopes and fears depend on a gangster's duel rather than genuine warfare.
The life of the dead is miserable.
We can't help but feel jealous and envious of the living.
Major, we ask you to at least remember...
the discipline and power we maintain.
And we ask you to burn into your memory...
the sense of horror.
Major...
Wait.
No, Major.
Captain, give me a second.
Prepare for battle! Focus the shots to the left!
Prepare to fire!
No, Major.
We cannot wait.
We will now see the major off.
Gun salute ready!
Aim!
Fire!
All ammo annihilated target!
Good.
Major...
Captain Jane Doe,
you skillfully deployed a moderate number of soldiers and carried out a saturation attack. I commend you.
We are greatly honored by your compliment.
But, if we are indeed soldiers of such caliber,
how did we end up so different from your unit?
Captain,
let me ask you a difficult question.
Were you...
discharged due to illness?
I see why you may suspect so.
I was practically deprived of my military position in an arbitrary discharge.
The reason is perfectly simple.
In a border transgression operation against international treaties,
I saved a child from a refugee camp, and the mass media saw me.
Yes. It was April of the year 1986.
Now,
leave this town quickly, Major.
And I hope we never meet again.
Everything is saturating, be it this town or my brain.
What am I doing right now?
Rock.
Do you still see a path ahead of you?
Yes, I do.
Of course.
Fine, then.
But I can't fight anymore.
It does not matter.
We'll manage without you.
I see.
Yes.
We'll be fine.
These are so neatly done:
counterfeit ship registry, river passage permit, service permit for three countries, NGO activity permit,
a whole set of press cards, and a heap of U.S. military night warfare equipment!
Did he order all that from the Church of Violence?
In the end, even Mr. Chang gave me a call to dispatch us!
Damn it! There was no way I could reject it.
When did he become such a top-notch negotiator?
Lagoon has set sail.
Even if the maid is still alive, she'll leave this town to pursue them.
Things have been going too well it's almost disturbing.
To deal with the war-crazed bitch, you invited, of all people, that Japanese coward,
and he's pulled off this much already.
I may as well tell you
I finally understand why the boss regards an ex-cop like you,
who killed all his mates, so highly.
You've got the toughest nerves of steel!
Don't flatter me so much.
Gentlemen!
I'm the captain of this ship.
Once we refuel on water a bit later, we'll take you to your destination.
I'm the leader, Caxton.
I'll be blunt. Can we trust you?
It's up to you.
I'm not happy that the cyborg woman might be coming after us now, either.
But we've been officially commissioned for this job.
So we'll fulfill the contract.
And no, I don't think that was enough to kill her off.
So yeah. He's a little annoyed by all this, but you can trust him.
He should be familiar with this route, too.
"Familiar"?
He served in the River Boat Forces during the Vietnam War.
This ship will be traveling upstream on the Mekong.
We'll enter through the Mekong Delta and travel upriver
to the border of the three countries Thailand, Burma, and Laos,
that is, straight to your destination, the Golden Triangle.
Oh, and also, this side of the door is my personal space. Do not enter!
Thank you for choosing to fly Bangkok Airlines.
This flight will depart Don Mueang International Airport and arrive at Mandalay International Airport at 14:30.
Hey you. You smell terrible.
Couldn't you have taken a quick shower? I know you're anxious to hunt down the foxes, but still...
Anyhow, you found the plane ticket we left at your hideout. Great.
We've made arrangements so you can get past the security even if you look a bit suspicious.
The foxes will arrive in 36 hours from—
Who...
are you?
Were you sent by the U.S. government?
Then...
You're talking too loud, bitch! Just shut up and listen.
I'm trying to tell you where the foxes are going! We also have vehicles ready to take you there!
I do appreciate your assistance.
You do? Well, I'm glad.
Therefore,
when I kill you at the end of the hunt,
I will give you a painless death.
We've arrived.
I'll lay the anchor here and wait for the oiler.
We'll enter the Mekong tomorrow.
Kid!
No turning on the lights. Switch it off.
What were you looking at?
Some English words.
I need to understand your language better.
That's diligent of you.
What's your Young Master doing?
He's alone on the stern deck.
Young Master keeps muttering to himself that the chief is alive.
Yeah. I think so, too.
And Rock's also intending to do something about her.
Yes, something.
But, as you can clearly see, I'll be useless.
That's why, in case something goes wrong,
I want to count on your gun.
We were the ones that made the request,
but I'm beginning to think that Japanese man is too dangerous.
Young Master met the U.S. Army soldiers exactly as that man arranged
and has suffered significant mental stress.
As I told you the other day, Rock is only good for relaxing on a bench on a sunny day.
So he's not the most experienced gambler,
and sometimes he bets a whole lot more than he can handle.
This is one of those.
If you think he can't handle it,
you can always point that out to him.
Why don't you?
What is it that you want?
Oh, I see why.
What?
You are too afraid to get close to him, only to discover the object of your aspiration isn't there.
Aspiration? You don't understand a thing.
You are the one who doesn't understand.
From my perspective, that man is nothing like you think.
You do not want to learn his true identity
lest you lose your fascination for him forever.
If, as you insist, he is indeed a peaceful, relaxed man
and those traits truly mean a lot to you,
then you two could run away to a South American backcountry and run a cheap restaurant or the like,
yet you do not.
This is rubbish.
You were inclined to believe that I am of your kind, and that he was our polar opposite,
for you sought salvation for yourself through him.
Well, we certainly have been relying on his scheming, so I'm not practicing what I preach.
My wish is to take Chief back and give Young Master, that boy, the peace of mind he once had.
That's all it's been for.
How's it different?
What?
You said you and I are different.
How are we different, and in what way? Tell me.
You have those stray dog's eyes.
I've seen countless people like you in my hometown.
You were brought up in a rough family.
Weren't you?
So what?
But my family was different. Dad was a frugal worker at a parking lot, and mom never tolerated sinful deeds.
One day, I stole a CD player my little brother wanted and got beaten up badly by my mom.
That's violence right there.
I could definitely feel her love and affection!
Oh, come on. I thought you grew up in the nastiest slum of the world's shit-hole.
Don't tell me you convinced yourself that you're the same kind of human as the Young Master.
Does the world look like a field of flowers to you?
Gosh, this is pointless. You're a plain idiot.
Hold it!
Who are you calling an idiot?
What's wrong with saying that to an idiot?
You've...
You've convinced yourself that man is your field of flowers.
Garcia, I'd like to speak to you.
It's about our next plan.
We now have all the actors on stage.
Do you still need something from me?
What's more...
you've brought an excellent stage prop.
I won't lose next time, either. You're the golden key...
Garcia.
NEXT EPISODE
Yes.
Yes, good.
Yes!
I'm definitely going to hit the jackpot!
Benny, he's going to lose!
Mr. Chang is going to lose!