I have a big gun
I took it from my lord
Sick with justice
I just wanna feel you
I'm your angel
Only a ring away
You make me violate you
No matter who you are
It's all up to you
No one lives forever
Been burn in the hell
By all those pigs out there
It's always been hell
From when I was born
They make me violate them
No matter who they are
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
Weapon . . . I have it all
Come on. You know what I do for a living.
Do you really expect me to spill everything?
You should know what I do for a living, Leroy.
In 1944, the Japanese army dug an underground
shelter here in preparation for attrition warfare.
That should make a safe hideout.
Did you kill Leroy for this information?
Hey, watch it!
I don't kill information brokers.
I buy information with money.
I put it all on Young Master's tab.
I only reminded him that the maid probably paid him too little.
Then—
Then, where is Roberta?
We're heading there right now.
Caxton.
It's Will!
This way.
Seems like you have some bad news for us, Will.
Something's going on. I sent out a zone recon squad just now.
Indeed. We've been detecting wiretap noise on the phone for a few hours.
Here's the latest local situation report and the modified operation plan.
It's from Brigadier General Wilder. The operation will continue.
Continue your reports.
Yes, sir!
Roads to Charkuan and Manthai Streets are closed to traffic due to construction.
However, no actual construction is happening.
Street vendors and prostitutes have completely disappeared from the vicinity.
There were approximately nine lookouts and four tailers within the 200-yard radius to the outskirts.
All right. We will conduct street cleanup operation.
Will, you'd best escape before the bullets start flying.
We're in formation in front of the hotel that Abrego told us about.
Understood.
The U.S. Army, FARC commandos, not to mention the mercenaries the maid got from this town—
a huge free-for-all lies ahead.
Stop right there.
Revy, where are you going?
I might not make it, but I'll get more people!
You guys, the phone's been ringing for ages!
Gosh, you people.
Aye, aye.
Yo, Shenhua! Time to make some money. You'll get to kill a lot of people!
I could chop ya up for free anytime, ya know.
It's your boss that got me into this, so don't blame me.
This time it's commissioned by a certain super wealthy South American.
That... how much?
Charlie to Alpha. Current situation Dog Four.
An apparently armed group is headed to your direction. Precaution is advised.
Understood, Charlie. Bravo and Charlie, prepare to move out.
I don't quite understand what we got ourselves into,
but it'll put an end to this boring standby period.
Now, time for action, gentlemen.
This is D1.
An armed group is entering the target building.
Locate the Bloodhound. Our only target is Rosarita Cisneros.
Understood.
Is it true that some country mafia took refuge here?
On this second floor?
Leroy's information is always accurate.
It can't be wrong.
Counting down. Three, two, one!
Cease fire!
We'll detonate the claymores. Everyone take cover!
Shit! What's happening?
All the guys who went upstairs are dead!
What're you doing? We're going up!
Fuck! What happened up there?
No one's in the corridor.
Bodge!
They're gone! The wall, too!
What happened? Where did they go?
Shane, there's an enemy on the building
to the rear, on top of the tallest billboard!
Everyone take cover!
Major, who exactly are we facing?
I don't know.
Wright! Horner! Suppression fire!
Others, move out quickly!
Rest of you, hurry up!
We're totally late!
Damn, the gunfire game is on, vintage-style!
This is a full-out war! We're charging ya extra.
If they're still fighting, then the chief must be alive!
Garcia.
Yes?
Dutch told me to withdraw here, multiple times.
However, if you want to see this
through to the end, I will join you.
I'm going.
If Roberta is waiting, then I have to go greet her.
Well said. That's the chivalric spirit.
Target located on the rooftop of the
rear building. We'll send a squad around.
Garcia, this is for you.
Not now. Open it when you can't figure out what to do next.
Why is he not coming?
He's only good for sitting on a bench in the sun
with canned coffee. Now, let's go.
Young Master is no different...
You lost your virginity at the bar, didn't you?
Huh?
Your first time shooting people, I mean.
You wield shotguns and grenades.
Anyone can tell you can't really aim.
You are...
Don't give me that face.
Here's the trick. Just think of them as signboards,
nothing more than rusty, corroded signboards.
If you keep that in mind as you live on,
you'll be a full-fledged gunslinger one day.
I'm not trying to be like you—
It's coming!
Now, cross!
Gunshots ceased. This is D1. Engaging the enemy!
We've cornered the enemy on the rooftop!
It's no good! Our cover is useless!
D3, go reinforce.
Wait, the Bloodhound is...
She's pursuing something.
It must be the unidentified group ahead of us!
Merge with D3. Pursue the Bloodhound together.
Understood!
So that's what's going on.
I can never trust those racketeers from the cartel.
Those shots are official U.S. Army carbines.
Hurry up! We're merging with D3!
Shenhua, go!
Those are out-of-range shots from a Barrett rifle!
We've cornered ourselves in the enemy's field, haven't we?
Goddamn it. They're all dead and useless.
You should have held back, too.
Is there any guy here that's at least half alive?
He's alive.
Which one?
This guy? Excellent.
Hey, beaner!
Wait! Don't be rough. He's almost dead.
I know. Translate for me.
"Where's Roberta? Tell me and
I'll take you to the doctor." Tell him that.
We won't hurt you. Where's Rosarita?
We just want to know where Rosarita went.
Tell us and we'll take you to the hospital.
Rosarita went after someone...
and is headed to the intersection to the west.
Am I going to die?
Worry not. God will save you.
The chief maid is headed to the intersection to the west after the U.S. Army.
The west? All right.
Beaner, does it hurt? Let me treat you right now.
Okay.
It must be the intersection at Lansup Street and Nankwai.
Let's head there for now. We've got no time.
Kid, follow me.
Fabiola!
Excuse me. You're pointing the dangerous end of the gun at me. What's the matter?
What are you doing?
The match was decided. What the fuck are you doing?
The match only ends after the final blow.
Isn't that true for your barrios, too? Isn't it the same?
But he sincerely sought relief at the verge of death.
Yet you shot him!
What you've done is aniquilación!
Speak English, chiquita.
She meant an annihilation, Miss Rebecca.
You enjoy shooting people, just like Jeffrey Murder!
"Dahmer", you mean.
Little maid...
More moral lessons? Then we'll just cut our way through you.
Let's go. We have yet to catch up to her.
And Young Master makes the smart choice.
Sawyer, lead the way.
Everyone does the dance of death in this corrupt town.
However, we need the professional troubleshooters...
that is, those ladies.
But that's precisely why you should act
as you believe is right, Fabiola.
And we will all return together, back to our home.
That's what I believe.
Me too, Young Master.
We will all return home together. That's why we are here.
Will Garcia catch up to Roberta? Hard to say.
In any case, the U.S. Army has no room for escape now.
It is virtually impossible for them
to shake off the Bloodhound of Florencia.
I have to complete the formation to let the U.S. Army escape.
To do so, I must wait for yet another syndicate that dwells in this town to join the scene.
Looks like you were too late, Rock.
I can see the fireworks all the way from here.
I don't need you calling me right now, damn it.
Close it up. Dutch could get mad any time now.
Mr. Chang, I cannot do that.
The actors are still on stage—both the boy and the maid.
I can't exit from the backstage now. So...
So what? You said you could get a checkmate in this game of chess, and I bet on that.
That was enough. Now that the situation has turned out this way,
what's the point in holding concern for the boy or the maid?
Rock, what I hate the most in this world...
is hypocrisy. That is more evil than an evil deed.
It's a poison that deceives not only others but also the self.
It may smell like a rose, but you can't hide the fact that shit is still shit.
I'm sure you already know, Rock.
For both me and, as of now, you,
the Young Master of Loveless and his maid...
are mere pawns on our chessboard.
Mr. Chang, you are...
one cruel son of a bitch!
Good! I haven't heard something like that for a long time.
I like that personality of yours.
Your rage is due to, first, being too
stubborn to give up a losing game,
and second, because I managed to sum up your innermost thoughts so succinctly.
In the past, I had to venture into people's
minds far deeper than you ever did.
How can you, a gangster living in violence, speak for a person's mind?
Want to know why?
The man talking to you right now...
once passionately upheld the worthless sense
of justice alongside the Hong Kong police,
fighting as a guardian of law and order.
It's not a big deal.
A life of hypocrisy isn't too uncommon in this place.
You should realize you're just another chess piece and step back.
That's the best for the sake of your mind.
I can't let it end just yet, Mr. Chang.
Oh well.
Then do what you will.
But, after this biting conversation we've just had,
I'll be expecting a pretty bold and daring game play.
Damn it!
Pursuit section D2. Target spotted one block ahead.
Approach her.
Hey, are we still going for it? The only ones left are—
Shut it, Jose!
Our friends' deaths will be in vain if we withdraw here.
Shit!
What a pain. Should I just ask them to let us pass?
We'll just have to get rid of whoever's in the way.
I do not mind breaking through.
But I have one question for you all.
What's up? So you can actually speak?
What's the matter?
Look at that high stand. Showing up from there...
might look cool.
Hey, what did you bring him along for?
Don't mind him. He's just a poor little kid.
The gunshots aren't ceasing.
Who's rallying with whom?
We'll let the enemy pass by and have a diversionary squad follow them.
In the meantime, we will coordinate with Bravo and Charlie for a pincer.
Everyone, check your bullets. Hold onto your magazines.
What comes after this operation?
Find a hideout in the outskirts and wait for NSA's orders.
But first, focus on capturing and annihilating the enemy at hand.
Let's hope she falls right into our trap.
Let's go around.
Serves you right. We took your back!
The chief is on the other side of this scramble.
Yes.
Let's go!
This is D4. Hurrying to support D2. Now combat—
Don't move!
Young Master, run to the other side.
But...
Get out of the way, kids!
You can make it through if you're alone. Quickly!
Don't move!
Hold on!
The sky is clear tonight, and the moon azure,
yet, poor wretches, your wicked weapons aim at the littlest lambs!
This favorite gun of mine
crushes every enemy it hits to a million pieces!
The Lord is present, yet He merely watches from above.
Then, who else but I can deliver in His name the—
Huh?
Fabiola!
Young Master!
I cannot cross over there, so please hide somewhere!
All right! Hurry up, Fabiola!
D4 was held back by another enemy.
That is not our true enemy.
"I would go for a pincer if I were
commanding the U.S. army troops."
"That's the U.S. army's strategy." That's what we told Rosarita.
Then the Bloodhound's position must be here.
Find her.
Fabiola?
No, it's the enemy!
They're still firing at each other.
Fabiola...
Oh?
Central nervous system stimulant...
It's the drug Roberta ordered from Doctor Hartland!
Communication with Lohes was cut off on the third floor.
Then we found her. She's right upstairs.
Roberta is here!
I'll finally catch up with her!
Lohes!
Lohes, anything unusual on the third floor?
Hey, what's wrong, Lohes?
It's all right. I can still make it. Roberta will never lose.
She won't lose! I believe in her.
Your skills are still up to par, Bloodhound.
It's no use.
Every single move you know, I know as well.
I am from Havana.
The Cuban Special Naval Missions Formation...
Precisely. I'm here on FARC Comandante Marulanda's direct orders.
You seem to be thinking "Why don't you shoot?"
I had many chances to shoot you had I wanted to.
The commander intends to kill you by
all means necessary, but I think otherwise.
You were the activist that drew the most attention
at the South American guerrilla meetings back in the day.
You were the only one who deserved to
inherit the title of Jackal after old Carlos.
Any organization is in absolute need of such a talent.
Return with me, Bloodhound.
Even if you remain a maid in a countryside mansion, you cannot resist the smell of blood.
Yes. You are right.
What a boring place that was...
with neither blood nor gunshots.
Master's death was a good opportunity.
My obligation ends once I take revenge upon the enemy.
Make the right choice, Rosarita.
I'm almost finished, so don't get in the way.
Well, whatever.
Americans' heads would make great gifts.
I doubt the Comandante will forgive me so readily.
Don't underestimate me. All of Havana follows my will.
The FARC cannot dare reject it.
Say...
Hm?
Considering what could come after this, would it be...
wise of me to befriend you in advance?
Pursuing the U.S. troops would come first.
They won't move until I leave here and follow their decoy.
And this place is just like...
a greenhouse warmed up by the heat of death.
It turns me on.
Bloodhound, are you testing me?
I will be the one doing the testing here.
Are you my dog? Stick out your tongue like a dog if you are.
Wait, don't rip it apart. I don't want to fight the Americans naked.
Will you strip my bottom for me?
Don't be ridiculous. Do it yourself.
You are careful. Fine.
I'll pull it down slowly, so don't shoot.
Y-You bitch!
Not enough.
You should have been even more, more, far more careful.
I will never join hands with you...
because both you and those foxes serve the same master:
doctrines and ideals!
I will never serve under that swindler again.
There's only one man in this world who can collar me:
Garcia Fernando Lovelace, the master I chose for myself,
the unique being that I will eat dirt
and sacrifice my life to protect.
Only for his sake will I pursue and kill the enemy!
I will bite to death even my own kind!
You are not a bloodhound.
You're a diseased stray wolf!
Roberta, stop.
No, stop it!
No, stop... stop...
Stop it!
Y-Young... Master?
Young Master?
Please, Young Master! Don't look at me!
No... No more...
Young Master!
No more of this.
Young Master, Young Master!
What should I do? What should I?
Didn't you keep envisioning me
to avoid this from happening?
Just... Just when will you stop following me around?
I follow you?
Not quite. It's you who isn't forgetting me.
When you assaulted the Magdalena branch of Taisho Electric
and shot two Japanese engineers to death—
yes, it has already been seven years—
you ripped apart my family photo before killing me.
That remained within you as one of your numerous little emotional wounds.
And the wounds hopelessly festered and gangrened amid the calm, peaceful daily life.
Had you remained with that boy,
those wounds may have healed someday.
However, it was you who ruined that chance.
Then, what should I have done to be forgiven?
If I could never be forgiven,
how could I show my face in that mansion?
You've kept following me like this...
so that I cannot forget, so that I can never forget!
Not only did you take my late Master as a sacrifice, but Young Master is now...
Oh.
Oh, that was it.
You're showing this to me.
Do you want to destroy me that badly?
That's right. Young Master can't possibly be here.
Young Master is waiting in the garden for me to return with the heads of the conniving foxes.
Young Master will greet me with a smile, and everything will be back to normal.
And yet you showed me this horrible vision of Young Master!
You showed me the last thing I'd want to see!
I will never forgive you!
This here is not Young Master,
but rather an illusion just like you.
I will prove it here and now.
This is Burrows.
Met target in building on patrol. Used tear-gas bomb.
Sergeant Major Horner secured a boy.
This is Sergeant Major Horner.
Ceasing tactical diversion. We will return to point!
What happened?
NEXT EPISODE
Mr. Rock, you told me to read this when I feel lost.
Mr. Rock...
Do you understand who exactly I'm dealing with?