I have a big gun
I took it from my lord
Sick with justice
I just wanna feel you
I'm your angel
Only a ring away
You make me violate you
No matter who you are
It's all up to you
No one lives forever
Been burn in the hell
By all those pigs out there
It's always been hell
From when I was born
They make me violate them
No matter who they are
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
Weapon . . . I have it all
What do you think we saved that little kid for, second lieutenant?
Come on! Are you trying to be
"Paladin, the Man of the West" now?
Aren't you just thinking about doing her too?
I guess it's fine. As long as you wait for your turn—
You really are a good-for-nothing rogue who's no better than a beast.
I won't let you lay a finger on this girl!
Come, Larkin!
Be a man!
Hotel Quebec.
This is Sierra Nine.
Morales has just arrived.
Morales is moving into the hall.
Understood.
Hotel Quebec, this is Lima Four.
The situation has moved to Phase 3.
Santa Ana has taken a seat.
Morales and Sesma as well.
Understood.
Hotel Quebec to each observer section.
Leave the CP and move to the ORP.
This is Hotel Quebec Actual.
Begin, Golf One.
Get Davy Crockett to the Lone Star.
I repeat: Get Davy Crockett to the Lone Star.
Code confirmed.
Explosion, confirmed.
Then let's begin to withdraw... perfectly.
Dear God, our deeply loving father...
My father never did anything bad, right?
In his every word and deed,
he had nothing to be ashamed of before God.
Yet God...
Why?
Blame not the Lord.
What kills a man is always...
a human.
What was that human thinking? Why?
I know the answer.
I know it too well,
so well that I do not have the words to convey it.
Come out, Rosarita.
They have left.
Sorry to bother you.
I will leave here as soon as the sun sets.
Wait, please hold on.
When a friend's daughter comes over for a visit,
I would be dishonored to let her leave without showing any hospitality.
It would not be so bad to settle down for a minute and think together
about where to go next, would it?
Rolling around the mountain and
running away can come afterwards.
Señor Diego...
Oh, please excuse my dress.
Since the day was so beautiful,
I thought of tending the garden.
Why? You could leave it to the gardener.
Nobody works here. Not for a mansion this old.
Then, Señor, where should I start?
No, no. Please be my guest and relax.
I would be uncomfortable if I were to merely freeload.
Borrowing the façade of a maid makes me uneasy already.
At least, please think of me as a genuine servant of yours.
This is it, Roberta.
This is...
I see that this is a gun, but...
Ever since the first Lovelace set his foot upon the New World with Pizzaro,
those weapons have remained with the Lovelace family.
There were good times and bad times,
but when I look at these weapons
in slumber, I realize how
the motto of our family that was formed amidst the wars now belongs to a distant past.
Charity for the saints,
Flowers for the dead;
Holding a sword for justice,
The sanction of death for the villainous.
Thus we...
Young Master, please forgive me for not telling you of the abominable cruelty!
What were they thinking when they killed?
They do not think at all.
They need not even restrain their emotions or remain calm.
The reason is...
no such thing as emotion exists there in the first place.
They do not care about the ones they killed.
They are better off killing those people.
Such is the path that I myself have followed,
and it cannot be helped even if I were to burn in the fires of Hell.
However, Master...
and certainly the Young Master should not be responsible for such a sin!
Young Master, I believed that night at Roanapur
would be the last night I laid my hands on a gun.
I will not gloss over it with excuses of retaliation and such.
This is a merciless struggle among the filthy canine beasts!
I swear on the name of Santa Maria
to counter every injustice with an iron hammer!
We can't just let the NSA's attitude slide this time.
They are very clearly stepping into our zone.
Their executive unit was last captured in Manila, for heaven's sake.
I see.
So they hate our hard-grown little garden that much, eh?
Cathy, another cup!
Put a lot of sugar and milk in it, enough for a pancake.
I will call Dr. Kaufmann!
Well, well.
Anyway, the challenge is to avoid warfare between the intelligence agencies,
and figure out what we can obtain
by exchanging what, isn't it?
Now our correspondent on the scene...
How is it?
The situation hasn't changed.
The tension on the Laos border still remains.
Due to our relationship with Thai Air Forces,
landing the air force in the target's
vicinity will not be possible, either.
We're to continue standby, aren't we?
We are trying to step into the CIA's domain.
It's politics, major.
Give me a break.
Ray, what is this town called?
Pardon?
The name of this town!
Oh, it's Roanapur, major.
It's such an unpleasant town.
As soon as we arrived, seven of us almost lost their luggage.
The prostitutes gather around in the day,
and the men who purchase them are uniformed policemen.
It's too much like that town back then.
I thought the same.
The city of Saigon, South Vietnam in the year 1969—
it's that strong smell of corruption.
I see a Japanese businessman.
Sorry?
He's extremely out of place.
He's all dressed up in a tie in this humid weather.
I see.
He really doesn't think much about his safety, does he?
Hey! What are you doing?
You know who I am?
Lagoon!
This wallet belongs to one of our crew.
We can't have people looking down on us.
Teach your apprentice to follow the rules here.
Here, take it.
If you're here for payment, please wait...
We always require immediate payment.
We gave you leeway this time for Colombia Cartel's sake.
Please don't disgrace their reputation.
Well, let's go talk somewhere else.
It's a little rowdy inside, but...
Ah, perfect timing!
Sounds like a match is over.
Please come inside.
No thanks. Behind me, a pretty good sniper is aiming at you.
You'd better be wary.
Really?
Anyhow, please wait until tomorrow.
Tomorrow then.
Rock.
I wouldn't mind giving that much to children on the streets.
We can never use all our income anyway.
But once that happens, the brat will reach for an even fatter purse.
And then your compassion will end up
washing away in a nearby body of water.
Good grief, you really help people out without thinking of the consequences.
The first amongst those being...
the person in the photo stuck inside this wallet.
Have you seen it?
It's obvious who it is.
They say a bullet will never hit the same spot twice,
so I just keep it there as a charm.
Hmph. Are you going for it again, Rock?
It's not a person or two:
the skull in the U-boat,
the Romanian twins,
and the daughter of that Tokyo yakuza.
Everything you've earned disappeared into nothingness for stuff like that, Rock.
This town is all about nothingness.
Many people end up in their
coffins at Roanapur, so what?
That's exactly why it's fun.
This is Lagoon Company.
And why do you ask?
Who knows?
I am just delivering the words.
The chief told me to ask. That's all.
I see.
Well, well.
Do we have a problem?
No, but he asked me whether we're looking after a strange client.
Again? It's getting creepy.
How many times has it been?
It's everyone from port merchant Isaac to police chief Watsup.
Just how strange can this person be to
captivate so many people in this town?
I've heard something interesting just now.
You know that dealer of Hotel Moscow, Kowalski?
Yes.
That guy said he saw it.
Saw what?
The maid, Dutch!
The one who came to reclaim her kidnapped young master
from Venezuela's back country with all the weapons.
That expert terrorist and a goddamn glasses bitch, remember?
That's one awesome joke.
Isn't it?
You know, Revy, I wouldn't approach the center of things right away.
I'll be getting in touch with two or three others as well.
Let's meet up at the Yellow Flag.
I just learned who it was.
Oh?
I couldn't help but sigh.
Are you kidding me?
Since I started this business in '78, I've seen fifteen partial and six nearly complete destructions.
And the absolute worst was when that maid-type killing machine appeared!
I feel for you.
But don't start worrying too early or you'll go bald.
We've asked the girls upstairs, but nothing came of it.
Let us know if there's something.
Sure.
The Hong Kong Triads are searching for the maid, too?
It's as if the whole town is beginning to move.
See? There's another.
Next one is a Colombian.
Hey, Gustavo.
Hey, the Lagoon pair.
Where's Señor Abrego?
Boss is in the office.
We're dealing with some trouble.
HQ said they'll be directly sending us some forces,
but it's such a bother when we're not ready for them.
But I sure am blessed by the Virgin Mary today.
I've got something to talk about with you guys.
It's the maid, isn't it, Gustavo?
You've just talked about some forces
from HQ. I wonder what that's about.
Don't give me the ugly face.
Let's exchange information and we're all happy.
Cut it out. It's a waste of time.
We're not going to spill the information. How does that sound?
Damn it!
But you tell me first.
All right.
Where should we start?
We didn't actually see that maid last time.
So first tell me her looks, race, features, and the like.
Black hair, a Hispanic but with white skin.
I heard she dresses like a waitress.
She's out of her mind.
SPAS in the umbrella, LMG and grenades in the trunk—
she's got enough for a whole platoon.
Damn! This is going to be pain.
I told you. She's out of her mind.
I-Is this a prank?
No one seemed to be present
at the Lagoon Company office.
As Young Master knew of this place, I have taken the opportunity to greet you here.
Young Master awaits you at the Sankan Palace Hotel.
Could you please come with me?
Are you...
related to the Lovelace family?
Please excuse me.
I work for the Lovelace of South America's thirteen families as a housemaid.
My name is Fabiola Iglesias.
Good god, even her speech is just like that goddamn glasses bitch.
While it is but a matter of speech, our chief is not a "glasses bitch."
Please revise your statement.
Bro, is this that maid?
She isn't, but we are truly in luck.
The hint for the quiz came right to us.
This girl's pretty heavy.
When I looked up the news articles, it came up right away:
a terrorist bombing in Venezuela's Barinas State last October.
It's a daily occurrence in South America, but...
MVR...
It was the inauguration ceremony of a new party.
It's a party popular among the poor,
but not so welcomed by the capitalists.
The problem is that the head of the
Lovelace family was also on that stage.
What?
He was a liberal character atypical of his race.
But I don't understand. Why would that have anything to do with this town?
Little girl, all the guys here are
actually big fans of your chief.
Even we have difficulty locating the chief.
Then why don't we search together, amigo?
We'll be going to that whatever Hotel, too.
I was careless.
I was aware that this town was full of inimical men,
but this stench like a horse's stable was indeed that of our family's enemy.
I'm ready anytime, bro.
She just...
stabbed my balls!
Guys! Put your guns...
She is no ordinary maid!
She's just like that chief maid!
So you pull the guns out as I expected.
I hoped to avoid this.
Hidalgo!
Yes, bro!
Check her body!
Approach slowly. We don't know what she might be hiding!
Let's... roll.
She's using shotguns!
Watch out!
Damn you, Revy! You triggered all this!
Didn't it get interesting?
Damn, I'm making a call!
Don't get in here!
Geez!
Benny...
Yeah, it's just my guess, but we probably
won't be getting a drink when we get there.
Yes, and if worse, we might get some holes through our bodies, too.
Let's hurry!
Yeah.
She's pretty good!
Bro, we're here!
Then start bombarding!
Idiot, don't make them shoot!
Shoot!
A maid came out!
It's that maid!
Marrero, fire it straight into the place!
It's that maid! Don't hold back!
It's just as the chief said. What a town!
Listen, you punks!
Your friends don't care a thing about you!
Now, what will you do?
Grab the wounded and get out right away!
Retreat, retreat!
Good grief, what a terrible place.
You!
Give up. It's a done deal.
D-Damn it!
Agent Chang!
Those Colombian guys are on the move.
Jumping into the scene now won't help at this point.
Even more so if the rumor about that maid is true.
I hear she's here to avenge her late master.
Indeed, Agent.
What's bothering me as much as
having to pee while I can't...
is that the maid's enemy is nowhere to be seen.
Someone has definitely sneaked into this town,
which irritates me.
You win. Is everyone in your
household armed like that?
Only myself and the chief.
There are five maids in the estate including me,
but the others don't even know that I wield a gun.
I was specially selected to ensure the safety of Young Master in the chief's absence.
Sankan Palace.
It's the most expensive hotel in the town.
I surely envy him for staying at a suite here.
Then, let me introduce again...
the twelfth head of the Lovelace of South America's thirteen families,
Mr. Garcia Fernando Lovelace's...
You're late, Lagoon folks.
Calm down, my cute maid.
Fabiola, he said he is only here for a conversation.
Please remain on guard. This town is riddled with filthy humans.
Sorry to interrupt, but what should we do?
My apologies. Please enter.
Here today...
Revy!
If you are going to smoke, ask him for permission.
Come on. Why would I—
Revy!
Tsk. Fine.
Young Master, would it bother you if I were to light up a smoke?
There is no ashtray. Please don't.
Immediately following the death of my father, a member of a right-wing militia organization was arrested.
So it was a terrorist bombing by those not too fond of the rise of a left-wing party.
That almost makes too much sense.
It makes so much sense that it feels contrived.
Roberta held the same suspicion.
They do not have the skills for such an explosion, not to mention they do not need it.
Nevertheless, the police simply closed the case.
At that time, some Air Force officers made a visit to my estate.
MVR, the Fifth Republic Movement—
it's a movement founded by a Venezuelan Air Force officer.
There are many sympathizers in the Force.
They came to tell us what they had learned over the course of the investigation.
They re-inspected the staff list for the ceremony,
looked into the people who went missing after the bombing,
and did a check on personal histories of suspicious persons.
Was it dead on?
Indeed.
The name of those six were recorded in another document as well:
the Register of Foreign Intelligence Service of the National Army.
As if arranged beforehand, they withdrew from the Service two months prior to the incident,
and they were all working as stage security officers on the day of the bombing.
Geez, what idiots! They couldn't do worse. They're just worthless brats.
We could all just be trimming our nose hair, and that goddamn glasses bitch will defeat them in an instant.
However... Fabiola.
Yes.
Please take a look at this.
It is a photograph we received from the Air Force officers.
This was taken in Caracas six months before the bombing.
It was incidentally taken by the military police while investigating another case.
The man on the right is the leader of the suspicious six, Marcos Jose Lucientes,
a former major of the Foreign Intelligence Service.
What about others?
They are foreigners.
The day after seeing that picture, Roberta...
Young Master,
do you remember that night at Roanapur?
How could I forget?
I was sold off like merchandise by a Colombian cartel,
and you crossed the seas to rescue me,
going through all that trouble.
Back then,
the late Master was against my involvement to the very end.
If...
I understand. If I was in my father's shoes,
I would have said the same.
Really...
you are all helpless.
So Roberta...
Yes, Young Master.
I, Roberta, will always remain by your side.
Yet she disappeared the day after.
Damn, who is she?
Mendes, it's me. Someone's tailing me. Please...
Unfortunately, Mr. Mendes can
no longer answer this phone.
Who the hell are you?
Would you like to know why I have this phone?
It's not just Mr. Mendes's phone.
But it seems that you are the only one who can answer the big question.
The corpse of Jose Lucientes was discovered in the canal on the outskirts of Calabozo.
So she figured out his identity and tracked him down, all with a single photograph?
No wonder people call her the "Bloodhound."
She is not a bloodhound! She's my family!
My bad, Señor Garcia.
Let's get back on topic.
Sure.
Getting back on topic...
The next person we could trace was the man second from the right.
Do you understand who I really am?
Surely. Special Manager of
Strategic Affairs in South America
of the NSA, National Security
Agency of the United States
as well as the head officer of the Special Program, Colonel Simon Dickens.
I am surprised you knew.
What do you want?
From what I have heard from Marcos Jose Lucientes,
October's Caracas bombing was planned and carried out by you and your little pet dogs.
Don't tell me...
you!
Where are... your dogs?
It would save me time if you start talking...
while this is still around body temperature.
You're one damn insane woman!
If you lay a hand on me, the whole U.S. government will become your enemy!
That is exactly my wish.
In an abandoned building that was burnt down on
the outskirts of Caracas, Colonel Dickens was found dead.
A key witness of this case, a female, purchased a plane ticket from Caracas to Thailand with a stopover in Miami,
and, moreover, reserved a long-distance bus ticket from Bangkok to Roanapur.
It was a U.S. military person on active service. That's for sure, right?
Yes.
I don't like where this is going, Young Master.
Anyway, what are you asking us to do?
That is...
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
What's the matter, Bao? Closed again today?
Shut up! Even in this condition,
I can still serve a drink anytime.
Hey, don't you see this mess?
If you're here to make fun of me...
War...
Mr. Chang, I see why you are so cautious today.
It's not a matter of money. We're off the case.
But... why?
Don't you get it?
Your chief is going to take on the U.S., an ally of every nation, with her two bare hands.
What did you just say?
"Please direct me to a store with every item necessary for a war."
...is what I said.
All those who attempted to resist the
overwhelming force facing them but couldn't
head to this town and are led to ruin.
We are not requesting this of the Lagoon Company itself,
but personally of you, the Japanese man over there.
W-Wait a minute.
I...
Wait a minute. Why me?
Please aid in our search for the chief maid!
We fully understand that
this is an unreasonable request.
Please.
Wait a minute! But I...
NEXT EPISODE
If you are the gun, I am the bullet.
But I'm nothing more than
a piece of lead right now.
The only thing that can light the gunpowder
is the gun.