One day, when I came back home...
the scooter became a three-wheeler.
Hello
A Sauna & a Meal & a Three-Wheeler
&
I'm home.
Welcome back.
I don't recognize that motorcycle out there.
What happened to the scooter?
Well, I sent it in for its yearly service.
That's the loaner.
What? But I was thinking of
going camping tomorrow.
Why don't you go and try the one out there?
Really?
Motosu
Didn't you get a light motorcycle license recently?
But that's a three-wheeler. Am I allowed
to drive it with my current license?
The regulations are hard to explain, but it's fine,
you can drive it with your license because it's only 125cc.
Camping with a three-wheeler, huh?
As expected of a 125cc scooter, it's so fast.
It effortlessly keeps up with the flow of traffic.
And even when traffic's slowed to crawl,
it's stable and easy to handle.
What is this? It's amazing!
I couldn't help giving it some throttle
and now it's freezing.
Well, I guess this sort of speed is normal
for this scooter.
My face is frozen stiff!
Hot springs really hit the spot
after riding around in the freezing cold.
Hot springs in winter are undoubtedly the best.
A sauna, huh?
That reminds me...
Hot springs in winter are good
but saunas are great, too.
First sauna,
then a cold bath,
then an open-air bath...
If you repeat that cycle,
you'll be in such a super relaxed state
that you'll be close to...
I'm rejuvenated.
And that's the story.
Oh...
I've never been in one before, but...
All right.
Whoa, it's so hot.
I feel like I'm being steamed from the inside
breathing in this air.
Saitou said to spend around five minutes
per sauna session.
I'm so bored.
SNOW COUNTRY
Sauna Murder Case
Maybe I can read a book in here?
SNOW COUNTRY
Sauna Murder Case
Nah, with this humidity, the pages
would definitely be a soggy mess.
Then, what about an e-book
on a waterproof tablet?
That won't work either. The screen would be
too fogged up to see anything.
Five minutes later.
Huh? That was quick.
Rinse yourself with hot water.
Then take a cold water bath.
Eek!
This bath is cold, isn't it?
That's because the water comes from a well.
O-Oh, I see.
After drinking some water,
take a quick break in an open-air bath.
Ahh...
All right! Time for the sauna again.
Eek!
Ahh...
Repeat that cycle three times.
What is this feeling?
My body's all like, up in the clouds, and it's like
there's some sort of bubbly feeling welling up from inside.
This must mean...!
rumble
I'm hungry.
Takaoka
Japanese
Restaurant
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Today's lunch is the humble tempura set meal.
Cooking tempura at a campsite
would be no walk in the park, that's for sure.
Time to eat.
Chrysanthemum with its
mildly contained bitterness.
Soft and light eggplants, maitake
and jikobo mushrooms.
Dense and flaky sweet potatoes and pumpkins.
After finishing up the veggies,
next comes the crispy kisu whiting...
And finally...
the springy yet tender shrimp!
So good!
Thank you for the meal.
Oh, I feel more carried away
about the food than usual.
Could this be another positive effect
that came from the sauna?
A sauna re-energizes you when you're tired,
while also helping you to sleep soundly.
And it enhances your appetite, too.
Oh...
IIIIIIIIIII
We use local
Rihoku Rice
from northern
Yamanashi
IIIIIIIIIII
Today's Set Meal
Mini Set
Chicken Tempura Bowl
& Soba or Udon Noodles
900 yen
IIIIIIIIIII
Today's Lunch Service
Tempura Set Meal
(8 Pieces)
930 yen
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you very much.
Now that I've eaten lunch,
it's time to go shopping.
Open
What can I say, this is so stable on gravel roads.
Sunflower
Supermarket
Firewood
1 Bundle
yen
Oh, they sell firewood.
Dinner should be soup plus something light...
Wow, veggies from Yatsugatake, huh?
What an incredible amount of spices!
There's all sorts of ham and bacon here, too.
As you'd expect from Yatsugatake.
This shop offers a pretty interesting
range of products.
It has a unique atmosphere too, so it might be
just the place to buy camp food.
Dinner's going to be a toasted sandwich with
Hakushu bacon and veggies from Yatsugatake.
Thank you very much.
Shopping done.
Sunflower Supermarket
From here, it's around 30 kilometers
to the campsite,
which includes 10 kilometers
of steep mountainous roads.
Show me what you're made of!
Leave it to me
Just as I thought, this is impressive!
Any cracks on the road don't worry me at all.
Went to a sauna for the first time
Oh
How was it?
Feeling rejuvenated?
Went to a sauna for the first time
Oh
How was it?
Feeling rejuvenated?
Went to a sauna for the first time
Oh
How was it?
Feeling rejuvenated?
Oh
How was it?
Feeling rejuvenated?
I don't know about that . . .
But it was nice and refreshing
Ah, okay
How you get in one makes a difference too
I figured that out after going a few times myself
I figured that out after going a few
How you get in one makes a difference too
times myself
Oh?
How you get in one makes a difference too
I figured that out after going a few
times myself
Oh?
How you get in one makes a difference too
I figured that out after going a few
times myself
How you get in one makes a difference too
I figured that out after going a few
times myself
Oh?
The path to rejuvenation seems so close and yet so far
and still it is close  ( ´ェ` )
Which one is it then?
The path to rejuvenation seems so close and yet so far
and still it is close
( ´ェ` )
Which one is it then?
The path to rejuvenation seems so close and yet so far
and still it is close
( ´ェ` )
The path to rejuvenation seems so close and yet so far
and still it is close
( ´ェ` )
Which one is it then?
All right!
All done.
Time to eat!
Yum.
The griddle's the way for
bacon, tomato and eggplant.
And the jalapeno pickles complements it well.
I'm rejuvenated.
This here is the kind of rejuvenation
I'm familiar with.
I guess I'll give the sauna another go
on the way home.