Episode 8
Tall Tales Spread Round the World
All righty!
What's that, Nadeshiko-chan?
I was thinking that if I ever find my sheet,
I can just paste this one in.
YAMANASHI
STAMP
RALLY
YAMANASHI
GIRL
STAMP
RALLY
Oh, that'd be perfect!
Righto, now that you're done,
wanna go someplace good?
SHIMOBE
GOLD FOOTBATH
Feels great!
My whole body's warming through!
Nothing beats a footbath!
But why's this place called “Gold Footbath”?
Well, you see...
There was this farmer here long ago, see?
And while he was relaxing in the footbath,
the sandals he'd left next to 'im
up and turned to gold.
Really?
What a weird legend!
That said, the gold sandals were real heavy,
and he wasn't able to wear 'em on the way back.
Wait, was that story...
Yeah, it was all just a tall tale.
Your récit was so magnifique!
I'd love to hear more!
Aki-chan!
Right! What will you do now, Inuko?
Y'know how this area's known as
Lord Shingen's Hidden Baths?
Uh-huh.
It's called that 'cause Lord Shingen
would come to these springs
and hide his belongings here
by chucking 'em into the water.
Wow!
Lord Shingen's beloved houtou noodles
were no exception,
and that's how simmering, bubbling houtou
ended up as Yamanashi's signature dish.
Wow! Merveilleux!
Whoa, now Inuko's become a world-class
tall tale teller...
Right, and speaking of Yamanashi...
Making people smile with her tall tales...
Good on you, Aoi-chan!
Souvenirs
Shimobe
Hot Spring Village
Thank you very much!
I've been wanting to try these for ages!
Hidden Wafer Sandwich!
Lord Shingen's
Hidden Baths
eeeeeeeeeeeeee
Registered Trademark
Lord Shingen's
Hidden Baths
eeeeeeeeeeeeee
eeeeeeeeee
Hidden
Wafer
Sandwich
Registered Trademark
Lord Shingen's
Hidden Baths
eeeeeeeeeeeeee
eeeeeeeeee
Hidden
Wafer
Sandwich
Registered Trademark
Lord Shingen's
Hidden Baths
eeeeeeeeeeeeee
eeeeeeeeee
Hidden
Wafer
Sandwich
Registered Trademark
Lord Shingen's
Hidden Baths
eeeeeeeeeeeeee
eeeeeeeeee
Hidden
Wafer
Sandwich
Registered Trademark
Lord Shingen's
Hidden Baths
eeeeeeeeeeeeee
eeeeeeeeee
Hidden
Wafer
Sandwich
The sweet white bean paste and raisins
go so well together!
It's heaps good, hey?
What's up?
Hidden inside my monaka's not raisins,
but real gold!
Fair dinkum, betcha it's 'cause
I was in those gold footbaths!
Barefoot
Shimobe
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET, CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT. PRAESENT AUGUE ELIT, VARIUS ID ALIQUET SIT AMET, MATTIS NEC VELIT. VESTIBULUM POSUERE INTERDUM JUSTO, EGET FRINGILLA JUSTO FEUGIAT VITAE. DUIS ORCI URNA, MATTIS A FEUGIAT AT, IMPERDIET AT QUAM. NULLA FACILISI. VESTIBULUM SED TRISTIQUE PURUS, PRETIUM DICTUM ERAT. SED VEL POSUERE DOLOR.
Come on, Nadeshiko.
You can't just put on a Kansai accent
and expect to fool us.
Whoopsie.
Well, some people do say that
since the Kansai accent's homier,
people are more likely to fall for your tall tales.
What? Really?
Nah, not at all!
Okay!
YAMANASHI GIRL
STAMP RALLY
Oh rain shower in the sunshine
Oh
rain
shine
Happy Monday
Hap
py
Mon
day
waraeba sora made shiny
Just laugh and even the sky will be shiny
Let's chill out, it's comfy time
Let's
chill
out
it's
com
fy
time
Our after-school
Our
af
ter
school
kono jikan ga nani yori bright
These times are especially bright
bright