Episode 5
True Teachings • Mt. Kachikachi
Oh.
Apparently, this is that Mt. Kachikachi!
Well, the setting for that story, anyway.
That's the one about the tanuki, right?
Yeah, there's a rabbit chasing her,
or something along those lines.
Oh, isn't there a turtle in it too?
Oh yeah, that's right!
She's pretty slow at the start.
At the beginning, the rabbit takes off,
with the tanuki soon following.
But the tanuki turns out to be surprisingly quick,
so the rabbit tries to mess with her from behind.
Banging flints, trying to get some fire catchin'.
And that's how it got the name Mt. Kachikachi!
Then, the rabbit tricks the tanuki.
Please.
Really?!
The tanuki takes the mud boat across,
while the rabbit paddles a wooden one.
Catch me!
Come on, catch me!
You'll never catch me!
Way ahead of the others,
she feels confident enough to take a nap.
Wait, what about the turtle?
The turtle does her best
throughout the whole race.
Not needing a boat, she swims across the river.
I've won.
Couldn't catch me!
And thus, the diligent turtle's hard work pays off.
An excellent ending.
Lake Kawaguchi's on this side!
That's where we went cycling!
Oh, you're right!
MT. KACHIKACHI
HEAVEN'S BELL
Tea
MT. KACHIKACHI
HEAVEN'S BELL
That tanuki's smiling a lot for someone who's on fire.
Maybe it's a surrealist piece.
MT. KACHIKACHI
HEAVEN'S BELL
Excuse me, could you take our picture?
Tea
Uh, sure.
MT. KACHIKACHI
HEAVEN'S BELL
Okay, say chee—
Oh, sorry. Could you hold on a sec?
Tea
Hmm, this isn't bad.
MT. KACHIKACHI
HEAVEN'S BELL
Tea
Wait, what about this?
Oh, that's it!
MT. KACHIKACHI
Oh, sorry!
Say cheese!
Thanks!
No problem!
Tanuki Cafe
Ooishi Park
So good!
Seems like those girls liked our joke.
Right?
Speaking of, there wasn't a turtle statue,
was there?
I'm sure it's around here somewhere.
I think we got it!
Nice!
Tanuki Teahouse
Tea
Oh rain shower in the sunshine
Oh
rain
shine
Happy Monday
Hap
py
Mon
day
waraeba sora made shiny
Just laugh and even the sky will be shiny
Let's chill out, it's comfy time
Let's
chill
out
it's
com
fy
time
Our after-school
Our
af
ter
school
kono jikan ga nani yori bright
These times are especially bright
STAMP
RALLY
bright
STAMP
RALLY