Episode 4
A Day in the Life of Shimarin
Snooze
Dismiss
Shimarin's morning starts early.
Snooze
Dismiss
Most of the time.
Here.
And yet you wake up so early for camping.
Thanks for breakfast.
Here's today's fortune for our October babies:
Watch out for surprise attacks!
Your lucky item is... tomato juice!
Surprise attacks?
What the heck does she mean, surprise attacks?
Are assassins going to jump me from behind?
So you're the first one up?
Takeda's Books
First, get a nice round circle,
then draw in a fish's face...
Throw in a single sesame seed.
Now turn it around, and it's Nadeshiko-chan!
What are you on about?
I said it was Nadeshiko-chan.
That's just pareidolia.
Here.
What's that?
Pareidolia is a type of a psychological phenomenon,
occurring when the brain perceives three marks as a face.
Yo!
It's when there's dots that look like eyes and a mouth,
and you end up seeing a face.
Rin-chan!
C-Cut it out! I'm getting flashbacks
of being chased at Lake Motosu!
Welcome.
So cold...
Surprise... attack?
Oh, for the stamp rally?
There's plenty to see in Yamanashi, after all.
Are we having hot pot tonight?
Yup.
As it happens...
Look, Grandpa sent us this.
He said it was a gift from Hokkaido.
I don't mind this kind of surprise.
Rin, could you put this in the pot?
Sure.
Rin-chan!
So this is it!
Oh rain shower in the sunshine
Oh
rain
shine
Happy Monday
Hap
py
Mon
day
waraeba sora made shiny
Just laugh and even the sky will be shiny
Let's chill out, it's comfy time
Let's
chill
out
it's
com
fy
time
Our after-school
Our
af
ter
school
kono jikan ga nani yori bright
These times are especially bright
STAMP
RALLY
bright
STAMP
RALLY