Episode 1
The Mystery of the Canned Tuna
Outdoor Activities Club
This is...
The smell of camping...
Or not.
It's so cold today!
Come on, Aki. You gotta buck up!
You're right.
Is there anything else?
Oh, these are still here?
Emergency rations?
But wait, wouldn't hardtack or something
be better?
What if they're not rations, but rather...
Hello.
Hello
R-Right!
Canned tuna.
By attracting the animal's attention,
this emergency-use item helps you survive
when you have nowhere to run.
Click clack!
Nah, no way.
You gonna eat that?
I was keeping them around
to use as canned-tuna oil lamps.
Huh?
A human being with a pine cone for a nose?
It's a koala!
Oh, it's houtou!
Yeah! I made it for the first time last night!
Nice twist putting the butter on there.
You're a real Yamanashi girl now!
Maybe!
Nope.
Nope, nope, nope.
You can't call her that just because
she added a twist to the houtou.
Why not?
Nadeshiko-chan's plenty Yamanashi.
You're being too sweet, Inuko.
So sweet you could be mistaken
for a Fuefuki peach!
What are you talking about?
When you talk sweet, you talk Katsunuma grapes!
They're both equally sweet!
Nadeshiko, you've obviously conquered the
Yamanashi Girl Stamp Rally by now, right?
Huh? Yamanashi Girl Stamp Rally?
Don't tell me you've never heard of it.
What's this?
YAMANASHI GIRL
STAMP
RALLY
The essential Yamanashi Girl Stamp Rally!
Travel around to the prefecture's best places,
stamp in all the stamps,
and win a year's supply of Minobu manju!
It's like a dream!
A year's supply?!
Okay, I'll do it!
I'll go!
Excellent!
Then we're leaving right now!
R-Right now?
Yup, let's get a move on!
Outdoor Activities Club
Onward to the great seas of the stamp rally!
Onward we go!
Gone
stamp rallying!!
Oh rain shower in the sunshine
Oh
rain
shine
Happy Monday
Hap
py
Mon
day
waraeba sora made shiny
Just laugh and even the sky will be shiny
Let's chill out, it's comfy time
Let's
chill
out
it's
com
fy
time
Our after-school
Our
af
ter
school
kono jikan ga nani yori bright
These times are especially bright
STAMP
RALLY
bright
STAMP
RALLY