Episode 6
The Two of Them,
Back in the Day
So cold!
Right?
And it snows a lot in Yamanashi too, doesn't it?
Depending on the area, yeah.
I even made an igloo once.
An igloo?!
My little sister and I built one in our front yard.
But when we checked the next morning,
some brat had messed with it,
making it look like a Balinese ruin or something.
Oh, that was me.
So, 'twas thy doing, knave?
Wait, were you guys childhood friends?
Nope.
We first met each other in middle school.
It's not like we started talking right away, though.
Really? Then when did you?
Okay!
Wow, it's huge!
We came here in the first spring of middle school.
We didn't know each other too well back then.
What's this place?
Every summer, they hold a big event
called the Nanbu Fire Festival here.
Oh, I just remembered!
Huh?
Back in second year of middle school...
Oh!
Are you all right?
I'm so sorry!
Whoa, I almost had a heart atta—
You're Oogaki-san, from my class, right?
I'm really sorry.
Oh, don't worry about it, uh...
Aoyama Inuko-san, was it?
Uh, it's Inuyama Aoi, actually.
Really? So that's how you became friends?
Yeah, that night is still seared into my heart.
Though you'd forgotten till just now.
Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
It's pretty hard to win these, isn't it?
Welcome to the
Lucky Drink Shop
Oh, uh...
Hey, you!
Huh?
Me?
Yeah, you!
Check this out! I won!
How cool's that?
Uh, sure.
Right?
I've never won before. I can't believe it!
It's gonna expire if you don't pick something soon.
Huh?
Oh, uh, um...
See ya.
Wait, hold on!
CHUNKY CORN SOUP
Discount Price
Set Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
I lost too.
All right!
I'll avenge you!
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Well, you win some, you lose some.
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
Set Price
Discount Price
Welcome to the Lucky Drink Shop
You got that right.
Oh rain shower in the sunshine
Oh
rain
shine
Happy Monday
Hap
py
Mon
day
waraeba sora made shiny
Just laugh and even the sky will be shiny
Let's chill out, it's comfy time
Let's
chill
out
it's
com
fy
time
Our after-school
Our
af
ter
school
kono jikan ga nani yori bright
These times are especially bright
STAMP
RALLY
bright
STAMP
RALLY