Episode 3
Full Speed Ahead! Lake Kawaguchi Rally!
Lake Kawaguchi, one of the Fuji Five Lakes.
Of the Five Lakes, it possesses the longest shoreline.
Oh, I just thought of something!
Imagine if you had a bike like this...
You could camp on the go!
Hey, Aki, isn't this stamp rally a bit full-on?
I don't even have the energy
to call Nadeshiko-chan out.
Nope, we're finishing what we started.
Figures.
Am I going too fast?
I'll go ahead, get the stamp, and come back.
You two can rest here.
Yeah, but going on alone...
So fast!
We can't just give up here, Aki!
Righto!
But aren't you—
We'll be fine!
Come on! We're going, Nadeshiko!
Those are from earlier!
Excuse me, over there!
Could you take a picture for us?
Lavender
Ice Cream
Coming!
Just push this button.
Gotcha!
Say cheese!
Please, take one!
Thanks so much!
So yummy!
I'm glad!
Are you on a biking trip?
Yup. My wife and I go all over.
For years, we've been taking pictures of
the most beautiful scenery along the way.
What's this?
Oh, that's from back in high school.
Ah, from our first trip by bike, right?
Even though it was summer, it was so, so cold!
I'll never forget it!
Me neither.
Mt. Fuji
Kagamihara Nadeshiko
Maybe this will be like that too.
Oh, found it!
Maybe, after we've grown up,
we'll look back at these stamps together too.
And be like, “Oh, those are from high school!”
Maybe.
I'm sure we'll remember
how tiring the bike ride was, at least.
Ooishi Park
Fujisan Center
One-Bite
Tsukapon
Oh, a lucky mustache one.
The Truth About UMAs
One-Bite
Tsukapon
The Truth About UMAs
Nadeshiko
Show
Close
New Message
We went to Lake Kawaguchi
Wow, Lake Kawaguchi, huh?
Ow, hot!
Oh rain shower in the sunshine
Oh
rain
shine
Happy Monday
Hap
py
Mon
day
waraeba sora made shiny
Just laugh and even the sky will be shiny
Let's chill out, it's comfy time
Let's
chill
out
it's
com
fy
time
Our after-school
Our
af
ter
school
kono jikan ga nani yori bright
These times are especially bright
STAMP
RALLY
bright
STAMP
RALLY