Episode 9
Shizunashi War II
I just realized something huge!
Ask at register
What's up?
What do you think this drawing is of?
Ask at register
Mt. Fuji, right?
That's right. When anyone in the entire country
thinks of a cartoon Fuji, they think of this.
But then, where do you think you're looking from?
Huh? Where I'm looking from?
Fuji's shape depends on your location.
Osawa Collapse
From the west, you'll see the Osawa Collapse.
From the south, Mt. Houei.
Mt. Houei
From the east, Mt. Houei and
the Yoshida-Osawa Valley.
Mt. Houei
Yoshida-Osawa Valley
With none of those visible,
cartoon Fujis must always be a view from the north.
In other words,
they're Fuji as seen from Koufu in Yamanashi!
Yeah, nah. The artists
definitely weren't thinking about that.
But Aki-chan's right!
This couldn't be a Shizuoka Fuji.
Score one for Yamanashi!
So good!
Nanbu
Tea
really good
Yup, Yamanashi wine's the best!
Yum.
Hey, it's Ena-chan!
Oh, everybody's here!
The tuna bowl looks really good!
Yup! Worthy of being on the
specialty menu signboard.
Hey, Nadeshiko-chan.
We're in Yamanashi, so what's a tuna bowl
doing on the specialty menu?
Now that you mention it...
It's 'cause even though it's landlocked,
Yamanashi loves tuna.
We're second in the whole country
for tuna consumption.
Second?
Lord Nanbu Saburou Mitsuyuki
Then who's first?
It's gotta be Shizuoka!
Looks like you're right.
What?!
Since they're also number one
in terms of tuna catch!
Shizuoka
Iea
xlwxlwxlwxlwxlw
Shizuoka
SERIOUSLY
GOOD
YYYYYYYYYYY
yyyyyyyyyyyyyy
Thish Shwuoka shtuff's nobad neither!
Whose side are you on, anyway?
Are you Yamanashi?
Or are you Shizuoka?
You're what, mate?
I can't just pick one!
I love Yamanashi, where I live now.
But I also love Shizuoka, where I grew up.
That's right.
I'm like Mt. Fuji, astride two prefectures.
Mt. Fuji?
A part of me's Yamanashi,
and another part's Shizuoka!
Like tuna caught in Shizuoka
and prepared in Yamanashi.
It's really good!
Nice one, Ena. You said it!
Mt. Fuji, tuna bowls, and even Nadeshiko-chan...
They're bridges between Yamanashi and Shizuoka!
Hey, let's go eat some tuna bowls!
Yup, let's do it!
Let's go, let's go!
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Ginger Chicken Set
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Pork Cutlet Set
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Beef Stew Set
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Pork Steak
Fatty Tuna Bowl
Sauce Cutlet
Oh, I haven't the cash!
Pleasant
Journey
Oh rain shower in the sunshine
Oh
rain
shine
Happy Monday
Hap
py
Mon
day
waraeba sora made shiny
Just laugh and even the sky will be shiny
Let's chill out, it's comfy time
Let's
chill
out
it's
com
fy
time
Our after-school
Our
af
ter
school
kono jikan ga nani yori bright
These times are especially bright
STAMP
RALLY
bright
STAMP
RALLY