Episode 2
Many Mt. Fujis
It's so pretty!
The colors are changing!
It's so magical.
Isn't it?
This place is really cool!
Paradise for a Fuji lover.
Sure is! I had no idea this was here.
Oh, right. What about the stamp?
Found it!
It's a big one—your first stamp!
All right!
Give it all you've got, Nadeshiko!
Fujisan Center
Mt. Fuji Float
Shingen Mochi
Ice Cream
Time to eat!
It actually does taste like curry!
Those really are pitch-black, huh?
It's lava fried chicken, after all.
So good!
Snowcapped Fuji's the best, isn't it?
Wait a sec, Nadeshiko.
That's the shape of Ezo Fuji!
Ezo... Fuji?
Yeah, it's a mountain in Hokkaido.
Known as “local Fujis”,
there are mountains that look like
Mt. Fuji all over Japan!
No kidding!
It's close, but the shape's a little different.
That's Aomori's Tsugaru Fuji!
Iwate's Nanbukata Fuji!
Tochigi's Nikkou Fuji!
Nagano's Suwa Fuji!
There's still a ton more!
Oh?
Wait, that shape!
European Fuji!
You mean the Matterhorn?
Thanks for the food!
Finally finished off Mt. Fuji, huh?
You really love Mt. Fuji, don't you?
Yup!
It's too bad we couldn't see it today, though.
The rain's letting up!
All righty, then. Let's go see the real deal!
Yeah, doesn't look like it's gonna be visible today.
It should be around there, right?
That's right.
Over there.
Oh rain shower in the sunshine
Oh
rain
shine
Happy Monday
Hap
py
Mon
day
waraeba sora made shiny
Just laugh and even the sky will be shiny
Let's chill out, it's comfy time
Let's
chill
out
it's
com
fy
time
Our after-school
Our
af
ter
school
kono jikan ga nani yori bright
These times are especially bright
STAMP
RALLY
bright
STAMP
RALLY