Who'd have thought we'd stumble
on such a beautiful campsite!
Isn't it?
Wait, no! This is just the schoolyard!
I've always wanted to try camping at school!
You're an odd bunch, aren't you?
Oh, thanks for letting us stay here!
Just make sure you take care of the fire, okay?
Oh, and if you need anything,
I'll be in the Mountain Climbing Clubroom.
Thank you!
Well, those guys were coming here too, anyway.
Have fun.
I think the hot pot's done.
Ta-da! Canned tuna hot pot!
Yum!
Whew, I'm stuffed!
FLUFFY WHITE
MARSHMALLOWS
Shall we have some marshmallows?
FLUFFY WHITE
MARSHMALLOWS
Sounds good!
By the way,
why did you two decide to do the stamp rally?
Ever since you moved here,
you've just been on a camping streak, right?
Yeah.
So we figured that you probably
still didn't know anything about the local area.
Our neck of the woods
has a few nice places too, you know?
And we wanted to share some of those with you.
Like the places Inuko and I like.
That said, though, we really
started running out of ideas towards the end.
That's 'cause you put too many spaces
on the sheet to begin with.
Even with the two of us,
we had trouble making the stamps in time!
My bad.
Nadeshiko-chan, your marshmallow!
Ah! Oh nom!
Ow, hot!
Are you all right, Nadeshiko-chan?
Here, have some water!
Aki-chan, Aoi-chan...
Thanks!
Good morning!
Kinda early, Nadeshiko-chan...
Come on, we've gotta get going!
Get going where?
On a new stamp rally, obviously!
A new stamp rally?
Ta-da!
NADESHI GIRL
The Nadeshi Girl Stamp Rally!
Not the Yamanashi Girl, but the Nadeshi Girl?
Correct!
STAMP
I, Kagamihara Nadeshiko, took all of my favourite spots,
and wrapped them up into one enchanting rally!
STAMP
We'll start with the first stamp point,
the Outdoors Clubroom!
STAMP
NADESHI GIRL
There's so many!
STAMP
NADESHI GIRL
Well, let's take a look, then.
STAMP
NADESHI GIRL
All right, on to the next one!
OUTDOORS CLUB
Right now?
Nadeshiko-chan, when you make a stamp,
you've gotta mirror it.
What?!
Oh rain shower in the sunshine
Oh
rain
Oh rain shower in the sunshine
shine
Happy Monday
Hap
py
Mon
day
waraeba sora made shiny
Just laugh and even the sky will be shiny
Let's chill out, it's comfy time
Let's
chill
out
it's
com
fy
time
Our after-school
Our
af
ter
school
kono jikan ga nani yori bright
These times are especially bright
NADESHI GIRL
bright
This is a work of fiction. It is not affiliated
with any persons, places, establishments or organizations.