Chihaya-chan, let me have that cookie.
Haruka,
that's bad manners.
That's right.
Now we've come to Vacation Island!
This place is really close to my hometown.
It's so nice...
I want to know what it's like to go to a resort too...
Everyone...
The tea's ready!
Hurray!
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Oh, everyone's already up and ready today.
That's just what I was hoping!
Ah, could it be... we've decided?
Yup!
Vacation Island?
International Music Festival?
Eh?
This island...
It's the one we just saw on TV.
"The local attractions include an outdoor stage, pools,
an amusement park, and all kinds of stores for your enjoyment."
Ehh...
It sounds like a wonderful place, right?
Mami and I wish we could stay our whole lives in a place like that.
Yup. Yup.
But,
what does this mean?
Ahem.
Actually,
765Pro has been officially invited to this music festival!
And a 3 night and 3 day stay is part of the deal. It's a wonderful outing, right?
Would you lik-
Really? Are we really going!?
A chance to learn and perform on a world stage, I'm so honored!
Come on Miki wake up! We got some big news!
You're supposed to let me sleep longer...
I wonder when we're departing?
H...HEY
H...HEY STOP!!!
Okay, so...
Not everyone can go...
Alright then, the members who
will be participating this time are:
Please come in
I'm afraid it's a bit messy though...
I'm sure since it's Azusa's place,
it'll definitely be neat and tidy.
We're coming in.
Feel free to sit where you like.
I'll go make some tea.
Okay.
This room's really girly and feminine, right?
Yeah.
I knew it, milk is critical for growth! Ku!
It was unexpected,
to be the ones who got selected.
I know what you mean.
I was really surprised.
But they picked us, so now we'll have to work hard on behalf of everyone else.
We have to fight for victory!
I like that Producer's selecting our songs but
we need to know more about the show before we know what to do.
Looks like we won't have any days off this week.
Azusa, do you have any preferences for the show?
Me?
I'm not sure yet...
Chihaya, how about you?
I'll leave it to the staff to decide on the production.
Okay...
I have so many different ideas bouncing around in my head, I'm having trouble deciding...
How troubling
But!
It's amazing we get to sing at a place
where people have gathered from around the world!
I can't wait!
People from around the world...
Alright!!
Starting tomorrow, let's do our best!
Oh!!!
Oh!
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Kotori, what are those three doing?
It seems that
they can't make up their minds about the music festival.
That's understandable when you have... Indecisive waffling, super excited curiosity and cool indifference...
What a mess...
Hey.
Thinking's important, but there's a time when you need to take action, too.
Do whatever it takes, but hurry up and make a decision already.
Sorry
But now I've switched to thinking about what happens if we can't finish thinking in time...
And now I don't think I can stop thinking...
You need momentum for this kind of thing. Momentum!
We'll start from here. Now, this new Producer's done well, right?
And, actually, about this music festival,
it turns out Producer's just found a job we can't possibly cancel, so he's asked me to accompany you instead.
Jeez, lately everybody's been overworked...
Um, Ritsuko...
Just now...
You said we could do whatever it takes, right?
Eh? What...
That's what you said, right?
You... don't tell me...
Ritsuko! Look at that!
The hotel has an ocean view! Ocean View!
It looks like a fun place
Hey now, what are you talking about?
We came here to work.
Um, Ritsuko
Can't we play, just a little...?
And who was it that asked me to come and perform on stage with them?
We don't have time to play.
There's a lot of foreigners...
Wait.
So cute!
Oh my, Chihaya has some admirers.
Bye bye!
Candy?
Okay, everybody.
We're going to the stage now.
I've planned it out perfectly, so if need be, I'll be relentless!
Okay!
When you get to see it in person,
it's downright immense.
We...
This is where we get to sing?
Everyone, look over there!
Wow, look how big it is!
I'd be fine with it if it were smaller.
Jupiter!?
To think you'd be here of all places.
Amagase Touma!
Little angels. Don't forget about me.
Yo!
It seems that Jupiter was invited.
Naturally.
Now's our rehearsal time for the show.
So how about you pests buzz off.
All of that is part of Jupiter's stage set?
That's right.
We'll also be using a 3D hologram for our show.
And an explosive CG act an-
Hey you! Stop running your mouth like that.
It's fine isn't it, Touma?
It's not our style to run away or hide.
Hmph, I guess you're right.
We won't run away or hide.
If you see us, stay out of our way.
I can't believe it...
They already prepared such a costly setup.
My research was completely off-target...
That's not true, Ritsuko.
That's right.
It's our fault for suddenly asking you to help.
I knew it, maybe it's better having a hard image than a soft one.
Ritsuko, how about adding these lyrics to our image?
Vapor trails from an airplane?
Oh! And then we can add smoke machines and why not an airplane on stage, too!?
We obviously won't be able to do all that.
I guess you're right...
Hey! Chihaya, come brainstorm with us.
I wonder what's on the other side of the ocean.
The other side of the ocean?
Hey, I'm back.
Welcome back, Producer.
That was quicker than expected.
Yup, I thought if Ritsuko and the others were doing their best,
then any encouragement from me might just make things more hectic.
Right now I bet everyone's enjoying a lovely meal.
That would be good.
But the four of them can take things too seriously.
Hopefully they won't worry too much over anything unusual.
That's true...
As I watched Jupiter's performance an uncomfortable feeling came over me.
Uncomfortable feeling?
Yes.
How can I say this...
It was a flashy show and certainly it would try to affect the audience as much as possible.
Yet, I wondered, is this the power of their music?
Chihaya's right.
This is a music festival so we have to show people the power of our music.
That's true, but we won't win if we try to beat Jupiter at their own game.
Right now,
We have to think about how we can present a unique image that only we can express.
A unique image that only we can express?
It's easier said than done but...
a hint for what we need would be really nice.
We're in a little bit of trouble
Chihaya! Look! Look!
A kid knocked somebody over!
Hey! Haruka come over here and think with us.
Well, I thought since we came out here, we should do some sightseeing.
There truly are people from so many different countries here.
You got that right. It's called the
International Music Festival after all.
Hey, it's those kids we saw at the seashore.
Ritsuko, I'm going over there for a second, okay?
Hey wait!
Then, I'll go too.
Azusa, you too...?
Even though we don't have any time to spare.
But...
With people from so many different countries here you'd think they wouldn't be able to communicate at all,
but it seems like everyone's having fun.
That's right. No matter where people are from, music can bring them joy. That's one of its best qualities.
Haruka looks like she's having so much fun.
Yeah, it's good to sing together.
Ritsuko,
I think I found a hint so
let's go, too.
Wai... Chihaya, you too?
That was so fun!
It feels like we've performed already.
Yes, it turned into a good rehearsal.
Hey now, the performance will be coming up soon.
Yes
Hey, Chihaya.
What is it?
Chihaya you asked this earlier, right?
What's on the other side of the ocean?
Yes.
On the other side is the same thing as here, music.
The place and the people may change, but I think the music's always there.
Yes, that's right.
Even without words, we can express ourselves.
We already have that ability inside of us.
Ok then, let's be the messengers who bring music to the world.
Oh that sounds really nice
Messengers that bring music to the world...
Oh, that's good!
With this, our plan's set!
Okay everybody, here's what we're gonna do.
We're just going to be ourselves.
But first, let's learn about the world!
Touma, this island might be the closest thing to Paradise.
That's all you've been talking about.
Ahh, found them...
Don't tell me... They've already given up on fighting?
You bullied them yesterday, so their self-confidence's crushed.
You're the one who was running his mouth.
I thought they were stronger than that. What a disgrace.
Oh my, Producer!
You came to see us?
Yes!
Azusa!
If you get too close to me um...
Producer, your nose is getting longer.
I was...
I got worried and ended up changing my plans.
But is everyone doing okay?
Just lounging around like this?
We're fine. Just take a look.
Producer, come with us, okay?
What's going on...?
Azusa, that looks good on you!
You look like you're really in high school.
Oh I wouldn't go that far Haruka
Jupiter's show really got them pumped up.
I wonder if we can actually beat them?
I think it'd be nice for us to win.
But winning isn't our only goal here.
What do you mean?
What we hope is to deliver the
best song we can to the whole world.
That's what we're thinking about.
That way Rather than worry about rehearsing, we can consider how our audience feels.
Mr. Producer, don't worry about it.
Yesterday, we met all kinds of people who powered us up.
Now it's our turn to give back.
We're focused.
I see.
Alright! Then sing with everything you got!
Right!
Today we want to share our vision of the world with you!
Everybody!
Here we go!
Even further... they're spreading so far,
these vapor trails I'm chasing.
Straight ahead!
It looks like we won't catch up today.
But tomorrow we probably can.
That's how I feel!
That dream we share,
I want to make it come true,
and I realize it so...
Let's head towards that sky,
to the edge of that borderline.
Racing there with all our hearts,
we're coming for you
I want to tell you (I want to tell you)
I love you so! It's Love!
Until the day we meet face-to-face, please believe my True Words.
Not yet, over there
there's still a wall.
It's fine.
Vault it!
On the other side of the wind,
to the edge of the borderline.
The future blooms from late Autumn leaves
It's changing! (It's changing!)
I love you so, and one day
when we join hands, there'll only be our honest feelings.
Don't hesitate! Sing it! Prime Word!
Vault That Borderline!
Ok, time for an announcement!
The winners are ...
the performers from 765Pro!
Hurray!
A series of battles were fought between
spirited hopefuls from all around the world!
This was a performance truly worthy of this stage!
Producer!
Everybody, way to go!
They're hoping for an encore, too!
But that's easier said than done...
I really don't think we can...
In that case, how about we give you a hand?
Everybody...?
Even so, I was really surprised!
Everyone talked about how we wanted to come cheer for you so...we came!
I thought it'd be a good idea for everyone to participate in the festival.
Thank you very much, Mr. President, Ms. Otonashi.
Thanks for waiting.
Okay then, let's ask 765Pro for an encore.
Encore!
Encore! Encore!
Okay everyone, get ready for the stage!
Umm... Producer?
About that, all of us talked it over and...
We want everyone to sing together for the ending.
I see...
That's a great idea!
You're coming with us.
And of course, Kotori too...
And the President as well.
Me, as well...?
Everyone, let's sing together!
Right? Producer.
Come on! Let's go! To our World of Music...
Come on PLAY START THE MUSIC♪
Forward...GO!!
Start running MELODY
to Now
now start the MUSIC
Catch it now GOAL!!
Get with this RHYTHM
to the Future
PHRASE!!
Let's try freely painting our hearts
Let's make words into lyrics and sing them
and make them echo
FRESH!!
Sing Nothing can ever stop music!
Up the VOLUME to the top
STANDBY STAND UP
Aim for the TOP!!
Let's play it, the music of dreams
With musical notes for wings
They can fly anywhere!
POWER!!
Let's sing our favorite songs
Any KEY is fine
Sing it and you'll see new DOORS
Opening and Sparkling
A new World begins LISTEN!!
to my MUSIC♪!!