Chihaya-chan, let me have that cookie.
Haruka,  that's bad manners.
That's right.
We've now come to Vacation Island!
This place, it's really close to where I'm from.
So nice...
I want to see what it's like to go to a resort too...
Everyone! The tea's ready.
Hurray!
It's yummy!
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Oh, today everyone's up and ready.
That's just what I was hoping!
Ah, Ah, could it be... we've decided?
Yup!
Vacation Island?
International Music Festival?
Eh?
This island...
It's the one we saw on the TV just now.
"In the area is an outdoor stage, pools,
an amusement park, and all kinds of stores for your enjoyment."
Ehh...
It sounds like a wonderful place, right?
Sis and I wouldn't mind spending
our retirement in a place like that.
Yup. Yup.
But, what does this mean?
Ahem.
Actually,
765Pro has been officially invited to this music festival!
A 3 night and 3 day stay is
part of the deal, a wonderful trip, right?
Do you lik-
Really? Are we really going!?
A chance to learn and perform on a world stage, I'm so honored!
Come on Miki wake up! There's huge news!
You were supposed to let me sleep more
I wonder when we're going?
H...
H...HEY
H...HEY STOP!!!
Ok, so...
Not everyone can go...
Alright then, the members that
will be participating this time are:
I'm so nervous...
I don't think I'm good enough to represent everyone...
I'm sure it'll be ok.
That's right, Yukiho.
With that view, even for battles where
victory is possible there won't be triumph.
Miki?
What's the matter, tuning out like that?
Are you still sleepy?
Rather, I feel like I'll be so anxious that I won't be able to sleep at all today..
After all,  I'll be going with everyone on a 3 night and 3 day vacation.
Also- Also-
being able to vacation with Honey
Watching the sunset with Honey
Having a romantic dinner with Honey
And at night, under a starry sky...
Miki, this is work-related travel, so that won't be possible.
Don't drag me back to reality so suddenly like that!
Miki really has the "lovestruck maiden" feeling about her, right?
I don't really know what that feels like...
I wonder if I'll be ready for the next stage...
You're probably right.
We'll be singing about love at the music festival but...
I also don't know much about things like love.
Takane, what about you?
No,
I haven't had any such experiences yet.
That's right... We should practice our singing and dancing.
Love song...?
A date with Honey?
Miki, what's wrong?
Everyone, leave the love and the performance to me!
Th-this is...
Vacation Island!
Ok everyone, about today's schedule...
Hey Honey,
today I want you to let us decide how to practice, ok?
Practice? What are you planning to do?
It's like  a lesson on the ABCs of love.
A lesson about love?
Could it be, we're talking about something serious?
Yes.  Up till now, we've practiced our singing and dancing.
But... um... we haven't had any experience with love.
Even if it's just for our time on this island...
to get the feeling of being like lovers with the Producer... and to give and return those kinds of feelings... is what Miki said...
The feeling of being lovers...?
What exactly are you planning?
That's something Miki spent a lot of time thinking about
Producer, when it's time, come to the place written in this paper, right?
Oi Miki! Come on, tell me what this is all about!
I mean... why are you leaving me here!?
If we don't look forward to our date, how can our hearts be throbbing with excitement?
Date!?
Ok, see ya later
Oi!
One o'clock in front of the park.
Three o'clock at the cafe in the forest.
Five o'clock at the scenic terrace. Seven o'clock at the pool.
What kind of lessons are these...?
Ahh but, there's good reasoning for what everyone talked about.
Producer?
Umm, sorry about today.
But... I thought that...If I too could... even just a little...maybe understand some of those feelings... that it would be good...
Is that ok?
This is something everyone decided on to prepare for the performance?
Y-yes.
Ok then, let's give it a try.
Someone like me is truly inadequate for this but if this can provide some ideas for the performance...
Yes!
There's a pretty good feeling here.
Yeah, looks like it will go smoothly. This "plan".
Huh?
I sense a bit of some complicated feelings too...
Ok then,
next is the cafe in the forest eh?
Who could be next I wonder...
Producer!
You're right on time!
Makoto, that outfit...
I mean, today's lesson is like practice for having an ideal date
so I wanted to try wearing something I really like.
Maybe... is it weird?
Nope, it looks good on you.
Heck yeah!
Hey now, and after putting on a dress and everything...
Once again there's a good feeling here.
There really is...
I wonder, could Honey be a playboy?
Well, this is something we asked for so it can't be helped...
That's right but...
Next is the scenic terrace eh?
But I mean, this kind of lesson with four of them and only one of me is kind of unfair I think.
My dearly beloved, I'd hoped we would meet like this...
M-my dearly beloved!?
I shouldn't say that?
No it's fine, I mean...
This thing Miki spoke of,
a "date." I have no idea what it should be.
So I thought, maybe if we shared a moment here together, watching the sunset...
So beautiful...
I mean the sunset!
I know what you mean.
Somehow, they seem to go together well as a couple.
Miki, what's wrong?
Hmm? It's nothing...
It's nothing...
And now only Miki is left.
Alright, I'll be counting on you
to get in touch with the performers.
Ok.
That's the music festival's
Excuse me!
You're an executive with the music festival, right?
I'm an official with 765Pro.
Oh no!
I thought I could just say hello but...
Miki!
Miki....
I'm sorry.
I stopped to greet an executive in the lobby and... Now I'm late...
Miki?
Honey, do you have any idea how Miki felt waiting here?
You weren't late meeting any of
the others only when it's Miki's turn.
Sorry.
You're right.
It's kind of a weird lesson but work is work.
Sorry for not being on time.
Say Miki... how about we...
Forget it!
Miki...
Miki, I'll leave this here, ok?
Come on Miki, let's do something to change the mood.
It wasn't totally the Producer's fault...
Makoto and the others had their dates so they can say things like that.
At least eat something,
or your legs will shake tomorrow.
After all, we came here to work.
I'll make some hot tea.
Leave me alone already!
Miki will be fine,
so I want you to leave me alone.
Sorry, Miki.
Miki...
Honey you idiot...
But... maybe Miki's the one being dumb...
Miki seemed so sad.
But we came here for work.
We really need to change the mood soon.
But, somehow... I feel jealous.
What is it?
Nevermind.
Love is like... the feeling of yearning for the moon.
Or so I had thought. And yet, when it comes to love,
unexpectedly it may actually be someone nearby...
At precisely ten o'clock.
We'll be waiting at the theme park.
Maybe Miki made them mad?
Nobody's here.
But Miki is the one who was wrong, so it can't be helped.
Miki!
Yukiho. Takane.
Sorry for what happened yesterday.
We said so many things without considering Miki's feelings.
No, it was Miki who...
Hey Miki, We've been thinking since then.
How can we cheer Miki up?
And so, there's...
Miki, Please go on a date with me today.
Makoto!
Really though,  you wish the Producer were here instead, right?
However, this morning we tried to contact him, but it seems like he's gone off somewhere.
And so, we thought "even if it's just us alone,we should do what we can."
Miki?
I knew it, I'm just not...!
I really love you all
It looks like everyone went on ahead without me again...
Producer!
Your clothes...?
I thought I could invite you on a date today, but it looks like someone took that role.
Maybe I just wasted some of my time...?
Nope, that's not true!
Let's have a date with everyone!
I just know it'll be the best date ever!
Ok everyone, do you think these love lessons will be helpful in our upcoming show?
Um... actually I don't think so...
The girls and I, speaking about love itself,
I think we probably don't really understand it yet.
However,  on the meaning of love, there'd never been a night where we'd pondered it so seriously before.
Thinking about Miki...
and then thinking about ourselves..
Maybe just a little...
Maybe we're just a little closer to the feelings within those songs.
I see.
Ok everyone!
It's showtime!
Let's get fired up!
Ok!
Hey Honey
If Miki and the girls win the show,
we want a reward!
Ok, you can count on it!
Wait what...
a "reward"?
And that is...
That is...
Nobody loves you like, I can love you.
and won't let go.
I met you under a blue sky.
I came to know the feeling of "I love you."
I trusted in this unfaltering destiny.
You said "farewell" to that girl.
I still remember those lips.
I'm not alone... I'm not alone anymore, right...?
I can't go back to when it was our last time together.
Sleepless. Love and Dream. Release the Light.
I long for you. I love you.
I've said those words so many times
like falling stars, for you.
A relentless cloudburst, and so...
As if I were bewitched...
Always, I believe.
By my side, forever love.
I need to see you. I miss you.
My heart painfully trembles.
From now on, stay with me.
As long as we can embrace,
An unending shower of sparkling falling stars
will descend on the two of us through breaks in the clouds...
Ok, time for an announcement!
The winners are...
the performers from 765Pro!
Hurray!
Thank you very much!
Honey!
Congratulations everyone!
Hey! Hey! You promised a reward, now gimme!
Wh-what!?
What do you mean "what"? It's a kiss.
A kiss for a reward!
Um... that's...
A promise is a promise, right?
in-the-heart-of-man, the-break-ing-of-pro-mis-es, un-ne-ce-ssar-y
I-I won't watch ok?
Uh oh...
Jeez, you are just the worst.
Eh!? Everybody...!?
After we went to all the trouble of coming to cheer for you.
You're such a perv, Producer!
We shouldn't stand too close to the Producer...
It's a misunderstanding!!!
Even so,
I was really surprised!
We all said we wanted to come cheer for you so...
We came!
I thought it would be a good idea for everyone to participate in the festival.
Thank you very much, Mr. President, Ms. Otonashi.
Thanks for waiting.
Ok then, let's ask for an encore from 765Pro.
Encore!
Encore! Encore!
Ok everyone,
get ready for the stage!
Umm... Producer?
About that, we all talked about it and...
We want everyone to sing together for the end.
I see...
That's a great idea!
You're coming with us.
And of course, Kotori too.
And the President too.
I as well...?
Everyone, let's sing together!
Right? Producer.
Come on! Let's go! To our World of Music...
Come on PLAY START THE MUSIC♪
Forward...GO!!
Start running MELODY
to Now
now start the MUSIC
Catch it now GOAL!!
Get with this RHYTHM
to the Future
PHRASE!!
Let's try freely painting our hearts
Let's make words into lyrics and sing them
and make them echo
FRESH!!
Sing Nothing can ever stop music!
Up the VOLUME to the top
STANDBY STAND UP
Aim for the TOP!!
Let's play it, the music of dreams
With musical notes for wings
They can fly anywhere!
POWER!!
Let's sing our favorite songs
Any KEY is fine
Sing it and you'll see new DOORS
Opening and Sparkling
A new World begins LISTEN!!
to my MUSIC♪!!