Chihaya-chan, let me have that cookie.
Haruka, that's bad manners.
That's right.
Now we've come to a vacation island!
This place is really close to where I'm from.
It's so nice...
I want to know what it's like to go to a resort too...
Everyone
The tea's ready
Hurray!
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Oh,
everyone's already up and ready today.
That's just what I was hoping!
Ah,
Ah, could it be... we've decided?
Yup!
Vacation Island?
International Music Festival?
Eh?
This island...
It's the one we just saw on TV.
"The local attractions include an outdoor stage, pools,
an amusement park, and all kinds of stores for your enjoyment."
Ehh...
It sounds like a wonderful place, eh?
Mami and I wouldn't mind spending our retirement in a place like that.
Yup. Yup.
But, what does this mean?
Ahem.
Actually,
765Pro has been officially invited to this music festival!
And a 3 night and 3 day stay is part of the deal. It's a wonderful outing, right?
Would you lik-
Really? Are we really going!?
A chance to learn and perform on a world stage, I'm so honored!
Come on Miki, wake up! We got some big news!
You're supposed to let me sleep longer
I wonder when we're departing?
H...
H...HEY
H...HEY STOP!!!
Okay, so...
Not everyone can go...
Alright then,
the members who'll be participating this time are:
Rock-
Rock-paper-
Rock-paper-scissors!
One more time!
One more time!!
Amazing
it looks just like a map down there, Iori-chan!
Of course,
we're flying in an airplane after all.
It's almost like a school field trip.
I haven't been on a field trip
since middle school. It's so much fun!
I know I said that but this is supposed to be work.
I know that
Would you care for something to drink?
Chu...?
Ah... Um...
Producer?
After the airplane ride, we're going on a boat, right?
Yeah.
it's like getting to eat fried shrimp and croquette together at the same time! I'm so happy!
That's good.
Hey hey nii-chan, after we get to the island, we can go play a little, right?
No, playing would be...
I told you we've already made a commitment
to be at the stage on time for rehearsal.
Waaah! At least for today, okay?
It's okay!
We'll work hard and do a good job!
Yes but,
we don't have that kind of free time...
Jeez, nii-chan's so stubborn.
Ami and I are big girls already,
so you should think about letting us have some fun.
I've got a good idea, Producer.
This time, the group leader should be none other than the amazing new sensation, the super idol: Iori-chan
Eh? Is that really true, Iori?
That's right.
Anyway,
as long as I'm here there's simply no possibility of failure.
So, playing just a little bit should be okay.
Huh?
Iori-chan, didn't you say we were
going to play all day today?
Shh
Come on nii-chan...
Producer
Alright.
I'll trust everyone.
But in exchange you have to stay together in groups,
and make a good effort in both your work and play.
Okay, teacher!
Somehow, it really became like a field trip.
Wow, it's even more amazing than I thought it would be.
Sis!
Ah! Chousuke!
It's been so long...
Good to see you!
How have you been?
Have you kids been good?
We've been good
Why are Yayoi's siblings here...?
I invited them.
Because, if Yayoi isn't with her family,
she can't sleep at night.
Iori...
you had it all planned out from
the start to play all day, right?
It's okay. We'll work really hard tomorrow, alright?
A maiden's warm heart
Okay, everyone. Today, let's follow Iori-chan's Flawless Plan and play till we drop!
I might have found it
My true color
Oh yea
Let's go on! We won't lose! Let's start from here
Let's join our hands and dash!
It's our future!
We won't lose! We can't be stopped!
The world is calling for us so
If we just jump in, it's probably ALL RIGHT!
It starts right now! It's a Brand New Day! Yay
Today was kind of tiring.
It ain't over yet. There's a fireworks show coming up!
Eh?
There's still more?
What are you talking about?
After the fireworks, there's the Night Version of the amusement park.
That's our Iori
It's really a perfect plan, right?
Oi oi,
it's ok to play for now,
but starting tomorrow morning we'll be in
rehearsal, and we'll have to practice diligently.
Make sure not to play so much
that you end up oversleeping.
It's ok
The super-star Iori-chan is here with you, so everything will work out
Right, Charles?
Is it really going to be okay...?
Iorin sure is late.
Even that old guy nii-chan woke up sooner...
Who are you calling old?
I'm still in my twenties.
Producer,
should I go check on Iori-chan in her room?
I think so...
if we don't leave soon, it'll be so late
that we'll miss the staff meeting.
Okay, I'll go then.
Okay, thanks.
Ah!
Iori-chan, good morning!
Um...
morning...
Jeez Iori, you're so late
Yea yea, you're even later than old nii-chan...
Iori-chan,
is something wrong?
Ah... no it's nothing.
I'm just not completely awake yet, that's all
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ok then, let's go.
One step, two steps, three steps
Iori-chan.
What's wrong?
What happened?
It's nothing.
Anyway, today we have a rehearsal,
so Yayoi, make sure your singing's good and clear, okay?
Iori-chan,
you're not telling the truth, are you...
I know you, Iori-chan, well enough at least to know when you're lying!
Y-yayoi-chi, what's wrong?
You're kind of being... scary...
Hey Iori,
what happened?
Something's not right.
Iori-chan, what happened to Charles?
Oh yeah...
I left him behind.
Hey, we promised to rehearse today, so let's go rehearse.
Iori-chan that's no good,
if you try to rehearse while
you're like this, you'll get injured.
Hey Iori, could you tell us what really happened?
I can't find him...
Yesterday, when we were watching the
fireworks, I thought we were together but...
Then I went with everyone to visit the town,
and later when we returned to our rooms.
And I fell asleep like everyone else, but...
I really can't remember when I lost him...
I-Iorin...
So that's what happened...
I'll look for him!
Don't!
I brought this on myself by playing around yesterday.
If I can't get the job done now, I'm a failure as a pro.
Nuh-uh
When I can't find my pets,
I'd keep searching for them, forever.
If they're your most beloved and cherished friends,
then there's just no way I'd ever stop looking.
Nii-chan!
Mami and I will search too!
Ah, well...
Yayoi!
I'll ask Sousuke and the others to help search too.
If everybody helps to look for him,
then we'll find him sooner!
Ok! I'll go look.
Ami too!
Iori, you can rest here for now.
Iori, how about we go too?
We need to take care of your problem first.
Okay... Everyone's being so silly like this...
Thank you, everyone.
Let's return to the stage.
Iori-chan! Don't!
We'll find him, so...!
I'm sure we'll find him, so,
let's return to the stage.
When we were searching, I was thinking:
"Why has Charles gone missing?"
And then I thought of it.
That maybe this is punishment...?
This is such an important music festival
and all I've done is play around,
and haven't taken it seriously at all.
So maybe he got mad at me?
And so, while we might not make it in time,
I want to put everything I have into this music festival.
It's not too late yet.
Iori-chan,
I'll do my very best too!
We'll do our best!
If we do that... then surely...
Charles, if you're there, then answer me
Yui Yui!
I don't think that'll work, Ganaha-san.
Wahhh, why couldn't he just
fall down from the sky?
Here, Iorin.
Charles...
Welcome back...
They told us he was picked up
from a hallway in the hotel.
Isn't it wonderful that we've found him?
Oh you, such a troublesome little bunny
Isn't it great, Iori-chan?
Thank you, everyone.
And also, I'm very sorry.
For taking away valuable time from
everyone's music festival to help me...
It'll be ok.
If we plan carefully, we'll make it in time.
Iori-chan,
let's return to the stage, and come up with a rehearsal plan!
Alright!! Let's do it!
Happy endings are great, right?
Yup, that's right.
Kasumi-chan, and little brothers,
sorry you couldn't play as much.
No it's fine, I got to visit lots of
different places today. It was fun!
Me too,
it was like a really fun adventure.
Me too! Me too!
Like an adventure...?
Lots of fun...?
That's right!
Our song...
What is it?
Hnn~ Hnn~ Hnn~
I figured it out too!
Way to go Iorin!
Magic Forehead!
Shindou,
go now and get our costumes ready!
And please hurry!
Yes, milady Iori.
Producer.
Because you're friends with this genius Iori-chan,
you can rest assured that tomorrow will be perfect!
Ehehe, maybe it's thanks to Kasumi and the kids.
Ok everyone, let's do our best!
High-five!
Yay!
If the Leaning Tower of Pisa were standing straight
That name will no longer do, ne?
Then, how about the Tower of Pisa?
If The Scream of Munch had a toothache
That name will no longer do, ne?
Then, how about the Tooth Cavity of Munch?
Let's change things in this world
With just a little imagination!
Look, so many strange things are happening!
Let's chant the magical word!
It's e-e-e-easy to change the world
Make up the rules as you go (Oh!)
No candy costs more than 2000 yen, okay!
Banana Bus! (not included)
Really real really real serious tension!
Everyone goes Kyo-eh!? and is super shocked
They say "it's really bad to eat so much!"
I just say "but hey, this is my world"
All wishes can come true I love this!
Sea-sea-sea-secret chance night
Hurry up and stuff your bag with all that you can carry (Hurray!)
Did I pack all my toys and dresses yet?
Let's go get them! (Oh!)
Sup-sup-sup-surprise unstoppable time!
No-one can get in our way (Roar!)
Hap-hap-hap-happiest feeling in the world!
Because this is my world!
No, don't wake up!
I was mad
I see...
All adventures together last couple days contributed to their performance.
Even if they slip and fall, they get back up again.
What an amazing show.
Right, Charles?
Pro~du~cer-san
H-haruka! And um...everyone?
Standing like that Producer,
while holding Charles so tightly...
What a cute scene to behold.
Ah! Um... no...
I'm just...holding on to this for safekeeping.
(They caught me...)
Producer!
Everyone! You were awesome
Really?!
Alright!
What a great feeling!
I'm so happy!
Compared to the first time they met, everyone's grown up a bit, eh?
Right, Charles?
Even so,
I was really surprised!
Everyone talked about how we wanted to come cheer for you so...we came!
I thought it'd be a good idea for everyone to participate in the festival.
Thank you very much, Mr. President, Otonashi-san.
Thanks for waiting.
Okay then, let's ask 765Pro for an encore.
Encore!
Encore! Encore!
Okay everyone,
get ready for the stage!
Umm... Producer?
About that, all of us talked it over and...
We want everyone to sing together for the ending.
I see...
That's a great idea!
You're coming with us.
And of course, Piyo-chan too.
And the President as well.
Me, as well...?
Everyone, let's sing together!
Right? Producer-san.
Come on! Let's go! To our World of Music
Come on PLAY START THE MUSIC♪
Forward...GO!!
Start running MELODY
to Now
now start the MUSIC
Catch it now GOAL!!
Get with this RHYTHM
to the Future
PHRASE!!
Let's try freely painting our hearts
Let's make words into lyrics and sing them
and make them echo
FRESH!!
Sing Nothing can ever stop music!
Up the VOLUME to the top
STANDBY STAND UP
Aim for the TOP!!
Let's play it, the music of dreams
With musical notes for wings
They can fly anywhere!
POWER!!
Let's sing our favorite songs
Any KEY is fine
Sing it and you'll see new DOORS
Opening and Sparkling
A new World begins LISTEN!!
to my MUSIC♪!!