This is a beast princess's love story.
One day, she meets a human prince
and wishes to become one with him.
"I want to live as a human.
I want to be united with him."
The witch replied like so:
"I can help you if you offer me your wings.
But keep this in mind.
No matter how you disguise
yourself, you are a beast,
and you will consume the
prince's life one day."
The princess ripped off her wings
Plantation 13
Ruins
and was assaulted by pain far more
intense than she had ever felt.
She could never fly again.
Even so, she smiled happily,
with tears of joy streaming down her face.
"I'm human! I'm human!
I'm the same as him now!"
Come over here beside me as my restraint crumbles.
Please don't fear me
Ah...
I want to taste you... Does that make me weird?
It's something we're unable to feel all alone
Embracing one another will keep our wounds sealed
So I'll seal your breath with my lips
Will your lips taste the kiss of death?
Darling
ko
dou
ga
yu
Darling, what is this melting feeling
Going from my heart to the tips of my fingers?
nee...
Hey...
Come to me, as our inhibitions crumble
Please don't fear me
Just kiss me now!
Mobile Aerial Fortress
『
』
Cosmos
『
』
Cosmos
Our parasite reserves have dwindled
to 60 percent after the last battle.
Don't you think we went too far
by blowing those plantations up?
The ends justify the means. Humanity
now has control of Gran Crevasse.
Hringhorni's construction has
entered the final phase, too.
Hringhorni Construction Site
The time has come.
I've already sent two
messengers to you-know-where.
This will likely be our
final warning to them.
There is no need for two keys.
Now, Klaxosaur Princess,
what will you choose?
That day, in the Battle of Gran Crevasse,
our plantation was left in ruins.
But we're still living here in Mistilteinn.
We are to stand by and
wait for our next mission.
One month has already passed since
we were given those orders.
Oh, it's Papa!
We children have always lived by ourselves,
but some things have changed now.
The damage to the plantation has
affected the water supply system,
and we've also had to restrict
our electricity usage.
Save Energy
And to top it all off, our mysterious
caretakers are gone now.
One, two...
Talk about making a racket.
She's on messenger duty this week?
Looks like it.
The only thing we were told
was that food supplies would
be delivered to us once a week.
That was all.
We're spending our days completely
in the dark about things.
The water's starting to go foul here, too.
Yeah.
But it might be drinkable if we filter it.
That said, there's no telling
how long we can keep this up.
The water supply to this
area could stop at any time.
Yeah, you're right.
Found you.
Time for breakfast, you two.
Take care of this, darling.
Doing okay?
Yep, all good.
I'm starving!
Man, this again?
What else can we do?
You don't have to eat it if you don't want it.
Hey! I didn't say I wouldn't eat it!
Sorry. I'll help.
Nah, it's fine.
Anyway, has your fever gone down?
I'm used to it now.
36.7 degrees...
Normal body temperature.
But don't push yourself, okay?
G-Got it. Thanks.
May Papa's heart be filled
with peace for eternity.
Let's eat.
Morning laundry: okay.
Carrying the rations: okay.
Thirty minutes for breakfast.
After that...
You're awfully meticulous.
Nobody's going to complain
if you go a bit off-schedule.
That won't do! We all agreed to these rules!
Everyone
washes
their
own
undies!
Put
them
in
the
laundry
box
and
you
will
DIE!!
Do
not
take
any
food
or
drinks
from
the
storage
without
telling
anyone!
Chore Wheel
Make it a
habit to turn
the lights OFF!
Do not leave
lights on when
not in use!
We're the only ones here,
so we gotta obey them.
Wow, look who's turned over a new leaf.
What happened to your wild side?
Exactly. That's why I wanna do things right.
Oh, really now?
Really.
What's wrong? Do you not feel well?
Oh, no.
Just, uh...
You know! I'm dieting!
You? Dieting?
You ain't cut out for that.
Say what?
Also, it'd just be a waste of time.
We don't—
You haven't made contact, I hope?
That's right.
Good.
If you intervene with the children,
this whole project will be ruined.
Doctor, I fail to understand this.
If we keep this up, all our
efforts will have been in vain.
They went to hell and came back alive.
I'm sure they'll continue to be
major assets to Papa and the rest.
Even if we are to keep the test
going, we should at least—
Always so inflexible.
You've been down this road too, you know.
Keep it up, Hachi.
Wait, Doctor!
Good grief! What is with him?
It's been one whole month.
How long will we have to stand by?
Do you want to get back
in the FRANXX already?
You know, we were fighting battles
in which we could die at any time,
but not having to fight makes
us all fidgety too, huh?
I'm surprised, though.
I thought you were the one most
obsessed with piloting the FRANXX.
You want me to cut your hair?
Where is this coming from?
Oh, I don't mind at all.
If you're okay with me, I'd love to!
What was I even hoping for?
Did I want him to apologize?
Or was I searching for
a reason to forgive him?
I got it all mixed up.
Both the promise we made,
and how he'd forgotten about it...
He'd done nothing wrong.
Maybe I was using my grudge against
Hiro to carve out a niche for myself.
And now, I have nothing...
Look up, Mitsuru.
Wh-What?
Does my hair look weird?
No. You look very handsome.
If you understand that,
you can start all over again.
Even after the misunderstandings, I believe
that the promise you two made is real.
Thank you.
It's funny. Hearing that from you
makes me feel like I can do anything.
You're very kind.
And you're gifted with your hands...
Wait, no... What...
I-I'm so sorry!
Goro developed a fever last week, too.
It must be the Child Fever.
Everything changed in that battle,
like our environment and our lifestyle...
Zero Two?
Oh, those are sakura buds.
Sakura? What are the flowers like?
What are they like? Well...
Oh, they're a really pretty color.
The same color as your hair.
I can't wait to see them.
What do you think of our lives right now?
I'm having fun.
You don't find it a pain?
Not at all.
In fact, I'd love to live like this forever.
I feel the same way, actually.
I do have my worries,
but all of this is new, and it's
so interesting and exciting.
And...
I was supposed to go bathing with the girls!
Huh? Oh...
No peeking, darling.
Did you see Mitsuru's hair?
So you really did cut it for him, Kokoro.
He looked pretty good.
Yeah.
Fishie!
Hey, sit right!
Okay.
Your hair really is so pretty.
Darling also said it was
a pretty color earlier.
He said flowers the same
color would bloom soon.
Do you two always talk
about corny stuff like that?
Now you've done it!
Sheesh.
Hey...
I'll wash your hair for you now, Miku.
I'll wash it myself!
Guess I'll take the body, then!
Wait, stop!
That tickles!
We have around five sources
we can use for drinking water.
And two of them are only
usable with filtering.
Can't we repair the circulation
system ourselves?
Mistilteinn doesn't have the equipment
to get it back up and running.
And our access to the
elevator is restricted, right?
Yeah.
Why don't we just send a letter
to Papa and ask him to fix it?
I don't think there'd be any point to that.
Huh? What makes you so sure?
Man, we never realized how big a part
the caretakers played in our lives, huh?
Yeah. They always made sure we
had hot food and clean clothes.
What'll become of us if we
stop getting rations, too?
We could just cook our own food, then.
Right.
The river still had fish in it.
If we can cook them...
But none of us have ever done that before.
We were never taught how to.
Actually, I think that's a pretty good idea.
I believe we had books about
cooking in the study.
Then maybe we could do it after all.
Yeah.
I want to give it a shot, too.
That's that, then!
Look, Zorome!
Aren't you dieting? Why are
you so gung-ho about this?
But this is fun! Look at
this stuff burning up!
Wow, you're right! That's so cool!
Welcome back.
We're back!
Wow, what a haul.
I caught eleven!
Really?
That's awesome.
How about you, Goro?
Two fewer than Zero Two.
That's still amazing.
Yeah.
And Hiro?
I didn't catch any.
Are you kidding me, Hiro? That's so lame!
I'll teach you all the tricks later.
I'll go fishing next, then.
I wanna go, too!
Could you teach me how to fish, too?
What's up?
Sure thing. I'll show you now.
Oh, I was just thinking
how the mood has changed.
When the rod twitches,
you immediately reel that thing in!
I don't know if I can...
It's easy!
Hiro was right.
I'd had it in my head that
Zero Two was different from us...
That she had different reasons
and goals for fighting.
I painted her as an unapproachable enigma
and never even tried to
see her for who she was.
Ichigo...
We'll probably never fully understand
what happened between them,
but right now, she's an ordinary girl.
She's one of us, an irreplaceable
part of Squad 13.
Yeah, I agree.
I want what's best for both Zero Two
and Hiro.
We're incredible!
We actually cooked for ourselves!
Weren't you slacking at first?
You never know what you're capable of, huh?
Yeah.
The question is, how will it taste?
We followed the book's instructions,
so it should be fine.
Okay, take your seats.
Forget about it.
Hey!
Why should we have to pray when
we did everything ourselves?
This is pretty good!
Really?
Yeah, it's totally edible!
Yay!
This is good.
Yeah.
Hey, we just did something
awesome, don't you think?
I bet none of the other squads
actually cook for themselves, right?
Yeah. I've never seen any others do that.
See? We're truly geniuses!
Come on, Futoshi! Eat up!
Someone's let this go straight to his head.
Come on, eat up! This is really good!
In a way, that's so him.
Right?
Eat already! What's the matter?
Isn't he getting a bit too worked up, though?
Eat, damn you!
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm fine.
Sorry, my hand slipped.
Hey.
Quit forcing yourself.
It's fine. I can handle this myself—
I know that you're forcing yourself
to eat and throwing it all back up.
Of course I'm not.
Don't lie to me!
Hey, cut it out.
You're wrong.
No, I'm not!
It's not like that!
You'd better eat if you wanna survive!
Otherwise...
If you keep this up...
It's okay! I can eat!
I'll eat it all!
Why? Why?
Look at us. Why isn't Papa getting in touch?
Why isn't he coming to get us?
Do you think he cast us aside?
A part of me always thought
it wasn't our problem.
Even after I saw what happened to Squad 26,
I was sure it wouldn't happen to me.
As FRANXX pilots,
there's a limit to our lives.
We've always received
constant reminders of that.
I was worried the entire time, too.
But I was too scared to speak up.
Not just you.
I had my fears, too.
Yeah.
I've been writing to Nana and Hachi
to let them know how we're doing.
But they never accepted the letters.
What the heck? You'd already tried?
Assuming we really have
been cast aside by Papa...
I think that's fine.
I'm not worried as long as I'm with you all.
As long as we're together,
we can work things out.
Look at today. We cooked our
own food, and it was a lot of fun.
Be it cooking together, or discussing
how to go about our daily lives,
we've never really spent much
time on these things before.
I never said I wasn't having fun.
It's just, I...
Fighting is all we've ever known.
I-I had fun, too! Though I couldn't eat it all...
We can just cook again.
Yeah, Mitsuru's right.
Cooking as a group, taking baths,
and talking things out...
I'm finding all of it so enjoyable
and valuable right now.
It's making me feel like this
is where we truly belong.
Where we belong?
There's more to our lives
than piloting the FRANXX.
Futoshi...
Oh, please! What are you crying for?
You're one to talk!
Shaddup!
And now I'm hungry!
What the heck?
Yeah, eat up! You need the energy!
Being a fatty is what suits you best.
Seriously, stop calling me that!
That day, we cried and laughed
more than we ever had before.
But you are a fatty!
"Humans! Humans!
They have neither the wings to fly
nor the claws or fangs to hunt.
Such weak and frail creatures,
but they are so, so warm.
Humans are wonderful!"
Wait, isn't this...
Yeah. The picture book we read together.
You remember it all? That's incredible.
But this story is kinda sad, isn't it?
You think?
It was my first "pretty thing."
I met you and wanted to have
something beautiful with you.
You showed me the outside world, after all.
But I understood nothing about
what being human meant.
I was made to realize that it
wasn't about appearances at all.
You guys shine too brightly in my eyes.
You cry, laugh, get mad,
and try to live as a group.
And you let me be a part of that.
I realized that this was the kind of
humanity that I wanted all along.
Zero Two...
Don't worry.
We'll be together forever.
Episode 16
Days of Our Lives
We're getting drenched in the unexpected rain
yohou hazure no ame ga bokura wo nurashite
What should I tell you as I see you tremble?
furueteru kimi ni nani wo hanashitara ii no
Wet to the skin, we feel so cold, so heavy
bishonure no burezaa ga tsumetakute omotakute
Helpless like a bird who just left its cage
kago wo deta hinadori no muryokusa wo kanjiteru
I was so close to my dreams and now they're beyond the clouds
sawaresou datta yume wa buatsui kumo no mukou de
All that's left in my heart is bittersweet pain
mune ni hirogaru amai itami dake kamishimeta
Maybe we shouldn't have met after all
boku to kimi wa deawanai hou ga yokatta ka na
I can't even see the stars...
nee hoshi sae mienai yo
I can't even shed any tears
nee namida mo dete konai