Good morning.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
Come over here beside me as my restraint crumbles.
Please don't fear me
Ah...
I want to taste you... Does that make me weird?
It's something we're unable to feel all alone
Embracing one another will keep our wounds sealed
So I'll seal your breath with my lips
Will your lips taste the kiss of death?
Darling
ko
dou
ga
yu
Darling, what is this melting feeling
Going from my heart to the tips of my fingers?
nee...
Hey...
Come to me, as our inhibitions crumble
Please don't fear me
Just kiss me now!
We will abandon Mistilteinn shortly.
Be ready to leave at any time.
Abandon it? So suddenly?
The situation has changed.
When the next supply ship arrives,
we will take it to the parasite camp.
After ignoring us for so long,
where is this coming from?
So they were watching us the whole time.
You okay? How's your fever?
Oh, it's no big deal.
Miku had one recently, too.
Goes to show that we all have our issues.
What's wrong, Ichigo?
Abandon, huh?
Can't we stay here somehow?
We only have rations for
a few more days at best.
Besides, Mistilteinn won't
last very long itself.
Looking back, our life
here wasn't all that bad.
But we can't stay here anymore.
That's kinda sad.
Hey...
There's something I'd like us
to do while we're still here.
A wedding?
What's that?
It was a ceremony where two
humans of old would make a vow
to be true to each other in sickness and
in health, and never part until death.
That's what it means to marry,
or so this book said.
And who's gonna marry at this wedding?
Kokoro and Mitsuru.
Hiro told us about it, and we
thought it sounded wonderful.
We decided to do it before
leaving this place.
You've got some nerve to try this
after how much they yelled at you.
That sounds so romantic!
You have my full support!
I don't really get it,
but it's a good way to make
one last memory here...
Futoshi, listen, I...
I'm taking this role!
I don't care what you guys say! I'm doing it!
I... I want to be right beside Kokoro
and Mitsuru and congratulate them!
Thank you, Futoshi.
We'll have to get to work right away, then.
Cheer up, man.
Yeah.
Right.
That's the wedding dress?
Yep. It's what you wear for the ceremony.
It's so pretty.
But can we really make it?
What material can we use?
Turn our curtains into a dress?
You sure come up with some crazy ideas.
Well, they're white. Just what we need.
"Our potential," huh?
What are those?
Rings. You apparently exchange
them during the ceremony.
Huh... Sounds nice.
I bet Kokoro will love it.
I sure hope so.
That should be enough chairs, right?
Yeah.
Hiro!
Hey, pass!
Y'know, don't you wanna
make this a bit more grand?
Grand?
Hey! How long are you gonna play around?
Oh, quit being a nag!
I was about to get to work!
Then help out with the preparations a little!
Are you awake, Ikuno?
Still feeling under the weather?
Do you have a fever?
Don't worry. It isn't like that.
Listen, did something happen with the Nines?
I'd never seen you get so angry before.
Nothing, really.
Sorry. I didn't mean to pry.
I get it. If that didn't
make us mad, nothing would.
Thanks for doing that for Kokoro and Mitsuru.
You're wrong. I didn't do it for them.
Then why?
Do you want to know?
Are you that interested in me?
Ikuno? What...
I was thinking the same thing
as the Nines back then.
And I slapped Alpha in order to hide that.
What do you mean, the same thing?
Only a boy and girl together
can operate a FRANXX.
And I've always wished that
annoying system would go to hell.
Ikuno?
But you know what I realized?
As much as I find it a pain, I wouldn't
be myself if I refused to acknowledge it.
You wouldn't be who you are without it.
And I would hate that.
God, my feelings are such a mess!
Your feelings?
I love you, Ichigo.
Why me?
You were the one who gave me my name.
Ikuro. She's Ikuro.
That's such a weird name.
Remember how everyone started following
in Hiro's footsteps and naming each other?
"No."
Your name's "Ikuno" now. Like it?
I bet you think it's a silly reason.
But ever since that day,
I've only had eyes for you.
You changed your hair
clip a while ago, right?
Yeah.
I notice these things about you.
Did you lose the old one?
Or did a certain someone give you a new one?
I'm a creep, aren't I?
I get insanely jealous of boys who get to
stand beside you just because they're boys.
I want to keep you all to myself.
That's so selfish, right?
It's a pain, isn't it?
Why am I like this?
I hate being like this!
Oh... She's just like I used to be.
Ichigo?
There's nothing wrong with being a pain.
I'm a pretty big one myself.
We're all complicated, difficult, and a pain.
But, y'know, I've started thinking
that we're fine this way.
I get the feeling that going through
all of this is what life is all about.
I probably won't be able
to give up very easily.
I don't often take no for an answer.
Yeah, I know.
Thank you, Ichigo.
All right!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Zorome
Enters
the Fray!
Okay, ready?
Zero Two!
You okay?
What's the matter?
I guess I dozed off for a bit.
Wow. It's almost complete.
Yeah.
I'll come show you as soon as it's done.
You were right. They are in full bloom now.
Look, Kokoro lent me this
to wear for the wedding.
It's kinda funny to see
you wearing our uniform.
Is that all you have to say?
You look great.
Do you remember that we promised
to marry all those years ago, too?
Of course I do.
A marriage is when two people who love
each other promise to be together forever.
You taught me that.
In that moment, you became my darling.
Wow!
This is amazing!
Darling!
The time I spend laughing with you
is filled with so much warmth
So much warmth
and so, so beautiful.
So, so beautiful
Mitsuru...
Mitsuru? Would you look at me, please?
I-I can't! Don't ask for the impossible!
Kokoro?
Let's find happiness together.
Yes, let's.
Mitsuru! Kokoro!
Now you look the part, too.
Here.
Thank you.
Thanks, Ikuno.
H-Hey, do we ring the bells now?
What do you say?
Go for it!
Should we say something?
Like what?
I-I don't know!
Look at him, acting all cool.
Kokoro looks really beautiful, though.
There!
Lookin' good!
That reading...
An APE assault ship?!
Hey.
What's the meaning of this?
Who authorized this?
Papa did, obviously.
Are you going to force them into the
parasite camp's re-indoctrination program?
Squad 13 is supposed to be exempt from it.
Not all of them. Just two.
What?
You know what they were up to, don't you?
Just sit there and watch like you always do.
The couple will now exchange rings.
Sorry!
I'm okay. Keep going.
Now...
Y-You may seal your vows with a kiss!
All of you freeze!
Lift one finger, and you will die!
Down on your knees!
Who the hell are you guys?!
Zorome?!
Run away, you two!
Futoshi!
Guys!
There's nowhere for you to run.
You are trapped in a birdcage, you know.
What is the meaning of this?!
Papa said you two were dangerous.
You need to be re-indoctrinated.
Still haven't given up on
playing human, have we?
It's getting embarrassing, really.
You're embarrassing.
You think so?
Zero Two!
You know you mustn't defy Papa's will,
don't you, Iota?
Take them.
N-No! Mitsuru!
Get your hands off of Kokoro!
Mitsuru!
Kokoro...
Mitsuru... Mitsuru!
No! Let me go!
Mitsuru!
Are we not allowed even the
slightest bit of happiness?
It's like nothing's changed
since we were in Garden!
Where were Mitsuru and Kokoro taken?
Will they ever come back to us?
None of us had any answers,
and time passed mercilessly by.
If I possessed emotions, what could
I have said to the children?
As you are now, maybe you could
have offered them support.
Mind explaining to us what happened in
the meeting with the klaxosaur princess?
I thought its purpose was
to tell her to surrender.
Why weren't we told they'd
try to assassinate her?
We seek a world where APE and
humanity can live for all eternity.
I thought we were working as one to achieve
that goal, but perhaps I was mistaken.
What happened was well within our
predictions. It won't be a problem.
We already possess the replacement key.
You must look at the big picture.
When we realize our ideals, you will be
freed from the shackles of your shells.
Or as you call them, bodies.
Camp for Children
『
』
Bird Nest
The parasites are being summoned in order.
Where are they being taken?
I don't like this place.
It reminds me of Garden.
How long will this go on?
We were told to stand by until
our next mission, remember?
But it's been weeks, man.
I hope Kokoro and Mitsuru are okay.
Guys!
Kokoro!
Mitsuru!
Thank goodness. We were afraid
we'd never see you again.
I'm so glad you're both okay!
Sorry! It was all my fault
for suggesting the wedding!
Wedding?
What's a wedding?
Come on! Don't you remember that ceremony?
"Until death do us part," and all that stuff.
You even exchanged rings.
Oh, this?
I don't know when it got here.
Who is she, anyway?
A new squadmate?
Huh? You're the new member, not me.
What's gotten into you two?
You're acting really weird!
Their memories have been altered.
Just like ours were back then.
The home we built for ourselves
was too brittle to live in,
and everything we ever hold dear is
always destroyed in the blink of an eye.
Sakura?
If that is our destiny,
then we can't let it rule us anymore.
We're at the end of our rope.
Episode 18
When the Sakura Blooms
We're getting drenched in the unexpected rain
yohou hazure no ame ga bokura wo nurashite
What should I tell you as I see you tremble?
furueteru kimi ni nani wo hanashitara ii no
Wet to the skin, we feel so cold, so heavy
bishonure no burezaa ga tsumetakute omotakute
Helpless like a bird who just left its cage
kago wo deta hinadori no muryokusa wo kanjiteru
I was so close to my dreams and now they're beyond the clouds
sawaresou datta yume wa buatsui kumo no mukou de
All that's left in my heart is bittersweet pain
mune ni hirogaru amai itami dake kamishimeta
Maybe we shouldn't have met after all
boku to kimi wa deawanai hou ga yokatta ka na
I can't even see the stars...
nee hoshi sae mienai yo
I can't even shed any tears
nee namida mo dete konai