After the successful kissing
with Plantation 26,
Squad 13 was given a special vacation.
It's the ocean!
So childish.
Being on break doesn't mean
you can get carried away.
I don't blame them.
This is our first time seeing
an ocean that's okay to swim in.
I didn't know a place like this
survived on the surface, though.
Ever since being assigned to the squad,
we'd been living our lives under
extreme anxiety and stress.
But this scene was entirely
removed from all that,
which put us in very high spirits.
Hey. Don't go too far out.
Nana said she'd come pick
us up tomorrow morning.
Do you think this is some
kind of training, too?
Who knows?
But...
This seems to be free of klaxosaurs,
and since we're here anyway,
let's enjoy ourselves.
Y-Yeah.
Let's go, darling!
Ease up a little, Zero Two!
I'm glad Hiro's all better now.
Hurry up!
We were all worried for nothing.
But now, that rumor about
Zero Two has been proven false,
and Hiro has become an official parasite.
Good news all around, don't you think?
Following that battle, the two of
them were made official partners.
Take that!
I still have my misgivings about Zero Two,
Come on, darling.
but one look at Hiro now makes it obvious
that she was exactly what he needed.
Yeah.
I'm really glad.
Come over here beside me. My restraint crumbles
Don't be scared
Ah...
A flightless bird dreamed of the sky
This thickly mixed love is a differently colored red
Love
I covered my ears to the sound of knocking on my door
Is that you knocking? Or is it someone else...
Will you leave just a kiss of death?
Darling, fate runs through my veins
k
e
Darling
Darling
As this world begins to move (Love)
I want to be your closest partner, Darling
Darling
So don't be scared...
Just kiss me now!
Who would've thought that failure of a
special specimen had so much ability?
Seriously. I wish he'd shown
us this from the start.
Our girl's silly search for
a man has finally ended.
We should be happy about that.
But it doesn't change the fact that she
still needs to be monitored closely.
Plantation 13 is hereby declared a
top-priority surveillance subject.
Code 016 is tasked with bringing our girl
to the Grand Crevasse safe and sound.
The time has finally come.
A special surveillance subject?
Is it because Zero Two is now officially
under Plantation 13's purview?
One of APE's special forces has become
a plantation's exclusive parasite.
There's no precedent, but it was
the obvious decision.
Oh, Zero Two. Glad to see you're okay.
All thanks to my darling's efforts out there.
You didn't have to come all this
way. We would've been fine.
Don't be like that.
You're leaving already?
Hiro, this is Doctor Franxx.
Well, I got what I came for.
Doctor Franxx
It looks like I wasn't needed.
The creator...
And this here is—
No need to introduce us.
We're sure to run into one
another again someday.
This is the first time
anyone's survived Zero Two.
Huh... So this is what you're like.
I must say, I've taken an interest in you guys.
Doctor.
As of today, Strelizia and Code 002 are
transferred into Plantation 13's purview.
I know. The geezers told me already.
As such,
Code 016 is hereby officially
appointed Code 002's partner.
Y-Yes, sir!
Darling! I'm so happy!
I can't breathe, Zero Two!
Hey, Doctor.
I'll be fine if I'm with my darling.
We'll do this together.
Often times, one needs foreign elements
in order to adapt to their environment.
I guess that's what this special order is for.
Not to mention,
sending the children to
the beach by themselves?
The doctor's ideas are always so crazy.
Here I go!
Bring it!
Ready... There!
Gotta love the beach, huh?
Yeah.
For some reason,
the girls look 50% cuter. It's a mystery.
Yeah, this is certainly a sight for sore eyes.
Huh? Are you one of us, Goro?
I thought you double-digits were
just a bunch of goody-two-shoes,
but we have more in common than I thought.
Wh-What the hell? I'm a guy, too!
How am I supposed to ignore
this marvelous view?
Ow... Are you all right?
Sorry. I was looking up the whole time.
That string's coming undone.
Oh, no! Tie it back up for me, please!
Long live the beach!
Hey, how far are you going?
Yo, check out those two.
Swimming in the ocean feels so good.
And it does taste salty.
It's the real deal this time, huh,
darling?
Darling?
S-Sorry. It's just, looking
at you in a swimsuit...
Is it weird?
No, you look really good! But for some
reason, I can't look you in the eye...
You saw me naked before, though.
I-It's not like I meant to!
You're the one who helped
me get here, darling.
I'd never taken a dip in an ocean before.
You're my wings, right?
If I'm with you, I can fly anywhere I want.
Say, darling.
We'll always be together, right?
Always...
Code 016.
Let me offer you a piece of advice.
Y-Yes?
Don't let her consume your emotions, too.
If you want to always
be her partner, that is.
Otherwise, you'll be the one to suffer later.
You and I have crossed a
line together, you know?
Your taste really does make my heart race.
Were you expecting a kiss?
A kiss is a declaration that the
other person belongs to you.
So you should only kiss
the person you love, okay?
Love? Kiss?
Wait... Have you done it with
someone other than me, perhaps?
Huh? W-Well...
Darling?
Gotcha!
Ichigo?
Distracted, are we?
Huh?!
By the ocean, I mean.
Aren't you going to swim?
You were always good at swimming.
Oh, that's what you meant?
Well, yeah...
I've got this book, so don't
worry about me. Go on.
Thanks, Ikuno.
You came all this way just to read?
Forcing myself to frolic
doesn't sit well with me.
No arguments here.
Give it up already!
Isn't it great?
Jeez!
The guy who looked like he
wanted to die not too long ago
Seriously, knock it off!
is now part of the group again.
Please don't look to me for affirmation.
I'm not like you.
Please. I was merely talking to myself.
Is that all you wanted to talk about?
Are we done now, then?
Nah.
I found something odd.
What's gotten into you guys?
I didn't mean to intrude,
but these guys just wouldn't listen.
Wh-What is it?
What's a kiss?
Huh?!
Y-You were listening?!
I've never heard the word "kiss" before,
but it sounds magical!
Hiro, my boy, where do
you think you're going?
Are you sure you're not
hiding anything from us?
What were you two getting up to?
N-Nothing!
C-C'mon, help me!
Hiro...
I also want to know.
What's a kiss?
Not you, too!
I-I don't really get it myself.
I-It's when two people stick
their mouths together.
Their mouths?!
Mouths are for something besides eating?!
Don't you breathe with yours sometimes?
And what happens when you kiss or whatever?
I-It felt really soft, warm,
and, uh...
It made my heart race.
B-But we didn't kiss back there!
I kinda wanna try it myself.
What the hell? I really wanna
know what it feels like!
Damn you! You got the jump on us again!
Let me kiss you!
Wait! You should only do it
with the person you love!
The heck is a "person you love"?
Stop it!
What are you guys doing?
Don't stop me...
Ow!
Do you know what a kiss is, Ichigo?
The thing where two people touch mouths.
N...
N-No idea!
Hey!
Got a sec?
Hey, are you sure?
Yes. You'll see it at the end of this path.
This is like an exploration. How exciting!
But it's so dark that I'm
getting a little creeped out.
You didn't have to come
along if you didn't want to.
Hey! Don't talk to Kokoro like that!
At the very least,
I can't guarantee your
safety from here on out.
Is there a relationship closer
than being partners?
Well, watching you two makes me wonder.
You talk about "kisses"
and "loving a person."
What's that all about?
I don't really understand, either.
"Makes your heart race," huh?
You know, I have fun being with Ichigo,
but it also hurts sometimes.
Maybe I'm not like you guys.
Ichigo?
What's the matter? Your face is all red.
I-Is it?
We can see it now.
What is this place?
It's like a small city or something.
A city? This?
It's nothing like the cities the adults live in!
Do you think people live here?
Who knows?
I've never heard of anyone
living outside the plantations.
Hey! Anybody here?
This isn't really what I was expecting.
And what exactly were you expecting?
I mean, look!
This isn't all that different
from our boarding house!
Yeah. It's like they used this as the model
to build the environment we live in.
But why?
Don't ask me.
Huh? Where's Kokoro?
Reception and Dispensary
Whats Best for Your Baby
Your First Childbirth
A baby?
Kokoro!
Please don't run off alone.
I told you, didn't I?
I can't guarantee your safety.
Your First Childbirth
Whats Best for Your Baby
S-Sorry.
Your First Childbirth
Whats Best for Your Baby
The Beat of a Kiss
Kiss... Mouth to mouth...
I've done it with darling.
Zero Two...
D-Done what?
Kissed.
I guess you guys aren't ready for it yet.
I-I've done it, too.
Really? With whom?
A kiss is something you share
with your special someone.
Is the one you kissed special to you?
W-Well...
Ichigo?
I'm beat!
We did walk around a lot.
I'm gonna be so sore tomorrow.
So what was this place, anyway?
If nothing else, we can be sure
that it was part of civilization.
So, people lived here in the past?
They abandoned it.
Humans once lived on the surface,
but then they abandoned it.
There are tons of places
like this around the world.
Woohoo! Food's ready!
Look, meat!
Can I dig in now?
I'm starved.
I can, right?
Wow, this looks good.
Seriously, when did this stuff get here?
Hot, hot, hot...
Jeez, be careful.
You okay?
I'm fine. All good.
Here.
Have some, too.
Whoa, it's roasting.
Let me try it, too!
Hey, darling.
I'm gonna go swim some more, okay?
When it's this dark?
Yeah.
I can't eat any more!
My belly's gonna explode!
Jeez, Miku, everyone's watching.
Where are your manners?
After how much I walked today, I don't care.
Get a load of their envious stares!
Hey, we all walked just the same!
S-So jelly!
Yeah, yeah, keep talking.
Why do you think humanity
abandoned the surface?
Oh, you mean what Zero Two said earlier?
Well, they must've had reasons
they couldn't live out here anymore.
But there's so much more
space and beautiful scenery.
I was surprised to learn there
was a world like this out there.
But we have that in Mistilteinn, too.
Besides, the outside world
is filled with klaxosaurs.
If humanity hadn't started
extracting magma energy,
I wonder if the klaxosaurs
would never have showed up.
Are you doubting Papa and the rest?
They decided to move into plantations in
order to protect mankind from klaxosaurs.
Isn't that a wonderful cause?
Papa and the others really are amazing!
I mean, the adults used to
live in these drab outdoors,
but now they live in bright, sparkling cities!
Yeah, you're right.
And we're the ones protecting their lifestyles!
We're being useful to them!
If we keep killing klaxosaurs,
we'll have food on our table,
and Papa will give us attention!
And one day, we'll surely become adults, too!
Yeah, yeah!
You agree, right, Hiro?
R-Right...
Why so aloof, man?
We're teammates, aren't we?
Teammates?
Huh? Did I say something weird?
Zorome aside,
you two are the newest members.
You'd better put in both your
and Naomi's share of the work.
As for me, I find it very reassuring
that you two are with us.
After all, Zero Two has helped us out a bunch.
You heard 'em.
Hiro.
Allow me to officially welcome
you and Zero Two to Squad 13.
As the leader, I'm going
to work you to the bone.
So you'd best be prepared.
Guys... Thank you!
I'll do my best.
All right!
Hey, look! It's a crab!
What? Where?
Is it edible?
You want to eat even more?
There's one over there, too!
Hold it, crab!
Sorry. Did I wake you?
I couldn't sleep, for some reason.
Same. I felt like it'd be
a waste if I fell asleep.
Look, Hiro! You can see
so many stars in the sky!
You're right.
Oh, hey, it's Orion.
In the past,
Orion was considered the most
prominent winter constellation.
Really?
You used to tell me about the stars
a lot when we were little, too.
Did I?
You did!
I might be stupid, but I remember
everything you taught me!
So... did you forget about that star, too?
You mean the Ichigo star?
The fifteenth star of Orion,
the same as your code.
I read in a book that it's so dark, it can
be difficult to spot with the naked eye.
I guess you really can't see it.
We'd promised we'd see it together
one day after leaving the Garden, too.
Wh-What the heck? You remember it just fine.
Ow.
We can look for the star again sometime.
I mean, we're going to keep
fighting on the same team.
Yeah.
I acted all bossy and said
you'd best be prepared earlier,
but the rest of us have to do our best, too.
You know...
I'm going to give it my all as leader,
so don't give Zero Two all your
attention. Look at me, too.
I...
I see the kiss we shared during the
mock battle as something special!
So I...
I want to be with you forev—
Look, Ichigo! Shooting stars!
With their long tails, the shooting
stars blazed a trail across the sky.
Drawn in by gravity, those stars
shone so brightly, just like us.
The light they gave off looked
to me like gentle rays of hope.
They say if you make a wish on
a shooting star, it'll come true.
What would you wish for?
I tried to say it earlier.
Stupid Hiro.
What the heck?
I wished on the shooting stars that
night for that light to never fade.
Hey! What'd you mean?
Episode 7
Shooting Star Moratorium
The hospitable sky and the welcoming beach
aozora to sunahama ga
are trying to relieve my embarrassement
hazukashi garanakutemo iiyo to sasotteru
But I'm too scared to look at you straight
tiishatsu wo nugou to suru
the moment you take off your t-shirt
kimi kara shisen awatete sorasu
When you're putting on sunscreen under the parasol,
parasoru no shita de hiyakedome nutteru
you look so grown up
kimi ga itsumo yori otona ni miete
Oops, I got thirsty
nodo ga kawaita
I wanna feel more of this excitement unique to summer days
manatsu no setsuna no tokimeki kanjiteitai
Getting soaked through cannot prevent me from enjoying the race with you
namiuchigiwa hashiru kimi wo bisho nure de oikakete
When you look back on me,
isshun furikaetta kimi no hajikeru egao ga
the brilliance of your smile is enough to melt me
boku wo toka shite
I can't hold myself anymore
atama karappo ni natte iku yo