Everything comes to an end eventually.
The only difference is whether
it happens sooner or later.
And even as we sense that the end is nigh,
we spend another day idling
in this cradle of our lives.
Come over here beside me as my restraint crumbles.
Please don't fear me
Ah...
I want to taste you... Does that make me weird?
It's something we're unable to feel all alone
Embracing one another will keep our wounds sealed
So I'll seal your breath with my lips
Will your lips taste the kiss of death?
Darling
ko
dou
ga
yu
Darling, what is this melting feeling
Going from my heart to the tips of my fingers?
nee...
Hey...
Come to me, as our inhibitions crumble
Please don't fear me
Just kiss me now!
Doesn't that hurt?
Not at all.
Miku, I'm ready.
Ta-da!
How's it look?
Perfect. I'm sure Hiro will love it, too.
Hey, we've got trouble!
Hey.
Why are you guys here?
To check on you, on Papa's orders.
Papa's?
So we weren't cast aside?
Of course not!
In fact, Papa has been
worried sick about you.
Th-Thank goodness!
What the heck? Let us know sooner, then!
Thank goodness!
Anyway, this is horrible.
Chore Wheel
Everyone
washes
their
own
undies!
Put
them
in
the
laundry
box
and
you
will
DIE!!
Do
not
take
any
food
or
drinks
from
the
storage
without
telling
anyone!
Make it a
habit to turn
the lights OFF!
Do not leave
lights on when
not in use!
It's no environment for children to live in.
Would you mind readying rooms for us?
You want to stay here?
I said I'd taken a liking
to you guys, remember?
Huh? All the surviving squads
have been gathered in one place?
Yeah, in a camp of sorts.
All of the FRANXX are being
fine-tuned there, too.
I see...
Why were we the only ones left out?
It wasn't what Papa wanted, that's for sure.
Nana and Hachi should know more about it.
I wonder why they didn't tell you anything.
Why are you crying?
I'm just so relieved.
I was so worried that
we'd be left here to die.
You guys are surprisingly nice! Here, eat up!
It's thanks for bringing us good news!
Don't be shy, now.
This stuff is pretty good.
Oh, you've never cooked
for yourselves, have you?
I assumed you were here
to take Zero Two back.
We aren't her babysitters.
Just her squadmates.
Though she didn't exactly
seem pleased to see us.
How long are you going to keep playing human?
You know you'll never be the same as them.
They certainly are a unique squad,
but they're hopelessly imperfect.
They're fundamentally different
from you and us, Iota.
Zero Two.
What?
My name's Zero Two.
You're throwing away the Special
Forces codename Papa gave you?
My darling gave me this name.
It's important to me.
Well, I wish you luck...
Iota.
Zero Two...
What is that?
Oh, Miku made it for me.
Wow.
Don't stare.
It looks great.
On second thought, you may stare.
They've grown bigger.
Do you think they really are horns?
It must be because you rode with me.
Or maybe because you ingested
my blood when we were little.
I've drastically altered
your destiny, haven't I?
Darling...
This actually makes me happy.
It's like I'm the same as you now.
Right.
Y'know, darling,
that picture book is inside me now.
I ate it all when they were
trying to erase my memories.
I didn't want to forget.
I started wanting to become human
because I wanted to see you again.
That's when they told me that I
could do that by killing klaxosaurs.
I shouldn't have believed them.
Papa and the rest told you that?
Hey, show me.
That.
You drew a page too, right?
Uh, n-no, this is...
Let me see.
No!
Lemme see!
What the heck?!
That's why I didn't want to show you!
This page is approved!
Are you serious?
I love this picture.
You okay?
Y-Yes. Thank you.
What are you doing?
Exploring the place.
Don't tell the others, okay?
Understood.
Have a good night.
Your First Childbirth
Whats Best for Your Baby
Reproduction, childbirth,
fetus...
It's all stuff Papa hasn't taught anyone.
Since the Nines are here now,
someone will surely come
to get us eventually.
Will that mean the end of this life?
That is the natural assumption.
But I'd be a bit sad to leave this place.
I mean, we only began spending time
together like this after I came here.
Mitsuru...
Kokoro?
Your body is much tougher than a girl's.
It's so strange...
Boys and girls have such different bodies.
There really is a reason for this.
What are you talking about?
Well... I read that a boy and a girl
can create a new life by
joining their bodies together.
U-Uh...
I believe that represents hope for us.
What are you doing, Kokoro?
I...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Did you two just try to
stick your bodies together?
What, are you imitating Hiro and Zero Two?
D-Did you need something?
Huh? Oh, yeah. You're on
water duty today, remember?
A-Anyway, what were you two—
I'll go get the water now, okay?
Wh-What the heck, man?
Hurry it up, would you?
Why did you do that out of nowhere?
It wasn't out of nowhere. I've been
thinking about it for a long time.
Huh?
Hiro...
I don't understand what Kokoro's thinking.
I see...
You've changed a little, huh?
Until now, you'd been
distancing yourself from us.
But that was all my fault, wasn't it?
Because I broke our promise.
But now, you've taken an interest in someone.
You want to know Kokoro better.
You want to understand what she's thinking.
I want to know Kokoro better?
Yeah. And that's probably what
it means to love someone.
I mean, I love Zero Two,
and I want to know her better.
Oh... I love Kokoro...
Sorry if I'm mistaken.
Unfortunately, I can only
tell you how it is for me.
No, I think that's very much like you.
I'm glad I got to have a nice
chat with you after so long.
Oh, there he is.
Zorome told us about you and Kokoro, Mitsuru.
I have to say, I'm not really surprised.
All I did was ask if a boy and a girl
getting all clingy was the cool thing to do!
Shut up, you big baby!
H-Hey, have you k-kissed?
Have you two kissed?!
W-Well...
N-No! My Kokoro!
Settle down.
B-But if the two of them are happy, I... I...
Hey, guys.
Do you recognize this?
Your First Childbirth
Whats Best for Your Baby
Looks like you do.
Your First Childbirth
Whats Best for Your Baby
Mind giving us an explanation,
Your First Childbirth
Whats Best for Your Baby
Code 556?
Your First Childbirth
Whats Best for Your Baby
You're the one who dropped this, aren't you?
But this is really strange.
It wouldn't have been
provided in the study here,
and it surely doesn't belong to you.
What's the meaning of this?
Huh? What is that?
What's that book about?
Well...
I'm sorry for not telling you all.
I want to make a baby.
A baby?
Like animal babies?
And how exactly would you make one?
Wow. But you do know that
Papa's banned that, right?
Huh? Really? Sounds like trouble!
Did she tell you anything?
Y-You know,
is that really such a bad thing?
I mean, that's how the adults, we,
and all humans were born.
What? Didn't Papa create us?
No. We're the same as any other animal.
It's what we've done since ancient times.
That's how all living things have kept
their species going for thousands of years.
So, well...
That must be why we have boys and girls.
This may be selfish of me,
but I want to leave a mark—leave
something behind before I'm gone.
Leave a mark?
Yes.
We've lived our lives believing our only
purpose was to ride the FRANXX into battle.
But you know what?
That might not be true!
We could carry new lives and
leave them here for the future.
When I learned about that, I was so happy...
Disgusting.
You are absolutely disgusting.
This is ridiculous.
Humans have evolved and cast their
reproductive functions aside in the process.
Reject that, and we'll all have to go
back to conforming to one gender.
B-But...
Doesn't the thought often cross your mind?
That gender is a pain, an annoyance that's
only tolerated to operate the FRANXX?
And that's all it really is.
That's...
Ikuno?!
A pain?
So what if it's a pain?!
Humans have also cast away their tendency
to be ruled by emotions like that.
Because it serves zero purpose in life.
And yet, look at you people...
Why, you!
Cut it out!
Calm down, Ikuno!
Let me go!
That's enough!
Nana! Hachi!
This is why I didn't want
to let the Nines in!
I knew it'd be nothing but trouble!
Papa sent them. We couldn't
just turn them away.
Now that things have come to this,
we ought to put an end to this test.
What do you mean?
It was on the doctor's orders that we
didn't contact you over the past month.
He said it was to be Squad 13's final test.
Of course, we still monitored
you the entire time.
We know what you were trying
to do with Mitsuru, too.
You want to make a baby?
That's something nobody is allowed
to even speak of, let alone do.
But...
Why do our bodies still have
reproductive organs, then?
Because they're necessary
for piloting the FRANXX.
That's why only children have them.
That's all there is to it.
Don't think your squad is special.
What about these feelings, then?
Why do we still have emotions?!
Quiet!
Nana...
Shut up!
Return to the dorm. We'll give
you your orders in due time.
When did it start?
A week or so ago.
Watching them go about their lives
made me feel so irritated, and...
Oh? Did you relapse into puberty?
N-No!
Puberty? Me? Never!
Didn't you two already undergo emotional
indoctrination when you were parasites?
Relapsing is really bad news.
You should have her replaced with a new Nana.
I hope you go back to doing
your actual job from now on,
instead of getting up to
mischief with the doctor.
I'll be reporting this to Papa and the rest.
Oh, so Nana is useless now?
I believe continuing the
test will be difficult.
I'm sure.
But I gained some intriguing data.
The development of humanity's
original reproductive instincts...
That's far beyond my expectations.
This is development that differs greatly
from human civilization and culture.
I never expected the klaxosaurs
to still possess such technology.
It is a great pleasure to meet you,
Princess of the Klaxosaurs.
Humans and klaxosaurs have waged
a war spanning close to a century,
and you have shown truly
admirable spirit and fortitude.
But it is now time for this protracted war
to be consigned to the history books.
You no longer stand any chance of victory.
Cease your resistance at once,
and surrender to us.
Are these words? Sent directly to the brain?
What? What are you saying?!
That can't be!
Prepare to die, Princess of the Klaxosaurs!
N-No... Don't...
Wait!
N-No! This isn't what we wanted!
We only came here to ask you to surrender.
Damned human wannabes.
Kokoro sure is taking a while to return.
Yeah...
I had no idea Kokoro had that on her mind.
I wish she'd talked to me about it.
Everyone has things they can't talk about.
Do you think we really can make babies?
Who knows? We weren't taught about it.
And if Papa didn't create us,
how exactly were we born?
Again, how are we supposed to know?!
What do you think, Hiro?
I'm not sure.
But we may have the potential to do
something Papa hasn't told us about.
You mean what Kokoro said?
To leave something for the future...
The future...
The future, huh?
I'm so envious.
Envious? About what?
The leaving something behind part.
My body can't do that.
Zero Two...
It's wonderful.
You're all wonderful.
You have the ability to decide
your futures with your own hearts.
Kokoro...
I was wrong about everything.
I'm sorry I tried to force
you to go along with it.
I'm so sorry.
Don't apologize.
You weren't forcing me to do anything.
Liar!
Don't bother trying to be nice.
Just leave me alone.
No!
Don't decide things on your own!
Lean on me more!
I want to make you happy!
Mitsuru, is it such a bad
thing to create a new life?
Aren't we allowed to think about the future?
Everything comes to an end eventually.
The only difference is whether
it happens sooner or later.
As for what comes after that,
we know nothing.
Nothing at all.
So the klaxosaur princess chose to
go down the path of annihilation?
So foolish.
And now, they'll feel the pain of having
their earth scorched by their own creation.
We're back, Papa.
There's something you need to know.
Episode 17
Eden
We're getting drenched in the unexpected rain
yohou hazure no ame ga bokura wo nurashite
What should I tell you as I see you tremble?
furueteru kimi ni nani wo hanashitara ii no
Wet to the skin, we feel so cold, so heavy
bishonure no burezaa ga tsumetakute omotakute
Helpless like a bird who just left its cage
kago wo deta hinadori no muryokusa wo kanjiteru
I was so close to my dreams and now they're beyond the clouds
sawaresou datta yume wa buatsui kumo no mukou de
All that's left in my heart is bittersweet pain
mune ni hirogaru amai itami dake kamishimeta
Maybe we shouldn't have met after all
boku to kimi wa deawanai hou ga yokatta ka na
I can't even see the stars...
nee hoshi sae mienai yo
I can't even shed any tears
nee namida mo dete konai