Plantation #13
『
』
Cerasus
This mission has but one objective:
taking control of the area
known as Gran Crevasse.
Internal Briefing Room
The 4th United Company is
currently carrying out attacks,
but due to klaxosaur resistance,
they're not making inroads.
Squad 13 is to group up with squads
from four other plantations
and take part in the mission
as the 6th United Company.
What exactly is in Gran Crevasse?
This might prove shocking to
you kids, but take a look.
What's that? A black wall?
What the hell? What's going on there?
No way...
That's awful.
This battle is clearly on a different
scale than all our prior ones.
Taking over Gran Crevasse is
Papa's long-standing wish.
This battle could be a turning
point in humanity's history.
H-Hey, look.
Mobile Aerial Fortress
『
』
Cosmos
『
』
Cosmos
APE Central HQ Council
She devoured them all? I should've known.
Silly hellcat.
We're almost there.
If we can take over Gran Crevasse,
we may finally have our wish!
Hringhorni's construction
is proceeding smoothly, too.
If we have them both, we can bury
those pests once and for all.
The time has come!
Where are you going, Werner?
I can't sit around here.
I want to watch it all happen
from a front-row seat.
Zero Two?
DARLING
in the
FRANXX
DARLING
in the
FRANXX
DARLING
in the
FRANXX
DARLING
in the
FRANXX
DARLING
in the
FRANXX
DARLING
in the
FRANXX
DARLING
in the
FRANXX
DARLING
in the
FRANXX
DARLING
in the
FRANXX
Damn it!
Near Gran Crevasse
There are so many of them, we can't link up!
What?
Hold on! I'll be right—
Don't!
Was that Strelizia?
Wh-What?
9’s Custom FRANXX
Hey. Good job hanging in there.
You did well, for humans.
『
』
M9
We'll take over here,
so you can chill in the rear.
Message from Mission Command.
Plantation 13 Command Room
The 6th United Company
is to prepare for sortie.
You're up, kids!
I repeat:
the 6th United Company
is to prepare for sortie.
All right. We're gonna go
kick some klaxosaur butt.
Leave my food alone, okay, Hiro?
Don't look so down.
No need to worry. We'll be fine.
I am...
Right.
Sit tight and wait, Hiro.
Once this battle is over, I'll teach you
how to pilot from the ground up.
Where am I?
Please come back alive, guys.
6th United FRANXX Company
Your goal is Point F2.
All units, move out!
You scrubs aren't even good for a warm-up!
Doesn't matter how many of you there are.
How boring.
Entertain us more!
Let's go, guys.
That's one lot down.
Wow. It's like we have a bunch of Strelizias.
We're joining in.
I really wasn't expecting these numbers.
There's no end to them.
Hey, Alpha. Look over there.
Who's that?
The children of Squad 13.
Alpha's shiny new toys.
Hey. So that's your FRANXX.
How truly adorable.
Gee, thanks.
So, what's the situation?
We're holding them off just fine,
but we're not getting anywhere.
You see that over there?
The Crevasse has been sealed
off inside a thick dome.
To get rid of it, we'll have
to strike from the inside.
So basically...
We have to go through there, huh?
Let's go, guys.
Argentea and Genista, follow my lead!
Chlorophytum, provide cover fire!
I'm going to disappear
Roger!
We're going full power!
Right on!
Wh-What was that?
I've never seen anyone fight like that.
It's Squad 13.
As ever, they're all over the place.
But I'm glad they're here!
Let's take this chance to regroup, everyone!
Yeah!
Mitsuru!
Here we go!
I see it!
Wait, is that man-made?
We're going in through that hole, guys!
Wh-What?
The klaxosaurs are fleeing.
Detecting magma energy readings underground.
Reanalyzing signals.
Oh? There was something like
that hidden down there?
Ascertained to be Super Lehmann-Class.
A Super Lehmann-Class?
I've never even heard of that.
Th...
The mountains moved!
Plantation 26... Our home...
Crap! It's going around destroying plantations!
Super Lehmann-Class Klaxosaur
moving from point E3.
Three plantations lie
on its estimated course.
Get Code 090 on the line.
We're moving to Protocol 32.
Did you say Protocol 32?
Is something wrong?
N-No...
Code 090,
this is a great honor, you know?
I... understand.
Super Lehmann-Class klaxosaur
heading right for us.
We estimate contact in 240 seconds.
It's going to hit us head-on!
This is bad! It's heading
toward Plantation 13!
S-Say what?
Well, what now?
That's...
I see.
All units, Protocol 32.
Roger.
This is for the best, right?
Squad 13, the rest is in your hands.
Wh-What the hell?
I-It stopped!
No...
O-Our home...
We're going to go defend it!
Yeah!
Zero Two?!
The line is blurring
Somebody
Get me out of here
Raise the bulwarks!
If we lose this place, we're done for!
That's right. Neutralizing the Super
Lehmann-Class is our top priority.
Doctor, it isn't safe here.
Please return to HQ.
Papa and the others will
take care of Gran Crevasse.
You get back to Mistilteinn, too, Hiro!
Don't you find her far more
beautiful than any human?
Pure and proud, and more alone than us all.
She's like a klaxosaur, through and through.
No! Zero Two is no klaxosaur!
I thought she'd finally found a partner.
Plantation 13
Inner City
The poor girl.
Jeez! How many more do we have to kill?!
Quit whining, fatty! We've gotta
protect our plantation!
Don't call me that!
Hey, fire more of those beams from earlier.
I don't have the energy for that!
I've used up all the reserves, too!
What? Don't be cheap!
Don't fight. We must work together.
My, how scary. She's in a foul mood today.
The thought of getting on that unseemly
beast's bad side gives me chills.
Zero Two...
Zero Two.
What were you trying to tell me back then?
What am I...
Who...
What am I hesitating for?!
...am I?
We're being pushed back.
We can't let them get any farther!
Out of ammo?
If we ain't got ammo,
use the arms!
H-Hey!
Damn you.
We can't give in! We must defend this city!
Hey, Ichigo.
Ichigo, behind us!
Stay focused, Ichigo.
Sorry.
Wh-What the...
What's a training unit doing here?
Whoa!
Wh-What's this?
W-Wait...
Is that Hiro?
That guy...
When was it that I stopped asking questions?
Back then, all I wanted was to
learn about the outside world.
I wanted to set foot outside of Garden.
I was always fighting alone.
Nobody took a stand with me,
and that scared me.
But when I saw you,
I realized there were others
fighting this world with me.
Zero Two,
I want to tell you.
And that made me so, so happy!
It has to be you.
Without you...
Without you, I can't fight.
I need you!
Why'd you come, Hiro?
What can you do in a training unit?
I'm not letting you go.
Wh-What?
H-Hey, Goro!
That's enough.
But...
I can't stand watching Hiro and
Zero Two like this anymore.
Get in, Hiro.
You have something to tell her, don't you?
Ichigo, get Hiro to Zero Two.
You're worried about her too, aren't you?
I'm sorry, Ichigo.
All of this boy and girl
stuff is such a pain.
Let's do it!
Hiro's mind is entering mine.
Won't you be my darling?
You were incredible, darling.
Piece of cake, right?
What are these?
You wanna ride me, huh?
Hiro's memories?
I can get you out of here, darling.
What'll it be? If you want off
this ride, now's your chance.
I'm going monster hunting, of course.
No... Don't show me this.
Do you think I'm a monster, too?
I'm finally connected to Hiro, but this is...
Because I'm a monster, maybe?
You're only my fodder, after all!
You are now...
Wait for me, Zero Two!
My darling!
I'm coming to you!
...I'm coming to you
Well, damn it. It's all about her...
Here we go, Hiro!
Yeah!
Good luck, bro.
What're you acting all cool for?
i preTended to Be, humaN
buT tHat gam'Es ov3r nOw
tHe 1ine is b1urring
How I longed to be human...
whO...... Am i?
Zero Two!
I-Ichigo? Why?!
I'm so sick of how you toy with me!
Stop it, Ichigo!
I wish...
I wish we'd never known you!
I'll let you have Hiro, so get
your act together already!
Zero Two, it's me.
I came to see you.
Keep Strelizia safe!
I hate to admit it, but only
Strelizia can kill that big lug!
Their numbers are going down.
But stay alert.
I've never killed so many before.
Hey, Miku. Something dropped.
What is this?
It looks like a human.
What? D-Don't be stupid!
Y-Yeah! It can't be—
An explosion?
What the hell is this?
Plantation 37's backup process
is 98 percent complete.
They can go.
Let's release them from
the cages of their bodies.
What's going on?
W-Weren't adults still in there?
Are they making the
plantations self-destruct?
There it goes.
It seems Papa and the rest are planning
to end this without Strelizia's help.
How many more will be sacrificed?
Who goes that far?
Of all the foolish...
Yeah, no response.
That means...
Sorry, Zero Two. I'm going to touch you.
Please, just one more time...
Take me to where you are!
Code 016's memory alteration is complete.
But 002 had some areas we couldn't erase.
It felt like there was something
strong protecting them.
Erase those memories. They're noise.
But repeated use of the device will
put her under too much strain.
It matters not.
What do we do with Code 016?
Return him to the Garden.
He's probably useless now
that he's ingested her blood.
But he's an interesting specimen.
I didn't want to forget.
Because I thought I'd
never be human if I did.
The first word I learned was the
way he referred to himself, "I."
After that came "Zero Two."
And the third...
And then, I'll be your darling!
...never let go, darling.
...was "darling."
Dalin!
You never forgot, huh?
I think I've taken a liking to you.
Won't you be my darling?
You are now...
My darling!
Even as you were hurt so badly,
you kept fighting this
world all by yourself.
I'm here for you.
D-Darling?
I finally got to see you!
D-Don't look at me!
Aren't you scared of me?
I used you, you know.
That doesn't matter anymore!
But... But I called you fodder!
And I called you a monster!
So we're even now.
That's right. I am a monster.
So...
That's not it! We've gotta talk it out!
We've gotta think it out!
There must be places we have to go!
Our journey begins now!
This world is surely much, much
larger than we can ever imagine!
We couldn't do it back then,
but this time, for sure,
let's go see the outside world together!
Zero Two...
Together, we are one.
How much longer, Hiro?
Crap!
Strelizia!
Look!
Come over here beside me. My restraint crumbles
soba ni kite kuzureyuku yokusei
That light...
Doctor...
He did it?
Don't be scared
boku wo kowagaranai de
Strelizia!
Ah...
Zero Two!
Darling!
A flightless bird dreamed of the sky
tobenai tori ga yumemita sora
Darling!
This thickly mixed love is a differently colored red
majiwatte koi Love sore wa chigau Red
Darling...
I'm really happy I met you!
I covered my ears to the sound of knocking on my door
doa wo tataku oto ni boku wa mimi wo fusaida
I love you!
Me too, Zero Two!
Is that you knocking? Or is it someone else...
tataiteru no wa kimi soretomo hoka no
I love you!
Cut the comms, dumbass.
Will your lips taste the kiss of death?
Seriously.
Those stupid idiots!
Darling, fate runs through my veins
Darling unmei ga kekkan wo hashiru yo
I'm happy for you two.
Zero Two, we need to destroy that dome.
Think we can?
If we're together, of course we can!
As this world begins to move (Love)
ugokihajimeta sekai ai
Shall we get going too, then?
I want to be your closest partner, Darling
dare yori mo tokeaitai yo Darling
Go!
So don't be scared,
boku wo kowagaranaide
Kiss me now!
I felt a something like the moment of death
shi wa yuku toki to nita
With your taste
kankaku to kimi no aji ga shita
It's time.
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Did your lips taste the kiss of death?
Darling, fate runs through my veins
Darling unmei ga kekkan wo hashiru yo
Wow...
As this world begins to move (Love)
ugokihajimeta sekai ai
The door to Gran Crevasse has been opened.
The day of humanity's liberation is upon us.
I want to be your closest partner, Darling
dare yori mo tokeaitai yo Darling
The Jian, also known as
"the bird that shares wings"...
...only possesses one wing.
So don't be scared,
boku wo kowagaranaide
Unless a male and female pair
lean on each other and act as one...
...they're incapable of flight.
They're imperfect, incomplete creatures.
Let me taste you
kimi wo ajiwasete
But...
To me...
Their way of life
Kiss me now!
struck me as profoundly beautiful.
Episode 15
Jian
Hey, look at that.
They won't let it end so easily, huh?
Is that a collective mass of cores?
Damn, that's huge.
We're out of time.
We'd better get out of here
before this entire area blows.
Let's go, Zero Two!
Right!
Wow, an instant reaction.
W-We're still alive...
But what was that?
A massive hand?