Current distance to klaxosaur group:
approximately 4000.
Bulwark in the last line of
defense now 85 percent complete.
ETA is still 0210 hours.
Estimated to be complete by 2200 hours.
Squads 26 and 13 are to stand
by for combat by 2030 hours.
They're moving in a pack.
Then that huge thing could
likely be a klaxosaur, too.
But I've never seen one like it before.
Episode 6
DARLING in the FRANXX
Are you really going to fight?
Yeah.
You complete fool.
I heard the klaxosaur numbers
are higher than estimated.
Do you think we'll be able
to come back here alive?
If nothing else, it won't be like
anything we've experienced before.
We can just let Squad 26 handle everything.
Y'know, since we're dead weight, apparently.
You're being awfully timid for once.
We can't afford to be too optimistic,
given the difference in numbers.
Hey, don't go wimping out on us now.
We've got me, Zorome the Great, on our side.
Zorome aside, we can count
on Strelizia this time.
Anyway, we're not letting
Squad 26 hog the glory.
That's not who you should be fighting.
Where's Hiro?
Still inside.
You should probably talk to him.
Go on.
Wai—
Ichigo?
Uh, well...
The operation starts late at night.
Did you get enough sleep?
You might get drowsy midway otherwise.
Nah, I was too wide awake.
I see.
Actually, I couldn't sleep much, either.
But I felt better once I took a bath.
Yeah.
Uh...
Ichigo...
Wh-What?
Let's make sure this operation succeeds.
Y-Yeah, let's.
Being a leader isn't easy,
but I know you're up to the task.
I'm counting on you.
I-I'm counting on you plenty, too!
I mean, you know, I...
I've always...
Sorry. You've always what?
I...
I've always thought of you as a sibling.
Yeah, same here.
I'm sure Goro feels the same, too.
Ichigo, do your best as leader.
Together with Goro.
How'd it go?
He sends his regards to you.
That guy...
Goro...
In this operation, we're going to save
Strelizia for as late as possible.
Got it.
It's time, darling.
Yeah.
Open force gate. Open force gate.
Lift carrier, proceed slowly at zero point five.
On the double.
Open force gate.
Numbers Two through Five are to
deploy in gamma quartet formation.
Crimping boosters decompressing.
I repeat: deploy in gamma quartet formation.
All FRANXX good to go. Code Beta's
alt mode yet unconfirmed.
Clear weather.
Temperature is 22.6 degrees Celsius.
Amending enemy's approach route.
Estimated point of contact unchanged.
Wind blowing from northeast
at 81 meters per second.
Safety systems all green.
We have updated intel on the klaxosaurs.
Aside from the Conrad-class pack, we've also
detected a large, tightly packed unit.
It didn't match any of the
ones we have on record,
but we've deemed it a klaxosaur
due to its independent movement
and codenamed it Target Beta.
It's huge!
The heck is that thing?
There are so many of the smaller ones, too.
Since we lack data on it,
attacking it would be reckless.
As such, prioritize wiping out the
Conrad-class pack once you engage.
090 will have field command.
Understood.
It's time. All FRANXX, commence operation.
Strelizia, stand by where you are.
Roger!
Let's go, Squad 26.
Yeah!
Focus on defeating in detail.
As long as we deal with them
calmly, we won't lose.
How many did we let through?
Three...
No, four!
Take care of them, Squad 13.
But be careful not to stray too far ahead.
If you move around haphazardly,
you could affect our coordination, as well.
If you think we're a hindrance,
come out and say it! Damn it...
I never thought we'd be seen
as such a big liability.
It's the truth. We're still green as hell.
Squad 26 has to carry us in their
arms, piggyback, you name it.
Say what?
Here they come.
We must stop them here.
Hold still, damn it!
What are you doing?
You put too much behind that attack!
Damn you! Keep your grubby paws off Kokoro!
Pull yourself together.
Thanks, Ichigo.
Zorome, bait the enemy
without getting too close.
You have the speed.
You don't have to tell me!
Mitsuru, stay close to Genista and back it up.
Ichigo, you shouldn't get worked up, too.
Code 015, huh?
What's such a skilled teen code doing in a
makeshift test team? They even have 016.
Second wave approaching.
Here they come. Don't let them through.
Take a look, darling.
Their tactics are all over the place.
A huge contrast to the
precision of the other squad.
Are you saying they're being pushed back?
They're barely hanging in there.
Man, I'm starting to get the itch.
I wanna join the fight already.
Why do you fight the klaxosaurs?
You always look like you're having fun,
so I was wondering if you have a reason.
A reason, huh?
Because I'm a monster, maybe?
How about you?
Uh, me?
To protect Papa and all the adults
in the plantations, I guess.
That's it?
That's it.
After all, that's our entire purpose in life.
Huh... How lame.
If they need help, we should move out.
Yeah.
Strelizia's here!
Tch. Her again.
Why'd you come out here? Don't ignore orders.
I'm just here to help my squad!
You can't do whatever the hell you want—
Damn it!
What do we do?
Ignore them.
Let's take it out in one fell swoop.
Whoa...
That's some teamwork.
Is that all you've got, darling?
Yes, good. That's the way.
Get back, Strelizia!
It's fine. We can still go.
Shut up and get back to your post!
So bossy.
Target Beta has breached the
second line of defense.
Squad 26 resupplying complete.
Understood. Leave the combat zone at once.
So it's not going to stop, huh?
We're going to attack Target Beta now.
Releasing safety on the
absolute cutter cartridges.
Be careful.
Safety release confirmed.
How exactly is it going to attack?
It doesn't have any limbs.
Good. It's working.
Now!
What?
What is that noise?
A shriek?
Look!
A-A humanoid form?!
This can't be happening.
A Gutenberg-class?!
This is bad news.
You're not getting any closer!
All units, we're trying again!
Crap.
Everyone fall back!
We're out of fuel?!
Quit spacing out!
You owe me one, okay?
Thank you.
All Squad 26 units fall back.
Squad 13 will deal with the Gutenberg-class.
Easier said than done.
How are we supposed to
stop something so massive?
Just stopping it would be meaningless.
We must kill it, or it'll breach
the wall and that'll be that.
We can do this if we link up with Strelizia.
Yeah, I think that's our only choice.
It doesn't matter how we do it.
We gotta show them
that our squad can handle things ourselves!
Got it. You can count on me.
Wait.
Stay where you are, Strelizia.
What?
We can't do this without them!
Do you have a plan in mind, Ichigo?
We'll have Strelizia land the finishing blow.
This is no time to hold anything back!
Calm down, Zorome.
Only Strelizia's spear can reach
that massive thing's core.
Goro...
So we're going to create an
opening for Strelizia to strike.
Isn't that what you mean, Ichigo?
Oh, y-yeah.
Let's show them what we're made of.
O-Okay, that makes sense.
You heard that, right, Hiro? Finish it off.
Got it.
Squad 13, move out!
Thanks, Goro.
Just focus on the task at hand.
Okay.
All right!
Here we go!
Bear with it! Be a man!
You give it your all, too!
Of course! I'm not gonna let
anyone call me dead weight again!
Futoshi!
We must set things up for
Strelizia, no matter what.
I know, I know!
Does it hurt, darling?
But this won't end until we kill that thing.
You can do it, right?
Yeah, of course.
Hiro!
Now!
I'm gonna finish this in one blow!
Get in there!
We did it...
Hiro!
Run!
Link between Code 002 and Code 016 broken.
No!
We had to run out of time now?
Hiro! Zero Two!
Come in!
Hey, Hiro!
Hiro...
Hiro's dead!
Ichigo!
Pull yourself together!
Hey, Hiro! What are you doing?!
No way.
Was that rumor true?
We must save them quickly!
What's worse, it'll break through
the wall if we don't do something.
W-We gotta stop it!
I couldn't tell him...
I couldn't tell him not to pilot.
Pull yourself together!
This is no time to be crying!
We gotta look out for
our own lives right now!
Oh... I died.
I did everything I could, right?
There you go again, feeling satisfied
and giving up all by yourself.
You're not even trying to
listen to your partner.
I didn't give up. This is
just as far as I can go.
It's not like when we split up.
Besides, I'm sure Zero Two
can keep fighting without me.
That's how she's fought all this time.
But are you okay with that?
I got to pilot a FRANXX
right at the very end.
I got to be of use to everyone.
So I have no regrets.
Liar.
Where is this?
Zero Two...
You came to say goodbye to me?
Thanks to you, I got to find
a place for myself again.
It wasn't for long, but I
belonged as a child once more.
Wait.
Why do you look so sad?
Huh? What?
Wait, we didn't kill it? No way...
Why, you... You're nothing but a monster!
Don't, Zero Two. You can't do this alone.
If you keep going, even you'll die.
Why do you go so far to fight?
Because I'm a monster, maybe?
Is this how it's always been for you?
Once you lose your partner,
you fight all alone?
You can't fly by yourself, either?
I'm always alone
I'm always alone,
Thanks to these horns
thanks to these horns.
What the hell is wrong with me?
What am I doing when Zero Two's
suffering in front of my eyes?
I want to help you.
I want to ride with you in Strelizia again.
My wings...
exist for you!
Dar... ling?
I'm your partner.
I'm not going to leave you all alone.
Hiro... He's still alive!
Hiro...
Hiro's vitals have returned to normal!
What is going on?
Oh?
Doctor?
It's changing forms again!
We can't let it.
Don't just stand around, Ichigo!
This is our chance!
It's our turn now!
Let's help them out!
Create another opening for Strelizia!
Yeah!
Hiro!
Zero Two!
Let's fly!
Yeah!
With our wings!
Wings?
That boy might just make
Zero Two's wish come true.
Zero Two.
Hmm?
I've found another reason to pilot a FRANXX.
Really? What is it?
I want to be your wings.
Though I don't know what'll happen next time.
I'm sure you'll be fine next time,
the time after that, and many more times.
Through the window of my classroom, I ask the skies
kyoushitsu no madogoshi ni bonyari to sora ni tou
The Jian, also known as
"the bird that shares wings,"
Why am I alive?
nani no tame boku wa ikiteiru no?
only possesses one wing.
Because I do not know
wakannai yo
When a male and female pair
lean on each other and act as one,
The dream I once depicted on the margin of the textbook
kyoukasho no yohaku ni kaita risou no boku wa
they can fly as high and as far as they want.
If I can be your wings,
Was never a puppet of the adults
otona tachi no iinari janai
It was like a soaring bird with true freedom
tobu tori no you na jiyuu ga atte
then even if my life burns out,
I'll keep leaning on you right here.
Why did they show me the future
yume wo miseta kuse ni
If they never meant to let me realize it?
kanaereru chikara wo
They were so cruel
ataete kurenai nante tsuraku naru dake da yo
I can't even decide the length of my skirt
sukaato no take sae
Because that may be my purpose in life.
Let alone pursue my dream
kimerareta nagasa de
Where is my true self?
yaritai koto mo dekizu ni boku wa doko ni iru no
I have to kill more and more klaxosaurs.
Well, well.
You're certainly hitting it off,
Nine Iota.