I have the same dream over and over again.
In it, I'm surrounded by
darkness for some reason,
staring at a distant
bright light, and crying.
I dunno if these are tears of sorrow or joy,
but they continue to flow endlessly.
Gradually, the light grows
larger until it envelops me,
and I let out a loud scream.
Now!
Finish it off, Strelizia!
Right!
Sit back and relax, Hiro!
This is my time to shine!
Gotcha now!
See that? Piece of cake!
H-Hey, hurry up and get out of...
Why, you...
Come over here beside me. My restraint crumbles
Don't be scared
Ah...
A flightless bird dreamed of the sky
This thickly mixed love is a differently colored red
Love
I covered my ears to the sound of knocking on my door
Is that you knocking? Or is it someone else...
Will you leave just a kiss of death?
Darling, fate runs through my veins
k
e
a
n
Darling
Darling
As this world begins to move (Love)
I want to be your closest partner, Darling
Darling
So don't be scared...
Just kiss me now!
My, how intriguing.
It's so strange.
Regardless of how they do it, they're
linking up in ways other squads cannot.
Does this mean the imbalances
caused by individualized FRANXX
can give a unique asset
to the squad as a whole?
But that's also a double-edged sword.
The future we at APE exalt is
one of calmness and uniformity.
So you say they are imperfect? How ironic.
I'm thinking it's high time we
moved them on to the next stage.
To that area, you mean?
We've detected klaxosaur activity in the
depths of the Grand Crevasse area recently.
It is Squad 13's duty to bring
Code 002 there safe and sound.
The plan is already in motion.
We must have them undergo
maintenance in the lab at once.
Before that, why don't
we award them something?
You mean... reward the children?
Awards have been the most common way
to inspire soldiers since ancient times.
It may prove more effective with them,
as their way of life reflects a bygone era.
Ah, that's an interesting idea.
I shall allow it.
Can we drop this already?
I apologized, didn't I?
You did?
You think that was an apology?
Your heart wasn't in it at all!
They're still at it?
Oh? And how can you be so sure it wasn't?
Can you read my mind? Can you?
Zero Two, what's wrong?
Just thinking about something.
Apologize right now!
Over my dead body!
Grr! I'm gonna kill you if
it's the last thing I do!
I'd love to see you try!
Come on, come on.
Can't touch me!
Jeez, hold it!
Ow! Stop, stop!
Kids, we need to talk.
I bring good news.
Tomorrow, all of you are to
dress in your formal attire
and gather in front of the
boarding house at 0900 hours.
Got that?
Formal?
What's happening?
Papa values what you've achieved
in battle so far very highly.
As such, though there is
very little precedent,
all of you are going to be awarded medals.
M-Medals?
What are those?
The ceremony will be held tomorrow,
in the Plantation Parliament HQ.
Really, Nana?
Wait, does that mean...
W-We did it, Zorome! Aren't you glad?
Huh? What are you talking about?
You idiot!
This means we'll be allowed into the city!
Hooray!
My ears! Quit yelling!
He must be really happy.
How can I not?
As he should be. This is what
he's been working toward.
Wait, Zero Two.
What?
This is convenient timing.
I'll arrange for you to undergo
tests while we're there.
I hate those tests.
I always feel lousy after I take them.
Besides, I'm in great shape right now.
So I'll pass on the tests for a while.
Here I thought she'd grown more obedient
since she teamed up with a certain someone.
We haven't worn these since
the welcoming ceremony.
Zorome, you're really owning that look today.
You look pretty mature.
Right?
He spent all morning checking
himself out in the mirror.
I don't understand how you
don't get bored of that.
Say what?
But you do look better than usual.
Right? Right?
Don't flatter him, Kokoro.
With boys, it goes straight to their heads.
Shut it!
Good morning. Everyone here?
Come on. Hurry up.
Whoa!
Plantation: Inner City
Central Tower
Plantation Parliament HQ
You are the first children
to ever be welcomed here.
This is a truly great honor.
I hope you consider this day a
source of pride for a long time,
live up to this honor bestowed upon you,
and make even further contributions
to this plantation.
Are you the team leader?
Yes! I'm Code 015!
You have achieved great things.
It shows that you're an excellent leader.
Thank you very much!
But I couldn't have done it alone!
Everyone in the squad contributed!
Plantation 13 is honored that a former
Nine like yourself has joined us.
And you've done well to live up to
all the expectations placed upon you.
Th-Thank you very much.
Thank you for defending us adults.
Papa is overjoyed by what you've done.
Your efforts have been splendid, too.
Keep it up.
I-I will, sir! Thank you very much!
Well, I'm going to visit
R&D before I head back.
Take care of the children.
Got it.
What?
That was it?
Well, yes.
That was over too soon.
I was expecting some kind of feast.
Too bad.
Hey, since we have the chance,
why don't we walk back?
Agreed!
It wasn't that far.
We can walk, right, Nana?
Oh, all right.
This is so great.
When I become an adult someday,
I'll get to live here too, right?
But I just can't picture us
"becoming adults," for some reason.
Same here, actually.
There's no proof that
we'll be able to, anyway.
That's because you guys have no imagination.
Imagination?
What you're talking about
is called "delusion."
You can say that again!
Zero Two, you called this city
lifeless before, remember?
What did you mean by that?
Exactly what I said.
You've been acting a little weird today.
Did something happen?
Nothing.
I just couldn't care less about this place.
I've never seen it from so close before!
It's so pretty!
That's the main energy
source for this plantation.
Right, Ichi—
Should I not have done that, after all?
Huh? Wh-What do you mean?
Telling you how I felt was
a selfish act on my part.
So please, don't let it bother you.
Okay.
We're heading back now.
Yes, ma'am.
Hup.
Awesome!
What?!
Seriously?
What a day...
Why isn't anybody here? Are they all asleep?
There's one!
Hey! Excuse me!
What? Why?
Oh, you've come to?
Thank goodness.
You didn't wake up even after I treated you,
so I was a bit worried.
Th-Th-Thank you so much!
You know how your body and other things
are a little different from ours?
The medical checker just
wouldn't work on you.
But I tried a bunch of things,
like using pet mode settings,
and then it worked out.
Am I in...
Is this an adult's home?
Oh... S-Sorry.
My...
That must've been rough.
They're so heartless.
Don't worry. I'll send word right away.
U-Um...
Before you do, could we just talk for a bit?
You see, I've always looked up to adults,
so I have a bunch of questions and stuff.
Very well. Let us have a little chat, then.
I'll make us some tea.
What are you doing?
Disinfecting.
Huh...
Go ahead. Help yourself.
Did you like it?
I-It was super delicious!
Really? I'm glad.
Aren't you going to eat?
I suppose not.
There was a time when I used
to enjoy the sense of taste,
but I don't really care now.
As long as my body gets the
nutrition it needs, that's enough.
Your home is pretty huge.
How many people live here?
Two. My partner and I.
What? Just two people
in this huge apartment?
Right.
Wow. And adults have partners, too?
That's right.
Does that mean...
Wait, it wouldn't be to pilot FRANXX.
What are your partners for?
Well, we're following an old custom.
You could say it's for convenience's sake.
Custom?
Apparently, pairs of men and women used
to form special relationships in the past
to make things easier for
themselves and to procreate.
Life must've been so
uncomfortable back then.
Uncomfortable?
Well, they had to rely on others
for every little thing.
Doesn't that sound really annoying?
I guess...
Would you like to meet my partner?
What? Is he here?
Come with me.
This is my partner.
I see...
That's a big smile. Is he having
an amazing dream or something?
He's not dreaming.
He's getting his dose of happiness.
He's activating his brain's reward
system to gain a sense of pleasure.
It's a truly, truly wonderful thing.
I'd rather gain it by eating
those snacks from earlier.
Is something wrong?
I feel a bit tired.
Let's go back to the living room.
Sure.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
It's been a long time since I've talked
with anyone so much, so I'm not used to it.
But you talk to your partner, don't you?
No. Come to think of it, I don't even
remember what his voice sounds like.
You haven't talked in that long?
There's no need to, after all.
Are you on bad terms?
Not at all.
I don't think either of us is
dissatisfied with our partner.
We don't meddle in each other's business,
which gives us the freedom to
live our lives as we please.
Is that so?
I couldn't begin to tell you how much I'm
forced to hear my partner's voice daily.
Oh?
And of all people, the loudest and naggiest
girl on the squad had to be my partner.
Talk about unlucky.
She gets hysteric at the drop of the hat,
so it feels like we're always arguing.
You got matched with the wrong person, then.
You should change your partner.
If there's a problem with your partner,
doesn't it affect your missions?
Uh... but it doesn't really bother
me much when we're fighting.
And I'm probably the only one who
can deal with how cranky she is.
I don't think the other guys could.
Oh? If there isn't a problem,
then I guess that's fine.
No problem at all! Even Miku...
Oh, my partner's name is Miku.
Name?
Oh, our squad has these
nicknames for each other.
I'm Zorome.
My actual code is...
666.
Huh? Did I mention that?
Anyway, Miku has an awful personality,
but her looks aren't half-bad.
Actually, I think she's pretty damn
cute when she keeps her mouth shut.
And while we're fighting
klaxosaurs and stuff,
sometimes I feel this urge to protect her.
It makes me wonder if that feeling
is what lets us fight together.
Huh?
Is that why FRANXX are built to
be operated by male-female pairs?
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
But I'm really tired now, so I'll send
word and ask someone to pick you up.
Oh, okay.
Fair enough...
Yes.
I checked with him,
so there's no doubt about it.
They say they'll be here right away.
Thank you.
Is something the matter?
Huh?
Are you still hurt somewhere?
No, I'm fine.
Then why?
I don't know.
But...
I don't know why.
I don't know why, but even though
this is the first time I've met you,
you felt really familiar somehow.
And then...
What made you feel that way?
I don't know.
I believe this is the first
time I've really met you.
Right.
But it feels like...
How do I say this?
Like, you know...
Someone's always been watching over me.
Gentle and kind, like they're
always there to protect me.
Then you really are mistaken.
I can't protect you.
You...
You kids are the ones protecting us, right?
We are, aren't we?
Right. You're protecting this plantation.
Yeah.
That's something to be proud of.
And I'll keep protecting it.
I'll fight more.
I'll fight and fight,
kill all the klaxosaurs,
and then one day,
I'll become an adult, right?
So, when I'm able to live in this city too,
would you, uh, be my fam...
W-Would you be my friend?
That's obviously out of the question.
Out of the question?
After all, you are...
I treated his wounds and fed him a little.
Don't make us waste our time.
This isn't a place infected
children like you should enter.
Cut it out.
They're basically victims in all this, too.
The poor, pitiful things.
They found Zorome, apparently.
That jerk... Making us all worry.
I sentence him to clean
the bath for one week!
We're not pitiful.
Hey! Take this seriously!
Huh? What are you keeping watch for?
This ain't a show!
You won't take this seriously unless I do,
Why did that adult woman feel so familiar?
and you might get lost again.
I thought about it a bunch
of times after that day,
Like I'd get lost here!
but in the end, I never found an answer.
Why must I have such a useless kid?
Life is so unfair!
Eventually, I stopped thinking
about it, and even forgot about her.
Why're you acting like you're my guardian?
Gross! I'm gonna kill you!
And ever since, I've stopped
having that dream.
Let's see you try!
Hold it!
Episode 10
The City of Eternity
I don't know
dou shite kimi bakari
Why I keep staring at you
mitsumete shimaun darou
You bring me joy
taikutsu na kyoushitsu ni
In this boring classroom
kimi ga irodori wo kureteru
I think you look cute
neguse nokoru kami mo
Even with your bedhead
kawaiku omotte shimau
I feel embarrassed but I can't get away!
terete hanasenakute
Open that window! Feel the breeze!
mado wo ake kaze wo uke
I take a deep breath
mune ippai ni iki wo suikon da
The blue sky so looks real, I can feel it
aozora ga sawaresou na hodo azayaka ni miete
I'm happy; I'm in pain
ureshikute setsunakute
This must be love!
kore ga koi nan da
All you have to do is call me by my name
kimi ga tada boku no namae wo nee, koe ni suru dake de
That's all it takes to set me free
jiyuu ni nareru ki ga shitan da