In the previous battle,
we successfully took over Gran Crevasse,
and the massive weapon that lay underground,
Star Entity, is now under our control.
Tomorrow, we'll be booting it up.
The FRANXX squads are tasked with the
mission of keeping all enemies away from it.
Many sacrifices will have to be made,
but please do your best.
Uh...
What is it, Code 390?
Where'd Nana go?
But I'm Nana.
Oh, I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm Code 007, and I've been appointed
the new caretaker of Squad 13.
What? New caretaker?
And your code's...
Um, this Star Entity is a
klaxosaur weapon, right?
Right.
Are you sure this isn't risky?
There's no need to worry on that front.
That's why we spent so long modifying it.
Long story short, we're implanting
Strelizia in Star Entity's core.
That will let us control it.
Code 002, we raised you with
so much care, all for this day.
We're counting on you.
Yeah, right. Says the one who lied to me.
Assuming we do manage to control Star Entity,
what happens after that?
If we exterminate the klaxosaurs,
will there be a place for us in that future?
Of course.
If we win this war against the klaxosaurs,
the future will belong to us, humanity.
This will be the last time we call you Papa.
We won't let you control our destiny anymore.
Come over here beside me as my restraint crumbles
Please don't fear me
Ah...
I want to taste you... Does that make me weird?
It's something we're unable to feel all alone
Embracing one another will keep our wounds sealed
So I'll seal your breath with my lips
Will your lips taste the kiss of death?
Darling
ko
dou
ga
yu
Darling, what is this melting feeling
Going from my heart to the tips of my fingers?
nee...
Hey...
Come to me, as our inhibitions crumble
Please don't fear me
Just kiss me now!
Doctor, we've received word that
Hringhorni is ready for action.
I see.
A massive spear built using klaxosaur cores.
Was such a thing really necessary?
It's way too overboard.
More than anything, it isn't beautiful.
Humanity must need it to prevail.
How's Nana doing?
I've had her brief Squad 13 on their mission.
Not that one...
Never mind.
Do as you wish.
The rings?
Not this again!
Seriously, what?
If you don't like it, don't eat it.
I'm saying Mitsuru and Kokoro
I'm not saying I won't!
both took off their rings.
I'm amazed you noticed.
Are you still not over...
Sorry.
Kokoro?
Hey, are you okay?
Kokoro!
Hey, wait!
Are you okay?
It's happening a lot lately.
Maybe you should take the
upcoming mission off.
I'll be fine.
Papa sent me back here,
even after erasing my memories.
So I must fight for him,
even if it means laying down my life.
No! You're wrong!
You don't belong to Papa!
None of us do!
But...
We must survive and leave
a mark on the future!
You're the one who taught us that!
I did?
D-Day
APE has always desired eternal
peace and prosperity for mankind.
Bird Nest: Assembly Hall
Fear not, soldiers!
Offer up everything you have in this mission!
On this day,
we shall finally wipe out the klaxosaurs
and prevail in this war!
I can't say I approve.
You guys stuck out like a sore thumb.
You were an eyesore, honestly.
There you go again,
being so openly hostile.
You're like animals.
These guys are much stronger than you
and have their eyes set on the future.
Don't look down on humans.
Don't get the wrong idea, Iota.
Papa only gives you guys special treatment
because he sees you as necessary tools.
You'll understand in due time.
Bird Nest: Strategic Command
Klaxosaur pack currently at a distance
of 3000. Heading fast for Gran Crevasse.
Multiple Gutenberg-class and
Lehmann-class klaxosaurs identified.
Estimated to reach first line
of defense in 103 minutes.
Bird Nest: Underground Hangar
We were partners before.
We should be able to connect.
Gran Crevasse Ruins
Okay.
This could actually work, Code 55...
Kokoro.
What was that?
What's wrong?
Hey!
Answer me!
Genista!
Don't stand still! Keep moving!
H-Hey, what should I do?
Answer me, Mitsuru—
M-My head!
This pain...
Is it because I said her name?
It sure is quiet.
Yeah.
What do you want to do
once we're done with this?
I wanna go see the world.
You said you'd show me, remember?
Where should we go? The ocean?
Then there's...
I don't care as long as I'm with you.
I just wanna travel the world,
like that princess did.
Hey, darling.
About the last page of that picture book...
Huh?
Nah.
Never mind.
Zero Two...
I'm sure we're going to be
put through a trial by fire.
But...
We've gone through these things
many times before, too.
You and I made things work out each time.
Yeah. We'll be fine.
Together, we can defy any fate.
We'll be together forever.
But what if we're torn apart?
I'll come get you.
Thanks. Same here.
Promise?
Promise.
Gran Crevasse
Bottom
Star Entity is ready to go.
Move out, Strelizia.
Roger!
Something wrong?
Something's coming.
Unidentified flying object approaching
rapidly from 10 o'clock!
Here they come.
Genista!
What?
What the hell?
It's heading for Gran Crevasse!
No... This can't be!
Guess they won't make this easy for us.
What's going on?
I'll call for reinforcements.
They won't get here in time.
Prioritize the mission, Strelizia.
Get going!
Zero Two!
R-Right!
We should get going too, Doctor.
Humans...
You will not do as you please with our child.
I see! So it is you, Code 001...
Princess of the Klaxosaurs!
It has been far too long.
Are you here to take back Star Entity?
But you can't operate it.
You don't have a partner.
You're the last surviving klaxo sapiens.
So I'll operate it.
Ever since the day I first met you,
that's all I've dreamed of!
That's what all my research has been for!
Princess, sit there and watch—
You sinful man.
Doctor!
I...
need no partner.
But since I have the chance, I shall
use the one you have provided.
What?
Nope.
It's not budging.
Darling...
Strelizia here.
Reached entry point, but the door won't open.
The enemy caught up?!
We'll have to fight here...
Zero Two!
The controls...
What?
Zero Two!
Ah, the fake that the humans created.
A duplicate that does not realize
it is being used by the invaders.
You are not fit to pilot our child.
Fake?
What are you saying?
Zero Two!
I shall take him.
Darling!
A curious taste.
You really must be no ordinary human.
What?
Surrender yourself to me.
I shall devour your body and soul.
No way!
Strelizia has entered Star Entity.
The worst has come to pass!
All the work put into Code 002
will have been in vain!
Should the klaxosaur princess connect to
Star Entity, our defeat is all but assured!
Worry not.
We've already taken measures.
What is this?
She connected to Strelizia?
Doctor!
I wasn't expecting her to link with a human.
At this rate,
she will devour once again!
Wh-Why?
How can you pilot Strelizia?
Of course I can.
This was originally one of our brethren.
Brethren?
What is this?
What the...
A voice...
...speaking...
...directly...
...to our brains?
Heed me, humans,
you ignorant fools who steal the symbol of
our bonds that courses the planet's depths.
"Courses the planet's depths"?
Magma energy?
I found something while
studying klaxosaur corpses.
At some point in time,
their kind split into two forms.
One returned to the earth and became energy.
Steal? That's an affront!
Magma energy is part of
the planet's resources!
Its discovery saved human
civilization from certain ruin.
Do you realize how self-centered
a viewpoint that is?
And now you wish to steal my child?
I could never allow that to pass.
For this child is a
crystallization of our bonds.
Don't talk down to Papa!
Damn klaxosaur!
And what was the other form?
It consumed that energy
and evolved physically.
It took an absurdly long time,
during which they stopped
mingling with one another
and eventually lost their intelligence.
Just what are klaxosaurs?
Biological weapons built by the klaxo sapiens.
They are comprised of one male
and one female klaxo sapiens.
The female's soul connected to the weapon,
and the male's soul took root
in the core, the cockpit.
That sounds almost like the FRANXX...
Exactly.
They're merely an application
of the klaxosaur system.
Klaxosaurs that can be piloted by humans
genetically modified to be similar.
That is what the FRANXX are.
So we've been piloting klaxosaurs
to fight klaxosaurs?
No way.
The klaxosaurs had pilots just like us?!
Could it be...
The thing we saw back then?
Yeah.
Also, remember the S-Planning?
They were excavating klaxosaurs that'd
serve as the base of FRANXX units back there?
Damn it... Damn it! What the hell is with that?!
We've been kept in the dark this whole time?!
What is this place?
Come.
Awaken, my child.
They are nearly here.
Who are "they"?
Strelizia has begun the implanting process.
No...
I was hoping it wouldn't come to this,
but we have no choice.
What?
We wanted to take it and
Hringhorni to space as soldiers.
Space?
If we can't have it, then it can
go down along with this planet.
What are you saying?
And we will return to our original roles.
An earthquake?!
Look!
Over there!
Are these...
...klaxosaurs?
They flew?
Again?!
An even bigger one!
What is this?!
Klaxosaurs?
No way. This is way too outrageous.
What the hell is this?!
This is nothing like our battles so far!
Just what is happening?
That's Star Entity's awakened form?
This is it!
My Strelizia Apath!
Beautiful!
I wish I could've piloted it...
No, that doesn't matter anymore.
Look how ugly the humans have made you.
But...
You are still our child.
A long time ago, when we were attacked
by invaders from the expanse of space,
we fought and drove them off.
And then, we holed up in the earth
and prepared for their return.
Invaders?
Indeed.
They are invaders. Our true enemy.
VIRM.
Reconnaissance Fleet
True enemy? Invaders?
Filthy invaders,
I shall not even let you
touch our planet this time.
Die.
You will not take our planet.
It's futile.
What happened?
Curse you, VIRM! What did
you do to our child?
Wh...
What?
What's happening?
This is VIRM's will.
What?
Star Entity is a mass of life that
could disturb the universe's peace.
As such, if the klaxosaur princess
took over the implanting process,
we programmed it to explode.
The die has been cast.
We're getting drenched in the unexpected rain
yohou hazure no ame ga bokura wo nurashite
This planet...
What should I tell you as I see you tremble?
furueteru kimi ni nani wo hanashitara ii no
...will explode...
...leaving nothing behind.
Hiro... Zero Two!
Wet to the skin, we feel so cold, so heavy
bishonure no burezaa ga tsumetakute omotakute
Stop...
Please stop!
Doctor!
It's all ruined!
Helpless like a bird who just left its cage
kago wo deta hinadori no muryokusa wo kanjiteru
Apath is my ultimate work of works!
Don't defile it!
We will absorb all lifeforms on this planet.
I was so close to my dreams and now they're beyond the clouds
sawaresou datta yume wa buatsui kumo no mukou de
And we'll take you to eternal paradise.
All that's left in my heart is bittersweet pain
mune ni hirogaru amai itami dake kamishimeta
You impertinent fiends!
Maybe we shouldn't have met after all
boku to kimi wa deawanai hou ga yokatta ka na
Damn!
I can't even see the stars...
nee hoshi sae mienai yo
Zero Two!
I can't even shed any tears
nee namida mo dete konai
I promised...
I'm gonna come get you, darling.
No matter what!
Episode 20
A New World