"Yesterday was rainy, and today is clear.
What will tomorrow be like?"
I'm always trying to figure
out what your outlook is.
I can tell what's coming, be it
sudden squalls or clear blue skies,
by following your gaze.
Your forecasts are always
simple and accurate.
Guys! They're here!
Awesome! Which one's mine?
You're still asking for that kiddie stuff?
Wh-What does it matter?
Presents?
Yeah. Once every year, we can
ask Papa for the things we want,
and we'll get them on this particular day.
Huh... What's that?
A picture book?
Oh, nah. This is an illustrated guide.
Do you like picture books?
I think we have some in the study.
Okay, listen up!
I'm gonna read Papa's message!
Ahem. Er...
"Boys and girls, your numerous
accomplishments represent
a ray of hope, a harbinger of
peace and prosperity for mankind.
Glory be to you noble parasites,
who risk your lives for us."
Hear that?!
He called us "a ray of hope"!
That makes me wanna do even better!
Come over here beside me. My restraint crumbles
Don't be scared
Ah...
A flightless bird dreamed of the sky
This thickly mixed love is a differently colored red
Love
I covered my ears to the sound of knocking on my door
Is that you knocking? Or is it someone else...
Will you leave just a kiss of death?
Darling, fate runs through my veins
k
e
a
n
Darling
Darling
As this world begins to move (Love)
I want to be your closest partner, Darling
Darling
So don't be scared...
Just kiss me now!
Hey, what are you doing—
Shh!
What's this?
It didn't feel right that we were
the only ones who got presents.
So I wanted to find something for you, too.
A girl called Naomi left that behind.
Should I not have?
Nah.
Thank you, darling!
H-Hey!
I never knew getting a present from
someone could make me this happy.
I'll take good care of it!
Great.
Your bangs have grown, Ichigo.
It'll be harder to see.
You think so?
Anyway, I asked for another
stuffed toy! What about you two?
Oh, there you are.
That was a surprise.
I didn't know Zero Two
smiled that way with you.
The heck? You were watching?
Sorry.
Isn't that Ichigo's...
Yeah. The same type of hair clip.
But this is one I tried and failed
to give her a long time ago.
Remember when I told you I didn't understand
this "love" thing you guys talk about?
Now, I'm starting to think it means
the other person is special to you.
Special? Maybe, yeah.
You've always been Ichigo's hero.
That's special, right?
Where is all this coming from?
I'm thinking she probably feels the same
way about you as you do about Zero Two.
The same?
Like, y'know, wanting to know more
about you, be with you more, and, uh...
do that kiss thing with you.
What? You really hadn't noticed?
B-But...
W-Wait, doesn't that mean you—
I know everything.
I know what makes her laugh,
and what makes her cry...
But none of them would work for me.
You might be the only one who can, Hiro.
Goro... You're being kinda weird today.
Yeah, I know it's weird.
Watching you lately made my
own feelings clear to me.
It helped me realize that I love Ichigo.
Whew! That's a load off my chest.
Time to sleep.
Wait, Goro!
But you know what?
I'm plenty happy with the way things are.
I'm turning off the lights.
Oh, wait a sec.
Go ahead.
Goodnight.
We've detected a Gutenberg-class klaxosaur
at a distance approximately 2,000 from here.
It's moving slowly,
but judging from its course,
we predict that it'll make
contact with the plantation.
We must avoid a repeat of the
previous attack at all costs.
Yes, ma'am!
Also, the target is a
long way away this time.
Your units have been loaded with more
fuel than usual, so make a note of that.
Look, there's a huge thundercloud.
Thundercloud?
What is that?
Target sighted.
It's kinda gross!
All units, prepare for combat.
Roger that!
Argentea, going in!
What?
Explosions?
This isn't good.
Damn it.
Hey, the core's right there.
Gotcha!
You idiot! Don't!
Damn, that's hard!
What is up with this thing?
I can't move!
No!
It's activating something!
Ichigo! Goro!
I can't move!
Everyone get away!
Ow...
Ichigo! Goro!
I can't move!
Everyone get away!
Goro.
Hiro?!
Thank goodness. I finally got through to you.
Is Ichigo okay?
She's fine. She got knocked out by the
ejection, but her injuries aren't severe.
She's getting treated along
with Zorome and Miku.
Oh... good.
Hey, Hiro. Could you contact
the transport team for me?
I can't operate this thing alone.
Goro, I want you to stay
calm and listen to me.
You're inside the klaxosaur right now.
What does that mean?
We didn't eliminate the klaxosaur?
It swallowed Delphinium right as it exploded.
Soon after that, we were ordered to retreat,
so we're back at the plantation for now.
So that's what happened.
But we'll figure something out,
so don't worry!
Got it. I'll try to figure
out what I can do, too.
Goro...
Sorry we retreated and left you there.
Don't worry about it.
Anyway, I'm wasting power here, so I'm
gonna switch to safe mode for a bit.
All right. We'll get in touch again.
You can't utilize a FRANXX's
magma energy without its pistil.
You mean...
Don't worry.
The FRANXX are programmed to run their
life support systems on backup power.
Then he'll die if it runs out.
Well, as things stand, this plantation
and all of us will go boom.
Wait!
Ichigo?
You should still be in bed!
What's all this about Goro getting
swallowed by the klaxosaur?
I told you, he tried to save us and...
Then why aren't we going
to rescue him already?
How could you turn tail like that?
Even now, he's trapped inside the klaxosaur!
That fool...
Why'd he cut me loose? He knows
he's helpless by himself!
You're so annoying.
Don't you realize that Goro's
always looking out for you?
What?
Like that time Hiro almost died.
You broke down immediately! And who
do you think got you back on your feet?
What gives you the right
to run your mouth at me?
You go around all like,
"I'm the leader, I'm the leader,"
but you lose your cool and
lash out at the drop of a hat.
Goro must have a hard time with
you as his partner! That's my point!
All right. That's enough.
I'm glad you kids are okay.
I see everyone's here.
Analysis of the samples stuck on your units
showed that it's a klaxosaur that vaporizes
its bodily fluids to expand and explode.
You mean Goro's stuck in its fuel right now?
Relax. Fortunately, the part
that Delphinium jumped into
has been confirmed to be harmless to FRANXX.
Then I guess we rescue Goro first.
I owe him one, after all.
Our top priority is preventing the target
from making contact with the plantation.
Estimated time of contact is
approximately one hour from now.
We'll set up a last line of defense
and eliminate the klaxosaur
before it crosses that line.
What if we can't eliminate it by then?
In that case, the plantation
will open fire, as well.
To protect itself, the target will use its
internal fuel and explode several times.
As long as we launch enough strikes,
there's a chance one of them will finish it.
Are you saying you'll leave Goro to die?!
In the worst case scenario, yes.
No...
The operation begins in 15 minutes.
All hands, prepare to sortie.
Um...
Please let me talk to Goro first!
Is that water I hear?
It's been 30 minutes since
Hiro and the others radioed.
There's only one thing I can do right now...
Goro.
Ichigo?
Thank goodness! You came to!
You idiot! What were you thinking,
getting yourself swallowed whole?!
Why do you always put
yourself second like this?
How are you going to get
out of there without me?
You've always been like this!
Always making selfish decisions,
and always coming back hurt!
Why don't you lean on me a little?
I'll save you.
I'll save you, no matter what.
So wait for me!
Ichigo...
Are you crying?
Shut up.
It's all right, Ichigo. I came up with a plan.
I'm going to kill this thing
and come home to you.
So don't worry about me.
Kill it? How?
Can't waste any more power.
I'm gonna hang up.
Goro!
I've got this in the bag,
even if I'm by myself.
Let me go rescue Goro!
Knowing him, I bet he's thinking
of doing something stupid!
He's just acting tough! I can tell!
I agree! Let us go, please!
And how exactly do you intend to rescue him?
W-Well...
There was one spot.
There was an exhaust hole,
of sorts, on top of the klaxosaur.
Someone could probably get
in there if they tried.
Genista and Chlorophytum are standing
by as the last line of defense.
If it looks like the target will cross it...
Yes, I know.
To get to Delphinium, you'll have to cross
an area of highly pressurized vapor fuel.
There's no guarantee that
it's safe, even in your suit.
I know.
But there's a chance, right?
Who knows? I wouldn't do it if I were you.
Hey, Zero Two!
But I will.
I believe in you, Zero Two!
I don't dislike this sort of thing.
Let's go!
Upsy-daisy!
Ichigo!
Go get Goro for us.
Hurry!
Just you wait, Goro!
Why does that guy keep
picking fights with us?
Sick of the communal lifestyle,
Well, he's weak as hell,
so it's no big deal.
I thought I'd get to be alone if
I made everyone else hate me.
Why do you keep getting into
fights when you're so weak?
Stay out of this!
C'mon, bring it!
Told you so.
I've got this in the bag,
even if I'm by myself.
Here.
I never asked for your help, all right?
But hey, we won.
Maybe we can't win alone,
but the two of us together can.
Yeah, I've loved Ichigo ever since then,
and Hiro has always been right beside her.
But I was okay with that.
Because Hiro was special
to me in his own way, too.
You two better not die!
It's Genista and Chlorophytum!
There'll be trouble if it crosses this line!
It'll be fine. Believe in Ichigo.
I used to think that I didn't mind if my
feelings never got through to her.
But if there's one thing I regret...
That's more than enough to self-destruct.
There's the backup fuel pack, too.
This will be one hell of a present, huh?
I just wish I could've told her...
Ichigo?!
Wow... The air's thin in here.
Why'd you come?
I said I'd save you no matter what, didn't I?
And I told you that I'd be all right!
You're an idiot, so I knew you'd try
to fix everything by yourself.
You're so headstrong,
even though you're weak.
Even though you can't do
anything without me...
But that doesn't mean you
had to do this alone!
You're wrong.
Maybe we can't win alone, but the
two of us together can, remember?
You were willing to cry for me.
I thought I was satisfied
just knowing that...
until a moment ago.
But now, seeing your face as you smile at me
is making me happier than
anything ever has before.
What's all this? Quit being gross.
Let's get out of here already.
Let's go, Ichigo!
Roger!
They're out!
Hell yeah!
Everyone, get the hell out of here!
Huh?
Hurry!
There. All done.
Ow...
Thanks.
Ichigo, where's your hair clip?
H-Huh? Did I lose it?
Here.
Oh...
You picked it up for me?
Nah. This is something I wanted
to give you, but couldn't.
You know, I think I love you.
Don't get so flustered.
I just felt like telling you.
But I don't want to think,
"I should've done that back then."
I don't want to regret things anymore.
I-I had something to say to you, too!
Thank you for being my partner.
B-But, uh, I don't know how to
respond to the love thing.
I wasn't trying to put you on the spot.
I'm not expecting an answer or anything.
But let me stay like this for a while.
Sure.
Crying one minute, smiling the next...
I don't get you at all today.
What's the outlook for tomorrow?
Right now, you're impossible to forecast.
Episode 9
Triangle Bomb
I don't know
dou shite kimi bakari
Why I keep staring at you
mitsumete shimaun darou
You bring me joy
taikutsu na kyoushitsu ni
In this boring classroom
kimi ga irodori wo kureteru
I think you look cute
neguse nokoru kami mo
Even with your bedhead
kawaiku omotte shimau
I feel embarrassed but I can't get away!
terete hanasenakute
Open that window! Feel the breeze!
mado wo ake kaze wo uke
I take a deep breath
mune ippai ni iki wo suikon da
The blue sky so looks real, I can feel it
aozora ga sawaresou na hodo azayaka ni miete
I'm happy; I'm in pain
ureshikute setsunakute
This must be love!
kore ga koi nan da
All you have to do is call me by my name
kimi ga tada boku no namae wo nee, koe ni suru dake de
That's all it takes to set me free
jiyuu ni nareru ki ga shitan da