Radical Revy-chan on stage!
Who are you?
~ The Magical Girl ~
Your sad lack of social skills has left you a loser hermit, and I've come from Hestonworld to save you!
As an emissary of peace and justice, I'm here to solve your problems!
So, c'mon. Tell me your deepest desire!
Um, well... How about, "please go away?"
Oh come on. Isn't there anyone that you want me to get rid of?
Look, can't you listen to me?
Say it!
Well yeah, I guess there's someone...
What'cha want, lowlife?
The Russian school gang leader?
She shook me down for my lunch once...
Ooh, this'll be a snap!
I'll cook this bunch's goose in no time!
WHAT?
GET HER!
Tokarev! Makarov! Krinkov!
Heckler & Koch, all together now!
It's search and destroy time!
You're not using magic?
Magic?
Who needs magic when all your problems can be solved...
...with guns!
It's a hell of a lot more practical and reliable than some old magic trick.
Um, I have a question.
Is everyone from Hestonworld just like you?
You bet!
People kill people!
That's why there's no fighting or domestic squabbles!
Well, duh.
They'd die if they tried.
Well, I guess I'll be on my way now.
Say, didn't you say something about being short on spending money?
Isn't that right?
Here's something special just for you!
Where did you get all this?
From a bank, of course.
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
And so, having fully satisfied her need to help people even when they don't need it, radical Revy returns to Hestonworld...
...as high-strung and clueless as ever.
It's magical maid!
Roberta-chan!
To the rescue!
Huh?
To be continued... (Not!)
What?