I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
Roberta...
Get down!
Stay out of the way!
No! Don't shoot Roberta!
If something like this could kill her,
we wouldn't have this problem, kid.
Roberta!
Damn it! Damn it!
Dutch, we're off the main road.
This way leads to the ocean. It's a dead end.
Not good!
No!
There's a payoff for being a religious man.
All survivors answer me.
We're safe, somehow.
What about Revy?
She's still peacefully unconscious.
How about you?
What is that woman... made out of?
Damn it.
Revy.
Hey, what happened to that stupid bitch?
Is she dead? Well?
Be glad. She's still alive and well.
That's just great.
More than anything else.
Revy! Wait!
Rock, I'm just about to get a red fucking tail light.
When that happens, it's over.
I won't be able to warn you when I give you more assholes.
That bullet she put in me is going to cost more
than anything you could stick up your ass.
I'm going to go beat that into her.
Ready, Señorita?
Or are you scared?
I have no need to use filthy words and be afraid.
Knowing that you cannot defeat me with skill, you kidnapped the young master.
You coward.
Rock! Watch out for stray bullets!
I can't see... either of them.
Roberta.
Damn it.
She managed to hit the great Revy.
Who is that woman?
You couldn't have had a good childhood.
Where did you come from?
Tell me.
I see.
That's the smell you have on you.
The smell of the gutter mud wrapped around your feet.
We need to settle this even more now.
I cannot...
I cannot return there any more.
Roberta!
What should we... do now?
We should get out of this car.
Y... Yeah. You're right.
Roberta!
Impossible.
Yeah, impossible.
No matter how many lives we have, it won't be enough.
I don't want to be the one getting between them.
Me neither.
There's an end to every beginning.
They'll settle this eventually.
Hey, kid! Wait!
Garcia-kun.
Roberta!
Do your best!
Don't lose to that woman!
The gunfire is coming this way.
I'm going to kill her! Fucking kill her!
I'm going to send you to Hell!
Don't move!
Why don't you two call it quits there.
There's no profit in fighting anymore.
Don't waste your energy, Two-Hands.
Shut up.
I'm going to kill her.
Let me tell you something good, Maid-san.
We, Hotel Moscow, had intended to start a war
with the Manisarera Cartel from the beginning.
Taking care of him was my job, but...
you saved me the trouble.
Right now, their headquarters
in Venezuela should be in ruins.
So... there's no problem on any front.
Garcia-kun being kidnapped is also no problem.
There's no reason to fight.
It's the three most fearsome women in the world.
This feels like Ground Zero.
It doesn't matter.
Indeed.
You think so?
Don't misunderstand me.
I wasn't asking...
but commanding.
Who are these guys?
They don't seem like the normal Russian mafia.
Military uniforms?
The military?
Roberta!
It's all right, Roberta!
I'm not hurt!
Let's go home!
I don't want to see you with a gun anymore.
I agree, kid.
But... what does the Bloodhound think?
Bloodhound?
Oh? So you don't know?
She's...
Shut up!
Keep quiet, bitch.
This isn't some servant who looks good walking the dog.
"The Bloodhound of Florencia."
Rosarita Cisneros.
Trained as an assassin in Cuba.
A former FARC Guerilla.
She's wanted internationally for
multiple kidnappings and murders,
and she's suspected of being involved with the
bombing of the US embassy in Tegucigalpa.
A real hard-core terrorist.
Roberta.
Is that true?
Young master...
Young master, I had no intention of deceiving you.
But young master...
There are things in this world,
that are better not knowing.
That is the truth, young master.
I...
I believed it.
That, one day... the revolution would come.
For that, I...
became a soldier.
For that... those ideals... I killed in many places.
Politicians, businessmen,
anti-revolutionaries, the shallow-minded.
Even women and children.
I stained many nights with blood.
I faced many cold mornings.
What I found out in the end was...
I was no revolutionary, I was just a guard
dog for the mafia and the cocaine fields.
Is it not ironic?
The revolutionaries worked with the cartels.
Saying that a revolution would not happen just on ideals.
They sold their souls.
I left the military.
The one who took me in was my deceased father's friend,
your father, Master Diego Loveless.
Young master,
allowing your kidnapping to happen was my mistake.
I did not have any other way to save you
than becoming my old, steel self again.
Bloodhound.
Guard Dog.
That was the only thing this dog could do to repay you.
Don't call yourself a dog, Roberta! You're my family!
We're a family, right?
Don't talk about being a dog like that!
That's no good!
I don't know any Bloodhound!
She probably died somewhere!
This Rosarita woman is probably
far away, burdened with her sins!
So, she's got nothing to do with Roberta!
The only one here is my Roberta!
Young master.
So...
let's go back to our home.
Young master.
Boys should not cry so easily.
So, that's taken care of.
Fuck off.
If they want a teary-eyed happy ending, that's fine.
But who the hell is gonna close
up this tunnel in my shoulder?
Why don't you just put up.
Sis, that stinks.
In our world, settling things is important.
You know that, Sis.
Well, I guess so.
That's easy.
Go at each other until you're satisfied.
No weapons, then no one should die.
Fine by me.
Young master?
Don't lose to that woman.
You're strong!
Then it's settled.
Have fun.
All right, bring it on.
Your shoelace is untied.
She nailed it!
It's good to be young.
Damn it!
D-Do your best, Roberta!
Don't lose!
Who do you bet on?
Two on Revy.
Then I'll put three on Roberta.
How about you Rock?
Shouldn't we stop them?
Let's make them stop.
Why?
That's too barbaric. You guys are crazy.
And two girls shouldn't be doing that.
Then, why don't you stop them?
You don't like it right?
Well...
Then go stop it.
We don't mind.
Umm...
You two...
Isn't that enough?
Maybe you should gaze at the
sunrise and let go of your aggression.
Stay the fuck out!
I understand. Will do.
See?
They're hanging in there. This is getting boring.
Why aren't you dead yet?
Fucking four-eyes!
Why don't you... go down?
Damn it!
There. Draw.
Roberta!
Y-young master.
I am sorry.
Don't talk.
You were the last one standing.
So, it's all right.
There.
That's a terrible face.
She's unconscious.
Can you stand up?
Here, hang on to me.
I am sorry.
Stop it, Roberta.
You want a hand, kid?
Leave me alone.
Roberta is a maid at my house.
So I won't take your help.
I will take her home.
A wonderful soon-to-be head of the house.
Comrade Sergeant.
Yes.
Check her wounds, then take them to the airport.
If there is an attack from any remaining
Cartel members, dispose of them.
Roger.
Young master, I have one favor to ask.
What is it?
My glasses.
Will you pick them up?
Why?
They're fake, aren't they?
No, I need them... to remain as the young master's Roberta.
Hey! It's the morning, Revy!
Wake up.
Not even a twitch.
She's going to be pissed off for a while. Geez.
But,
what was that?
Balalaika-san and the Russian mafia.
They were like a... military.
They're ex-military.
Either in the paratroopers or the Special Forces,
Her immediate subordinates have had
enough training to take on World War III.
Afghan vets with an insane amount of experience and skill.
With her as the brains, every one
of them acts like a killing machine.
That's how they returned from that hot-sanded hell.
Everyone's feet...
...were covered with mud from the gutter.
Five teams will leave Roanapur at the same time.
They will all head to separate locations.
There are five cases.