I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
They're not the same...
...my home town and this dirty city.
I'm sorry.
This isn't a city that a child like you should see.
Roanapur at night...
It's all right.
You must believe in your people from home.
Of course I do. I believe in them...
...that they'll come and save me.
You're lucky.
You can feel it in your heart.
That the maid who you believe in will come for you.
I don't know if it'll come true or not, but...
...you must have a great family if you have such strong faith.
I always wonder how my family feels about me.
Is that...
No, it's nothing.
Do you miss your mama?
Do you think so?
If I did, I would have said goodbye to this place long ago.
Rock, that's a pointless story.
That's just the story of a brat who chases after mama when it's convenient.
We're just talking about ideals.
To see if you hold in your heart something to believe in.
So, if I'm ever kidnapped, are you going to wave your Cutlass around and come save me?
I won't forgive anyone stupid enough to get kidnapped.
In this world you just bite off your navel, beg forgiveness for causing trouble to your comrades, and then die.
See? These are my friends,
but they're worth sticking with.
Kid.
I just wish that maid of yours is as strong as you believe.
This hasn't seen much use lately.
This Cutlass.
Just kiddin'.
I guess there's no point in wishing.
Not when I'm stuck with a maid-obsessed brat from the fucking countryside.
Did you hear that?!
Be rude?
This bitch!
She's making me laugh!
What are you gonna do?
What's this? A fight?
I am afraid I will not be able to hold back.
Please pardon me.
Please enjoy yourselves.
And he just reopened this bar.
She sure has something flashy.
W-Why you!
Bitch!
God dammit!
Boys!
Don't hold back! Kill her!
Please do as you must,
if you can.
Shut up!
Roberta!
You...
It's no good, Bro!
What's going on?
Is it Kevlar?
God dammit!
You better pay for all of this!
We've walked into a very bad fight.
But the fact that they're going at it is in our favor.
How about we take off while they're busy?
Take off? To where?
We can go fishing at the Phuket beach until this cools down.
I'm not in the mood for drinking with a gunfight on the side.
Giuliano Gemma is a famous actor in spaghetti westerns
I'm no Giuliano Gemma.
Hey, will you hurry up and decide if I need to shoot or not?
Good call.
I'd rather not shoot.
We'll leave the kid here.
I don't want to go for a walk carrying a claymore.
But he's worth something, Dutch.
The exit became a war zone while we were talking.
There's no way out over there.
Anyway, this kid isn't money anymore.
We're leaving him here.
OK?
But that's...
We've got no choice.
Damn, damn, fuck.
All right then.
Garcia, listen.
Don't move from this spot until the gunfire dies down.
When it gets quiet, go home to Venezuela with your maid.
I... didn't know...
...that Roberta was...
She's not someone who would kill, but...
Why?
Garcia-kun...
Rock!
What are you doing!?
10,000 dollars for the bottles, 15,000 dollars for the furniture,
plus 20,000 dollars for the building.
Now the problem is figuring out who to send the bill to.
Revy!
Y-You!
Revy, is this your doing again?
How many times do your friends need to tear up my shop?
They're not my friends!
I don't know who they are, you idiot!
Don't get quiet, you idiots.
Lagoon Company! Why are you here?
What happened to delivering our package?
W-Wait!
Don't jump to conclusions, Gregor!
Why is the package here? Did you ignore our contract?
I said don't jump to conclusions!
We'll talk about the payment later.
Young master.
Roberta...
So you were here, young master.
The master has been very worried about you.
Please...
It cannot be helped if you are afraid.
I will explain myself later.
Who are they?
Not good.
Their eyes met.
Wait! Roberta!
No!
Stand back, maid.
Everyone here would rather be alive than dead.
You too, right?
Don't be stupid. Stop it or we'll be the villains.
Shut up!
As long as you don't start shooting, you'll get the young master home in one piece.
You won't have to see his brains on the floor.
Got it?
I am thinking.
Don't you ignore us!
I have finished thinking.
Una bendicion por los vivos.
A blessing for the living.
Una rama de flor por los muertos.
A flower branch for the dead.
That's Spanish.
Mercy for the living.
Con una espada por la justicia.
With a sword of justice.
A bunch of flowers for the dead.
A punishment of death for the wicked.
Un castigo de muerte para los malvados.
Wield a sword for justice.
The punishment of death for evildoers.
Asi llegamos en el altar de los santos.
Like this we arrive at the alter of the saints.
However, we are not joining the line of saints.
The Loveless family creed.
I will have the young master home in one piece.
However, I must work by this creed.
In the name of Santa Maria.
Those words...
A hammer blow to all injustice!
That... That bitch!
Now! Let's go!
Stay away!
Stay away!!
Revy!
Go and Die!
Hunting dog of Florencia!
Florencia is a municipality in the Caquetá Department, Colombia
What a crazy bitch.
This makes the Battle of Khe Sanh look like a picnic.
Khe Sanh was a particularly bloody battle in the Vietnam war
Hey! Is Revy all right?
The wound doesn't seem serious.
But she's got a concussion.
Revy!
Hang in there! Hey!
Please stop.
Please stop, Roberta.
Stop!
Garcia-kun...
Rock!
Stop fucking around!
We're leaving!
Run!
Take me with you.
Young master!
I...
I don't...
I don't like this Roberta!
Wait up!
Now I remember, from what you just said.
El perro de cassa de Florencia.
The hunting dog of Florence.
The hunting dog from Florencia.
I can't believe you're alive.
Even Jesus couldn't have guessed.
These four years since you left the Colombian Revolutionary Army,
everyone from the drug cartels to Interpol has been after you!
The cartels put a 40,000 dollar bounty on your head.
Dead or alive.
Finally luck is on my side!
If I bring your head back, I'll be a lieutenant of the cartel!
I no longer have a reason to keep you alive.
If you will excuse me, I must be going now.
Please accept this.
So, everyone,
farewell.
Damn it.
She's unbelievably thorough.
Rock, you bastard.
I told you to leave the kid behind.
I couldn't help it.
I couldn't leave him in there.
Do you think that killed her?
Get in the car!
I know I can't hear anything,
but I feel something.
Like her footsteps are getting closer,
and her black maid's outfit is about to appear from that fiery exit.
So hurry up and get in the car!
Where should we go?
Is there a place we can run to on this planet?
Impossible.
I believe it.
That's a killer robot from the future!
The only thing different from the movies is that Schwarzenegger isn't here.
That's not funny and I can't laugh.
We've got her precious young master.
Just head for the port! Hurry to the Lagoon!
Bad news doesn't take much effort to hear.
She's pretty famous.
Her code name is "Bloodhound".
She got it because once locked onto her prey, she always kills.
It's going to be a pain.
They're calling, Sergeant.
It's probably bad news.
She's really coming.
Rock!
Wake Revy up!
It's no time for her to be comfortably sleeping!
Revy, Revy!
Revy!
Damn it!
Shit!
Sergeant Benisov, what is the situation?
The Yellow Flag has been mostly destroyed.
The Bloodhound and Lagoon are both gone.
But a Primus was seen heading towards the city on the main street ten minutes ago.
Do not leave that spot, Sergeant. Continue gathering information.
Roger.
What shall I tell the shop's owner?
Tell him not to worry about insurance.
I am heading towards the city with a squad.
Capitan, are you going to war after so long?
Playing mafia is not good, it dulls your body.
We'll see.
But there's no reason not to be prepared.
We owe Lagoon...no, we owe Dutch.
We can't let them be.
Let us go, comrades.
Cock your hammers.
Die!
Let me go!
You bitch!
Damn it!
Now's our chance!
Hang on, Dutch!
We'll head to the port using these back-roads.
Once we're out to sea, no matter who she is...
Damn it.
No good, Benny.
We'll lose speed this way.
Her radiator was shot.
She can't run.
You should have paid more attention to Rock's joke, Benny-Boy.
Imagine her as an invincible killer robot.
We're gonna punch it.
Rock, get Revy up!
When things get tight, we're going to need her gun.
Revy! Revy! Wake up!
Benny, take the next turn.
Get to the main road and go at full speed.
Roger!
Are you all right, Benny?
Wake up!
Damn it.
It won't start.
Hurry, Benny!
Get down!
Young master.
Roberta...
It's like the top three most fearsome women in the world.
This feels like Ground Zero.