It's the very first...
...summer evening spooky story contest!
~ Summer Evening Spooky Story Contest ~
It's not even summer dude...
Just play along!
We're all here to tell each other the scariest story we know!
Okay! You're first, lady!
You two wanna die again?
A scary story, huh...
Once, when I was in Afghanistan, we were surrounded by the enemy, and our supplies got cut off.
That was really scary.
Sorry, sis. How's that scary...?
What?
There's nothing scarier than having your supplies cut off when you're surrounded!
Tell us one of your scary stories then!
Huh? Me?
Uh... Well...
One time I broke into this place, and it turned out to be a cop's house.
And?
They get really pissed when one of their own gets killed!
I made next to nothing and ended up on the run for months!
That's just the story of one of your blunders.
That sucked.
Don't you have a better one?
Oh. Then I'll try...
I heard this from Maki-chan, but...
Once when her friend stepped into the bathtub...
She slipped and jammed her toes really hard into the tiles...
She looked at her foot, and the nail of her big toe was flapping up and down like a toilet lid...
That's not a scary story. That's a painful story!
Okay, next.
Sniff, sniff.
Yo, yo. How about you tell us one.
Fine. I heard this from somebody else, but...
This lady had a cat.
And she was being stalked and getting weird calls all the time.
Then one day she got a message on her phone saying, "three left."
She thought it was just another prank, as usual...
But one day she noticed her cat walking funny so she looked at its legs...
It had...
...one leg...
...chopped off...
That wasn't so great.
I'd-a killed the bastard if I found him.
Yeah, but at least...
...act creeped out like a girl for once, will you!
Nothing fazes her...
All right, Rock! Then you tell us one!
Me?
It's not such a good story, but...
This happened to an acquaintance.
He said ever since he heard a scary story about a little girl in a red skirt from a friend...
...strange things started happening.
Nobody paid attention at first...
But one day...
...his friend called him late at night...
He said, "a little girl in a red skirt's outside my window right now," and just hung up.
So my friend went by his place later and found him dead, hanging from a beam.
Aw, I thought you could do better.
If you ask me, I'd say it's scary, but...
Well... There's more to it...
Everyone who's heard this story...
...has seen a girl in a red skirt at their house within three days.
So watch out guys.
Hey? Wait, wait!
It's just a story!
You guys were the ones who wanted to hear it! C'mon!
This week's scaredy-cat award
Sergeant.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Roger...
All done!