~ The Melancholy of Balalaika ~
Just what sort of upbringing did you give these children?
Children don't normally know how to build pipe bombs while they're still in the second grade.
I am the mother of two children...
But I feel great anxiety regarding my parenting skills...
Just last week, these two took a lighter to a can of bug spray and burned all the hair off a classmate's head!
I'm terribly sorry. I feel horrible.
You two! Start apologizing!
Moron. Loser. Octopus-headed asswipe.
Go dive in the ocean and fart out black ink.
Apologize now!
Aw mooooom!
So much anxiety...
Just what sort of parenting are you conducting in your home!
Are you prepared to take responsibility for the young master's nervous breakdown?
I haven't the slightest idea what you're-
Goodness gracious! Don't you play coy with me, ma'am!
Hey hey... What do you want to play today?
Well... I was thinking of playing doctor!
I even got all the tools and stuff ready!
See?
Uh, gosh, my favorite anime is about to start, so...
Ooh, we can play that kind of doctor too.
Playing doctor the way the grown-ups do it.
Your little boy won't last a minute in our capable hands.
No, no, no, no!
I don't wanna! Mommy!
Let's play Unit 731!
Ever since, the young master has begun to wet the bed again!
He keeps mumbling about marathon man or some such, making no sense at all!
What a wimp, brother dearest.
Indeed, sister dearest.
If he can't handle something like that, he's going to have hard time in life.
Go apologize. Now!
My anxiety keeps on growing and growing...
I tried talking to my husband about it, but he refused to get involved.
Honey... Can't this wait till tomorrow?
Anyway, isn't raising the children your job?
Well, at least they're young children when they sleep...
How to make a shamisen
So very anxious.
But after a while...
Say, mom?
Have you seen the pressure cooker?
Oh, um... I think it's in the pantry, on the right.
Okay, mom.
So, did you bring the you-know-whats?
...you put ball bearings in that thing and I'll kill you.
I think I've gotten used to it.