I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
Now...
Now, now, now...
My name is Takenaka. Takenaka Masahiro.
What's your name?
Why do you want to know?
It doesn't seem right for you to stay nameless. That's all.
Though I don't mind calling you "bro".
Hey baby!
I didn't know you wanted to die that badly!
Volunteering for suicide, are you?
You're from... Tokyo?
Yeah. Well...
I was born in Adachi.
You go to Shinjuku a lot?
Is the Etoare still there?
They probably pulled down the Nichigeki theater, too.
Abashiri Bangaishi: 1965 film about a reformed prisoner and a hardened criminal who are on the run together
After they promoted it, I watched the "Abashiri Bangaichi" there.
I saw Ken-san there too.
That was afterwards.
I still had my black helmet and war-stick.
It was good to be young.
Do you miss Japan?
Let me ask you why you're crossing this dangerous bridge, bro.
It's not to eat.
There's not a lot of folks who'd do this when Japan is experiencing economic growth.
If you ask me, you and I are outsiders from that country.
You know...
I feel empathy towards you.
I want to know why you've become an adventurer.
I'm... different from you.
Don't group me with people like you.
Oh? How are we different?
I wasn't chased out or anything.
But you're different.
You were chased down and you escaped.
I'm young, but I know what you did.
Bro, I gambled everything on human activism and complete, world-wide revolution.
When you have the will and a mission it's not called losing.
Do you have something like that, bro?
If we're different, that's what it is.
I have that as well.
Are you sure?
A resolution and a mission are synonymous.
Then how about you?
You don't have a mission anymore, do you?
Or at least, you don't believe in it.
Hey, bro...
Cut this shit, Takenaka!
Even I understand that this Japanese conversation has nothing to do with the interrogation!
Listen up, Japanese.
I'm not as kind as this man.
We don't have time. Where are the documents?!
We're going to walk from here.
Not good as is?
I don't want to charge in with a junkie at the wheel of this piece of crap.
Fuck off!
This is the world's greatest four-wheeled vehicle, you bitch!
I'm already sick of being stuck with a drunkard.
Listen up, you fucking Irish.
Wait here until you get the signal.
If you run away, I'll hunt you down and kill you.
She says good things. I agree intensely.
Like hell I will!
Anyway, don't overdo it.
I don't want you drugged up when we make a run for it.
He OK like that, yes he is.
Even with brain flying in Mars he never mess up driving.
Let's go, "yes it is" lady.
You want ass split into four?
Not good to make fun, fucking bitch.
I heard this story a long time ago.
A man came to a city.
He turned a corner and began preaching.
"To make the world a better place."
that man continued preaching... day after day.
At first, many lent him an ear.
Some even said they would fight alongside him.
But, then they all lost interest.
To them, it didn't matter what happened to this world.
But, the man didn't stop.
Even as he aged, with no one listening to him, he continued.
Then one day, a child who was walking by asked him,
"Why do you continue preaching when there's nobody here?"
He answered,
"I thought I could change everyone."
"Then I realized that was a hopeless dream."
"But I do not stop preaching because..."
"The reason I won't stop fighting is..."
"I gambled my life on this, back then, bro."
"And I don't want to make that a lie."
Well, well. It seems that you and I really are different, bro.
Sorry.
Takenaka, how much shall we harm him?
It won't be necessary.
He's not a soldier, just a delivery boy.
He has no reason to be loyal.
Leave him alone and he'll talk.
If he doesn't talk by morning...
well, we do have soldiers here.
Make an informal court and send him to the firing squad.
Tomorrow?
We need every minute we have!
We're on the brink! This decides if the plan goes ahead or not.
Don't you understand, Takenaka?
Don't be so tense, Ibraha.
If not him, we'll go after the girl we left at the village.
She just might come waltzing in here to save him.
Three at the west gate.
Four at the east gate.
A CAR-50 at the front. Light guns elsewhere.
Any mines?
No. Camp is always moving.
Takes too much time.
We hurry, yes we should. If idiot talks, worked for nothing.
Don't worry, he's tight-lipped.
He won't talk even if the judge's trumpets go off.
Let's move in when the sun sets.
You ready, "yes it is" lady?
Perfect.
When this over I carve some meat off your ass.
You whore.
God damn it!
Takenaka!
Sorry for calling you, but something was bothering me.
I've received reports of the teams investigating Thailand.
The other three were blanks.
That Jap has the key!
Your actions are interfering with the plan, Takenaka!
You know why this is so important to me.
Hey.
What happened with the team we sent into the city?
Don't change the subject, Takenaka.
I'm not changing the subject.
How long has it been since they left?
Why haven't they reported back?
That's because...
And the surveillance team at the government camp.
That woman hasn't been found anywhere.
In that case...
Where is she?
How is it? Feels so good you can't pull the trigger?
Men stab often but usually not stabbed themselves.
I'm starting up too.
Revy?
Revy! I'm in here! Revy!
Baby, baby. Been a good boy?
If you behave a little longer, sweetie-pie,
I'll buy you some licorice candy.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Is this that idiot?
Who the hell is that?
Here's your change.
Rock, get over here!
Rock, come up with a strategy!
What are you talking about, just run!
That's fine.
Get going!
Whaaa? I've got nowhere to go.
It's your job now. Now get the fuck going!
I forgot!
I need to go to Liverpool!
It's over.
He's super relaxed.
Jimmy Hendrix is calling me!
He's telling me to defeat Klingons!
Captain P-Picard!
It's not this way!
Idiot!
This is the middle of enemy territory!
Damn it, there's no choice now.
Crazy bastards.
Split up!
Go after that Jap!
Get them no matter what!
Go after them and kill them!
Follow me!
Nothing will come of this.
Shut up.
If Rock hasn't snapped yet that means the enemy's not all that bad.
No.
Look at that.
Idiots are coming at us en masse.
Oh, perfect!
Damn it!
I understand how you feel, but Ibraha...
I have a mission I've been trying to accomplish for years.
I won't let that gangster ruin it!
Damn. Damn. Damn.
What's with him?
Here they come.
Revy, I talked to that Japanese guy, and...
Rock. Paper. Scissors!
I lost, god damn it! I get leftovers.
Excuse me.
Trade me once you take out two cars.
Did you say something?
No, never mind.
Here I come!
Jump for me!
What are you doing?
Look.
You idiot, I said don't kill them all!
The left! I get the left, you take the right!
Quit it! It tight here!
Spread out! Don't hit any obstacles!
After them!
Look!
What?
Rachel Welch and Jane Fonda are in a footrace!
Oh. I see.
Get down!
You're in the way!
Idiot!
Where are you luring me to?!
Could it be... could it be?!
The legendary nudist beach?!
Dutch, there's just thirty minutes until the time limit.
Do you have your ass settled in?
I see.
Nothing really.
You're free to use any means necessary. It's all right.
It's me, Mr. CIA.
Right on schedule, don't worry.
Don't crack bad jokes.
How about the money? I don't take AmEx.
When you get it, let me know.
Later.
What does Hong Kong say?
"We allow the bringing of justice, but do not make things dirty."
So avoid fighting them head-on.
That's a tall order.
Well, for now all we can do is wish the delivery boys luck.
Start over.
Rochambeau: An alternative name for Rock. Paper. Scissors.
How about Rochambeau one more time?
We don't have time. Here they come!
Barbarella is holding up an anti-war placard in the nude!
We've got to kill them all.
But they have too much range on us for your weapon.
Stay back.
No choice. Let's see what you got.
Saucy bitch.
I'll make your eyes roll.
Damn it!
Take this!
Oh, all mouth she not. Cool.
If we had a M72 or a minigun this would have been quicker.
Stupid. Cannons run out of ammo.
Blade and body last forever.
Best weapons in the world.
Don't be stupid. Even a knife chips.
Guns over swords.
Nuclear bombs over guns.
If we had one of those, it'd be great.
But it's set so only politicians get 'em.
Shit!
There something wrong with your head.
Leave that to pros. Bad guys do bad things.
What!? Only three people can enter the Peace Park?!
Stupid.
Rock, light one up, you'll feel better.
After them with all the base's vehicles!
Don't stop at the DMZ border. Charge in and get the documents!
Stop it! They'll all die!
Give that back!
Ibraha!
We have a job to do! Ibraha!
Shut up!
No matter what you do,
your son isn't coming back.
DMZ.
I can almost see the camp.
How is it, Rock? Having fun?
How to say it...
running away always makes it worse.
I feel like I've been running away since kindergarten.
It's over.
It went the wrong way.
I screwed up.
He's so upbeat, I thought he'd be okay.
No. The mood very important.
When I talked to the old guy I acted high and mighty.
Now that I think of it, I'm all talk, then I just run away.
Look ahead!
What? Again?
What is it now?
The playmates!
There are a hundred playmates, starting from 1990!
Attack of the playmate armyyy!
Command! Unknown vehicle has entered DMZ!
Permission to fire!
To Number Three Bunker! That is a guest. Do not fire!
To all bunkers and guards! That is not the enemy!
Our job is not a profession! It is our way of life, isn't it, Takenaka?
Then there are times when we cannot give in!
Ibraha.
The monsters in Jerusalem and those that protect them,
they're finally within our reach!
I'll show them the Red Cross camp in Beirut in '87!
That's why I've come this far!
Commander! Orders!
After the enemy!
Charge into the government camp!
Retreat!
Don't lose focus on our goal because of our cause.
Our cause?
Aren't we fighting for them?
Isn't that why you came to the Becker Valley?
Answer me Takenaka!
To all units.
Retreat.
Do not return to camp.
Move to the secondary gathering point.
Roger!
You and I can only see behind us.
As long as we do that, nothing will change.
But...
It doesn't matter now, but you were a good comrade.
It's a terrible story, Ibraha.
Has the launderer's delivery boy arrived?
You're late, Langley.
Langley's busy. There are too many assholes shitting on freedom and justice.
So where's the thing that's going to get us excited?
No! The briefcase!
Wha?
I don't have the briefcase!
Revy, I messed up!
Don't panic.
If Harry Houdini rubs the magic lamp...
Here! Just like that!
Then why did we go to save this idiot?
You wouldn't have come unless I said that.
It's covered in sweat.
Well, thanks.
Next time, deliver it in a better manner, will ya?
Or the boss will be pissed.
And Miss Rebecca.
If the chief at Buffalo Hill and the NYPD 27th Precinct heard about you now, they'd shit themselves.
Damn it.
Don't worry.
Our job is to destroy enemies of the United States.
We're not paid to chase criminals as well.
Just a little reminder for when we ask you for the next job!
Later!
Hey Revy.
I haven't said thanks yet.
Thanks.
Don't be stupid.
We're buddies, right?
Yeah.
Hey Rock.
Oh my.
What the fuck are you babbling about?
I'm never pulling this kind of shit again, you dipshit.
All the rescue expenses are coming out of your pay.
If you want to be saved next time, you'd better pray to God.
Geez.
Ah, it's Ken-san.
This is a coincidence.
Ah, Mr. "Excuse Me". How was your vacation?
It was very nice. You?
It was a pain.
The trade fell through. I hurt my hip.
I ended up leaving after a fight with my friend.
And I tried pushing what I couldn't accomplish onto the young.
All things that make me sick. I think I'm getting old.
But, there'll be a next time.
Of course. There'll always be a next time, until I die.
There is always a next time. Later.
Hey mister, what do you do?
My job...
But of course, I know now.
My job is to be an enemy of the state.
Vampires?!
That's it.
It has to do with vampires.