I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
At the entrance to the gulf,
a Buddha statue, that's supposed to bring peace to the world, stands in ruin.
Beyond that lies the port of immorality, Roanapur.
From the overland entrance to town, there's always a noose,
hanging for some unknown person.
Beyond that lies the city of pleasure, Roanapur.
At one time I was a businessman in Tokyo, now I'm a pirate here.
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
You bastard! You bastard!
I'll kill you!
Cheating bastard!
Die you bastard!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Revy, I'm going out for a bit.
Got it. Be careful.
Going out?
Yeah, for a while.
What the hell is this?
Revy!
Where's Dutch going?
Who knows.
It doesn't matter what Dutch does, when he's off.
I was just curious.
Curious types don't get popular.
What the hell is this?
I don't know how much you paid for this, but it's worth less than nothing.
You got burned.
Yeah i guess. So, the situation downtown in this place is the same too.
Yeah, international villains run around here bashing horns. They all trick one another, from top to bottom.
You're not qualified to live, if all you can trust are your eyes.
But that's great while you're still alive.
I'll take that to heart.
I may still be too soft.
They're so protected by their own independence,
that I still don't know about their pasts.
But I don't care.
That's how I feel.
Hello, it's me.
You doing OK?
Yeah, thanks.
International number 10013.
Yeah.
Send $120,000.
Under "Flyer's Company".
Yeah.
Hey, Dutch.
I'll talk to you later.
Geez.
Nice weather, huh?
How are you guys doing?
Not bad, Chin-san.
We're pulling through somehow.
That's great.
By the way,
how long are you going to work with that Fry Face bitch?
I don't know, Chin-san.
What are you talking about?
That crazy Russian.
Ever since that Ruskie got here, the market's been down.
Ivan's taken all the hotels rights, and the heroin routes.
Not even a shred of honor.
And if they get the sea routes on top of that, we're dried out from head to ass.
Get it?
What I mean is: Pull out, quickly.
Let me give you some advice, Chin-san.
Even villains have sense.
When you shipped junk to the NPA, we did it.
It wasn't even close to a
"no problem" situation, but who pulled out then?
Don't fuck with me, Dutch.
Don't bring up the past like some old bitch.
I don't know much.
But, at the very least, Balalaika has more honor than you.
We'll ship your goods at our rate.
We're done talking.
You'll regret this, Dutch.
You don't get second chances with us.
Use your head to survive, Chin-san.
Hi, Dutch.
Why don't you drop some money onto us, from time to time?
I know what's inside your bottles.
I shipped them, after all.
That bastard.
Is it true, that that torpedo boat was bought by some country bumpkin Russian?
Yes sir.
But it seems that they'll take jobs from pretty much anyone.
This city sure has fallen.
Dutch, I got it.
The new board is here.
This is the pure, unadulterated, real deal.
Pure is a funny word to use in this city.
Just get it on the boat, Benny.
Sure thing.
Geez, our crew is so damn simple-minded.
Hey, Dutch.
Wake up, sailor!
We've got a job!
Oh, OK.
Job?
Where's Rock?
I told him to wash his face, but he's taking his time.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
What is it today?
An adventure.
It was Donnie Yen's influence.
Donnie Yen?
He gives us jobs from time to time.
We're receiving a package from the Vietnamese military at Phu Quoc Island.
And since our schedule is open...
They say labor is to be respected.
What are we going to do with all these pathetic jobs, Dutch?
No wonder we can't get him out of these fucking white collar suits.
Stop that.
I like wearing these.
I remember now.
What did you do with that Aloha shirt I got you at the market?
That ugly Aloha shirt?
I thought that was some kind of punishment.
You're saying I don't have taste?
Stop that!
Got it.
Looks like they fell for the trap.
It's do or die from this point on, Luak-san.
I know you've been down on your luck lately.
You fucked up the last hunt and got chased around by a battleship.
You take care of this, and you get all the tolls between here and Kalimantan.
Yeah, that's right.
Think about that.
I told you, Dutch.
You'll regret this.
This...
Like this...
Then this...
And then.
Like this.
Hey.
That's odd.
You're...
...desperately clumsy.
Or aren't you trying?
Sorry.
You're not cut out for this.
Like this.
A monkey could do this.
Don't be so hard on me.
I never did this at work.
Rock.
What did you do at work?
I was in the raw materials research department.
So I went on business trips, wrote reports...
...made phone calls, but I think being a subordinate was my real job.
At night I had to deal with my superior's drinking.
I got my ass kicked once, when they were drunk.
That's fucked up, Rock.
What a disgusting story.
Putting up with all that crap.
You a masochist?
Putting up with it is part of the job.
No one wants to be jobless.
Everyone survives like that.
Pathetic.
Revy,
what did you do before coming here?
What I do hasn't changed from then to now.
So you were going wild at the river, swinging around a cutlass, as a kid?
It's true.
I stole, I killed, and did all sorts of bad things.
It was beyond fucked up.
Dutch, we've got several boats.
You better pray, Dutch, so you know which heaven you're going to.
There shouldn't be any merchants around.
It's a pirate's bay.
Can you find out what they are?
They're small and fast.
It's either cops looking for pirates or...
Dutch, it's a Red Alert.
Passing right by yellow, straight to a red lamp.
They're coming at 28 knots.
Dutch!
Hold on, Benny'll explain it.
Wait a sec.
There's three more. A total of six.
The first three started accelerating from the island we just passed.
The three on port side came from behind a different island.
Changing course to the left is dangerous, the ones there will get us.
The same with the right.
A basic hunting pattern.
They're fast too.
Hey Dutch.
I smell it.
You too?
It stinks all the way up to here.
They aren't cops.
This is the stink of blood and smoke.
Pirates!
We're being targeted by pirates?
Dutch, what's the background of our client?
Rock.
That observation hurts.
I've been neglecting checks on Donnie Yen's financial situation.
Hello!
Hello! Can you hear me, Lagoon?
It's me. It's been a while, Dutch.
Oh I see.
It's Luak.
There's no prey here.
Go home, before you get lost.
There's prey right here, Beans.
An old torpedo boat, with a nice wingspan.
Six on the right.
If it's Luak, he brought everything.
Damn it, all these bastards.
Chin get you on this, Luak?
God must feel sorry for your stupidity.
Once you have a pint of lead in you, maybe you'll shut up.
The enemy's got us on both sides.
But these positions, Dutch...
I know, Rock. Get inside.
Don't shoot!
It worked.
It's common sense to position yourselves out of each other's line of fire. Amateurs.
That bastard.
Don't get too excited.
I'll send you right to Hell.
They still have four ships.
Dutch, they're coming
Revy.
It's your turn.
Two-Hand's turn.
Leave it to me.
It's show time.
Can you make them dance?
Of course.
Revy!
What are you going to do?
Rock, take a break from talking about your world.
I need to concentrate on this world.
Benny-Boy.
There's two on the left, and two more to the right, behind us.
Am I right?
And one more right behind us.
That's it, Revy.
All right.
Let's start with the shit on the left.
Let's dance the jitterbug!
She flew!
She jumped ships.
Do something about that bitch!
I can't see with the smoke!
Don't shoot an ally!
Kill her! Kill her!
Kill her!!
Damn it!
Rock.
Which ship is she on?
She's on her fifth.
Wait, the third is still alive.
There she is!
Kill her! Kill her!!
Damn it. My ships...
It's a dead end.
The one who ended up dancing with hot lead was you, Luak.
Damn it.
Get the hell out of here!
We're not dealing with those demons anymore!
Wow. She did it all herself.
I said that out loud, but I thought something else.
I don't know what broke to make her like this,
but I must be broken too, if I'm standing here praising her destructiveness.
Damn it!
Luak fucked up.
That idiot. I'd like to see what his mother's like.
He shoved a burner up my ass, before he croaked.
This is a disaster!
I'd like to kill that Luak bastard all over again.
Well, well, well.
Moving out so quickly?
Such hard work.
Shall we help, Chin-san?
You must have something mistaken. It's a pathetic rumor running around.
If we sit down and discuss it over lunch, we'll get it sorted out.
OK, you piece of horse-shit, listen up.
We've got nothing to ask you. We know all we want to know.
Pray.
That's all you can do, while you're still alive.
Geez. We busted our asses for nothing. So damn stupid.
It's all right. It's just like being bitten by a dog.
It's not all right, moron.
Bullets aren't free.
Hello, Lagoon Company.
Oh, Japonski! It's been a while.
Is Dutch around?
Who is it?
It's Balalaika-san.
Hi Dutch!
I heard you went on a goose chase.
And you got stuck playing with Chin.
Who told you?
He told me himself.
He's a bit too loud to conspire about anything.
I told the other groups in the area what was going to happen.
He was dead from the start.
We'll make sure this doesn't happen again.
It was a pain for you, wasn't it?
No, it was fine.
We don't even need aspirin.
Thank you, Dutch. It's not much of a return...
but I'll let you hear something amusing.
What they call "Pleasure and Pain".
Is it cooler than J.B.?
Of course.
That's cool.
We'll have a job for you soon. I'll call you then.
Was that a call about a job?
Something like that.
She told me some gossip.
Revy, Rock, do you have somewhere to go after this?
Not really.
How about you, Benny?
Maintenance on the electronics.
But there's no rush.
Well then.
Considering the mental anguish incurred due to external interference,
as your employer, it is my duty to provide entertainment as compensation.
Therefore,
I propose a trip to the Yellow Flag, to drink away our pain.
Of course, it's on me.
Who's coming?
So, we can go till dawn?
I'm coming.
Me too!
Benny, it's decided! Get the car!
Rock, it's not a job. Wear that Aloha shirt!
I don't want to.
Despite that, there are fights that you must still take on.
Let's go. Prepare the submerging torpedo ship.