I drank too much last night...
What a headache...
Now where was I supposed to go to...
Boobs?
~ Boys and Girls ~
Rock
Dutch! Benny! Revy!
I've...! I've... turned into a woman with huge boobs!
What's wrong, Rock?
What?
You too?
Y-y-y-you... W-w-w-why... How?
What's wrong? You okay?
Are you still hungover?
Uh, well, I don't... quite...
Oh, hey...
If it isn't the handsome Balalaika.
What's up?
Balalaika
What's got you so excited, Rock?
Strange woman...
Somebody! Anybody! Tell me what's going on here!
Chang
What is it, Rock?
Chang-san?
Eda
Hey, Rock.
Nice tits as always...
Gimme some sugar, baby.
Hänsel
Gretel
I'm a boy!
I'm a girl!
I think I'm gonna lose my mind if this goes on any-
Hey Rock... How ya doin' Rock. Whassup?
Oh thank God! Revy, you're a girl!
Finally someone who's the sex they're supposed to be!
Jeez, that's crazy talk, Rock.
I'm a man.
See?
Young mistress.
I believe I heard a woman shrieking.
Garcia
Roberta
You're imagining things.
No punch line here. Move along.