I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
Are we out of those missiles' range?
Seems like it.
We're safe at this distance. Shitheads.
Let's keep our distance and watch.
Geez. What are you doing?
Hey, you all right?
You didn't warn me you were detonating it!
What if we'd flooded the place?
You're too rough.
We can't be screwing around like that.
The more we fuss, the less time we'll have.
You could have just warned me.
How do you expect me to talk underwater?
At least keep track of what I'm doing.
Just give me a signal or something when you do something!
Bones!
There's gonna be bones.
They're all over the place.
Rock, this is a graveyard that humans, living on the surface, have forgotten.
The end of those who were visited by the Grim Reaper against their will.
No flowers or candles.
No one comes and no one remembers.
A fucking catacomb without saints.
I've never liked these sort of places.
It smells like something's rotten.
If we stay too long, our lungs will rot.
Hey, Revy.
How do you think they felt when they were down here?
What did they think once the light died, and they struggled for breath?
That's too damn gloomy.
I wouldn't know anyway.
Dying without air just feels like dying without air.
How strangers die, is just how strangers die.
Thinking about it isn't gonna do a damn thing, Rock.
Just think of things that won't trouble you.
Look at this. These guys...
It's like they had the Gunfight at the OK Corral right here.
Captain?
Captain!
You bastard!
You shot the captain you bastard!
Revy, this one's probably the captain.
That Aabe guy, right?
Is his iron cross lying around somewhere? It'll be worth something.
Come over here!
This guy's uniform is different.
He's that SS.
Where's the painting?
I don't know.
If it's not here it's got to be in a safe.
What kind of mindset started this gunfight, anyway?
Panic caused by desperation?
That's a laughable theory.
Despair is the same as the end of cancer:
You've got nothing left to lose.
Well, I don't know the details, but this Gestapo was the one that shot first.
The sailors came in here to avenge their captain.
And that ended with the Last Stand at the Alamo.
On a ship, they might as well have been family.
They wouldn't have fought amongst themselves when they knew they were gonna die.
The only one that'd start shit, would be the outsider.
It that how it works?
That's how it works.
What's up, Rock?
Is that the goods?
This is the same as that image.
Yeah! This is it, Rock!
You put this away.
I'll take care of the rest.
The rest?
This is what we were after.
We're not kids on an errand, Rock.
If we don't grab everything that's worth some money, it's a wasted trip.
The captain had an iron cross with a sword.
It's got a diamond on it.
It's a little too expensive to leave as food for sea breams.
But-
Hey!
When I've got everything that's going, I'll be right back.
Just sit tight.
Don't glare.
I don't think it's the right thing to do either.
What's the distance, Benny-Boy?
It was 5,200 yards when I last checked.
We're well out of range.
What a dangerous bunch.
They're maniacs.
And seeing that they launched three at once, they're well equipped too.
They're right over that U-boat.
We can't do a damned thing.
All soldiers fall in.
Prepare for the commander's instructions!
Gentlemen! My beloved braves of the Aryan Socialist Union.
Today, at this moment, you will witness the creation of a new world!
In one stroke, we will reclaim the great order that was lost in the last great war...
...due to the interference of the Zionists and Communists.
True patriots are counting on you, gentlemen on the front lines!
This is an act of courage for strict order and patriotism!
To restore the racial hierarchy to the way it was meant to be!
Suicide Corps, salute!
Kruppen Feller!
You are the hero chosen to fulfill this objective.
You represent the courage of the Aryan race.
There has never... There has never been a more glorious moment!
I... I... cannot find words to express this through my emotion and tears.
I'm filled with emotion, commander!
I will fulfill this sacred duty at the cost of my life!
Begin the anthem!
'Raise our flag on high'
'Pave the road'
'We, the strike force, will march forward...
...towards the last battle-'
Hey hey hey.
Take a look at this, Dutch.
They're holding a concert.
It's a distasteful little marching song.
I can hear it.
When you try and live it up by raising your useless self upon a podium,
you end up with a march-loving idiot.
It's a formula that's all over the place.
What do you think, as a white man?
That kind of machismo doesn't agree with me.
Besides, I'm Jewish.
"Fuck the Nazis" was a family creed.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
So, is the beacon on yet?
They're both still in the submarine.
There's nothing we can do, but pick at each other's politics.
I'm not worried about the job.
I'm worried about the time.
That's always the problem.
If we had the time, I'd send them back to port.
I could have shown that fancy dress parade on that piece of shit ship what their Führer went through.
I feel the same way.
Damn. They're doing something.
They're lowering a pod.
At this rate there's going to be a fight in the sub.
What are we going to do, Dutch?
There's nothing we can do.
They still have TOWs.
It pisses me off to say it, but...
...we wait for our chance like a snake.
If you want, pray while you shit.
That's all we can do now.
Big catch. Big catch.
Not only did I find iron crosses, there were other goodies that'll make the collectors pay.
This kind of haul would make grave robbers jealous.
Revy.
I've been thinking a lot and...
Let's leave that here.
Hey now.
"Thou shalt not steal"?
When did you become a priest?
That's not what I meant.
Those medals are proof of what these people did.
We don't have the right to strip them of those.
If anyone has the right to those medals...
...it's these people.
Isn't that right?
It was right next to his body.
The captain had this with him until the end.
The captain left his family to come here.
To us the medals are just antiques, but to them they're priceless memories.
Is that the way you think?
I see.
Since we're here...
I've got a story that's perfect for this atmosphere.
I'll tell you a little secret, Rock.
Let me ask you this.
What are these two things?
A medal and a human skull.
That's wrong, Rock.
These are things.
When you strip away their meanings, that's all they are.
Just things.
And if you were to give these things meaning again, it isn't some memory.
The one thing that a million people agree on.
Money.
That's the only value these have. Anything else is emotional bullshit.
Is money... God?
It's power.
And a lot more useful than God.
Rock, besides this, what do you put value on?
God? Love? Don't make me laugh.
When I was a brat, and crawling around in the streets,
for some reason God and love were always sold out.
Before I knew better, I hung on, and cried out to God.
Until one night when cops beat the shit out of me for something I didn't do.
Just because I was in a poor neighborhood.
What can a powerless Chinese bitch rely on if there's no God?
It's money.
And guns.
With those two things, the world's a great place.
That's terrible.
Sorr-
Shut up.
If I wanted pity, I would have whored up the story a little more.
The moral of the story is that when you're living on life's edge, that's all that matters.
Not everyone can get off on the normal bullshit, Rock.
And one more thing:
Wealthy fat bastards that live under a palm tree,
bitches who see life's greatest work as putting on make up,
I don't want you to listen to this story like those hypocrites would.
There's nothing worse than being treated like a prostitute by your companions.
If you ever turn these stories on me, you stop being one of us.
When that happens...
...I'm going to kill you.
All right, I got it.
Revy, what was that?
Revy!
Get somewhere where bullets won't go and keep quiet, Rock.
The only ones that knock on a door in a place like this are ghosts or villains.
And ghosts don't exist in this world, so...
...what's left is just troublemakers.
We left our gear on the other side.
There's only one way to get there.
There's no escape.
One.
Two.
There's more.
Rock, that's not enough.
What you need to listen for are the guns on their belts.
What do we do?
What we do?
There's only one thing to do:
Kill them all.
Rock! Get our air!
Grave-robbers. There's two of them.
John, go around!
Rock! Duck!
Damn it. The painting!
It's Brunhilda.
We got it!
Cover me.
They got the painting.
We won't let 'em get away that easily!
Cut it off.
But Richert is still down there!
He's already dead.
Hurry!
Run, Rock!
We need to get to our gear!
The beacon's on.
Where are they?
Just above the sub.
What are they doing?
Where are they going?
Their position isn't changing, they're going straight up.
Towards the Nazi ship.
We did it, Captain.
We have the painting.
You did well!
But we have enemies.
She can't be planning on doing it.
They don't know who they are.
She's probably going to.
Dammit.
These guys shoot anti-tank missiles without warning.
Revy's current equipment won't be enough.
If she comes up, she's done.
It's over.
Not yet.
It's too soon.
Dutch.
Want to show some bravado, charge in, and all go to Hell together?
It'd make a great painting, but it won't be much of an ending, boy.
Just pray Revy's not done yet.
The grave robbers are coming up.
The grave robbers are coming up!
Prepare the machine gun!
Fire!!
They started.
Is it all right?
If they're still shooting, it means they're alive.
It's over.
Seems like it.
We got them!
They're sinking!!
Idiots.
It was your misfortune for touching our glorious inheritance with your dirty hands.
Regret it at the bottom of the dark ocean.
Retrieve the pod. We're leaving this area.
The beacons are still active.
They're drifting southeast, away from the ship.
I can't determine if they're dead or alive.
Can you hear me, Dutch?
Yeah.
And their ship is moving.
Shall we go pick up some bones?
That's too much, boy.
My nerves aren't as tough as yours.
I know.
Revy, look.
It's our boat.
So they got the goods.
Who the hell were they?
Monsters.
They're the Nazi Party.
Leftovers from the dark ages.
I don't know which country they came from, though.
Fuck this.
The skinheads got one over us.
It's not over yet, Revy.
The job we took isn't over.
Let's do it, Dutch!
Let's turn the Nazi Party into a bloody party.
Agreed.
Putting politics aside, our ship won't profit if we leave it at this.
Idiots playing heroes need some strong medicine.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
But Dutch, I can't.
I can't partner with that guy.