I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
Once a businessman in Tokyo,
now I work for a delivery company in the South China Sea.
With that, we're done transferring the crates.
Would you please sign this?
Excuse me, could somebody sign this?
It usually doesn't work out that way.
A pitiful delivery company.
To eat, we brush up against the law from time to time.
So everything's OK, Rock?
All OK, and I even got them to sign.
We should have a package from them as well. Did you get it?
Well, about that...
I did get it.
Is there a problem?
If not, ask them to use the crane once more and get down here with the package.
Roger.
So the troublemaker is making something out of himself.
Well, I'd like to say that, but nothing's changed.
It's just that his white collar look was perfect for this job.
So far.
Is he worried about the package?
Seems like it.
Helpless.
It's just a cartel's little errand.
I counted the crates we delivered, like you wanted me to.
And I brought the package here too.
Is... he it?
Once we've landed, we're handing him over to a certain Colombian mafiosa buyer at a designated point.
Revy, put him in a cabin for now.
Now, come on.
Don't you fight back.
Over here.
Come on. Get in this hole.
He looked like he was gonna puke.
He's still not a pro.
Rock.
We're a delivery company.
We take packages to their designated destinations.
That's where our resposibilities end.
Understand?
I understand.
I won't get too attached to the boy.
Good boy.
Bring it on!
Rock.
Want me to show you what you had for breakfast?
Sorry, but would you trade the baby-sitting duty with Revy?
Get over here! You!
Her professionalism is a problem in itself.
Son of a bitch!
It's no good if the package has holes in it.
Taking advantage of my kindness!
Revy...
What are you glaring at?
That's enough!
He doesn't need something as good as a cabin.
We ought to chain him up and throw him in the hold.
That brat.
We're in the middle of the sea. He can't escape.
We don't need chains.
Shut up!
Well,
it'll only be for a short while,
but we're going to be on the road together.
Can't you stop throwing food?
I won't say a thing.
Santa Maria sees through all this, you villain.
Well, there's not much I can say to that since I'm helping with this kidnapping.
You're... different from the tattooed woman or the black man.
You seem like a normal person.
It must seem like it.
I'm just a villain in training.
The people who put me on the boat didn't tell me anything.
Am I being sold somewhere?
Are you worried?
I'll be fine.
My father will save me.
Father? Aren't you an orphan?
Who said that? The cartel? They're liars.
My father is a member of one of the great thirteen families of South America.
The 11th head of the Loveless household.
Diego Jose San Fernando Loveless.
I'm his only son.
I'll eventually become the head of the family.
Garcia Loveless.
If you're after pity, stop waisting your time.
If you're going to lie, you should come up with a better one.
Pity? Don't be stupid.
What could I gain from lying now?
You're a pretty unlikable kid.
Where did you hear the name Loveless anyway? It's the lowest noble house of the thirteen families.
Though that makes it a little more believable.
Well, things haven't been going well lately.
But we've been getting by.
Father is a man of good character.
He never did anything on the side.
Business wasn't going well, but the plantations were stable...
until the mafia came.
So you were kidnapped by the mafia.
You're pretty good at making up stories.
They came to forcefully buy our land.
A geological test showed that lanthanides could be found there.
When my father refused, they showed their true selves.
They began harassing our farms.
But father still wouldn't nod his head.
That's why I'm here.
Lanthanides?
It's also called rare earth.
Don't you know your periodic table?
Good grief.
Where did you learn a word like that?
You still don't believe me.
That's fine then.
Well, it's not that easy.
What can I do to make you believe me?
What else do you know about rare earth?
Lutetium, atomic number 71, was found on our land.
It's used as a repairing medium for ceramics.
How's that?
No good, huh?
Then the next question:
The Loveless household has a dog.
Regarding that dog, what do you know?
That's easy.
That dog became a member of our family six years ago.
His name is Lazlo, a white-furred Volpino Italiano.
Revy, Rock is taking too long.
He's probably getting himself worked up.
He'll probably give us a sob story and ask us to let him go.
Told you. With eyes just like that.
That's odd.
I don't like how this feels.
I think we might want to wait until after we dock to give him to the mafia.
The cartel was lying.
If they're lying, it means there's trouble.
Rock.
Don't have pity for our packages.
You're going to feel like shit, if you imagine where he might end up.
But as long as it's profit for our company, there's no problem.
Understand? There's no problem.
The world will keep on spinning even if justice doesn't exist.
I'd be lying if I said I didn't pity him.
But I'm also concerned that our client lied.
I used to be in the resource investigation department of my company.
I know a lot about rare earth and rare metals.
And he's correct in what he says about the Loveless family.
I remember papers we had from our South American division.
Family structure and whatnot.
Impressive. That's impressive, Rock.
You're a very brilliant businessman.
I'll have to get you some of Mama's homemade cherry pie as a reward.
Either way, it's up to Dutch. I'll go with what he says.
I just don't get it.
The moment they had the kid, they could have demanded a ransom and accomplished their goal.
Is there any reason for them to keep it a secret and sell him off?
I don't know why they'd keep it a secret.
But selling him off has a simple and clear reasoning.
They were pissed off.
Mafias and cartels can't stand having shit rubbed in their faces.
Right?
Revy, if their face is what's at stake, then this is going to be a hassle.
I'm going to put a little insurance on our package before we deliver it.
I'll ask Balalaika to see what's going on.
Oh my.
It's rare to have Dutch asking a favor.
Details about the Manisarera cartel and the Loveless family.
Can you prepare that for us?
Ohh?
We've actually just got a job in, concerning Manisarera.
You have good timing, Dutch.
Thanks, I owe you one.
But since we're still just setting up the insurance, can I ask that you don't stir things up?
Well that's impossible.
What?
In our business, when things get stirred up, they get stirred up like a typhoon.
Just do your best, do it cool.
OK, OK.
Do I respond to your office?
No. We'll be having a drink at the Yellow Flag.
All right then, Rock.
There's one more thing we need to check out.
Is Daddy Loveless the type to spend personal resources to deal with a hostage situation, like the kid says?
I don't think so.
Right now, they only have enough resources to keep one servant.
A servant? What kind?
Just a house maid.
Think the maid's gonna rush in to save the little prince?
That'd be fun.
What did you just say?
I am just a lonely soul who has come all the way from South America.
I am in search of a place where I can find my countryman.
From your country?
Of course.
This little lady's countryman?
Could she mean...
There are no other South Americans in this area.
We can't really say...
Then, who might I ask that could tell me?
Miss, there is a place where you might be able to find out, but...
...that place is like a den of gangsters.
I do not mind.
So long as I can find out about my countryman there.
Miss, I really wouldn't recommend the place.
Please do not worry.
We're here. It's land.
Hurry up!
That's not the disposition of an adult.
You were a brat once too.
Then pay me as a baby-sitter.
This isn't a joke.
Revy.
Get in!
Hey, isn't that enough?
What? You too?
You gonna treat him nice and get a job at his house?
You'd be better off as a white-faced butler than as a sailor.
I see. I'm sorry.
Asking, "Master, how would you like your Mint Julep?"
Just like Old Black Joe,
surrounded by a dozen other servants and having a dandy ol' time.
I told you before, we only have one servant.
A maid named Roberta.
And even though she's a maid, she's no good at cleaning or chores.
We don't have milk here.
Then may I have a water?
I only arrived here today, and I do not know my way around.
I am in search of a Colombian friend...
This is a bar. Order a real drink, idiot.
I've only arrived here today, and I do not know my way around.
I am in search of a Colombian friend of mine.
Might you know where the proper authorities are?
Lady, does this look like the tourist department or an employment bureau?
No.
She's a klutz.
She can't clean or do chores but...
but,
Roberta is a lot stronger than you!
Of all the god-damned things to say!
She's not going to throw a teapot at me, is she?
If that's true, I'll believe that Jesus blazed across Route 66 in a chopper!
Have you seen her strength?
I haven't, but I remember one thing.
We lived at my father's house.
We lived peacefully, Roberta, my father and I.
I didn't have many friends to play with, so she played with me.
I loved to arm wrestle.
Because I could beat Roberta every time.
Roberta lost every single time.
She was arm wrestling me on that day, too...
when...
...they came.
To threaten my father.
She knew what was going on, long before I did.
She hardened up as soon as she realized they were coming.
I tried to beat her with my usual amount of strength, but...
her arm was like steel.
Roberta always lost to me on purpose.
She had a reason to always act like a weak maid.
I found out then.
Fallen nobility.
The wife died four years ago.
The ones pictured are, the head, Diego; his only son, Garcia; and their only servant, the house maid.
I don't like it.
This isn't good.
Comrade Sergeant. Take a look at her eyes.
Don't you notice anything.
The eyes of a soldier.
That is correct, Sergeant.
And that's not all.
She's one hell of a wild dog.
Woman, I've got business with you.
I heard a woman in a strange maid's outfit is looking for the Colombian mafia.
In a crazy outfit that you'd only see in Hollywood movies...
any idiot would remember someone in clothes like that.
You called us here, what are you after?
Who the hell are you?!
I wanted you to find me.
You are from the Manisarera cartel, correct?
I am a servant of the Loveless family.
I have a few things I would like to ask.
I hope you'll excuse me, but I am afraid I may have to be rude.
Did you hear that?
Be rude? This bitch!
She's making me laugh!
What are you gonna do, miss?
I'm afraid I will not be able to hold back.
Please pardon me.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Roberta!
It can't be.
I believe it!
That's a killer robot from the future!