[Script Info]
;  Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.9
;  http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-02-10 00:09:56
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:Sorawoto 13
Original Script:SumiSora&CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: opjp,Meiryo,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,5,1
Style: opcn,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,5,1
Style: edjp,Meiryo,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,3,30,10,5,1
Style: edcn,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,30,5,1
Style: title,微软雅黑,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,黑体,15,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.00,0:01:40.50,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}本字幕僅供攪流試看之用，如您喜歡本作品，請支持正版。\N若因私自散佈傳播造成法律及相關一切問題，澄空學園&華盟字幕社都絕對不負責。
Dialogue: 1,0:01:40.00,0:01:45.50,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}片源：jaka volence   翻譯：KonW 電波92   時間：mikuru   後期：yulius\N校對：ever silver 天方夜譚   友情：linzy oilon
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.89,0:00:13.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}この空の輝き　君の胸に届いてる？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.90,0:00:22.98,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,600)\be1}夢見てた調べは静けさのように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.52,0:00:28.32,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}君の手がまだ夢に遠くても
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.46,0:00:33.30,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}思い出してよ　優しい声を
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.51,0:00:46.13,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}誰かが君のため　歌った幸福の和音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.30,0:00:55.61,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}空の音響け、高く哀しみを超えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.71,0:01:05.99,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}君の目に映るものは全て本当の世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.36,0:01:15.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}涙さえ君をここに留めておけない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.69,0:01:27.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\be1}降り注ぐ光の中　明日を奏でて
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.89,0:00:13.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}這片天空閃爍的光輝  能否傳到你的心中？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.90,0:00:22.98,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,600)\be1}夢中聽到的歌聲  靜靜流淌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.52,0:00:28.32,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}你的雙手  離夢想依然遙遠
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.46,0:00:33.30,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}但請想起  聽到的溫柔之歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.51,0:00:46.13,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}那是僅為你而歌的幸福和聲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.30,0:00:55.61,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}輕聲奏響天籟之音  超越那一切的悲傷
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.71,0:01:05.99,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}在你眼中映出的一切  全部是真正的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.36,0:01:15.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}即便是滿腔淚水  也無法讓你止步
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.69,0:01:27.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\be1}在洋溢的光輝中  唱出明天的歌謠
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.47,0:27:27.99,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}愛情×友情　想い重ねて
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.39,0:27:31.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}たいせつを奏でよう
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.64,0:27:55.23,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}うれしくって泣いた　痛くって笑った
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.65,0:28:04.12,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だけどそんな全部が生きてる証なんです
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.52,0:28:08.63,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ゆっくり歩いていこう
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.66,0:28:10.19,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Everybody singing!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.49,0:28:14.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ひとさじの本音　聞かせて？
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.70,0:28:16.07,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}You're just my friend
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.09,0:28:22.02,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}愛情×友情　時に揺れても
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.04,0:28:22.02,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}I know, You know little happy
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.02,0:28:27.88,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ずっとずっと　響きあいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.96,0:28:27.88,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Can you hear my precious note?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.03,0:28:33.78,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ありふれてる言葉では伝えきれない
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.04,0:28:39.64,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私たちのHarmony
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.94,0:28:44.68,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}聴こえる　our Harmony
Comment: 0,0:04:43.90,0:04:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.47,0:27:27.99,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}愛情×友情  堆積層層思念
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.39,0:27:31.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}吹響心愛的音色
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.64,0:27:55.23,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}時而喜極而泣  時而忍痛大笑
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.65,0:28:04.12,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}如此日常點滴  儘是活著真我風采
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.52,0:28:08.63,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}緩緩邁步向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.49,0:28:14.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}讓我傾聽你的心聲
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.09,0:28:22.02,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}愛情×友情  即使被時光動搖
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.02,0:28:27.88,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}永遠  永遠  響徹你我心間
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.03,0:28:33.78,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}日常瑣碎的平淡話語無法盡訴
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.04,0:28:39.64,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我們的和聲
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.94,0:28:44.68,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}定能聽見  我們的和聲
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.19,0:01:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是  我來曉時堡差不多快一年時的某個下午發生的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.77,0:02:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厲害  真的變得很會吹了呢彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.98,0:03:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎  真是太好了  最近梨旺前輩也會時不時誇獎我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.56,0:03:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼方說過自己是因為想學小號才入的軍隊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.41,0:03:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  彼方的夢想是什麼？
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.30,0:03:23.31,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(400,277)}空\N之\N音\N?\N夢\N的\N彼\N方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.74,0:03:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢想？  你的夢想不是一直很清楚嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.91,0:03:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是把小號吹好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.97,0:03:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我這樣說後
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.94,0:03:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是眼前的小目標罷了  不算夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.74,0:03:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她卻這樣說
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.58,0:03:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米希歐這小孩還真拽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.73,0:03:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  夢想不就是目標嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.01,0:03:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正是不清楚才問的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.66,0:03:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.53,0:03:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼  疼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.66,0:03:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近在眼前且知道完成方法的是目標
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.70,0:04:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而遠在它方飄忽不定的就是夢想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.17,0:04:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飄忽不定
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.76,0:04:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.62,0:04:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛  你沒有自己的夢想嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.69,0:04:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暮羽有嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.72,0:04:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.70,0:04:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.26,0:04:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢…夢想  是不能隨便對他人說的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.79,0:04:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乃繪留也有嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.67,0:04:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有  是秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.41,0:04:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近你和梨旺前輩在暗地裡搞著什麼吧  和這有關係嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.55,0:04:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是興趣  不是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.07,0:04:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.04,0:04:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那為什麼是秘密啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.51,0:04:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是說出來了  好像就會沒那感覺了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.56,0:04:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊  夢想嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.75,0:04:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說來  我好像確實沒有那種
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.12,0:04:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大大的  飄忽遙遠的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.23,0:04:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此一想就會覺得好寂寥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.17,0:05:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨旺前輩有嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.76,0:05:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是有吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.02,0:05:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.10,0:05:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吹好小號也夠算是一個不錯的大目標了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.68,0:05:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用沮喪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.84,0:05:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話是這麼說
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.66,0:05:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那麼急著長大
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.88,0:05:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.12,0:05:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  給無夢少女一個當前的目標吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.47,0:05:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在要出去一下  我回來前搞定之前的那個樂譜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.74,0:05:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直到第三樂章  徹底練熟它
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.82,0:05:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那個那麼的難
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.41,0:05:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回來後可得吹給我聽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.05,0:05:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真是讓人期待
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.43,0:05:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.13,0:06:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過也對  目前得從自己能做到的事情慢慢開始
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.55,0:06:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.71,0:06:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克勞斯先生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.41,0:06:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺和往常有點不一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.36,0:06:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  可能是因為我剪頭髮了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.88,0:06:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊  我是來把這個交給梨旺的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.13,0:06:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是從羅馬皇帝直遞的專用郵件
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.23,0:06:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是第一次送這樣的郵件
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.51,0:06:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且好像必須要對方收到的證據
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.28,0:06:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒簽名的話我還回不去  梨旺呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.86,0:06:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,急嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.86,0:06:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  希望能盡快
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.67,0:06:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我直接去找她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.00,0:06:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了  克勞斯先生  你有自己的夢想嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.18,0:06:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有啊  若我能幹到能領養老金
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.71,0:07:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我準備回老家種個大大的田
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.28,0:07:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.15,0:07:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  超大的那種
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.92,0:07:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後  大口大口地吃自己種的好米
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.05,0:07:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  真棒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.11,0:07:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常年做我這種只是東奔西跑送東西的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.00,0:07:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就會想要自己動手做些什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.52,0:07:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的話很讓我受益  謝謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.53,0:07:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暮羽在食堂準備午飯  方便的話我的那份就請克勞斯先生吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.07,0:07:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暮羽肯定會很高興的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.91,0:07:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.39,0:07:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是節日的準備
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.08,0:08:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧  彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.81,0:08:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美娜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.54,0:08:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真嚇了我一跳  就看到你直往那衝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.80,0:08:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我剛學會開車  還不怎麼熟
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.47,0:08:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開車不能東張西望
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.99,0:08:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.38,0:08:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米希歐這樣說了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.96,0:08:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  她問我的夢想是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.06,0:08:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我卻沒有自己的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.11,0:08:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想到了為什麼米希歐會提這樣的問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.23,0:08:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼方  看前面  前面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.27,0:09:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.14,0:09:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美娜
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.01,0:09:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.87,0:09:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美娜
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.59,0:09:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.05,0:09:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美娜
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.87,0:09:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼方  沒問題嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.02,0:09:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美娜  我好像不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.21,0:09:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能不行！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.00,0:09:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.03,0:09:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.04,0:09:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美娜
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.31,0:09:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝萬神  我還活著
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.48,0:09:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.42,0:09:51.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個叫繪馬  據司祭說是這裡自古就有的一種習俗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.66,0:09:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寫上自己的願望  神就會聽到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.75,0:10:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛好馬上就是今年的潑水節  大家就想也來試試
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.11,0:10:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了  塞亞寫的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.33,0:10:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和彼方姐姐結婚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.46,0:10:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.96,0:10:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的感想呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.52,0:10:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感到很榮幸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.05,0:10:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞亞  真是可惜了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.74,0:10:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來你還無法得到彼方小姐的青睞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.51,0:10:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦  我只是  結婚什麼的根本沒想過
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.54,0:10:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  米希歐應該可以放心了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.41,0:10:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道嗎  米希歐喜歡的就是塞亞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.26,0:10:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才問的彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.52,0:10:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的夢想是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.79,0:10:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可愛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.41,0:11:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  大家都有自己的夢想呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.17,0:11:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺真是耀眼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.97,0:11:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不彼方也試試吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.39,0:11:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美娜有自己的夢想嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.36,0:11:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我身為神的侍奉者
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.15,0:11:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  若能還俗  我想
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.94,0:11:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當個裁縫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.84,0:11:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是洋裝的裁縫嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.84,0:11:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  要製作五顏六色的可愛的服飾
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.80,0:11:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軟軟的輕飄飄的禮服之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.89,0:11:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光穿上就能無比華麗無比幸福的那種
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.24,0:11:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得還是現在的更適合你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.88,0:11:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有夢想真是好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.65,0:12:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美好的夢想嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.00,0:12:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是彼方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.68,0:12:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真理亞
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.38,0:12:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨旺去玻璃工廠了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.41,0:12:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真理亞也找她嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.82,0:12:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  老爸說訂的東西做好了叫我送去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.53,0:12:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真理亞  為什麼在玻璃工廠打工呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.23,0:12:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我的夢想正是做出不比老爸差的作品然後在這裡賣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.12,0:12:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.57,0:12:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰要把棄家而去的女兒的作品擺上架啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.32,0:12:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真過分呢  媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.23,0:12:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你自己選擇跟那死木頭學藝的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.27,0:12:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我娜奧美  或者大姐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.39,0:12:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  媽媽什麼的  選擇跟誰什麼的是在說…？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.28,0:12:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  彼方不知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.76,0:13:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實老爸和娜奧美原本是夫妻哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.58,0:13:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年輕氣盛一時衝動的錯誤
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.71,0:13:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他們愛的結晶就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.89,0:13:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  證據都在照片裡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.55,0:13:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼分手了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.93,0:13:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難以回答的問題你居然那麼直接說出來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.50,0:13:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.76,0:13:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是  夢想不一樣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.02,0:13:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我來說這個商店最重要  而對他來說是擺弄玻璃
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.68,0:13:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互相都難以讓步
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.47,0:13:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時真是年輕呢  兩人都
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.42,0:13:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他倆結合的結果就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.80,0:14:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路上小心  不要光顧著看風景
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.49,0:14:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.39,0:14:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  這個就拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.44,0:14:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.26,0:14:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,項鏈  就是炎之少女用的那個
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.25,0:14:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過真是怪呢  時間上來看我一定和梨旺在哪擦肩而過了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.05,0:14:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼方  說不定梨旺正在途中什麼地方發呆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.31,0:14:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也多注意下路邊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.69,0:14:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  也可能是我多嘴了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.97,0:14:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼今年的炎之少女也要堡裡的人當了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.96,0:14:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.15,0:14:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.73,0:15:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  你也聽彼方她們說了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.05,0:15:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅馬來的那個叫愛莎的女孩子所說的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.19,0:15:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅馬版的炎之少女傳說
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.16,0:15:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挺在意所以去查了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.20,0:15:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後發現
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.81,0:15:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來羅馬所傳承的故事  更接近原型
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.53,0:15:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久之前把少女們逼進死路的人們
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.01,0:15:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了追悼她們而創立的祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.13,0:15:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不覺中變成了讚揚少女們的自我犧牲
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.99,0:15:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.11,0:15:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,潑水節的真相嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.59,0:15:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.01,0:16:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發現梨旺前輩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.36,0:16:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我嗎  抱歉  我在想一些事情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.53,0:16:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是關於炎之少女的事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.88,0:16:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你聽娜奧美說的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.51,0:16:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.99,0:16:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼想
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.52,0:16:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天一天都在到處打聽別人的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.99,0:16:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都有著美妙的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.49,0:16:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是我在想
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.21,0:16:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我不知道很久之前究竟發生過什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.57,0:16:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  能有這麼一座城鎮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.95,0:16:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城裡的人們能擁有夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.54,0:16:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是拜炎之少女所賜的話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.30,0:16:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是一件挺好的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.21,0:17:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算人們不清楚真相
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.62,0:17:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也能夠隱約感覺到
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.44,0:17:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才懷抱著愧疚與感謝之情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.81,0:17:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舉辦這麼一個祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.79,0:17:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢想嗎  沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.99,0:17:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因有過去才有現在
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.13,0:17:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後  正因為有現在  才會相信明天追尋夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.37,0:17:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.20,0:17:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了  我還有一件東西要交給前輩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.10,0:17:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.46,0:17:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.69,0:17:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克勞斯先生要你簽收  否則他不能回去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.62,0:17:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎  有勞你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.81,0:17:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前輩真的是公主啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.65,0:17:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能收到皇帝的信  太厲害了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.25,0:17:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說  彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.67,0:18:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界正在走向終結  你聽說過嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.10,0:18:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多多少少聽說過
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.61,0:18:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而卻依然戰火不斷
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.52,0:18:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅馬與赫爾維西亞之間也許能暫時平息干戈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.73,0:18:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  與羅馬國境接壤的還有加利亞和弗蘭克
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.79,0:18:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及西方的超級大國  元  目前許多國家依然被戰火所籠罩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.23,0:18:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相互爭奪著人類僅剩的土地
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.08,0:18:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,削減著本來就為數不多的人口
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.41,0:18:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僅剩的土地？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.33,0:18:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.45,0:18:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是第一次看到吧  這是世界地圖
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.07,0:18:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是在羅馬繪製的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.12,0:18:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為有未探索區域及人類無法涉足的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.29,0:18:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以有不少地方純屬推測
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.28,0:19:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡是赫爾維西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.24,0:19:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼小的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.54,0:19:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你看這麼一大片
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.54,0:19:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個曾被稱為歐羅西亞大陸的大部分
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.13,0:19:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今已經成為死亡地帶「無人之地」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.49,0:19:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且「無人之地」現在還在不斷擴張
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.88,0:19:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞茲國境附近還算好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.14,0:19:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但羅馬的北部正不斷被沙漠侵蝕
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.10,0:19:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人預測不久的將來羅馬舉國會被沙漠所吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.70,0:19:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抱著出嫁的覺悟前往羅馬
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.59,0:19:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親眼目睹了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.74,0:19:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界真的在走向滅亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.23,0:19:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來必須分秒必爭地停止戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.96,0:20:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在世界終結之前
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.49,0:20:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道這就是前輩的夢想嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.95,0:20:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,創造一個和平的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.22,0:20:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.34,0:20:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬要說的話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.15,0:20:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  按米希歐的說法
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.88,0:20:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這叫目標
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.24,0:20:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那前輩的夢想是什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.03,0:20:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.59,0:20:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.28,0:20:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.41,0:20:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乃繪留
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.53,0:20:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.30,0:20:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的飄起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.76,0:21:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像成功了  不愧是乃繪留
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.20,0:21:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.51,0:21:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒好棒  前輩快看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.50,0:21:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,建御雷神變得這麼小
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.45,0:21:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看城鎮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.72,0:21:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我夢想的第一步
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.25,0:21:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小時候聽母親說過
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.51,0:22:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界盡頭的某處有一片重生的海洋
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.00,0:22:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡有孕育著新生命的土地
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.60,0:22:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要尋找它
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.54,0:22:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以這個氣球為開端
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.90,0:22:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一步是讓飛機重現
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.36,0:22:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搭著舊時代裡人類能像鳥兒一樣飛翔的機器
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.06,0:22:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後向著它進發
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.18,0:22:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界的盡頭  甚至到達它的彼端
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.05,0:22:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界盡頭的彼端？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.96,0:22:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前還是夢想而已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.92,0:22:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一個模糊的藍圖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.05,0:22:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過總有一天我會一步步的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.41,0:22:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令這個夢想成真
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.04,0:23:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來  決定今年的炎之少女吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.99,0:23:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要抽籤
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.08,0:23:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.91,0:23:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看上一年…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.48,0:23:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.28,0:23:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就來猜拳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.34,0:23:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一回定勝負
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.11,0:23:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有請主角登場
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.45,0:23:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鏘鏘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.35,0:23:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  太適合你了  小彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.58,0:23:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.34,0:23:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  最後來畫龍點睛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.52,0:23:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從你來到這裡  剛好過了一年
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.10,0:24:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是光陰似箭
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.56,0:24:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨旺前輩  我決定好我的夢想了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.29,0:24:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以一直追隨著前輩嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.79,0:24:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和前輩追尋同樣的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.93,0:24:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.12,0:24:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.79,0:24:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要追隨我的夢想嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.85,0:24:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了  我寫好這個了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.02,0:24:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以看看嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.87,0:24:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨你的便
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.61,0:24:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望可以成為軍醫  拯救很多人的性命
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.11,0:24:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過去  我的夢想就是姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.21,0:25:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是現在…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.86,0:25:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  真好
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.18,0:25:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽曾經當過醫護兵
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.98,0:25:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在愛莎中槍的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.47,0:25:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨我身為媽媽的女兒卻幫不上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.24,0:25:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暮羽的話  一定能行的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.76,0:25:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也寫了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.35,0:25:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成為可愛的新娘
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.91,0:25:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事  乃繪留一定做得到
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.81,0:25:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對對  一定會有人好你這口的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.26,0:25:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.57,0:25:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我擁有了屬於自己的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.26,0:25:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你寫了什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.47,0:25:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我寫了「希望能和大家永遠在一起」
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.81,0:26:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老土
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.65,0:26:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真過分
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.41,0:26:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以終有一天
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.49,0:26:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也能找到自己的夢想  開始前進
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.08,0:26:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不為他人  只屬於你的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.64,0:26:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.71,0:26:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前我會牽著你的手
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.42,0:26:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到你找到自己的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.81,0:26:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到屬於自己的音色
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.39,0:26:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始演奏的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.12,0:26:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能聽見
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.92,0:26:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢想的腳步聲  未來的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.02,0:26:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路走好  我會一直留在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.06,0:26:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓大家無論去到何方都可以回來
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.67,0:26:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲利西婭
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.61,0:26:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨旺前輩
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.71,0:26:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨旺前輩  快來
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.38,0:26:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  走向夢想的彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.84,0:27:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使世界會走向終結
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.33,0:27:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那一刻到來之前  我們都有自己的未來


