[Script Info]
;  Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.9
;  http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-02-10 00:09:14
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:Sora no Woto 01
Original Script:SumiSora&CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: opjp,Meiryo,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,5,1
Style: opcn,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,5,1
Style: edjp,Meiryo,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,3,30,10,5,1
Style: edcn,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,30,5,1
Style: title,微软雅黑,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,黑体,15,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.00,0:00:07.50,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}本字幕僅供攪流試看之用，如您喜歡本作品，請支持正版。\N若因私自散佈傳播造成法律及相關一切問題，澄空學園&華盟字幕社都絕對不負責。
Dialogue: 1,0:00:07.00,0:00:12.50,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}片源：jaka volence   翻譯：KonW 電波92   時間：mikuru   後期：yulius\N校對：ever silver 天方夜譚   友情：linzy oilon
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.94,0:02:22.13,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}この空の輝き　君の胸に届いてる？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.95,0:02:32.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,600)\be1}夢見てた調べは静けさのように
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.57,0:02:37.37,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}君の手がまだ夢に遠くても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.51,0:02:42.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}思い出してよ　優しい声を
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.56,0:02:55.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}誰かが君のため　歌った幸福の和音
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.35,0:03:04.66,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}空の音響け、高く哀しみを超えて
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.76,0:03:15.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}君の目に映るものは全て本当の世界
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.41,0:03:24.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}涙さえ君をここに留めておけない
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.74,0:03:36.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\be1}降り注ぐ光の中　明日を奏でて
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.94,0:02:22.13,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}這片天空閃爍的光輝  能否傳到你的心中？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.95,0:02:32.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,600)\be1}夢中聽到的歌聲  靜靜流淌
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.57,0:02:37.37,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}你的雙手  離夢想依然遙遠
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.51,0:02:42.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}但請想起  聽到的溫柔之歌
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.56,0:02:55.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}那是僅為你而歌的幸福和聲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.35,0:03:04.66,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}輕聲奏響天籟之音  超越那一切的悲傷
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.76,0:03:15.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}在你眼中映出的一切  全部是真正的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.41,0:03:24.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}即便是滿腔淚水  也無法讓你止步
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.74,0:03:36.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\be1}在洋溢的光輝中  唱出明天的歌謠
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.57,0:22:47.09,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}愛情×友情　想い重ねて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.49,0:22:50.38,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}たいせつを奏でよう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.74,0:23:14.33,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}うれしくって泣いた　痛くって笑った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.75,0:23:23.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だけどそんな全部が生きてる証なんです
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.62,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ゆっくり歩いていこう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.76,0:23:29.29,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Everybody singing!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.59,0:23:33.80,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ひとさじの本音　聞かせて？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.80,0:23:35.17,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}You're just my friend
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.19,0:23:41.12,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}愛情×友情　時に揺れても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.14,0:23:41.12,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}I know, You know little happy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.12,0:23:46.98,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ずっとずっと　響きあいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.06,0:23:46.98,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Can you hear my precious note?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.13,0:23:52.88,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ありふれてる言葉では伝えきれない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.14,0:23:58.74,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私たちのHarmony
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.04,0:24:03.78,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}聴こえる　our Harmony
Comment: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.57,0:22:47.09,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}愛情×友情  堆積層層思念
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.49,0:22:50.38,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}吹響心愛的音色
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.74,0:23:14.33,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}時而喜極而泣  時而忍痛大笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.75,0:23:23.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}如此日常點滴  儘是活著真我風采
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.62,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}緩緩邁步向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.59,0:23:33.80,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}讓我傾聽你的心聲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.19,0:23:41.12,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}愛情×友情  即使被時光動搖
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.12,0:23:46.98,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}永遠  永遠  響徹你我心間
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.13,0:23:52.88,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}日常瑣碎的平淡話語無法盡訴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.14,0:23:58.74,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我們的和聲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.04,0:24:03.78,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}定能聽見  我們的和聲
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.40,0:00:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.02,0:00:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  那你是密史特拉來的啊  真不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.08,0:00:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我們那東西好吃  美女也多
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.43,0:01:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停戰以來快有半年了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.43,0:01:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們能活著看到這天真是  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.73,0:01:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接招  J
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.12,0:01:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊  怎能這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.70,0:01:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又來了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.44,0:01:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.76,0:01:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐  醒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.69,0:01:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的戰利品  分你點
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.10,0:01:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  牛奶糖
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.49,0:01:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能  能收到如此貴重之物  感激不盡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.60,0:01:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…  軍曹大人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.02,0:01:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼啦  據說只要能和司號兵拉近關係
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.08,0:01:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就總能順利的聽到撤退的號角
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.15,0:01:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已經不徵兵了  竟然還能看到新兵  真稀奇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.23,0:01:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,志願的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.70,0:01:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.68,0:01:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了學習音樂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.27,0:01:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.18,0:01:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.54,0:01:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.13,0:01:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老實說出來很好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.64,0:01:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是這樣啊  小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.48,0:01:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二等兵  你名字叫什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.56,0:01:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.50,0:01:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫空深彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.29,0:03:51.29,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(400,288)}響\N奏\N之\N音\N?\N拂\N曉\N之\N街
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.97,0:04:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞茲今天正過節日
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.18,0:04:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,節日？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.93,0:04:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以只能送你到這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.36,0:04:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.69,0:04:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是你的分派地  俗稱「曉時堡」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.26,0:04:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向著那裡前進
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.26,0:04:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.85,0:04:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任命  空深彼方  二等兵  到特魯瓦州的塞茲  1121小隊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.62,0:04:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赫爾維西亞共和國陸軍總司令部
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.22,0:04:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1320  任務完成
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.64,0:05:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.35,0:05:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湖泊和玻璃的城市  塞茲
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.11,0:05:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.45,0:05:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,報道時間是1500
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.72,0:05:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於能夠讓你歌唱了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.26,0:05:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方向檢查  沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.41,0:05:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時刻檢查  沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.46,0:05:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裝備檢查  沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.30,0:05:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向前起步  走！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.76,0:06:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降G調  美麗的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.29,0:06:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  是魚
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.36,0:06:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,￥10.25  哎…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.63,0:06:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊  好漂亮的人偶…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.88,0:06:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.63,0:06:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了  梨旺
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.01,0:06:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一隻沉浸在節日氣氛裡的小貓  向錯誤的方向疾奔而去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.71,0:06:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是理所當然的嘛  小貓就是愛亂跑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.95,0:06:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才可愛嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.66,0:07:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是野貓的話還好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.25,0:07:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜  那是家貓
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.76,0:07:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}喂  拿到這邊一下…快快…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.50,0:07:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是嚇了我一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.50,0:07:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過又發現了另一種美麗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.04,0:07:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.41,0:07:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.35,0:07:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  軍官小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.75,0:07:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是碉堡的少女吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.28,0:07:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.81,0:07:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了「火焰」謝謝！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.40,0:08:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.77,0:08:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你給我潑的  瞄準
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.25,0:08:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射擊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.29,0:08:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.09,0:08:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.02,0:08:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.81,0:08:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是笨蛋嗎  跟著鬧什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.33,0:09:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄成那一副樣子打算怎麼辦？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.80,0:09:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.82,0:09:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  你多保重
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.68,0:09:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝…謝
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.90,0:09:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  跟我來！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.63,0:09:31.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水溫還合適嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.66,0:09:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  很幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.17,0:09:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.90,0:09:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是個好靶子啊  不知道躲閃嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.81,0:09:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.01,0:09:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種染料乾後是不會留下痕跡的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.22,0:09:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.30,0:09:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  是節日活動吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.18,0:09:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個是源自塞茲的傳說的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.83,0:09:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傳說？  什麼樣的傳說呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.05,0:10:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炎之少女  守護城市…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.44,0:10:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你費神了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.05,0:10:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會給你記下的  那邊的修理也完成了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.86,0:10:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.88,0:10:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.50,0:10:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲利西婭嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.56,0:10:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個多管閒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.62,0:10:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真慢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.39,0:10:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真慢  真慢  真慢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.89,0:10:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還虧我特意來迎接
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.22,0:10:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們  慢慢地等吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.50,0:10:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是爸爸給你的禮物吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.31,0:10:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是個好東西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.43,0:10:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降D調
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.55,0:10:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝款待泡澡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.69,0:11:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  我不知為何總是迷路
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.60,0:11:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  也因此我才能遇到這麼好的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.71,0:11:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用謝
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.34,0:11:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  在這裡可不要迷路哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.90,0:11:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能聽懂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.13,0:11:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.05,0:11:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依稀  有一種懷舊的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.33,0:11:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是在問那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.70,0:11:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小偷！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.86,0:11:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.08,0:11:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.75,0:11:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  你要為了那種東西死嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.95,0:11:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  那個鈴鐺是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.63,0:12:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.47,0:12:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是  就這樣最好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.92,0:12:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遲到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.73,0:12:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真幸福
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.05,0:12:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.97,0:12:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有事要出門  別再迷路了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.73,0:12:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個鈴鐺  一定很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.03,0:12:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.58,0:12:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.68,0:12:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.98,0:13:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向前進
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.76,0:14:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炎之少女？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.02,0:14:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久以前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.08,0:14:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遠在世界變成現在的模樣之前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.29,0:14:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這座城鎮的山谷底下住著一隻長翅膀的惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.32,0:14:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔口吐烈焰  搖撼大地
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.27,0:14:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使人們陷入痛苦之中
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.64,0:14:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接著  惡魔掠走住在碉堡裡的少女
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.52,0:14:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她們關在地下迷宮裡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.70,0:14:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而  少女們並不言棄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.84,0:14:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用天主大人授予的金色角笛互相呼應
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.27,0:14:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃離迷宮後
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.36,0:15:02.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借助巨大蜘蛛的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.46,0:15:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打敗惡魔  並刎下其首
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.39,0:15:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨即  那顆頭顱噴出熾熱的火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.04,0:15:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去  山谷上的城鎮就要化為灰燼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.74,0:15:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少女們為了制止噴出的烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.65,0:15:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輪流地抱住惡魔的頭顱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.26,0:15:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向著燃燒的惡魔頭顱以及少女們
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.53,0:15:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村民們日復一日地潑水
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.08,0:15:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一年之後火焰終於消失
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.16,0:15:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後來  為了慰藉拯救城鎮的少女們的英靈
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.81,0:15:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便設立了這個潑水節
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.70,0:16:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒來啊  新人小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.52,0:16:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨她去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.70,0:16:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請看看  隊長  梨旺前輩她…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.14,0:16:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  跟她很合適
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.44,0:16:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交給她果然是正確選擇
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.15,0:16:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是抽籤…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.75,0:17:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又迷路了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.73,0:17:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是沒用
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.72,0:17:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然迷路有時會是件快樂的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.08,0:17:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是因為能和陌生的人相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.78,0:17:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孤獨一人  好難受
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.04,0:17:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷路？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.49,0:17:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想找媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.47,0:17:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題  只要你這麼希望的話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.92,0:17:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能傳達想要相見的心意
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.34,0:17:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.42,0:17:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聲音一定會響起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.77,0:17:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定會響起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.46,0:17:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定會響起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.89,0:18:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後  傳達出去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.11,0:18:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炎之少女  於此沉眠
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.79,0:18:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懷抱惡魔  鎮其詛咒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.56,0:18:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈願永無覺醒之日
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.12,0:18:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.65,0:18:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金色角笛  難道惡魔醒來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.51,0:18:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暮羽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.13,0:18:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要傳達到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.82,0:18:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要有人  聽到我的聲音啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.44,0:18:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傳達出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.29,0:18:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聲音一定會響起…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.99,0:18:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.74,0:19:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點起床  空深彼方二等兵
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.52,0:19:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  這裡是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.09,0:19:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕快醒醒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.78,0:19:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡是曉時堡  1121小隊的駐紮地
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.15,0:19:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天  真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.47,0:19:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給您添麻煩了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.16,0:19:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.76,0:19:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  不過…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.24,0:19:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開玩笑  但是再也別亂來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.87,0:19:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就為這麼一個鈴鐺
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.43,0:20:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.76,0:20:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小號
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.13,0:20:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這座要塞會稱作曉時堡
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.09,0:21:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.76,0:21:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和宮梨旺
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.72,0:21:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.77,0:21:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我將在號手方面指導你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.92,0:21:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多多指教  梨旺曹長殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.25,0:21:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫梨旺就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.06,0:21:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是菲利西婭  隊長的規定
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.26,0:21:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡不分軍階
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.00,0:22:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  那麼  梨旺前輩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.82,0:22:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就趕快開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.12,0:22:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起床號  吹一下看看
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.87,0:22:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.61,0:22:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次的孩子吹得真難聽
Comment: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.99,0:24:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集  初陣?椅子的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.98,0:24:16.04,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,40)}{\1c&H000000&}初陣?椅子的故事


