F
ound
er's
Festiv
al
Bu
dget
Do
cumen
ts
Having been selected for the important role of Founder's Festival committee president,
the girl's days became very busy.
You should check the budget proposals of each club
by comparing them with the amounts allocated last year.
Y-Yes.
Also, have you collected all the equipment request forms yet?
Yes, here...
Are most of the clubs doing what they did last year?
Y-Yes, I believe so.
You should confirm we have the equipment we need.
Nakata-san?
Do you have something else to do this lunch break?
N-No, I-I don't.
S-Sorry you have to help me out so much...
As for the boy...
His days were lonely.
He had been hopeful that he'd hear the girl call him "instructor" like she used to...
But in fact, there was nothing the boy could do to help.
From the moment we met
Deatta shunkan
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
Everything about you
Kimi no subete ni
Check My Soul
My heart begins to wake
Haato ga ugokidashita
Let's break into a run together right now
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Even in dreamlike moments
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
I only want to gaze at the truth
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
Inside your eyes
Hitomi no oku no
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
There aren't any big changes with the
refreshment stalls compared to last year,
so we can just check it with the proposals from last year.
That way...
I made a wish.
I wished that I could be with you forever.
Even though he knew the girl's
feelings towards him hadn't changed...
...the boy still felt a cold wind blow through the cracks in his heart.
Nakata Sae
2nd Half
Wish
Nakata Sae
2nd Half
Wish
Nakata Sae
2nd Half
Wish
I'm home.
You're back early.
Yeah.
Oh, right.
You have nothing to do because
Sae-chan's busy with committee work.
That's not the reason.
Sae-chan's working so hard.
Why don't you do something for her?
I don't wanna hear that from you.
Even so, his sister's sharp words reverberated loudly in his heart.
More and more, he felt aware of the
difference between himself and the girl.
"I won't be able to do anything at this rate."
"I'm indecisive, dimwitted, hopeless, a
little perverted, and I have nothing to do"...
Do you really have to go that far?
As a bear about to go into hibernation,
I have to make sure I eat my fill before then.
Sorry, but I'll have to eat you up.
Rawr!
That's right! I have this!
Judging from the boy's face, I get the
feeling he's thinking of something pointless...
I'm heading off!
Nii-nii, you're going already?
You're unusually early today.
Founder's Festival
Committee Headquarters
Huh? A documentary?
I'll follow you closely as you go about your work
as committee president and record it all on camera!
My hunch was indeed correct.
It'll make a good reference, and I also want to try doing non-fiction for the first time.
That sounds really interesting!
Senpai, I'd like to give it a try too.
Hey girl, are you sure about that?
Well then, let's start today...
No, would right now be okay?
Yes, of course, director!
S-Sae-chan.
Could you call me that again?
Yes, director!
All right!
Let's start with your thoughts on
becoming the committee president.
O-Okay.
Ready... action!
Um...
It's the first time in my life I've
been given such a big... um... big job...
Um... I don't know if it'll all go well, but I'll try my very best...
Good morning, school council president.
Oh, Ayatsuji-san. Morning.
Good morning. What's that?
Um... we're recording what a Founder's
Festival committee member does on camera.
I figured we'd create a record of it...
I see.
That sounds good.
Though...
Don't film me too much, okay?
Huh? It's kinda chilly in this room for some reason...
So, are things going well?
Yes, I started with what you told me before.
Okay.
By the way, make sure you don't forget about the ingredients order list for the food refreshment stalls.
Sorry, I haven't gotten around to that yet...
You should do that ahead of time, since you might not get everything you need if you do it last-minute.
Y-Yes, I understand.
Sorry.
You still have time, so don't worry.
Get the other committee members to
help and discuss it with Takahashi-sensei.
O-Okay.
I'll confirm the food ingredients later today.
The boy had never seen the girl's face like that before.
Okay, let's stop here for today.
Boss, we haven't had lunch together in a while, so how about it?
It's lonely eating by yourself.
Sorry, I have something to do.
That's cold, boss.
I guess this is all I have now, then...
Whoa, is that...?!
Onii-chan!
Sae-chan's in trouble!
What?!
Sae-chan!
Sae-chan...
No...
S-Sae-chan?
Please... no...
Tachibana-senpai...
No!
Nii-nii!
Miya!
What are you doing?!
You got it wrong, Miya!
What did I get wrong?
I didn't do anything...
But Sae-chan was screaming "No"!
Sae-chan's just talking in her sleep...
Sae-chan! What did he do to you?
Miya-chan...
I fell asleep...
Ah, Senpai?
Sae-chan, are you okay?
Are you not feeling very well?
No...
I was up late last night, so I thought I'd take a nap this lunch break...
I see.
Seriously, Miya makes such a big deal out of things.
Sorry I worried you, but I'm fine now that I've had some sleep.
That's good.
By the way, what were you dreaming about?
The boy really wanted to know what the girl had been dreaming about.
School Staff Room
Um...
About the ingredients for the Swim Club's oden, the Basketball Club's yakisoba and the Tea Club's sweet sake...
I was thinking it'd be cheaper to
buy them all from the same store.
Indeed, that sounds like a good idea.
Okay, I'll talk to the heads of each club.
By the way, did the Tea Club request for the
same amount of sweet sake as they did last year?
Yes, I believe so.
That wouldn't be enough...
It's fine, I'll beg the Tea Club directly...
I mean, I'll confirm it with them.
Okay, thank you.
Was that okay?
Yes, it's perfect, Sensei!
Okay, that's good.
Grounds
Special
For rent
Fried Dough Cake
Oden
Yakisoba
Udon
Chocolate Banana
Gym
Fried Dough Cake
In capturing how hard the girl was working on
camera, he felt that he was doing his part as well.
Those were his thoughts at the time.
Huh? Um...
An increase in the budget?
This was ten days before the Founder's Festival.
Yes.
The stage equipment cost more than expected, so the allocated budget isn't enough at all.
At this rate, we won't be able to buy costumes...
But we've already increased your budget compared to last year.
Is it still not enough?
You're right, but...
Prez, please do something!
Founder's Festival Budget Request Form
Group Name
Drama Club
Founder's Festival Budget Request Form
Group Name
Drama Club
I see.
Founder's Festival Budget Request Form
Group Name
Drama Club
So the drama club's requesting a budget increase.
Yes...
That, and the equipment the Swim Club and the
Tea Club had been using until last year is getting old,
so they'd like new equipment to be bought...
It took you this long to find out?
Sorry, the equipment checking ran late...
Well, no point in worrying about that.
The drama club's request aside, we'll figure something out about the new equipment.
Thank you.
Sae-chan.
Senpai...
What's wrong?
I keep making mistakes.
I'm thinking this big job really is too much for me to handle.
I'm wondering why I decided to do it.
Sae-chan, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Um-
Prez!
Can I have a minute?
Okay.
See you.
Thanks for worrying about me.
The boy felt useless for being unable to help the girl.
That was a pretty big sigh.
What's wrong?
Ayatsuji-san...
Oh, right! Do you have a minute?
I see.
Yeah.
Last year, just like Nakata-san, I was panicking, thinking I had to do everything myself.
I was worried it might all be too much for me.
Even you?
I worry about things too!
Well, um...
You just need to ask others for help when you need it, though.
Don't hold on to the belief that you have to solve everything yourself.
Indeed.
Shouldn't you just tell Nakata-san that?
Huh? Me?
Well, aren't you having this discussion
with me because you're worried about her?
I guess that's true...
How nice.
I'm jealous that she has someone by
her side who'll always worry about her.
Really...
The boy has a bad habit of being easily swayed.
However, the boy was thinking, "Yes, it's not enough
to just be by her side. I also have to support Sae-chan".
That's exactly it, boy!
Ayatsuji-san, thank you!
This part's important, so make sure you remember it.
Founder's Festival
Committee Headquarters
Yes?
Senpai...
There's something I want to show you.
It's almost done.
Just a little more to go!
Um... how about using this color here?
Looks good!
Prez, your aesthetic sense is really great!
Senpai, you even managed to capture these scenes too?
I've been collecting footage by
following you closely the whole time.
You know, Sae-chan...
Whenever you're worried about something or hit a wall, could you tell me?
Well, maybe I can't really be of help, but...
I want to do more than just be by
your side. I want to be your strength.
Senpai...
Yes, thank you.
So, is there anything I can do right now?
Right...
Okay, could you do something for me?
Yeah. What?
U-Um...
Could you continue to follow me closely and film me?
Um... I want you to look at me the whole time.
But of course, Sae-chan.
Um... that video...
Senpai?
This isn't anything!
Look away for a sec.
Founder's Festival
Committee Headquarters
What? Really?!
I managed to rent some old costumes from the store at the shopping district.
Wow, these are amazing!
Thank you!
If these aren't enough, I can make costumes for you.
Huh? You?
Yes.
I've made dresses myself before.
Ooh... I'll take you up on your offer, then!
Okay!
She had told the boy that her mother made the dress.
You know what wedding dress I'm talking about.
At long last, it was the day of the Founder's Festival.
Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
It would also be the girl's big moment.
Sae-chan, go for it.
Senpai, I'll do my best.
The Kibitou High School Founder's Festival will now begin!
Here you go!
It's hot, so please be careful.
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
The Best Couple Contest will now begin!
Best Couple Contest
Waiting Room
Please head to the stage wing
in the order you'll be presented.
Sae-chan!
Ooh, Miya-chan!
It really does look good on you!
Really?
I'm only doing this because you asked me to, Sae-chan.
I'm gonna let myself loose!
Hey, do we even fit with the whole point of the Best Couple Contest?
Toroko! We'll definitely win this year!
I guess everything goes.
Well, off we go!
Miya-chan, you're so cute!
I'll have to pet you once in a while!
Sae-chan's attacking me back!
Stop, Sae-chan!
I won't hold back!
Not there!
I'll get you back for this!
Senpai.
Good work, Sae-chan.
Senpai, I'm sorry.
I've been running all over the place and didn't really talk to you much...
Nah, it's fine.
Wait just a bit.
It's your Christmas present.
I didn't prepare anything for you today, though...
Sorry.
It's fine, don't worry.
Here.
Th-Thanks.
I hope you like it.
What is it?
Please take your time opening it later.
Um, if you don't mind, could you tell me what you'd like?
What I'd like?
Yeah.
In that case...
We haven't... done it in a long time...
What?
W-We haven't... kissed...
Just a little more...
Yeah.
It was the best Christmas present the girl could hope for.
8 Years Later
Go, Inago Mask Ultra Hyper Third!
Don't lose, Inago Mask!
Ah, it moved!
Do you think the baby's cheering for Inago Mask too?
Seems like it.
Indeed.
She was enjoying the Hero Show with the boy and her family.
That was the other wish the girl
had made at the shrine that day.
At any rate, let's wish from the bottom of our hearts that the two of them will remain in love forever.
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
Suki da yo
"I love you"
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
It's finally my turn, Tachibana-kun!
Yes, that's right, Morishima-senpai!
Geez...
Now I'll expect all sorts of things
because you made me wait so long.
B-By all sorts of things, you mean...
All sorts of things.
Which means?!
Oh come on, you
shouldn't make a girl say it.
N-Next episode: "Sexy".
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
1st Half
Sexy
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
1st Half
Sexy
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
1st Half
Wait, is this episode title really okay?
Well, everyone, are you ready?