Sakurai!
If you don't get up now-
Hot!
Sakurai...?
Kanae-chan.
Good night.
Good night... wait!
Sakurai, how much longer are you gonna sleep for?
Forever...
Why didn't my alarm clock ring?
It rang loud and clear, like it always does.
Though, it did seem like you had gotten up at one point.
This isn't a good thing for someone who's supposed to be the Tea Club president.
Junichi is vice-president and he does all sorts of stuff for me.
Oh? Is that so?
I can't agree with you there.
Junichi's really reliable.
Well, maybe to you, Sakurai.
Now hurry up, or you'll be late for summer class.
Wait!
It's been several months since the seniors graduated
and Junichi joined the Tea Club so I wouldn't be alone.
I'm still in a one-sided love with Junichi.
From the moment we met
Deatta shunkan
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
Everything about you
Kimi no subete ni
Check My Soul
My heart begins to wake
Haato ga ugokidashita
Let's break into a run together right now
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Even in dreamlike moments
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
I only want to gaze at the truth
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
Inside your eyes
Hitomi no oku no
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Sakurai Rihoko
1st Half
Twilight
Sakurai Rihoko
1st Half
Twilight
Sakurai Rihoko
1st Half
The section we covered today is likely to come up in your exams, so make sure to review it well.
Okay, that's it for today.
We'll start contemporary history in our next lesson.
Sensei.
What is it, Ayatsuji-san?
I have a question.
This'll be our last ever summer holiday as highschool students, but...
At this rate, it'll probably end with nothing but classes.
Don't be ridiculous!
There's no way I'll let my summer end like that.
I'll definitely make two or three girlfriends this summer!
Two or three girlfriends, he says...
You won't even meet any girls if you're stuck in class every day.
Why the pessimism?
I'm hitting on girls.
I'm gonna hit on girls all summer this year!
You're unbelievable...
Hey, Sakurai.
Wanna go somewhere on the way home?
I'm sorry.
I'm cleaning up the club room with Junichi today.
Oh? Should I help out, then?
...or that's what I'd say, but I shouldn't intrude like that.
Huh? What do you mean?
So like, how's it going?
How's what going?
Like, did things really pick up with Tachibana-kun after that?
Well...
No progress? I knew it.
Uh...
Geez, you take things too slowly.
You guys are in the same club now, so I
was thinking it'd just be a matter of time...
Uh...
As an observer, it looked like things were going well, too...
Really?
I mean, you two already look like you're going out with each other.
That's not true...
He's not exactly bright, either...
I'll give this back to you before I forget.
So how was it?
Wasn't this porn vid pretty good?
Thanks to it, I'm suffering from a serious lack of sleep.
I see, I see.
Good, very good.
Anyway.
You'll have to really send some
huge fireworks flying this summer!
Fireworks?
It's about time you let Tachibana-kun know how you feel.
Y-Yeah.
We cleaned up the place before the summer holidays, but there's so much dust already...
True.
The first term ended in the blink of an eye.
At this rate, the second and third terms
will end just as quick, and we'll graduate.
True.
That reminds me, Junichi. Have you decided on what you want to do?
Are you listening to me?
Junichi, what's wrong?
Heat fatigue, I think.
You okay?
Persistence
yields results
I was up late last night.
Why?
Well, uh, I was studying up on some stuff.
I see.
So you've been studying for the exams.
Yeah.
Rihoko, you're not tired from the heat?
Me?
I'm fine.
So if you eat well and sleep well, you don't suffer from heat fatigue, huh?
Though, maybe it'd be better if
you suffered from it a bit, Rihoko.
Huh? Why?
Well, you lose your appetite when you get heat fatigue.
Huh? Really?
Rihoko.
Aren't you fatter than you were in the spring?
Absolutely not!
Doesn't look like anyone's here.
Just saying, but I'm wearing my uniform, so I might be a little heavier than usual.
Excuses already?
That's because it's important.
But it's not like I know your weight anyway.
It's fine. Just measure it for yourself.
O-Okay.
Don't look, okay?
Fine.
No way!
What's wrong?
It went up by a lot...
Geez, Junichi!
Well, Rihoko?
Don't look!
So how'd it go?
I-It didn't change.
Oh, that's right!
Trying to change the subject?
Junichi, do you remember?
I think it was right before the
summer holidays during 5th grade.
Didn't we do measurements like we did today?
Doesn't look like anyone's here.
Let's measure you first, Rihoko.
Okay, sure.
I grew taller!
My turn now.
Uh...
What?
Yay! I win!
Huh? No way!
I-In that case, we're competing on something else!
Sure, but what should we compete on?
Ch...
"Ch"?
Ch-Chest measurements!
Okay, sure.
Well?
This is...
Junichi.
Junichi!
Your turn now, Junichi.
O-Okay.
Uh...
Yay, I win again!
Wh-What?!
Yay! Yay! I did it!
Yay! Yay! I win!
How nostalgic.
We used to compare our heights every year, and you'd always win, but that was the only year in which I won.
Yeah.
I was especially surprised with how ample it was.
What do you mean?
Your measurements. What else?
Measurements?
Like, uh...
I was really shocked with how tall you were.
I know! Let's try competing again like we used to.
Huh? You'll obviously be bigger than me.
We can just add our heights and chest measurements together.
Wouldn't that make for a good game?
Hmm... I wonder...
All right.
Now we just need to measure your chest, Rihoko.
Could you put your arms up?
O-Okay.
Junichi, are you done yet?
Just a little longer.
Uh...
Junichi.
You're done, right?
Yeah, sorry.
So what'd I get?
I still lost.
Well, at least this means we've both been growing.
Yeah.
Looks like a serious case of heat fatigue.
I haven't been eating well recently.
How come?
You see...
My uncle strained his back, so both of my parents went to see him.
By uncle, you mean the "Easy Millionaire Game" one?
Yeah, that uncle.
I've been eating nothing but watermelon and white noodles.
You'll turn into a rhinoceros beetle at this rate.
Why don't you ask Miya-chan to make something?
Nah, I'd probably have something worse than heat fatigue if I ate her cooking.
Then maybe I should go to your place to make dinner.
Huh? Really?!
Ah, well...
If you're fine with it...
I'm more than fine with it!
Please come over!
I mean, I beg you!
Well, what'd you like to eat?
Hmm... anything besides watermelon or white noodles.
At least give me an idea.
Something that'll cure my heat fatigue, then.
Food to cure heat fatigue?
Cure heat fatigue, huh?
Okay, then!
I'll make you something good!
I'd better go buy some groceries then.
I'll be on time for dinner tonight.
See you later!
Yeah.
Be careful not to trip over!
I'll be fine!
What should I make?
I'm home.
All right!
Yep!
This one?
Or maybe this one?
No, I should just go with this one...
I guess I don't really need to change it...
All right!
Delicious Recipes
Full of nutrients
Delicious
Lots of recipes!
Food
Yeah.
Let's see...
Eggplant in bonito soy sauce...
And cold pork salad, so I guess I'll go to the butcher's first.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
You there, the little lamb lost in her dinner menu.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
Cold Pork Salad
Pork 300g
Cucumber 1
Lettuce 1/2
Perilla 4 leaves
Ginger 1
White Sesame Apt Amt.
I shall lead you back to the right path.
Rukko-senpai! Manaka-senpai!
Rihocchi. You look well.
Been a while.
Senpai, what are you doing?
Can't you see?
A scholarly investigation.
Huh?
Basically, as students of the
seafood department at university,
we're using our summer holidays to come in contact with the fish here and conduct ecological research...
Mmh, smells good!
Hey, listen to me...
She's not listening.
You haven't changed at all, Rihocchi.
You still won't be sick of it after a week!
Ways to prepare watermelon!
Riho-chan's coming over to make dinner?
Yeah.
Yay!
We won't have to live on watermelon anymore!
Didn't you say that you could live on just watermelon
for the whole summer when they delivered them here?
I was pretty excited at first, but I
eventually got sick of eating it too.
Looks like I can finally enjoy my dinner tonight!
Yeah.
It's all because you can't cook
anything other than fried rice, Nii-nii.
Coming from you?
Ouch.
We only have watermelon in our fridge.
I guess that makes us rhinoceros beetles.
Hey, let's go buy some ice cream.
Okay.
Oh, so that's why you're buying groceries for dinner.
Yes.
I've already decided what I'll be cooking...
...but eel's pretty good too.
Mmh! So good!
So how's it going?
Have you kissed your vice-president?
That was out of the blue!
Judging from your reaction...
No development.
Yes.
Rihocchi.
Yes?
You can have this.
Once he eats this, his heat fatigue will be cured right away.
But...
Don't be so reserved.
Don't be.
I-I see.
Then I'll take it...
What are you doing?
We'll give you some that's already roasted.
I-Indeed.
I'll tell you another ingredient that can cure heat fatigue.
P-Please do!
Lotus root.
Lotus root?
Lotus root is written in Chinese with the characters for "training" and "pole", so it has the meaning of robustness.
I hear it's eaten by all swordsmen well-versed in kung fu.
Wow... huh?
I get the feeling something like this happened before...
Rihocchi, do you know the etymology for the word "choux crème"?
No, I don't.
In ancient Hebrew, "shook" stood for "love", and "lim" meant "charm".
I'm not falling for it again!
I've matured slightly since then, you know!
We wouldn't do anything that childish anymore.
We're university students, after all.
Fine adults.
R-Really?
You don't trust us?
How regrettable.
Sorry for suspecting you...
"Thinly cover it with batter and fry it in oil at 170 degrees"...
Thank you!
So how's university life been?
Is it fun?
Well, it's okay.
You joined the Tea Club again?
Well, no.
We're in the Tennis Circle right now.
Surprised?
No, well... uh...
Uh...
You were imagining something rude, weren't you?
H-How did you kn-
Geez, you're always such an honest girl.
Good girl.
Here. Livers included.
Make eel-liver soup.
Thank you!
I hope Tachibana will like it.
Yep!
May the power of the eel give you virility tonight, Tachibana Junichi.
Then you can get it up!
Peerless virility.
Hey, girl.
How about some tea?
Makabe-kun?
Huh? Sakurai?
Doing some shopping?
Y-Yeah, something like that.
What about you?
O-Oh, I'm doing groceries for dinner.
Well, I'll get going.
Hey, wait.
Uh, what did you want...
Sakurai.
You look really nice in those clothes.
Very sexy.
Makabe-kun?
When I look at the you right now, it's like the passion
inside me's about to burst forth, or has been awakened...
I don't know why I never noticed it until now.
Sakurai, I'm in love with you.
Will you go out with me?
But... this is all too sudden...
Don't be silly.
Love is something that always starts suddenly.
Just say yes.
Well? Why not?
Um... I...
I... have someone I like.
Who's he?
I...
I...!
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
Suki da yo
"I love you"
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
Fishing's pretty nice.
Nature is magnificent.
Wanna join us?
Me too?
By the way, how long have you been fishing here?
Hmm... about five years?
And eight months.
You're joking, right?
I did exaggerate a bit, but-
That's more than "a bit".
Anyway, fishing really requires patience.
Just like love.
Rihocchi has a lot of patience.
How are things going with Rihocchi?
Have you confessed?
Uh, please don't come at me like that...
Next Episode
Sakurai Rihoko
2nd Half
Wind Chimes
Next Episode
Sakurai Rihoko
2nd Half
Wind Chimes
Next Episode
Sakurai Rihoko
2nd Half
I'll fall!
I'll fall into the sea!
N-Next episode: "Wind Chimes"!