Founder's Festival
Kibitou High School
The 58th Founder's Festival will now begin.
Welcome.
Congratulations!
Wow!
Oh, Romeo!
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
Oh, Juliet!
Wherefore art thou Juliet?!
Oden
Girls
Swim
Club
Here you go!
Boiled egg, fish cake, and ganmodoki, right?
TL note: Ganmodoki is deep fried tofu with some other vegetables in it.
Thank you very much!
Captain, we'll take over.
You should take a break, Captain.
Thanks.
I'll leave it to you, then.
I wonder if Senpai's working hard at the training camp.
Winter Training
Extra Mock Examination
Mock Examination
Last year was so much fun.
We ran the Oden stall together...
...and went to the hot spring together...
Oh no...
Since when did I become so weak?
Senpai...
From the moment we met
Deatta shunkan
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
Everything about you
Kimi no subete ni
Check My Soul
My heart begins to wake
Haato ga ugokidashita
Let's break into a run together right now
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Even in dreamlike moments
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
I only want to gaze at the truth
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
Inside your eyes
Hitomi no oku no
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Escape
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Escape
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Escape
And with that, the 58th Founder's Festival comes to an end.
Good work!
Good work.
Yeah.
The two of you really matched each other!
I know, right?
It's all thanks to Sae-chan.
More like I feel sorry for taking until
the last minute to get the hang of it...
That's not true at all.
Thank you! Thank you all!
Everyone loved it!
R-Really?
Thank you all so much!
Yeah.
Sorry I couldn't help you guys out with the play.
Don't worry about it.
You're busy with your work as the Swim Club captain.
I'm sorry myself for being unable
to help you out with the Oden stall.
No, don't worry about it.
The freshmen worked really hard.
I see.
That's good, then!
I know!
We're having a sleepover party at Sae-chan's place tonight.
Ai-chan, wanna come too?
You don't mind, Sae-chan?
Yeah.
I'd be happy if you came too.
But...
You should come, Ai-chan!
I guess I will, then.
All right, it's decided, then!
Ooh, it's so cold!
Let's go straight to Sae-chan's place for the sleepover party.
Yeah.
By the way, what are we doing at the sleepover party?
Let's see...
We'll probably start with a game competition.
Then we'll have a chat competition...
And then we'll have a meat bun competition!
Nothing but competitions.
What's wrong?
Sorry, I forgot something important.
I was so busy with morning training and Founder's Festival preparations recently that I forgot to buy Ikuo's present...
I'll go buy it and give it to Ikuo straight away, so can we start after that?
Yeah, sure.
We'll be waiting.
Thanks!
Shopp
ing
District
Sale
Café
The next thing I'm looking forward to is probably our Christmas Eve date.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it too.
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
It moves!
It lights up!
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
Inago Mask
Action Belt
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
Inago Mask
Action Belt
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
Inago Mask
Action Belt
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
This is the same toy as last year.
Here we go!
It's time for your signature attack!
Transform!
Now!
Mask Thunder Kick.
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
Inago Mask
Action Belt
Oh no, not again...
It feels so lonely to be forced apart from Senpai...
What'll happen to us once Senpai goes to university?
How nostalgic!
Isn't that the Inago Mask action belt?
Do you still remember how to do the Transform pose?
Senpai...
Wh-Why are you here? What about training camp?
I sneaked out.
I finished all of today's stuff, though!
We had our mocks, and I did all the
subjects and wrote down my answers.
It's just...
Just?
How should I say this...
I wanted to see you so badly, I just couldn't stop myself.
You're crazy.
So, like we promised, let's have our Christmas Eve date.
What's wrong? Do you already have something else?
Actually...
Hello, this is Nakata.
Hello, Nakata-san? This is Nanasaki.
Ai-chan...
Ai-chan? Lemme speak to her.
Hello, Ai-chan?
You finished shopping?
We're geared up and ready to go here, so come over soon!
I, the phantom thief, have taken Nanasaki Ai!
S-Senpai!
Unfortunately, this means Nanasaki
won't be going to your place tonight.
Don't be too upset.
What... happened?
All right! Well done, Nii-nii!
Miya-chan...?
Oh, sorry, Sae-chan.
Ai-chan can't come anymore.
I don't really know how, but it looks like
Nii-nii came back from the training camp.
I see.
It's too bad, then.
Senpai, why did you do that?
I just felt like playing a prank, so I did.
That's your reason?
Seriously, you're such a hopeless upperclassman.
Merry Christmas.
Sorry for making you wait.
It's no problem.
Is that everything?
Yes.
Let's go, then.
Okay!
There's a lot of people out tonight.
This event only happens once a year, after all.
What's up?
Well, I wasn't expecting to get to spend Christmas Eve together with you, so this feels like a dream.
Me too.
Senpai!
I rushed to leave, so I forgot my coat.
Sorry I didn't notice until now.
Um, take my coat...
Nah, it's fine.
But...
We can just go into some store and warm up...
Ah, let's go into that one!
Come on.
Ah, but that's a...
Yup, it looks great on you!
U-Um, this...
Truth is, I saw this coat on my way to cram school.
I've always thought that it'd look good on you.
So let's make this my Christmas present to you.
But...
We couldn't see each other much because of cram school.
So go ahead and take it.
It'd make me happy, too.
Okay, thank you.
Senpai, I'll really treasure it!
Okay.
In that case, I'll get you a coat as your present.
No, you seriously don't have to.
You can't do that.
You can't afford to catch a cold at such an important time.
Oh, then I'll borrow this.
Eh? But...
It's fine, it's fine.
Mmh, it's really warm!
Well? Does it look good?
Huh? It doesn't?
Uh, sorry.
That's not it.
Thank you very much.
Now then, where should we go?
Let's see...
Why?
Why can't I get a girlfriend?!
At this rate, all three years of my high school really will be devoid of color.
Huh?
Isn't he supposed to be in cram school training camp?
Ah, excuse me.
Yes?
Have you seen this person?
Oh? I think I saw him not too long ago...
Really?
So why are you looking for him?
He sneaked out of cram school training camp.
So where did you see him?
Let's see...
Ah, over there.
I see. Thank you.
No problem~
Boss, this is my Christmas present to you.
All right, I can't lose either!
Oh, hey girl!
You free tonight?
I wonder what Ai-chan's doing right now.
I wonder, too.
We'll need to have just as much fun as her!
Yeah.
With that said...
It's time to start the meat bun competition!
Soft and fluffy attack!
Miya-chan, why are you doing...?
Well, I want to get something out of this, too!
They're seriously really big, though.
Sae-chan, can you split some of it with me as my Christmas present?
I-It's not like I could even if I wanted to!
Don't be such a killjoy!
But... what you want isn't... possible!
Why not? Why not?!
Ah, that was fun!
Yes, it's been a while since I went all out!
All right, where should we go next?
Yes, where shall we go next?
By the way, where are we?
Versailles
Nanasaki, I didn't bring you here on purpose...
Nanasaki?
H-Hey, Nanasaki...
Yes...
Ahh, that felt great!
Tachibana... kun?
Crap, let's run!
S-Senpai!
Hey, wait!
Hey there, young lady!
"Young"?
Yes?
Wanna have tea...
Man, that really surprised me!
At least it'll be a memory you'll never forget.
Yeah.
I don't think I'll ever forget it.
It's so pretty.
Yeah.
It's snowing...
I...
...felt really lonely.
During the time I couldn't see you, I felt really lonely...
I felt really afraid.
Yeah.
I was wondering how I'd become so weak...
As well as what would happen to us if you were to go to university...
I couldn't stop thinking about those things...
Nothing would change.
Even if I went to university, nothing would change.
I love you, Nanasaki.
And I'm sure I'll grow to love you even more.
We'll always be together.
Senpai...
Oh, but I'll have to go back to the training camp tomorrow.
So about always being together...
In that case, I'll make you a bento and go to the training camp to secretly give it to you.
Really?!
Yes!
Ah, but if they found out, it wouldn't be just the instructors who'd give me a hard time.
Are you afraid?
Not at all!
More like I'll feel proud of myself!
Hey.
Yes.
Once I start university, I actually intend to
rent an apartment and start living by myself.
And... if you don't mind... well...
Could you hold on to a key to my apartment?
Are you sure?
If you don't mind, that is.
I'll be coming every morning to wake you up.
Yeah.
Senpai, wake up.
Huh?
It's almost time for the fireworks.
What?! It's time already?
Ooh, there it goes!
Just in time!
Senpai, you're way too excited.
You're just like a kid.
R-Really?
Yes, a big kid.
Isn't it pretty?
Yeah, it is.
I want to watch the fireworks together with you next year, the year after, and forever after that.
Me too.
Senpai.
Please continue to take care of me.
Same here.
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
Suki da yo
"I love you"
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
Hey, Nii-nii.
Have you thought about having a
first experience during summer break?
Huh? Wh-What on Earth
are you talking about?!
Eh? I was just asking if you were thinking of
trying a new activity like diving or fishing this summer.
That's what you meant?
Don't surprise me like that.
What? I'm more surprised
with how you reacted.
I was thinking of traveling
somewhere this summer.
Oh, and where is Nii-nii
headed for on his trip?
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
1st Half
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
1st Half
Sketch
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
1st Half
Sketch
Next episode: "Sketch".
What? You're going on your own?