Hey, look at her, man.
Whoa, she's really hot!
Is she a model or something?
Tachibana-kun!
S-Sorry I took so long, Morishima-senpai.
Huh? You're right on time.
But I made you wait...
Anyway, let's get going!
My arm's touching her chest...
Is that her boyfriend?
He's so lucky to be going out with such a hottie!
Until a couple months ago, I never even imagined
I'd be dating Morishima-senpai, the girl of my dreams.
Hmm? Is there something on my face?
No, that's not it...
I was just thinking how happy I am...
Yep, yep.
...that we could be together like this.
Geez, when you say stuff like that,
I feel like making you even happier!
Hey, Tachibana-kun! Look at that!
It's so pretty!
Indeed.
Hey, Tachibana-kun.
Yes?
When will you come meet my parents?
From the moment we met
Deatta shunkan
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
Everything about you
Kimi no subete ni
Check My Soul
My heart begins to wake
Haato ga ugokidashita
Let's break into a run together right now
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Even in dreamlike moments
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
I only want to gaze at the truth
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
Inside your eyes
Hitomi no oku no
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Morishima Haruka
1st Half
Sexy
How daring of you.
So what was Tachibana-kun's answer?
He didn't say anything.
His face got really red and he was really embarrassed!
It was pretty cute, though.
I can imagine his face at the time.
Did you come across an interesting article?
Yeah!
A special on England?
This chapel...
What about it?
This was where my grandpa proposed to my grandma.
Ooh...
That's right, your grandpa's from England, isn't he?
Yeah.
They told me a lot about it when I was young.
They'd been dating for less than half a year,
but my grandpa just suddenly took my
grandma to the chapel and proposed to her.
What's more, it was my grandma's graduation day.
That's amazing...
They made a promise then to love each other forever.
I remember him telling me really happily
that's why they still love each other.
I was always telling Jessica at the time how
I wanted a marriage like grandpa's and grandma's.
Who's Jessica?
Oh, I never told you?
She's my relative in England, Morishima Sexy Jessica.
She's a year older than me.
R-Right, Sexy...
Jessica just graduated last year, but apparently
her boyfriend proposed to her on graduation day.
I was a little jealous of her when I heard about it.
So that's why you made Tachibana-kun look at wedding
dresses and asked him to meet your parents during your date.
No, no!
I only remembered the whole proposing thing just now!
Really?
Seriously, I'm not lying.
Though I'd be really happy if it did happen...
But you're not allowed to tell Tachibana-kun!
It'll make it look like I'm begging for it or something...
Yeah, okay.
Tachibana-kun!
Morishima-senpai! Tsukahara-senpai!
T-Tachibana-kun!
What are you doing here?
I-I was just chatting with Hibiki-chan.
What about you, Tachibana-kun?
I stayed up late last night, so
I took a short nap at the infirmary.
I see.
Tachibana-kun, Haruka was just telling me-
Hibiki-chan!
What's the matter?
...that she has a relative in England named Jessica who's one year older than her.
Oh, really?
Y-Yeah, that's right!
So what's this Jessica-san like?
Let's see...
She's a year older than me, a girl, and looks just like me!
Just like you?
Sort of like a me with blond hair and green eyes.
Senpai with blond hair and green eyes...
Hey!
That's awesome!
Wh-What is it?
You know...
Yes?
Do you have some time right now?
Japanese
Dictionary
Uh, what's this?
A rehearsal, a rehearsal.
Since everyone will do this sometime in their lives.
Right...
I kind of get what you're thinking, Haruka, but aren't you being a little too direct?
Th-That's not it!
Anyway, let's start!
I guess I don't have a choice.
Uh...
The groom, Tachibana Junichi.
Y-Yes!
Do you promise to love, cherish, and devote yourself to
your bride, Morishima Haruka, in sickness and in health?
Yes, I do!
The bride, Morishima Haruka.
Yes!
Do you promise to love, cherish, and devote yourself to
your groom, Tachibana Junichi, in sickness and in health?
I do.
Then I hereby pronounce you man and wife.
The wedding kiss comes next.
Hey!
Any more than that, and we'd be crossing the limits of a rehearsal.
No no, after the wedding ceremony, what obviously comes next is...
...the wedding night!
Come, Junichi.
S-Senpai...
I'm pregnant!
Huh? Uh...
What about all the important stuff in between?
Huh? What?
No, it's nothing...
Hey, Haruka.
It's true that I'll be studying medicine in university,
but I want to be a pediatrician, not an obstetrician.
Both are fine!
They both deal with young children anyway.
This is a scenario where the couple's at the hospital
for the first time after finding out the wife's pregnant.
Okay, let's start!
Doctor, how's our baby doing?
Huh? Ah, uh...
E-Everything's going well.
You're twelve weeks pregnant.
We did it, darling!
Darling?!
N-Nothing!
A-All that hard work paid off!
Did he say "hard work"...?
Hey, touch and see.
The new life we've created is right here inside me.
D-Doctor!
Is it a boy or a girl?!
Ah, uh...
A-A girl, I guess.
A girl...!
Good!
Now that we've had the marriage ceremony and a baby, a family dinner's next!
Hey, Haruka.
Are we really doing this?
We are.
We already planned this out, right?
Just for today, okay?
Well then, let's start from when the
dad comes back home in the evening.
Okay, start!
I-I'm home.
Welcome home, darling.
Hibiki, you need to welcome your papa home as well.
Come on, Hibiki.
P-Papa, w-welcome homesies!
Huh? "Welcome homesies"?
"Papa", seriously?
I've never even called my actual dad that...
Well, darling.
Dinner's ready, so let's eat.
It's the deluxe set today!
Ooh, what a feast!
I'm digging in!
Darling, open wide!
Is it good?
Yeah, really good!
Mama gets some too.
Call me Haruka.
I won't eat if you don't call me Haruka.
Say it!
No, but like, that's...
That's what?
Kind of... you know, embarrassing...
You're no fun!
It's a wonder how you got Mama to marry you, Papa.
By the way, you never told me.
What did you say to Mama when you proposed to her?
Nice one, Hibiki-chan!
Hey, what did you say?
Uh, I...
You what?
It's a secret!
What?!
Um, Morishima-senpai?
Hmph!
Let's do the rest another time.
Hmph.
You should probably have a proper
proposal ready the next time we do this.
H-Hey, Hibiki-chan-
Hi!
J-Jessica?!
It's been so long, Haruka!
What are you doing here?
I couldn't wait to see you!
I'm so lucky to see you here!
When did you arrive in Japan?
Today.
I just got here!
They really do look alike.
You haven't changed very much, Haruka.
Including how big you are here!
Hey, stop that!
By the way, who are these two people?
Tsukahara Hibiki-chan, my classmate, and Tachibana Junichi-kun, a junior.
Nice to meet you!
N-Naisu to meechu.
Let's get along, Hibiki and Junichi!
Thank you.
Th-Thanks.
Morishima-senpai's are amazing,
but this person really is a foreigner...
Wh-What is it?
You must be Haruka's boyfriend.
Just like what she said, you're very cute!
W-Wait, Jessica! What are you doing?!
Huh? It's just a greeting.
I know, but...
We're in Japan, remember?!
Oh, sorry!
So why are you in Japan?
I'm here to attend your graduation
ceremony and do some sightseeing.
You didn't need to take the trouble to come...
But you got a boyfriend, right?
Just like grandma and me, maybe he'll-
What's wrong, Senpai?
Oh, a bug. There was a bug!
It's already spring, after all.
Ah, looks like it went away.
Phew...
Hey, Junichi.
Y-Yes!
Do your best, Japanese guy!
Uh, okay...
Geez, Jessica!
You can't tell Tachibana-kun! It's a secret!
Why not?
There's nothing wrong with telling him.
There is!
It'll look like I'm asking for it if I tell him!
I asked my boyfriend for it.
I'm different from you.
Oh, don't be such a bore!
You even managed to get a boyfriend before your graduation, so...
Just saying, but that's not why we started dating.
It's just that... well...
I happened to fall in love with him just in time for it...
I know.
It's not like you're shrewd enough for that anyway.
But does he know about the whole thing?
No, I didn't tell him.
You're running out of time.
I know.
But...
But man, Morishima-senpai and Jessica-san really look alike.
Hey, Nii-nii, look at this too!
Beaver
Three Kingdoms
This volume's really funny!
It's the newest installment of Beaver Three Kingdoms!
Huh?
What's wrong, Nii-nii?
If there was a lookalike of Miya
with blond hair and green eyes...
Hey!
Meat buns, very delicious, man!
I can eat lots and lots of them!
Nah, I don't think so.
What?! But you haven't even read it!
Fine, then! I'm not letting you read it.
I'm here to attend your graduation ceremony.
Graduation, huh?
Senpai will go to university after she graduates.
That would mean we'll have less time to see each other...
It'll be pretty lonely when that happens.
Morishima-senpai!
Huh?
Morishima-senpai.
O-Oh, it's you, Tachibana-kun.
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
It's fine, I was thinking about something.
What do you want?
Well...
Nothing really, I just wanted to say hi.
I see.
Huh? Morishima-senpai seems down.
Could she be feeling lonely that she's about to graduate?
Or maybe it's because we stopped that game halfway yesterday...
S-Senpai.
What?
If you'd like, should we continue where we left off yesterday?
We'll invite Tsukahara-senpai too, of course.
Uh... You don't want to?
Um, I'll think about it.
I'll see you later. Bye-bye!
Morishima-senpai isn't quite herself?
Yeah, something's strange.
It's probably because she's about to graduate, right?
So that really is it, huh?
Hey, man.
Anyone would feel sentimental when the time comes.
I dunno...
What's up? Did Junichi get dumped?
No!
How about taking out your seething
frustrations on some part-time work?
We just happen to be short of people.
Like I said, I wasn't dumped!
Junichi!
Oh, Rihoko.
I heard that you got dumped by Morishima-senpai.
How about healing that gap in your heart by
joining the Tea Club and having some delicious tea?
W-Wait!
I didn't get dumped or anything!
Oh, really?
But rumors are flying around that you got dumped by Morishima-senpai.
It must be Kaoru.
Tachibana Junichi-kun of Class 2-A.
You have a call.
Huh? You have a call, Junichi.
Who's it from?
Excuse me.
S t a f f   R o o m
Hello? This is Tachibana.
Hallo!
Is that... Jessica-san?!
Wow!
I'm surprised you could tell even
though we only just met yesterday!
I don't know anyone else who'd greet me with a "Hallo!" over the phone.
Good, I'm glad we can skip the pleasantries.
Why'd you take the trouble to call the school to reach me?
I'll be away from Kibitou for a while.
I'm going sightseeing in Kyoto!
Cool, right?
Right...
But that's not what I called you for.
I... see.
Haruka's feeling lonely.
There are plenty of guys in England who love her.
There was Robin, Terry, Stea, and Neil the bully...
Right...
Haruka might be taken away from
you if you make her feel too lonely!
So do your best, Tachibana Junichi-kun!
Wait, what do you mean-
Tachibana-kun.
What are you doing here?
T-Tachibana-kun?!
Hey, what's wrong?
Tachibana-kun?
What's the matter? You're acting weird.
S-Senpai!
Yes?!
I-I really love you, Senpai!
I won't lose to those England guys!
I won't lose to Robin, Terry, Stea, or Neil the bully!
I won't make you feel lonely!
I see, so Jessica told you.
But that was back when I was a kid.
B-But...!
Tachibana-kun.
Y-Yes!
Know this.
I belong to you, Tachibana-kun.
S-Senpai...
This place brings back memories.
Yes, indeed it does.
Senpai?
It was really ticklish, you know!
You were kissing the back of my knee...
And you didn't stop until I told you to!
Sorry.
The back of your knee was really smooth and felt really good.
Geez, there you go again...
Oh right, you never got back to me.
On what?
Well, you said you'd probably be able to understand why dogs do that, right?
What did you learn from it?
Uh... I'm almost there.
Maybe I'll know for sure if we do it again.
Nope!
I can't do something that ticklish a second time!
I guess so.
But I'm glad.
I'm glad we could come here again.
We made memories here, so I wanted to see it one last time before I graduated.
My wish unexpectedly came true.
Senpai...
I was really surprised at first.
I mean, you just took my hand and pulled me without saying anything.
Sorry.
How do I say this...
My feelings got all worked up...
It's fine. I forgive you.
Good thing she seems to have returned to her usual self.
Morishima-senpai!
What?
Do you...
Do you want to come over to my house sometime?
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
Suki da yo
"I love you"
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
It's the first time I got invited
to Tachibana-kun's house.
I just couldn't help inviting you.
So how should I introduce
myself to your parents?
Huh?
Um, my parents will be away because of work, and Miya's staying over at her friend's place...
Oh, I see.
Yes.
Tachibana-kun, you pervert.
What?!
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
2nd Half
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
2nd Half
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
2nd Half
Departure
Next episode: "Departure".
I, Tachibana Junichi, will be a man!