Inago Kick!
Inago Mask, at the ready!
Yay, it's Inago Mask!
Go go, Inago Mask!
Go go!
Kaoru's really enjoying this.
All right, Inago Mask!
Get him in one hit!
Inago Punch!
Kick!
Wait, no way...
Inago Attack!
Damn it, Kaoru...
This wasn't in the script!
I'll show you.
Thanks to all of you, Inago Mask has won!
Behind you, behind you!
Super Change: Namako Man!
H-Hey!
Ultra Change: Kujira Man!
Kujira Splash!
Squid! Squid squid squid squid...
Deluxe Change: New Squid Man!
At the ready!
If you're wondering why we're doing this,
a certain plan came up between Junichi and me just before summer break.
From the moment we met
Deatta shunkan
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
Everything about you
Kimi no subete ni
Check My Soul
My heart begins to wake
Haato ga ugokidashita
Let's break into a run together right now
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Even in dreamlike moments
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
I only want to gaze at the truth
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
Inside your eyes
Hitomi no oku no
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Good morn'!
Morning.
What'd you call me out for so early in the morning?
Well...
Art homework?
I'm finding it hard to draw well...
At this rate, I'll be in trouble.
Please, Kaoru!
Help me out!
Sure, leave it to me.
Tanamachi Kaoru
1st Half
Sketch
Kaoru, I'm so glad you're good at drawing.
Let's see...
Oh, so you're doing abstract art?
That's pretty difficult stuff.
Uh, it's supposed to be the scenery from here.
What? It's supposed to be landscape art?!
Seriously?
Sorry about that.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?!
What? I'm fixing your work.
Wh-Why would you sit here?
I can't?
I-It's not that you can't...
Then don't worry about it!
You might be fine with it...
But...
Can you fix it?
Let me think...
All right.
T-Tanaka-san?!
Kaoru!
Oh, Keiko.
What? Oh? Huh?
You guys seriously look like lovebirds.
I'm talking about you and Tachibana-kun.
Right...
I dunno about doing it at school...
I mean, won't everyone see it?
That's a misunderstanding!
What happened this morning totally wasn't what you guys thought.
Well yeah, but the two of you are technically dating now.
Did we look like lovebirds?
Yeah.
I'm so embarrassed!
I know you guys are still really friendly with each other despite having dated for over half a year.
I know, but...
The two of us...
...don't really want to change how things are, though.
Either way, you guys should keep that sort of thing to when you're alone together.
Alone together, huh?
Alone together...
Now that you mention it, what do Junichi and I do when we're alone together?
Pretty much the same things you did before you started dating, right?
Yeah.
Hey, Kaoru.
It's almost summer break, so how about going on a trip with Tachibana-kun?
A trip?
Yeah.
It'll be your last summer break of high school, after all!
Well?!
Our last summer break, huh?
Yeah.
You're right!
Huh? A trip?!
Yeah, a trip.
It'll be our last summer break of high school, after all.
Don't you want to mark the first page of our adolescence with a memory?
A trip, huh?
So where would you like to go?
Let's see...
Junichi!
Junichi...
Junichi.
Junichi!
I'm fine with you wearing a swimsuit, a yukata, or nothing at all...
Huh? What are you talking about?
B-But a trip?
I don't have any money in my wallet.
Then you'll have to pick up some part-time jobs.
Work hard and get the money to go on the trip!
Check this out!
Inago Mask Hero Show
Looking for Part-time Staff!
Won't you join forces with the heroes
to fight the battalions of evil?
Staff for a hero show...
I've never had a part-time job
before, so I dunno if I can do it...
Don't worry!
You can count on me!
When Inago Mask gets into a tough spot, you can help him by cheering for him!
Everyone, be sure to yell,
"Inago Mask, hang in there", okay?
Okay!
All right everyone, let's give it a try!
One, two!
Hang in there!
One more time!
Yes, just like that!
All right, we're counting on you!
It's now time to start the show!
Please enjoy it until the very end!
All right.
Squid! Squid squid squid squid...
You've underestimated the power of New Squid Man!
Huh? This wasn't in the script!
Afghan of Anger!
Whoa, New Squid Man's awesome!
Go for it, New Squid Man!
Well? Do you give up, Kaoru?!
This is the true power of New Squid Man...
What's the point if the monster and MC stand out more than Inago Mask?!
Damn it, you guys totally messed up the show.
You're only getting half the pay.
We only got this much after all that work...
The staff were pretty mad.
This was supposed to be a fun job with good pay.
They even told us never to come again.
Geez, it's all because you
decided to totally ignore the script.
You're as guilty of that as I am!
Huh? I am?
You are!
Plus...
You kept taking Inago Mask's side...
I didn't like that, so I...
But I had to!
Geez, you're so hopeless.
There goes my dreams of going to a
quiet mountain villa or a cottage by the sea.
What are you talking about?
We'll find another job right away and do anything it takes to go to a trip this summer break!
Kaoru?
I got a limited-time flavor!
Summer Only
Watermelon                         Tomato Soda
40% Fruit Juice
Summer Only
Watermelon                         Tomato Soda
40% Fruit Juice
Summer Only
Watermelon                         Tomato Soda
40% Fruit Juice
It's good!
Wanna try?
I'm fine.
Oh, come on.
You know it'll be good since I recommended it!
O-Okay...
It's good!
I know, right?
W-Wait! You left some for me, right?
Hey, when will you stop drinking it?!
Geez...
Hey, there's none left...
Sorry.
Well, what can I do?
This was the last can.
Sold
Out
Kibitou Tours
National and
International Tours
Super Cheap
Bus Tours!
What's the matter, Kaoru?
Junichi, look!
A bus tour?
Limited Offer
Summer Holiday Special Plan
Super Cheap!! Bus Tour
For the first ten pairs of customers!
It's so cheap, we can even go on it tomorrow!
Yeah!
I'm so happy!
I'm so jealous of you, boss!
And I'm stuck with making sushi for the whole of summer break...
It's a budget tour on a late-night bus, though.
What? Who needs money when you've got love?
So, boss, since I'll probably be playing with
fireworks all alone by the river this summer as well...
Did you bring you-know-what ?
Yeah.
This porno will be my messiah!
So this summer, I'll be on sushi training and you'll be on man training, huh?
Work hard at it!
Bath and Steam
Work hard at what?!
Yeah, a bus tour.
Three days and two nights.
What? You'll be spending nights?!
Well, uh... It's true that I'm the one
who recommended going on a trip...
But I was thinking of a one-day trip...
It says two nights, but we'll be sleeping on the bus.
I see... You scared me.
Why would that scare you?
I'll buy you something on the trip.
You don't have to worry about me.
Well uh, during the trip...
Work hard at it.
W-Work hard at what?!
Starting tomorrow...
I'll be alone with Junichi, huh?
Oh no, what am I thinking about?
And that's how Junichi and I
managed to go on our desired trip.
What? Is something wrong?
That's not it.
You know.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me too.
Hey, Junichi.
It's a race to the bus!
Hey! Wait, Kaoru!
Kaoru, that's not where it is!
What?
Just kidding!
Meanie!
A race is a race.
What should I make you do for your punishment?
Geez...
Off we go.
Tada!
You bought a lot.
I got all the limited-time flavors.
It's just like you to do that.
Here, say "ahh".
What the hell, Kaoru?
Too bad for you!
Hey, Junichi.
Do you have anywhere you really want to go to on this trip?
Not really...
Don't be so boring.
We're on a trip and all.
That's not it.
I...
I don't mind going anywhere if it's where you want to go...
Oh, I know.
Kaoru, it's time for your punishment.
You have to eat the chocolate part only.
But you're not allowed to touch my lips.
Wh-Why do I have to do something so lame?
You can't do it?
I'll do it!
That's all I need to do, right?
We'll be taking a 20-minute break.
My back hurts...
We finally get a break!
It's tough to just sit there for so long.
It's a budget tour, after all.
No complaining or being greedy!
Okay, okay.
But to me, well... how do I say this...
I'm just really glad that I can go on a trip alone with you, Kaoru.
Geez, what's with you, Junichi?!
You say the nicest things!
Ow...
Limited-time Flavors !!
Kaoru, you're gonna buy more?
We still have a lot of snacks left.
But this is a treasure trove of limited-time flavors.
I can't possibly pass up the chance to try out flavors I've never had before!
R-Really?
Didn't you say that we can't be greedy?
This is different.
Sample
You can't buy this limited-time stuff anywhere else!
It's like a one-in-a-lifetime encounter!
It's not being greedy.
Kaoru, I know you said that it's a
treasure trove of limited-time stuff,
but this is too much...
What are we gonna do with all this stuff?
They're for everyone back at home!
I'll be eating some of this myself, though.
I'll go drop this off on the bus.
All right.
This is kinda embarrassing.
Junichi!
I've dropped off my load!
Well then, just don't buy any more.
I know!
Kaoru, won't the people on the bus laugh at you if
they see the mountain of snacks you're bringing back?
Don't worry.
I did the perfect camouflage.
Camouflage?
Come on, we need to hurry!
Wait...!
Eel and Tea Set
Ahh, I really want to try this!
Japanese Eel and Tea Restaurant
You still want to eat?!
But this place is famous for this food!
Japanese Eel and Tea Restaurant
I can't possibly pass up this chance!
That again?
Japanese Eel and Tea Restaurant
But don't we have to go back to the bus soon?
Huh? Didn't they say we have until 20 past?
Japanese Eel and Tea Restaurant
Huh? They did?
Yeah! We have plenty of time!
Come on, we're losing precious time discussing this!
Hmm? I guess they're sleeping.
Well, it looks like everyone's here.
We can get going.
Man, this was really good!
See? Aren't you glad we had it?
Yeah, seriously.
Ah, it's time.
We should head back.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure this was where the bus stopped.
This isn't the bus, right?
No, the color's different.
No, it looks different.
This isn't the bus, right?
No, it's shaped differently.
Which means...
Don't tell me...
The bus left us behind?!
I wonder if Kaoru's having fun.
Where could she be right now?
We're screwed!
Now what?
All our luggage is on the bus.
We should try calling the travel agency.
Yeah.
Hello-
This is Kibitou Tours.
You have called outside of our business hours...
Damn it!
I know!
Incoming call...
I don't want any more shaved ice...
Well?
I see...
Hey, Kaoru.
Are we all alone right now?
Looks like it.
But...
Yes, the two of us were alone at
the time, just like he had said, but...
What are we going to do?!
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
Suki da yo
"I love you"
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
I'm Keiko!
So Kaoru, how was the trip?
Well, about that...
Did anything happen?
I really wanna know!
Can you please not make such a big deal out of it?
More importantly, did you buy us something from the trip?
Don't tell me you forgot?
Sorry! A lot of things happened, and...
It's fine, I'll settle with just stories of your trip.
What? Stories don't make you full!
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
2nd Half
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
2nd Half
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
2nd Half
Companion
You just wanted food the whole time?
Next episode: "Companion".
How boring.