Junichi and I left for a bus tour during summer break.
Maybe we received divine punishment for being too excited,
but we were left behind in a service area.
I knew we shouldn't have had that eel and tea set.
Are you saying it's my fault?
You had the set too.
I did, but...
What? Stop pushing the responsibility onto me!
I'm not!
You are!
However, the two of us could never
have imagined what was in store for us.
From the moment we met
Deatta shunkan
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
Everything about you
Kimi no subete ni
Check My Soul
My heart begins to wake
Haato ga ugokidashita
Let's break into a run together right now
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Even in dreamlike moments
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
I only want to gaze at the truth
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
Inside your eyes
Hitomi no oku no
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
That's some hard luck.
Yes, we had no idea we'd be left behind.
Kaoru, you're way too weak towards
limited-time items and local delicacies.
You're still harping on about that?
You said yourself that you were glad you had some!
I did think that.
But that was because I didn't think that you'd have your times wrong.
If you figured that I had it wrong, then you
should've been more insistent in telling me.
Well, you looked like you really wanted to try it.
Stop putting all the blame on me!
I'm not even blaming you or anything!
Listen to the tone of your voice.
That's about enough arguing, don't you think?
You guys would make the perfect example.
Huh?
Of what?
Don't you know of this phrase?
"To love each other enough to have arguments".
Anyway, like I said before, I'll
drive you to nearest train station.
Sorry.
I apologize.
Tanamachi Kaoru
2nd Half
Companion
I recall there being a hot spring inn by the
train station, so you can stay there for the night.
Hot spring?!
I believe it's like some mountain hot spring.
It's a nice place in the countryside, it is.
I see.
Hot spring...
Hey, Junichi.
How does the water feel?
Nice...
Very nice!
Junichi.
What's wrong?
Nah, it's nothing.
I guess it's decided if you're that excited about it.
Y-Yeah.
But man, it must be nice to go on a trip with your partner.
Don't you know of the saying, "companions for trips and compassion for the world"?
Yeah.
Just like how it's reassuring to have a companion on a trip,
having the compassion to support each other in the journey of life is also important.
Thank you so much.
You really helped us out.
See ya. Don't have too many arguments!
What a nice person.
Yeah.
This is the hot spring inn he recommended, right?
Old Dragon God Hot Springs
Is this really the place?
I think so...
Let's check it out.
Y-Yeah.
What's wrong?
Are you scared?
Wh-Why would I be scared?
Kaoru?
I-It's nothing!
That totally scared you, didn't it?
You're totally fine with the rides in amusement parks, but you're actually scared of this stuff?
I-It's not like I'm not scared or anything!
I was just pretending to be surprised.
Um...
Go ahead and take a bath if you'd like.
It's a natural hot spring.
You two are the only customers here tonight, so take your time to enjoy.
This place is kinda creepy.
Yeah.
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
What?
I-I'm going too.
Don't tell me you're scared of being left alone?
That's not it!
You're obviously scared.
I said I'm not!
I'm just doing you a favor by going with you!
Right.
Is it over here?
I guess not...
What are you doing?
Why are you stuck to my back?
You... You think so?
Aren't you just imagining things?
Right.
What was that sound?
No idea.
Junichi, go take a look.
I guess I can...
You stay here, then.
W-Wait, I'll go with you, after all.
Is something the matter?
Your meal is being prepared,
so feel free to take a bath first.
O-Okay.
Female
Male
Well, see you in a bit.
Yeah.
Hey, don't go back to the room
without me. Wait for me here, okay?
Yeah, I won't.
Kaoru's a scaredy-cat.
Who are you calling a scaredy-cat?!
This place has a nice feel to it.
Kaoru, what's wrong?!
Something seemed to be there just... now...
Now?
Get out, you pervert!
Sorry!
Wait, don't go!
I don't mind if you take the corner.
Hey, Junichi.
Come...
What?!
Hey, monkey!
Give me my bra back!
Junichi, you idiot!
That sucked.
Damn that monkey!
That was one of my favorites, too...
Wow, what a feast!
Please enjoy.
I'm digging in!
What should I start off with?
I'm so happy!
Why are you suddenly in such a good mood?
It tastes really good, you know!
Thanks for the food.
Mmh, I'm so full!
Having a full stomach makes you kinda sleepy.
What's wrong, Kaoru?
Hey, Junichi.
I can't make up my mind on something.
On what?
How to approach our relationship.
It's getting harder for me to tell where the
line between being friends and being lovers is.
That's why I was hoping to clear it up by going on this trip.
But this ended up happening...
Junichi?
Good night.
Huh?
What's wrong?
No, my coin purse...
I'll pay for now.
Sorry.
Please come again.
Did you find your coin purse?
Well...
No way!
Did you leave it behind at the public phone?
Yeah.
I was panicking at the time, so...
Now what? I barely have any money left from paying the inn fees.
Sorry.
If I knew this'd happen, I would've walked all the way to the station last night and waited for the first train.
I didn't realize I left my coin purse behind at the time, you know.
I mean, it's partly your fault too.
How come?!
You wasted money buying way too many snacks at the service area.
How is that wasting money?
Coming across limited-time items is...
..."like a once-in-a-lifetime encounter", right?
I'm sick of hearing that!
Whatever!
Which path did we come from?
Hey, Kaoru...
Kaoru, we came that way?
I'm just going by my instinct.
Instinct?
What'll we do if you're wrong?
You can go take the other path, then.
Have it your way!
This really is the wrong path...
Wait-
Junichi?
Ow...
Are you okay, Junichi?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Over there!
Old Dragon God
Central Bus
Thank goodness there's a bus stop here.
Right, Kaoru?
Yeah.
Damn that monkey!
That was one of my favorites, too...
What's wrong?
No, uh...
No, I didn't see anything!
Old Dragon God
Central Bus
I mean, I did!
No, I didn't see anything important!
Junichi, you idiot!
Old Dragon God
Central Bus
That hurt.
I get the feeling this happened before.
Before? You did something to make a girl slap you?
It's just a feeling.
What? That's not nice of you to suddenly laugh.
But there's this hand mark on your face...
You slapped me hard enough to leave a hand mark?!
I'm sorry!
You were right.
Your instinct. We managed to find a bus stop.
Sorry.
I kept saying horrible things and blaming you...
Well, I did lose my coin purse.
Nah, I was the one who insisted on having the eel and tea set.
And like you said, I guess I do buy too many limited-time snacks.
That's not true.
I went too far myself.
I'm really sorry.
Me too.
Sorry.
Hey, Kaoru.
We're still in the middle of our trip, so let's have fun from now on.
Let's have the rain wash away what's happened so far.
That's pretty poetic.
It stopped.
It did.
Excuse me, but this bus stop isn't in use anymore.
There's no bus coming.
This is all the change I have left.
Got it.
Hello, this is Tachibana.
Hello, Miya?
Oh, it's you, Nii-nii?
Someone from the bus company called this morning.
Miya, truth is-
I don't really know why, but he apologized and said he'd hold your luggage for you.
Did you lose your stuff?
Well, about that-
I'll be paying to have it delivered back home, so don't worry.
I'm so considerate, right?
I see. But you know-
So there's no need to worry at all.
Miya, stop talking for a s-
By the way, Nii-nii, where are you?
I'm trying t-
Junichi?
I got cut.
We should look for a police box.
Yeah.
Kaoru?
But since we're here anyway, let's play around for a little longer.
Junichi, come on!
Hey, Junichi.
I learned something from all this.
I learned that I really do have a lot of fun when I'm with you, after all.
That's true for me, too.
Let's continue to get along.
My sentiments as well.
Hey!
Boss! Tanamachi!
What's Umehara doing here?
This summer, I'll be on sushi training and you'll be on man training, huh?
Work hard at it!
I see.
Is the man training going well?
It's going awesome!
I'm so jealous of you, boss!
I'll double my efforts!
We're saved.
We're saved, Kaoru!
It's like Buddha's come to save us from hell!
And that was how my trip with Junichi ended.
My very last high school summer break turned out to be amazing.
Good morn'!
Morning, Kaoru.
Tachibana-kun hasn't arrived yet.
I'm looking for you.
This again?
It's okay, I know what you mean.
No seriously, I'm looking for you.
If it's about the trip, you've already told me plenty about it over the phone during summer break.
It's enough for me. I enjoyed it.
No, I wanted to thank you face-to-face.
Thank you, Keiko.
Huh? What?
Thank you so much for suggesting that I go on a trip.
I made some really good memories.
I see. That's good.
Morning.
Sup.
Morning, Junichi.
Here, I fixed this up for you.
Thank you.
Well? Nice, isn't it?
Yeah.
You're so lucky to get help with your homework.
No fair, boss.
Thanks.
No problem.
Oh no, I forgot to draw the lighthouse.
Excuse me.
Hey, wait...
Kaoru, what are you doing?!
Huh?
I'm fixing the drawing for you, obviously.
No, that's not what I meant...
What is it, then?
Well, like...
It's nothing to worry about.
This is how you and I are.
Yeah.
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
Suki da yo
"I love you"
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
Summer break ended already.
Time passes really quickly, doesn't it?
They say that time flies like an arrow, don't they?
Hey, wait-
Oh by the way, Umehara-kun.
Didn't you go on sushi training?
Yeah. I've taken the first step in
my quest to become a sushi chef!
The quest to become an adult is the same
as the quest to become a sushi chef, right?
You have to take it one step at a time!
What the heck's that?
Oh, I didn't know you were here, Tachibana-kun.
You should perk up, boss.
You guys are unbelievable!
Next Episode
Nakata Sae
1st Half
Next Episode
Nakata Sae
1st Half
Next Episode
Nakata Sae
1st Half
Doubt
Next episode: "Doubt".
By the way, who was supposed to be narrating?