It's really cold.
But of course, we're at the beach in winter.
You're the one who wanted to come here.
Yeah, but we'll probably catch a cold at this rate.
Can I warm myself up?
Huh? Warm yourself up?
Wait, Senpai! What are you...
You're so warm, Nanasaki.
You wanted to come here just to do this?
Wh-What's wrong with doing this just for today?
I mean, we haven't been seeing each other in school much.
I've been attending cram school for my university exams,
and you're serving as the captain of the
Swim Club along with your household chores.
Indeed.
The next thing I'm looking forward to is probably our Christmas Eve date.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it too.
It's almost been a year since then.
The Christmas season is approaching fast again.
Last year was a lot of fun.
But as for that hot spring, we probably can't go up the hill since the deer have been breeding at abnormal rates.
We'll go somewhere else this year...
Senpai, about this year's Christmas Eve...
I know... I'll...
...definitely...
...get into university...
...and become a man fit for you...
Geez, you're such a hopeless upperclassman.
From the moment we met
Deatta shunkan
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
Everything about you
Kimi no subete ni
Check My Soul
My heart begins to wake
Haato ga ugokidashita
Let's break into a run together right now
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Even in dreamlike moments
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
I only want to gaze at the truth
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
Inside your eyes
Hitomi no oku no
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Coming!
Oh! Morning, Ai-chan!
Morning, Miya-chan.
Where's Senpai?
He's still in bed.
Looks like he was up studying until pretty late last night, so he's still sound asleep.
Okay, I see.
Excuse me!
Thanks for waking him up for me, as always!
No problem, don't worry about it.
I'm doing this because I want to.
Nii-nii's so lucky to have Ai-chan as his girlfriend.
Senpai, wake up.
Senpai.
You'll be late if you don't wake up soon.
I still wanna sleep.
You don't have much time left.
Are you skipping school today?
Sounds pretty good to me...
I'll pull you out of bed if you don't get up!
W-Wait, wait!
Nanasaki Ai
1st Half
Bold Front
Nanasaki Ai
1st Half
Bold Front
So you were up late last night.
Miya-chan told me.
Yeah, I got a little too into it.
It's like my passion as a test-taker has flared up.
I know you're trying hard, but don't push yourself too much.
I know. Thanks.
Good morning, captain.
Morning.
As usual, you two are all lovey-dovey in the morning!
Wha...
I beg you, boss!
Wh-What's the matter, Umehara?
At this rate, all three years of my
high school will be devoid of color...
I want to get a girlfriend somehow before Christmas.
I'm sure you have connections
through your sister or girlfriend.
Please introduce some girl to me!
I-I don't know if I can do that...
You're the only one I can count on, boss!
C-Calm down a bit, Umehara.
Come on, come on!
Keiko!
Ow...
I beg you, please, boss!
This... This is too sad...
H-Hey, get off me!
What the hell are they doing?
No clue...
Tachibana-kun?
Oh, Ayatsuji-san.
How rare to see you here. Are
you studying at the library today?
Yeah, the cram school I go to is off today, so
I figured I'd try changing things once in a while.
Are you studying too?
Huh? But I thought you got an offer already...
Yes, but it seems like studying's become a habit.
I somehow feel uneasy when I'm not studying.
You're amazing.
I wish I could study until it became a habit.
I dunno about that.
Well, see you later, Tachibana-kun.
Yeah.
Well, this is a good place to stop, so I guess I'll go home too.
Oh, that's right.
It's pretty full around here with the many freshmen girls that joined.
No, no.
I almost forgot what I came here for.
Next, focus on your breathing and the timing of your kicks.
Go!
She's become a great captain.
Just like Tsukahara-senpai was last year.
Huh?
What do you mean, "huh"?
You should already know this, but boys aren't allowed in here when the Girls Swim Club's using the pool.
You forgot?
N-No, it's not that I forgot...
Then what?
U-Uh, um...
I'm sorry.
I think that's enough, captain.
Huh?
That's right.
I mean, you're always looking toward the entrance around this time.
Th-That's not...!
A-Are you sorry for what you did?
Don't come in here when club activities are going on again!
Got it?
Y-Yes, I got it!
I won't come in here when club activities are going on again.
I'll reflect on my actions.
I'm sorry!
Okay then...
No, Ai-chan!
You can't let him go that easily!
M-Miya! What are you doing here?!
I joined the Swim Club starting this year.
I-I had no idea!
I never told you.
Why would you do that?
Isn't it more fun to keep it secret?
Just like this time.
I'm sure you knew about it, Nanasaki.
Miya-chan told me to keep quiet about it-
More importantly, you can't let him go that easily, Ai-chan!
Onii-chan wasn't just looking at you. He was also looking at the other girls in their swimsuits and smirking, you know.
I-I wasn't smirking!
You're full of lies.
I'm not lying.
Why do you have such a pervy look on your face, then?
I-I don't...!
You fell for it, Onii-chan!
Senpai.
N-No, it's all a misunderstanding!
W-Wait, listen to me!
You're seriously unbelievable!
I'm sorry.
You're seriously such a perv, Senpai.
Though I already knew that.
But I really did go to the pool just to meet you.
I don't have cram school today, and I figured we could go home together since it's been so long...
So... um...
I see. I forgive you.
Nanasaki...
In return...
R-Right!
...come with me on my grocery shopping as punishment.
They're doing a huge discount for
up to two packs of eggs per person
and one bottle of milk per person at the nearby supermarket.
I'll gladly take the punishment of going with you!
Just saying, I really won't forgive you if you dare to peek again!
Okay.
I n f i r m a r y
Nanasaki?
Sorry, did I wake you?
Nah, it's fine.
You fixed the sheets for me.
Thanks.
Ah, you don't have to get up. Keep laying down.
But what are you doing here, Nanasaki?
I was looking for you.
I was wondering if we could have lunch together.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I heard from Miya-chan that you were up late studying last night.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
You reminded me of something when you mentioned Miya.
She often used to sleep on my
dad's belly when she was small.
I see.
My brother Ikuo falls asleep right
away when you sing him a lullaby.
He doesn't sleep on my belly, though.
I see.
Yep.
Senpai?
You know...
Yes?
I was just thinking... well...
If I could sleep on your belly while you sing me a lullaby...
I'd probably sleep very well.
What? Here?!
If you don't mind...
N-No way!
It'll be really embarrassing if someone saw us!
It's fine, we could just pull the curtains around the bed...
I'm sure it'll blow away my fatigue from the studying.
You don't want to?
Fine, then.
So... how do we do this?
Um...
Why are you covering my eyes?
This is pretty embarrassing, you know.
D-Don't move!
Sorry.
Well, here I go.
Please.
Meow, meow~
Lay down~
Meow, lay down~
You're a good boy~
It's time for bed~
Your sleepiness will go away~
Senpai?
He really is sleeping very well.
Ikuo!
When you're done with your homework,
get ready for tomorrow and sleep early...
Come on, get up, Ikuo.
You'll catch a cold if you sleep in the kotatsu.
Oh, that's right!
I'll need to decide with Senpai
where to go for Christmas Eve soon!
What?
I'm really sorry!
Well, uh...
I have no idea what you're apologizing for if you just do it suddenly...
Yesterday, I got the results for the mock exams I had in cram school a week ago.
And, well... how should I say this...
It was bad?
Yeah.
How bad?
You'd reach me quicker if you started counting from the bottom of my class.
N-No!
I got most of the questions right. Really.
It's just that... all my answers were off by one row on the answer sheet...
That's an understandable mistake.
How embarrassing...
But you didn't need to apologize for that.
Just do it right next time.
Well, that isn't actually what I'm apologizing for...
Hmm? Then what?
My cram school's really tough.
Everyone who did badly in the mocks has to go to this training camp that will take place soon.
And it starts on December 23rd.
I did talk to the cram school teacher!
I told him I shouldn't need to go since my answers would be right if they weren't off by one row.
But he said it's not like I can make this excuse if I made the same mistake in the real thing.
Rumor has it that they have this really scary camp leader there.
What's worse, we're pretty much confined inside
and have to wake up at five in the morning and study without any free time all the way until bedtime...
I... see.
Yeah.
Hey...
Don't worry about it.
I actually also have to go to the after party for the
Girls Swim Club's Oden stall after the Founder's Festival.
I was worried that it would cut into our date.
Really?
Yes.
I mean, I'm the team captain, so I have to go.
I guess it's convenient that it happened...
So please don't worry about it.
Ah, okay.
H-Hey...
I'll definitely make up for this, so...
Yes, I'll be looking forward to it.
Please work hard in the training camp!
Yeah, I will!
Um, our class has decided to do a
play in this year's Founder's Festival...
So I'd like us to decide on the cast and backstage roles...
Founder's Festival
Play
Roles
Please raise your hand if you have any opinions.
Why did I say something like that?
The morning training for the swim meet that'll take place early next year will start next week.
There's also the Founder's Festival preparations, which means we'll be able to meet each other even less...
Hey, what role do you want, Ai-chan?
I know you have the Oden stall, but I want you to do this too!
You might as well enjoy both while you're at it!
Ai-chan?
Ode
Sure
Pass
Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
How's this?
It's a horse!
Senpai'll be going to the training camp soon.
I couldn't prepare anything other than a lap blanket for him...
But it should be okay, right? He can use it in the training camp...
It's a little early, but my Christmas present to him will show that I'm rooting for him.
What do you think are some good places to go to on a Christmas date, Kaoru?
A Christmas date?
Let's see...
The Port Tower is a popular choice.
Yeah!
Then there's also the amusement park, the cinema, and the karaoke bar!
I wonder if they'll have movies suitable for a Christmas date at the cinema.
I dunno...
That reminds me, I hear they're doing a special lightup at the aquarium just for Christmas.
That's wonderful!
A Christmas Eve spent together with the
one you love at the magical aquarium at night...
How romantic!
Influenced by such an atmosphere, any guy would fall to his knees!
Just thinking about it is making my heart race!
Wait, there's no point in this if you
don't get a boyfriend in the first place.
Hehe, you're right.
This is bad, Ai-chan!
What?
Onii-chan was taken to the cram school training camp last night!
What? But I thought he was scheduled to go later...
Well, the people with especially bad grades have to start earlier and therefore do it for longer.
The cram school people suddenly
showed up and took Onii-chan away!
Miya!
Make sure you tell Nanasaki!
I... I see.
Yeah.
Ai-chan?
Senpai...
I wonder if he's studying hard right now?
Senpai's working hard, so I have to endure this, too...
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
Suki da yo
"I love you"
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
Senpai.
Nanasaki.
Senpai, I...
I know.
Sorry for leaving you
alone on Christmas Eve.
I...
Nanasaki.
I may be alone, but I'll live on bravely, so
please watch over me from the distant heavens.
Hey, wait!
I'm still alive!
I was just forced to attend the cram school training camp!
Just kidding.
Geez, don't surprise me like that.
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Escape
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Escape
Next episode: "Escape".
But I do feel lonely, after all...