You look really nice in these clothes.
Very sexy.
Makabe-kun?
When I look at the you right now, it's like the passion
inside me's about to burst forth, or has been awakened...
I don't know why I never noticed it until now.
Sakurai, I'm in love with you.
Will you go out with me?
But... this is all too sudden...
Don't be silly.
Love is something that always starts suddenly.
Just say yes.
Well? Why not?
Um... I...
I... have someone I like.
Who's he?
I...
I...!
Just don't regret having rejected me!
It's about time you let Tachibana-kun know how you feel.
Hey there, girl.
Wanna go out with me?
Says he, Hibiki-chan.
Are you hitting on her?
E-Excuse me!
From the moment we met
Deatta shunkan
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
Everything about you
Kimi no subete ni
Check My Soul
My heart begins to wake
Haato ga ugokidashita
Let's break into a run together right now
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Even in dreamlike moments
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
I only want to gaze at the truth
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
Inside your eyes
Hitomi no oku no
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Sakurai Rihoko
2nd Half
Wind Chimes
Sakurai Rihoko
2nd Half
Wind Chimes
Sakurai Rihoko
2nd Half
Coming!
Good evening.
Riho-chan! I've been waiting!
Hey, did you see Nii-nii on the way here?
No, I didn't.
Weird.
I'm home!
Ah, he's back.
Aww, the ice cream's all melted!
Sorry.
H-Hey.
Th-Thanks for having me here.
What's with you both?
It's nothing!
U-Um, you must both be hungry.
I'll get the food done quickly, so wait just a little longer.
I'll help!
Wait!
Don't you do anything!
Huh? Why?!
Well, you got the dashi and barley tea packs mixed up
the other day and made some funky-tasting miso soup!
Shut up!
Everyone makes mistakes.
What's with that punch line?!
I'll be done soon, so just wait a little longer.
Junichi?
Uh...
I kinda want to ask you something.
What is it?
Well, uh...
When I was out buying some stuff earlier...
Earlier?
No, like when I was out buying some stuff earlier.
I was just thinking you see a lot
more couples come summer break.
What do you think, Rihoko?
Me?
Hmm... let's see...
I didn't see that many couples when
I was out doing the groceries, though.
Uh, I suppose so!
I guess I just happened to see a lot of them.
That's all you wanted to ask?
Yeah, that's all... I guess.
All right, I'll leave you to it.
Junichi.
What?
I... uh...
I'll make some really good food, so wait just a little longer.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
I'm so hopeless.
It's done!
Amazing, Riho-chan!
It looks really good.
But isn't this pretty expensive stuff?
Actually...
Rihocchi is probably busily making some spirit-inducing food right about now.
With every ounce of her spirit.
She fell for it again.
I'll tell you another ingredient that can cure heat fatigue.
Yes, please do!
Lotus root.
Lotus root is written in Chinese with the characters for "training" and "pole", so it has the meaning of robustness.
I hear it's eaten by all swordsmen well-versed in kung fu.
Wow...
Poor girl.
But it's about time Rihocchi lets Junichi know how she feels.
Agreed.
C-Could this be...
...the king of the sea?!
You're not getting away!
How are the Senpais' university lives going?
They said it was okay, but they seemed to be having fun.
Enbi
Oh yeah, they said they joined the Tennis Circle.
What? You serious?
I know, right? I was really surprised myself.
They still kindly taught me all kinds of things like they used to, though.
In fact, they taught me how to make today's dishes.
I see.
I'm done!
I'm really full.
Wow!
Nii-nii's appetite's back!
Well, it was really good.
It's a good thing I made the food, then.
Thanks, Rihoko.
No problem.
Since it makes you both so happy...
Is it okay if I come make dinner again next time?
You're more than welcome to!
Right, Nii-nii?
Yeah.
I'm so full that I can't move.
Nii-nii, go get it.
I bet it's for you anyway.
You go get it.
Rock, paper...
Hello, Tachibana residence.
Ah, this is Nakata.
Miya-chan?
I know it's sudden, but how about going to the amusement park with me if you don't have any other plans tomorrow?
How come?
Ah, right.
See? I knew it'd be for Miya.
Rihoko.
Um...
Should I help with the cleaning up?
Thanks, but I'll be fine.
Junichi.
You know, I...
The Inago Masks?!
Sounds really fun!
Yeah, I'll definitely go!
Okay!
Ai-chan's going too? Right.
Okay, I'll be looking forward to tomorrow!
I'm going to the amusement park
with Sae-chan and Ai-chan tomorrow!
Fun, fun!
Oh, that's right.
Dessert, dessert!
What? Didn't you say you were full-
There's a separate stomach for dessert!
Riho-chan, you'll have dessert too, right?
Yeah.
Your and Miya's "separate stomachs" scare me every time.
Penguin-chan ice shaver~
Cold, cold shaved ice~
Penguin-chan ice shaver!
It's done!
Hey, isn't that a little too much?
You'll ruin your stomach if you eat it all.
I'll be fine!
We would've been putting ice cream on instead.
I'm sorry.
Oh well.
Hey, Riho-chan.
This is Miya's special seven-colored shaved ice!
Want some?
Right...
That's pretty heavy rain.
Yeah...
Hey, Riho-chan. How about staying the night?
Eh? But...
Well, it'll be bad if you catch a cold going home in such heavy rain.
Hey, Nii-nii.
It's better this way, right?
Yeah, you're right.
If you don't mind, Rihoko.
Really?
Okay, I'll stay the night.
It's decided, then!
I can't believe...
I ended up staying over at Junichi's place...
Way too many things happened today.
I...
Persistence
Yields Results
I'll let him know this time, for sure.
Ahh, the bath felt really good!
Okay, Riho-chan. You'll be using this futon.
Thanks for going through the trouble, Miya-chan.
I wouldn't mind sleeping with you, though.
That way, I could use your soft boobs as a pillow!
Geez, Miya-chan...
Can I come in for a bit?
What?
I was just wondering if my clothes are okay...
Soft...
Soft?
No, it's nothing!
So... Well? Are my clothes okay?
Yeah, they fit just right.
Thanks.
It's true!
My clothes would've been too tight around here for you to wear.
You did the right thing to borrow Nii-nii's clothes!
Y-Yeah.
Now that you're done, time for you to get out.
Huh?
Miya! No, no!
You're still half-asleep, Miya!
Huh? Nii-nii?
Geez, get a grip on yourself.
Bathroom...
I bet it's because you had too much shaved ice.
Are you in elementary school?
Rihoko, what's wrong?
I couldn't fall asleep.
What about you, Junichi?
Me too.
I feel wide awake for some reason.
The rain stopped.
Yeah.
Hey-
Fireworks...
Wanna light some fireworks?
Okay.
When we were kids, we'd play with fireworks almost every day during summer break.
Yeah.
Didn't there use to be this firework with a parachute?
Yeah, there was.
You really liked to catch the little parachute that would fall from the sky after it burst.
You've always liked sparkler fireworks.
Yeah.
It's really cute how the small sparks crackle.
Oh yeah, we often used to
compete on whose would last longer.
Oh, come on.
Here, have mine.
Thank you!
Aww.
Here, have this.
Thanks.
Our very last high school summer break is ending soon.
Yeah, it sure went by fast.
It feels like the school entrance ceremony only just happened.
Yeah.
Hey, Junichi.
Hmm?
Have you decided on what you want to do in the future?
Not yet.
What about you, Rihoko?
Me? I haven't decided yet, either.
Looks like we both need to decide real soon.
Yeah, you're right.
We've been together the whole time since kindergarten.
Um...
You know, I...
It'd be nice if things could stay that way.
Um... I...
Ow!
I'm sorry!
S-Sorry!
I-I'm sorry, too.
Rihoko!
Junichi!
Rihoko.
I like you.
No.
I never noticed because we've always been close...
But I've been in love with you all this time, Rihoko.
I know that well now, though.
I love you too, Junichi.
That's why...
I want to be with you from now on, forever.
This tea's really good.
Yeah, it's high-quality green tea.
Enbi
Isn't it because you prepared the tea well?
Really?
Maybe it's because I was making it for the guy I like...
Morning!
Huh?
Your faces are pretty red.
M-Maybe it's because the tea's hot.
Maybe it's because it's hot in here.
Something's weird.
N-Nothing's weird!
Why are you so mad?
I'm not mad!
You are.
I'm not.
Nothing's strange. It's all good.
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
Suki da yo
"I love you"
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
It's finally Nanasaki's turn next week, Tachibana-kun.
Tsukahara-senpai.
I'm glad things have been going well since I graduated.
Yes, thanks to you.
I n f i r m a r y
It's just...
Just what?
There are times when she can't bring herself to say what's on her mind.
She could be hiding her true feelings.
Hey, gimme a break!
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
1st Half
Bold Front
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
1st Half
Bold Front
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
1st Half
Next episode: "Bold Front".
Love can make someone strong,
but it can also make someone weak.