It's a Sunday in December close to Christmas...
But I'm bored with nothing to do.
Ah, there you are, Nii-nii.
Miya?
Why are you dressed like that?
I'm heading out!
Heading out?
Where?
To Kibitou Land.
They've opened new hot spring facilities, so I'm going there!
I'm surprised you feel like going out in this cold.
But I'm going to the hot springs because it's cold.
And what's more, in commemoration of the opening, they're doing a free-of-charge campaign only for females right now!
By the way, that apparently means guys aren't allowed in.
What the heck?
Isn't it great?
I'll be meeting up with my friends, including Sae-chan.
What?!
Nakata-san's going?
That's right.
Ai-chan's also going.
N-Nakata-san with her perfect full-volume body and Nanasaki's swim-toned slender body in the same room...
Hey, Nii-nii.
I'm going too, you know.
Nope, nothing there.
You...
...idiot, Nii-nii!
From the moment we met
Deatta shunkan
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
Everything about you
Kimi no subete ni
Check My Soul
My heart begins to wake
Haato ga ugokidashita
Let's break into a run together right now
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Even in dreamlike moments
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
I only want to gaze at the truth
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
Inside your eyes
Hitomi no oku no
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Tachibana Miya Arc
Hot Springs
Kibitou Spa
Miya-chan!
Sorry I'm late!
Did the two of you wait long?
Nah, not at all.
That's good...
Did something happen?
Yes! Listen to this!
You know, my brother is...
...such a perv.
I know mine aren't as big as yours, Sae-chan.
But Ai-chan, I think mine would
give yours a good run for their money.
U-Uh...
Why would you talk to your brother about that?
Right? Isn't my brother horrible?
At this rate, I'm worried he'll get so pervy that he'll become a criminal!
I-I guess I don't really know...
Anyway, why don't we head in?
We shouldn't just stand here and talk.
You're right, it's cold and all.
Also, my brother's even worse than that.
Huh? There's more?
Oh!
Isn't this is one of those charming
old-style Japanese public baths, Haruka?
Yeah.
It's a traditional Japanese socializing area, the public bath, Jessica!
This place just opened, so it's not
really old-style or traditional, though...
Thank you, Hibiki, for inviting me as well.
It's fine.
Haruka said she wanted a breather
from studying for the exams anyway.
Yup, no worries!
Let's all enjoy ourselves!
You're doing more studying once we get back.
A-Anyway, I'll show you my
supreme back-washing techniques!
Oh, fantastic!
What the heck's that?
Look forward to it, Hibiki-chan!
I'll be pouring hot water in time with the bish bash of Japanese drums.
Excellent!
Wonderful!
You've been watching those old geezer comedy videos again.
All right, let's invade the hot springs!
Go go go!
Okie dokie!
There's less people than I thought there would be.
Isn't that a good thing?
There'll be more space for us, and we can take our time.
You're right.
Wh-What?
So nice...
What?
Your extra-large meat buns...
M-Meat?
And...
This sensitive body!
It sucks to admit it, but I kind of
understand what Onii-chan was getting at!
It tickles!
Miya-chan!
Is this it?
Is this the good spot?
What?
What's the matter?
Riho-chan?
M-Miya-chan?
Riho-chan, you're here too!
Wait, was that your scream just now?
Y-Yeah, it was.
Sorry if I scared you.
Did something happen?
Wait, are you hiding something?
N-Nothing! It's nothing.
Hey, Sakurai.
Sorry I'm late.
What's going on?
N-Nah, nothing...
Miya-chan, it looks like they have all kinds of baths here.
Building Map
Let's hurry so we can try lots of them out.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's go!
Full Breasts
Bath
By virtue of the special blend of minerals in the water, the cells of your body will be aroused,
Full Breasts Bath
Water Quality
Simple Thermal Spring
Sulphuric Acid and Saline
Effective for
Fuller Breasts
Dry Skin
Women's Diseases
Sensitivity to Cold
Neuralgia
Fatigue
Increased Health
Special Characteristics
By virtue of the special blend of minerals
in the water,
the cells of your body will be aroused,
stimulating womanly development.
However, it's believed that staying in too long
can interfere with restful sleep,
so please exercise caution.
stimulating womanly development...
Now I'll get them, too!
This must be the place.
T-Tanamachi-san?
A-Ayatsuji-san.
You're here too, Tanamachi-san.
So what effects do you think this bath has?
But weren't you just saying that this must be the place?
I bet you came in here knowing exactly what this bath does.
Looks like this isn't the bath I was looking for.
See you, Tanamachi-san.
Are you sure?
If you go, it's not like I'll particularly mind.
Wh-What could you be talking about?
Well, you should just get in as well.
You're here anyway, so there's no need to keep pretending.
Ah, this is paradise!
The water does feel good.
If someone with well-developed boobs saw us here in this bath, I'd be so embarrassed that I could die.
Indeed.
Ooh!
Boobs really do float in water!
Squishy Islands discovered ahead.
We're landing!
Ooh, the softness and warmth feels super good!
S-Stop, Miya-chan...
Bobbing and floating, the Squishy Islands~
Blown by the wind, wobble wobble~
Tossed by the waves, boing boing~
Hey, Haruka.
What, Hibiki-chan?
This seems to be the opposite of what
you were talking about before we came in.
Don't worry about it!
Washing each other's backs is
the best thing about public baths.
That's right, Hibiki.
Washing each other is the best thing about public baths!
I bet you have no idea what you're talking about.
Is there anywhere you'd like me to rub?
You're mixing it up with what they say at the beauty parlor.
T-Tanamachi-san.
Maybe we should get out before we get dizzy from the heat.
I'm sweating a lot.
I-I'm fine.
Shouldn't you be getting out, Ayatsuji-san?
This is normal for me.
Th-This is normal for me too.
Oh? What bath could this be?
I can't see it because of all this steam...
Over here, Ai-chan.
Over here!
Miya-chan, it's dangerous to run.
A-Also, I don't really need...
W-Wait, Miya-chan, Ai-chan...
What effects does this bath have?
Hey, Nakata-san!
Yours are big enough already!
Wh-What's big enough?
Morishima-senpai, there's a really cute bath over there!
Really?
Let's go and see, Hibiki-chan, Jessica!
Yeah, that sounds really fun!
Let's go!
You should come too, Nakata-san.
But...
I'm borrowing Nakata-san for a while, Nanasaki.
Okay.
See you later, Sae-chan.
O-Okay...
Good luck, Nanasaki.
H-Having big ones isn't everything!
Y-Yeah!
But you know, it's such a happy feeling to touch big boobs.
The squishy marshmallow-like texture of
Sae-chan's boobs is really quite something...
Whoa, really?
Miya-chan...
Oh yeah, where did Riho-chan and her friend go?
Doctor Fish
Bath
I-It really tickles...
Endure it.
The fish are eating away the unneeded parts of our bodies.
Y-Yeah.
They're eating the unneeded...
Unneeded parts?
Sakurai?
Wait, what are you doing, Sakurai?!
Th-This way, the fish will eat away the unneeded parts of my body...
No, they only eat away the old keratin and stuff...
Hey, are you listening?
Stop making such weird sounds.
Ai-chan, where are you going?
I'm feeling a little hot, so I thought I'd look for
the bath I want to visit while cooling off my body.
Wait, I'll go too.
There's also a bath I want to visit.
But I forgot where it is.
Let's go look for a guide board together, then.
Okay.
Those underclassman young'uns have already escaped.
Yes.
They have no idea what a huge difference this little bit of extra effort will make.
Building Map
Looks like mine's this way.
Mine's this way.
See you later, then.
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
There's someone you've always liked.
Yeah.
I've liked him ever since elementary school.
I even chose to go to the same high school as him.
Sure pure love!
I dunno...
Don't you have someone like that?
I do, but I was rejected.
I went for it and wrote him a letter, but he showed it to everyone...
That's horrible.
It's fine. That was a long time ago.
But I'm surprised.
I know we're in the same school, but
talking to a stranger about all this is kinda...
I guess it's because you don't really feel like one to me.
Same here.
So who's the person you like?
Um, well...
Sup, boss.
I've been waiting, Umehara.
Did you bring it?
I did.
I borrowed my older brother's secret collection.
Since Miya-chan won't be around, us lonely guys can have a porn mag and video viewing party.
Yeah.
Well, come in.
Yeah, excuse me.
I see, so you're a freshman at our school.
Yes.
You're very well-developed for a freshman.
BATH
It's so cute!
Yes, very cute!
It's really just as Ayatsuji-san said.
W-Well, this atmosphere isn't really my thing, but I guess I'll accompany you guys anyway.
There you go again!
I know you've been stealing
glances at the place since we came in.
You're so cute, Hibiki-chan!
Yes, you're so cute, Hibiki!
I thought so before, but having pretty
much two Harukas around is a lot to handle.
Come on, let's get in.
Okay, let's go, Hibiki, Haruka!
Ramen Bath
I can't get enough of this butter-like sensation and juicyness!
Yeah! You can't help but feel like eating it!
If I bring that home as a present, I'm sure Nii-nii'll be shocked!
Rejuvenating Sauna
Rejuvenating?
It's hot!
Huh? Takahashi-sensei?
T-Tachibana-san.
So you're here too, Takahashi-sensei.
Y-Yes, that's right.
I just got in here.
You're sweating a lot for someone who just got in.
My metabolism's really good.
By the way, this sauna's the "Rejuvenating Sauna", isn't it?
Oh?
Really?
I didn't know that!
I just thought I'd drop in, since
milk tastes so good after a sauna.
I know what you mean.
Right?
It's too hot! I can't stand any more.
Sorry, but I'll get out first.
Yes, see you.
Just a little longer, Maya!
I'll become so young that I'll surprise everyone.
And then...
This is so exciting!
I feel dizzy...
We were in for too long...
That's not good, you two.
Staying in a hot bath too long is actually bad for your body.
I know that, but...
...human greed has no bounds...
You're one to talk, Sakurai.
You've been going on and on about how your tummy hurts.
Well...
What? You ate too much?
No!
She just laughed too much.
Kanae-chan!
I smell something delicious, so I figured that was it.
Yeah, you're right.
It smells like miso or something...
Yeah, there's also a rich butter smell.
Oh yeah, I remembered something in the bath.
What was it?
Junichi gets out really quickly whenever he takes baths.
Maybe he doesn't like hot baths very much.
W-Wait a minute, h-how would you-
Owww!
It hurts!
Ow...
I can't believe you took a bath with a guy!
But we're childhood friends.
What a pervert.
That was also during our early elementary school years.
What were you all thinking?
Atchoo, damn it.
What's wrong, boss? You got a cold?
Nah, someone's probably talking about me.
There's no way something that cliched would happen.
You're right.
I found it.
Bath
I got what I came for, and the milk's delicious.
How satisfying!
Though, is everyone still in the baths?
Maya wants to drink milk too!
T-Takahashi-sensei?!
She rejuvenated that much?
I wonder how much younger I've gotten.
In that case, could this really...?
Bath
Kibitou Spa
I'm home!
Oh, welcome back.
The hot springs were so much fun!
This is for you.
What's this?
Bath salts?
It feels really good!
Go try it.
Okay.
Nii-nii, how was the bath-
Abstinence Bath
Why do my mind and body both feel so refreshed?
N-Nii-nii?
It's like I've been released from all my desires and reborn.
Now that I look back, it's amazing what a terrible guy I was.
I've decided to bid my old self farewell!
I know!
I'll start by burning my entire collection of collector's edition porn mags and videos!
While I do that, I'll burn the stuff I borrowed from Umehara too.
I'm sure Umehara'll appreciate it! Yep!
W-Wait!
You're gonna burn them now?!
And you're burning Ume-chan's stuff too?
Wasn't that what I said?
You can't! You'll disturb the neighbors!
And Ume-chan'll get mad at you!
It's fine. There's no need to worry.
For Medicinal Use
Abstinence Bath
Bath salts formula to take away your desires
Kibitou Spa
Was the bath too effective?
What are you talking about, Miya?
Eww, he's so gross...
Abstinence Bath
Bath salts formula to take away your desires
Nii-nii, think it over!
Go back to being the Nii-nii you used to be!
Come back, Nii-nii!
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
Suki da yo
"I love you"
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession