I'm home.
Welcome back, darling!
You're home early today.
Yeah.
I managed to wrap up my work faster than expected.
I see.
Come.
Give me your coat and bag.
Sorry, Senpai.
Sorry? Senpai?
That's no good.
You're my husband, so you're not supposed to say sorry.
Also, why aren't you calling me by my first name?
U-Uh... well...
I'm sorry.
You're hopeless.
Okay, let's continue.
Hey, darling.
Y-Yes?!
What is it?
I've prepared everything. What will you have?
Will you have dinner? A bath?
Or will you have... me?
Me?
Me
O-Of course I'll have you, Senpai-
Okay, cut!
Ah, that was refreshing!
Um, you said I could have you...
I've always wanted to try saying that.
Mmh, that was satisfying!
What?!
Your heart beats pretty fast when you actually say the words.
What a discovery!
The game ended halfway the other day,
so I invited her to my house, figuring we wouldn't need to worry about the time and stuff.
I'm glad she seems to be having fun.
What's up?
Well, let's go all out and have fun today!
Okie dokie!
I hope you're ready, Tachibana-kun!
From the moment we met
Deatta shunkan
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
Everything about you
Kimi no subete ni
Check My Soul
My heart begins to wake
Haato ga ugokidashita
Let's break into a run together right now
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Even in dreamlike moments
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
I only want to gaze at the truth
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
Inside your eyes
Hitomi no oku no
Check My Soul
Listen to the voice in my heart
Kokoro no koe kiite
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Morishima Haruka
2nd Half
Departure
Um... can I help with anything?
Just sit back and relax.
O-Okay.
Ow-
Are you okay?!
I'm fine. It was just a little hot.
I'll be done soon, so just wait a little longer.
Okay.
Let me know if there's anything I can do to help.
Yep, I'll let you know.
I didn't expect Morishima-senpai to come over and make dinner for me.
Awesome... this is awesome!
It's like we're newly married!
Hey, Tachibana-kun.
Y-Yes?
Where are your parents today?
They're both away on a business trip.
They'll be back tomorrow evening.
I see.
What about Miya-chan?
She's having a sleepover or something, so she's out with her friends right now.
She won't be back until tomorrow evening.
I see.
Yes.
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
That's not why I invited you over today...
I guess it was just coincidence... that it happened...
I don't mind even if that was the reason.
Huh?
Uh... Does that mean...
U-Um, well...
What did you mean by that?
Well...
I'll be staying over tonight.
Staying over?!
Huh? I'm not?
N-No, you are! You are!
Okay, that's good!
Th-This is gonna be incredible!
Senpai's staying over...
Doesn't that mean...
Here, open wide!
We'll do that...
Does this feel good?
And that...
We'll stay like this until you fall asleep.
And even that!
W-Will I really be okay?
Can I really survive this day?
It's ready!
O-Okay!
I-Isn't this...
I need to practice cooking more.
I-Indeed...
Huh?
Your brother's alone at home tonight?
Yeah.
Ume-chan might have gone over to his place, though.
Those two guys are probably having
a lonely porno viewing party right now.
P-Porno?
I... I'm seriously popular, so...
That's really funny!
S-Senpai's staying over?
H-How will the night turn out?
What on Earth's gonna happen?
S-Senpai?
I don't have a kotatsu at home so
I never knew, but they're wonderful!
We can even communicate through it.
Wait...
Communication? That really tickles!
That's what you say, but I know
you're actually really happy about it!
Take that, take that!
It seriously really tickles...
Well? Do you give up?
No way! Here's the counterattack!
Hey, stop! That's against the rules!
My history with the kotatsu is just as
long as my age, so don't take me lightly!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Do you give up?
I do! I give up!
Geez, you're mean, Tachibana-kun.
S-Sorry.
Since I had a good sweat, I guess it's time to take a bath.
Enbi
What?!
Miya-chan...
She's like an old lady.
Masayoshi, go take a bath.
I can't stop now, so I'll go later!
Now what?
What should I do?
That reminds me, last Christmas...
Why didn't you come peek at me?!
...that happened.
Does that mean going to peek
is what a gentleman should do?
No, but...
All right, I'm going!
I choose to regret going over regretting not going!
Plus, if I apologize with all my heart, Senpai will forgive me!
I think.
That's why I'm going!
I-I'll show you!
Ah, that was refreshing!
The bath felt really good!
That's good-
What?
S-Senpai, why are you dressed like that?!
Huh? What's wrong?
N-No, nothing's wrong, but...
It's my mom's négligée.
I secretly borrowed it!
I can see various things in all the wrong ways.
This doesn't make her Morishima Lovely Haruka, but Morishima Sexy Haruka instead!
Why are you acting so strange, Tachibana-kun?
U-Uh, Senpai...
Could you please change into something else?
Huh? Why?
Well, uh...
I can see all sorts of things...
It's for the sake of my mental stability.
So...
Really?
But I brought it here to show you.
Does that mean I can look?!
Would not looking be a betrayal of Senpai's feelings?
If so, then taking a good look
is what a gentleman should do!
Even if it's for the sake of burning the sexy sight of Morishima-senpai into my memory!
Enbi
Will this do?
Tachibana-kun?
Well, uh...
Thank you.
I think I understand why the
Morishima family has so many kids.
You should take a bath too, Tachibana-kun.
It feels really good.
Yes, I'll do that.
Well, good night.
Good night.
There's no way I can sleep.
Um... Senpai?
Hmm? What?
I feel bad about having you sleep on the floor, after all.
If you'd like, you can use my bed-
Tachibana-kun.
Y-Yes?
There's something I forgot to tell you.
Something you forgot to tell me?
Yeah.
I'll be going to England after I graduate.
Huh?
E-England?
Is that for real?
Yeah.
Grandma and Grandpa have been asking me for a while now.
They told me to go to England after I graduate.
B-But Senpai-
I'll be fine.
It's not like I have to go now, and I'll be in Japan until the graduation ceremony.
Until the graduation ceremony?
Senpai's going back to England...
Is Senpai going to a university in England?
Oh yeah, when we were at the water pump shed...
But I'm glad we could come here again.
We made memories here, so I wanted to see it one last time before I graduated.
My wish unexpectedly came true.
So that's why we had that marriage rehearsal at school.
She wanted to make memories before she graduated...
Hey, boss. Where are you going?
Class is about to start.
I'm going to the senior classrooms!
Wait a minute, boss!
Don't stop me, Umehara!
But...
Starting today, the seniors won't be coming to school until the graduation ceremony.
Their classes have all ended.
You didn't know?
Well, a lot of things happened... so I completely forgot.
Hey, are you okay?
So what did you want to talk to me about?
I'm just here to pass down the captainship of the Swim Club.
Tsukahara-senpai, did you know that
Morishima-senpai'll be going to England?
Huh?
Yes, she did mention it.
What about it?
Why did Morishima-senpai keep it from me?
Something as important as going to a university in England after graduating...
I don't know why Haruka decided to keep it from you either.
But what will you do about it, Tachibana-kun?
Are you going to let Haruka go to England without asking her what's going on?
Can you still call yourself Haruka's boyfriend that way?
H-Hello?
Is this the Morishima residence-
Hallo!
Is that Jessica-san?
Wow, that's right!
And you must be Junichi.
Y-Yes.
Huh? Weren't you sightseeing in Kyoto?
I just got back today.
I had so much fun!
Especially when the dancing girl let me try her costume-
U-Um, sorry.
I'll listen all you want about your trip later.
What?!
Is Morishima-senpai there?
Oh, Haruka?
Haruka's packing her stuff for England at the moment.
For England?
Yeah, Grandma and Grandpa are really excited about seeing Haruka again.
So Senpai really is going to a university in England.
Huh?
Um, could you please get Morishima-senpai on the line?
Jessica-san?
Sorry, but I can't do that, Junichi.
B-But why?!
Haruka didn't really want to go to England at first.
That was probably because of you.
But I have to take her back to
England with me, no matter what.
That's why I came to Japan.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I can't allow you to see or speak to Haruka.
I don't want Haruka to long for Japan,
and it'd be bad if she decides to run away.
B-But that's just...!
If Haruka goes to England, she
probably won't come back for a while.
She might never come back.
She'll be leaving right after the graduation ceremony.
If you want to stop Haruka before then,
think carefully about what you should do.
Don't get me wrong, though.
I'm actually rooting for you two.
Good luck.
See you!
W-Wait, Jessica-san-
Jessica, who was on the phone?
Jessica?
This is going to be interesting.
Look forward to it, Haruka.
Senpai will go to England.
I don't want her to do that.
But what exactly can I do about it?
The 55th   Kibitou Municipal Kibitou High
Graduation Ceremony
The 55th Graduation Ceremony
Next, we have some words from
the current student representative.
The representative is...
Huh?!
E-Excuse me.
The current student representative is Tachibana Junichi-kun of class 2-A.
The 55th Graduation Ceremony
Yes!
O-Onii-chan?
Junichi?
B-Boss?
Wait, weren't you the current
student representative, Ayatsuji-san?
Tachibana-kun begged me to let him do it.
He said he had something he wanted to say, no matter what.
Tachibana-kun?
The 55th Graduation Ceremony
Today, we transition from a harsh winter to a season of budding flowers.
To everyone who is graduating from Kibitou High and about to depart on a journey...
Congratulations on your graduation.
Memories of the days we spent with you all will remain with us forever.
We've made so many memories that I can't
possibly say everything I want about them here.
The 55th Graduation Ceremony
Ever since I entered high school, Senpai, you've been the girl of my dreams.
Senpai, do you remember?
When I first confessed to you, you quickly rejected me.
But when I confessed the second time,
you said I could remain in love with you.
Tachibana-kun...
Many things happened after that.
We played leapfrog together and looked for photobooks of dogs in the library.
I was really surprised when you suddenly
asked me if I was carrying a girl's swimsuit.
We then went to the pool where the
Girls Swim Club was having their training,
but Tsukahara-senpai got mad at us both.
I haven't forgotten any of them.
I remember them all.
That's why I want to make more memories with you, Senpai.
I don't want you to go to England.
Haruka, I love you!
I really love you!
Please marry me!
The 55th Graduation Ceremony
Nicely done, boss!
Let's find happiness together, Haruka!
With me!
Junichi...
Junichi!
Haruka!
I'm so happy! I love you!
Of course I'll marry you!
Nice one, Nii-nii! You're so cool!
M-Miya-chan...
S-Stop that, you two!
You're making me jealous-
No, I mean...
Quiet, everyone!
Oh, my.
You never mentioned any of this, Tachibana-kun.
I didn't expect him to propose like that.
He might have overdone it a little.
Haruka's just going to England for a week.
But this was a pretty big success!
Congratulations, Haruka!
Let's love each other forever and ever.
Yes, of course!
Congratulations, boss!
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Okay, here we go!
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
Suki da yo
"I love you"
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
Everyone, wanna go to New York?
Yeah!
Huh?
Hey, Miya!
Or would you rather take a bath?
TL Note: Nyuuyoku (taking a bath) puns with New York.
Yeah!
Wait a minute!
What you're saying doesn't make sense!
Well, of course it wouldn't.
You won't be in the next episode anyway.
No way!
Guys are banned! It's a girls-only episode!
Of course you won't be in it.
B-But I'm the protagonist...
Next Episode
Tachibana Miya
Hot Springs
Next episode: "Hot Springs".
Splish, splash, it feels so good!