[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 1280
PlayResY: 720
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: ED_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&Hc8c0c0c0,&Hc8c0c0c0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H28000000,&Hf0c0c0c0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H124080ff,&Hf0000000,&H32ffffff,&Hc8c0c0c0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1
Style: ED_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&Hc8c0c0c0,&Hc8c0c0c0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H14ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H140d0d0d,&H3c1c1c1c,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,20,20,12,1
Style: Warring,微软雅黑,36,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&H282d2d2d,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H14ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H140d0d0d,&H3c1c1c1c,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,12,1
Style: Default3,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H00000000,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&Hf0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Zhushi,微软雅黑,35,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&Hf0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default4,Arial,18,&H00ffffff,&H0000ffff,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: title2,方正准圆_GBK,60,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&Hf0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H124080ff,&Hf0000000,&H32ffffff,&Hc8c0c0c0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.73,0:00:12.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夫人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.84,0:00:14.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早餐已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.44,0:00:34.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.78,0:00:35.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.11,0:01:04.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.13,0:01:09.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 已经请她作为班级代表出席辩论大赛了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.77,0:01:16.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,令嫒她无论学业还是体育都很优秀 简直是无可挑剔..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.03,0:01:17.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.38,0:01:29.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说她无可挑剔是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.95,0:01:31.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是的..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.24,0:01:35.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种让其他学校的男生护送到校门口的学生..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.20,0:01:37.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的无可挑剔吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.26,0:01:40.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她毕竟是理事长的千金
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.70,0:01:42.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是这种小事的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.10,0:01:46.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果不给点相应的处罚怎么让其他学生信服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.71,0:01:51.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可理事长吩咐过我不要干涉令嫒的生活..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.56,0:01:52.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是我家的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.39,0:01:56.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我丈夫也不会希望学校对她进行特别关照
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.59,0:01:59.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会叫你让她停学退学
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.23,0:02:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是像警告啊记过啊 不是还有很多做法吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.99,0:02:07.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就给她一次严重口头警告吧..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.46,0:02:12.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请给她一些切切实实的处罚 这是命令
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.85,0:02:15.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊..我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.79,0:02:27.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,皐月
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.77,0:02:28.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.08,0:02:30.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也来喝一杯？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.80,0:02:33.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本人还在勤务之中 请夫人见谅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.90,0:02:35.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听我的 来喝一杯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.44,0:02:36.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夫人..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.52,0:02:40.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你们在用这种态度来嘲弄我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.33,0:02:44.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夫人 如果您再喝下去的话对身体不好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.97,0:02:45.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要你管！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.69,0:02:50.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夫人 是不是该上床休息了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.04,0:02:54.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,彻彻底底地把我当傻瓜看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.67,0:03:04.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 每个人都一样！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.05,0:03:06.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全都把我当傻瓜！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.24,0:03:37.24,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,眠れない夜に　聞いた物語が
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.24,0:03:37.24,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,在无法入眠的夜晚 听到的那个故事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.62,0:03:42.00,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,絵空事だとしたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.62,0:03:42.00,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是天马行空的妄想的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.87,0:03:58.76,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,永遠を知るより　快楽を求めて
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.87,0:03:58.76,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,与其探求永远的奥秘 不如把握当下的欢乐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.11,0:04:02.58,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,今を悔やんでしまうのは
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.11,0:04:02.58,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,别让此时此刻成为一生的悔恨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.31,0:04:09.28,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,心の深くに　住み着いた影から
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.31,0:04:09.28,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是为了逃避盘踞在内心深处的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.53,0:04:13.13,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,逃げるためだとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.53,0:04:13.13,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,那片黑影的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.83,0:04:18.87,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,それでも　あたしはあたしを
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.83,0:04:18.87,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此 我还能发自内心地
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.01,0:04:22.48,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,愛していられるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.01,0:04:22.48,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,爱着自己的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.69,0:04:26.34,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,半分に割れた太陽が
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.69,0:04:26.34,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,分成两半的太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.60,0:04:28.68,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,朝を連れてきて
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.60,0:04:28.68,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,带来了明媚清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.87,0:04:33.83,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,闇に慣れた神経を　じわり刺激する
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.87,0:04:33.83,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,微微刺激着已经习惯黑暗的神经
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.19,0:04:39.02,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,置き忘れたの愛は　あえてそのままで
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.19,0:04:39.02,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,把忘了带走的爱原封不动地摆在那
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.50,0:04:43.89,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,シナリオの消えた物語は
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.50,0:04:43.89,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,缺了剧本的故事就会..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.99,0:04:49.16,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,自由に　自由に　舵をとって
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.99,0:04:49.16,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,自由地 自由地  操起船舵
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.50,0:04:55.66,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　高くへ　舞い上がって
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.50,0:04:55.66,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,一起飞向更高的地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.38,0:05:10.38,Warring,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,300)}翻译 TL旧民  后期 aoi  恶魔岛字幕组制作 仅供交流试看之用\N请勿添加广告 相关资源和讨论请访问恶魔岛动漫世界：http://bbs.emland.net
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.21,0:05:18.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊..差不多该别看了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.98,0:05:21.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.34,0:05:23.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明刚到精彩的地方说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.05,0:05:26.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 这部拍得又不怎么好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.46,0:05:29.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(905,580)}{\fad(250,150)}#14 「身是僵尸...心是...」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.39,0:05:31.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不然的话 这部《恶魔的嘈杂》可算是杰作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.46,0:05:32.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看到最后啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.98,0:05:34.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人家会很在意剧情发展的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.12,0:05:37.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之后不会发生什么让你吃惊的剧情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.98,0:05:38.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.31,0:05:41.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,萌路 你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.99,0:05:43.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥 快过来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.92,0:05:50.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会出现在寺堂底下..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.24,0:05:53.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是个谜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.42,0:05:56.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且这身打扮是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.41,0:05:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很独特呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.86,0:06:02.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多几岁呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.50,0:06:05.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概十二三岁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.30,0:06:07.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,长得真漂亮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.13,0:06:08.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.28,0:06:10.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不这么想吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.95,0:06:13.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没有那种兴趣啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.85,0:06:15.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦？兴趣？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.73,0:06:20.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥 那种细微区别礼弥大人是体会不到的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.73,0:06:22.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那到底该怎么说啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.59,0:06:24.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 还不给我安静一点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.79,0:06:25.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.99,0:06:28.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,江户川巡佐一会就来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.00,0:06:30.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概是迷路了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.29,0:06:32.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.59,0:06:35.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是被父母抛弃的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.24,0:06:45.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能不能至少告诉我你的名字呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.56,0:06:47.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,家住哪里？念年级啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.18,0:06:55.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.31,0:06:59.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一说要带她去医院就突然..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.65,0:07:01.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.67,0:07:03.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 不用害怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.27,0:07:07.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 不要！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.09,0:07:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小女孩 没事的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.87,0:07:09.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你冷静一下..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.66,0:07:16.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看这样没法带她去医院呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.97,0:07:20.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我会让大夫来这里帮她看看的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.09,0:07:22.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们和她年纪相仿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.08,0:07:25.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定她跟你们比较说得通
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.10,0:07:27.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能不能帮我试着跟她聊一聊呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.78,0:07:29.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.60,0:07:34.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不会说话吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.29,0:07:37.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是不想说话吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.52,0:07:41.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有什么不顺心的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.86,0:07:47.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伤脑筋了 这样根本无计可施呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.36,0:07:54.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥 你在卖萌吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.16,0:07:58.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我想这么做说不定能让她敞开心扉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.25,0:08:03.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,觉得有趣吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.03,0:08:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 不如一起看电影吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.97,0:08:09.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看僵尸电影很欢乐哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.54,0:08:11.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥大人 这招还是算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.96,0:08:12.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.97,0:08:14.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想她一定会喜欢上的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.14,0:08:17.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得可能性不到万分之一吧..
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.04,0:08:20.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样吗 我就看得很欢乐的说..
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.83,0:08:23.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即便是我也冒不出那种奇思妙想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.97,0:08:27.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,每次都会被礼弥大人天然的样子治愈呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.41,0:08:28.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这..这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.61,0:08:43.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大夫呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.85,0:08:44.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.14,0:08:46.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是什么都不说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.42,0:08:49.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像决定先托管在我们家了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.79,0:08:52.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,家里多了她和礼弥大人 会变得很热闹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.25,0:08:55.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯..要帮忙吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.85,0:08:58.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就帮我把晚餐拿去给那孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.46,0:08:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.14,0:09:04.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我拿晚餐来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.77,0:09:06.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要进来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.11,0:09:10.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.90,0:09:34.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥！你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.19,0:09:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥大人 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.49,0:09:41.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 降谷同学 萌路酱..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.33,0:09:45.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我的脚不小心滑了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.30,0:09:48.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊 真是的..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.56,0:09:51.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,..对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.55,0:09:54.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的没事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.88,0:09:56.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊..是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.25,0:10:02.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.98,0:10:04.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.87,0:10:07.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥大人早安 请问身体还好吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.70,0:10:09.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全没事的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.47,0:10:12.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起这些 请问发生什么事了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.80,0:10:15.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给礼弥酱准备的紫阳花找不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.03,0:10:16.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.95,0:10:19.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我记得是放在这个食品盒里的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.00,0:10:24.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事的啦 我会自己去后院采的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.70,0:10:32.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真过分啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.44,0:10:34.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是动物干的好事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.87,0:10:36.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说 还是多加小心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.85,0:10:39.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叶子我会去后山摘的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.07,0:10:40.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.43,0:10:51.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果要添饭的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.50,0:10:52.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请尽管跟我说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.82,0:10:59.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,纱..纱叶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.84,0:11:03.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,纱叶诶~~
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.82,0:11:06.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是他这样就不用对他客气哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.07,0:11:10.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是普通的女孩子呐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.09,0:11:13.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让她修理一下爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.33,0:11:15.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定就会更加对我们放下心防呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.74,0:11:19.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 开玩笑也不能这么讲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.51,0:11:21.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样我也没问题的哦？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.98,0:11:22.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老爸..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.09,0:11:27.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶~
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.52,0:11:30.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这是礼弥酱想太多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.10,0:11:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.11,0:11:36.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为昨天才刚刚到你们家
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.01,0:11:37.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会一下子对你有怨恨呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.18,0:11:39.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话是这样没错啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.57,0:11:41.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是你的错觉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.35,0:11:43.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样就好了..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.82,0:11:47.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得那孩子对礼弥酱没有恶意哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.58,0:11:50.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概是在害怕礼弥酱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.41,0:11:52.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,害怕我？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.93,0:11:54.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为她是个小孩子对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.73,0:11:56.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比较不擅长表达害怕的感情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.47,0:11:59.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会变成那种冷淡的态度
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.34,0:12:01.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗..
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.08,0:12:02.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.59,0:12:05.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不如礼弥酱主动接触她试试？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.05,0:12:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 那孩子的态度也会改变的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.38,0:12:11.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是..
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.69,0:12:15.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可以进来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.50,0:12:19.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我进来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.40,0:12:28.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你感觉舒服一些了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.56,0:12:31.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道是什么情况
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.49,0:12:34.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过能尽快跟家人相会就好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.45,0:12:38.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.01,0:12:43.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是说我做了什么让你不开心的事情吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.21,0:12:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是这样的话尽管说哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.80,0:12:49.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我对那种事非常迟钝的..
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.47,0:12:53.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起打扰你休息
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.62,0:12:56.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么一会见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.29,0:13:06.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,紧张死了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.96,0:13:12.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.10,0:13:14.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.51,0:13:18.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,关于那孩子 你是怎么想的？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.18,0:13:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么想..是指什么方面？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.76,0:13:23.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是有些在意降谷同学的看法..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.74,0:13:25.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.50,0:13:27.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得她蛮可怜的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.74,0:13:29.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.61,0:13:32.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.92,0:13:34.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 没事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.18,0:13:37.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.11,0:13:43.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的只是在害怕我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.02,0:14:33.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请问..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.93,0:14:37.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是什么意思呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.76,0:14:39.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对降谷同学做那种事..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.13,0:14:44.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去破坏紫阳花丛以及把我推下楼梯的都是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.62,0:14:47.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果讨厌我的话是无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.90,0:14:50.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是请你不要对降谷同学出手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.10,0:14:55.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你保证不再胡闹下去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.96,0:14:57.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就不会把之前的事情说出去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.33,0:15:00.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.77,0:15:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.30,0:15:09.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.75,0:15:12.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 请问昨晚睡得还好吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.32,0:15:14.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯..为什么这么问？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.85,0:15:16.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 是那样的话就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.20,0:15:34.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.16,0:15:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.49,0:15:38.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥酱 你能稍微来一下吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.38,0:15:40.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好的..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.52,0:15:48.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然并没有开口
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.02,0:15:52.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是通过摇头点头还是能进行沟通
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.22,0:15:55.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能再问一下刚才发生的事情吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.15,0:16:00.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个伤是被别人打的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.57,0:16:03.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是被谁打的呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.33,0:16:14.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥酱 虽然我并不是完全相信啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.21,0:16:18.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是事实上那孩子就是这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.87,0:16:19.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.38,0:16:22.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为她不会平白无故说那种话的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.02,0:16:25.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是知道些什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.93,0:16:30.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.04,0:16:46.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你适可而止！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.61,0:16:55.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.62,0:17:02.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底发生了什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.67,0:17:06.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她想要和降谷同学接吻！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.50,0:17:07.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接吻？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.62,0:17:11.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥大人 你是不是看错了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.78,0:17:12.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.41,0:17:15.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥酱 不要露出那么可怕的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.20,0:17:17.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你把人家吓到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.05,0:17:18.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是她的骗局
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.51,0:17:20.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要这样妄下结论
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.48,0:17:22.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.76,0:17:24.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙是打算要亲我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.35,0:17:25.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.79,0:17:29.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥说的事情是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.34,0:17:31.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙有点奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.20,0:17:34.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么想都不是一般的小孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.83,0:17:35.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.32,0:17:37.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子..这是真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.49,0:17:40.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.07,0:17:42.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我站住！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.26,0:17:55.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是怎么回事啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.86,0:17:59.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你忘记了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.54,0:18:02.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊？你在说什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.67,0:18:06.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点没变呢 居然喜欢那种小丫头
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.23,0:18:08.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.08,0:18:10.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真迟钝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.66,0:18:11.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还不懂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.94,0:18:16.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,..妈妈？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.44,0:18:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本打算夺走你的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.70,0:18:24.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果你身边还是一堆笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.10,0:18:27.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明照我的话去做就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.48,0:18:30.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都礼弥礼弥礼弥的..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.24,0:18:33.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都只关心礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.96,0:18:35.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有人肯看我一眼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.50,0:18:38.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 原来你是礼弥的老妈啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.69,0:18:42.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好的活人不喜欢 却沉迷于僵尸的臭小鬼！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.41,0:18:44.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也差不多该长进一下了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.33,0:18:47.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又在说这些啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.73,0:18:49.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没长进的是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.02,0:18:50.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.27,0:18:55.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样因为嫉妒而总想陷害别人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.17,0:18:56.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然会被人讨厌啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.55,0:18:58.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该给我发觉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.21,0:19:00.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正因为这样你才这么孤独
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.57,0:19:03.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的这么寂寞的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.80,0:19:05.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就让我来抱抱你吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.09,0:19:09.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,..鬼才要这么做嘞~
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.90,0:19:14.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你转生成为有着纯洁心灵的僵尸娘
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.20,0:19:15.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本大爷倒是不介意临幸你一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.05,0:19:20.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶..什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.32,0:19:23.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,..难不成要来一场超能力大战吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.54,0:19:33.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛..真的假的啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.04,0:19:34.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.47,0:20:03.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是梦..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.74,0:20:05.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌的梦..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.42,0:20:21.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幻觉？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.67,0:20:26.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 今天我也不吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.18,0:20:29.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明..明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.05,0:20:37.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,关于对令嫒的处罚一事..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.38,0:20:41.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我将以警告处分罚她义务劳动两周
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.67,0:20:45.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,外加取消她在辩论大赛的出场 请问意下如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.52,0:20:48.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,关于这次的处分
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.47,0:20:50.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有些教师也表达出不满之情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.12,0:20:53.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而令嫒在学生中的人气也非同小可
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.46,0:20:54.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,取消吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.83,0:20:55.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.02,0:20:56.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我改变主意了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.67,0:21:02.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我突然觉得没必要不惜违背丈夫之意而坚持处罚女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.97,0:21:05.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样..吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.22,0:21:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.54,0:21:22.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 只是看到了妈妈的车子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.93,0:21:25.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难不成今天你被她说了些什么吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.58,0:21:27.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不..不是啦 今天她没有说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.02,0:21:31.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 是我的说教起作用了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.69,0:21:33.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？那是什么意思啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.15,0:21:35.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不啦 昨晚我做了个梦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.43,0:21:38.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有个女孩子倒在寺庙那边
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.30,0:21:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可不知为何她居然是你的妈妈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.76,0:21:45.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而她像以往一样找我们麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.96,0:21:48.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,于是我教训她“像你这样的烂性格啊”..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.55,0:21:49.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.15,0:21:51.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶~是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.16,0:21:52.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.38,0:21:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 降谷同学
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.95,0:22:00.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊..不客气啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.18,0:22:29.19,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ　叶うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.18,0:22:29.19,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,如果只能实现一个愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.16,0:22:41.22,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,君の手の中 揺れる小さな花でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.16,0:22:41.22,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,我想成为在你手中随风摇曳的小花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.04,0:22:47.77,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,はじめてみる眩しいこの世界で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.04,0:22:47.77,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,在这个陌生 而又炫目的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.25,0:22:53.19,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,君ともしはぐれたとしても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.25,0:22:53.19,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕和你走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.19,0:22:55.61,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.19,0:22:55.61,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,一定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.70,0:23:06.31,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,見つけだして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.70,0:23:06.31,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,会找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.22,0:23:24.30,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,目覚めたら　そばにいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.22,0:23:24.30,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,醒来的时候 就在你身边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.00,0:23:32.17,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,明日も
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.00,0:23:32.17,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,明天也一样
