[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 恶魔岛字幕
Original Script: 恶魔岛字幕组
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 1280
PlayResY: 720
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,2,0,2,20,20,12,1
Style: Warring,微软雅黑,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H282D2D2D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Zhushi,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,2,0,8,20,20,12,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H28000000,&HF0C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title2,方正准圆_GBK,60,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default3,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ED_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: ED_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.96,0:04:20.96,Warring,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,300)}翻译 TL旧民  后期 aoi  恶魔岛字幕组制作 仅供交流试看之用\N请勿添加广告 相关资源和讨论请访问恶魔岛动漫世界：http://bbs.emland.net
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.82,0:02:47.82,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,眠れない夜に　聞いた物語が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.20,0:02:52.58,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,絵空事だとしたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.45,0:03:09.34,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,永遠を知るより　快楽を求めて
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.69,0:03:13.16,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,今を悔やんでしまうのは
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.89,0:03:19.86,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,心の深くに　住み着いた影から
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.11,0:03:23.71,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,逃げるためだとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.41,0:03:29.45,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,それでも　あたしはあたしを
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.59,0:03:33.06,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,愛していられるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.27,0:03:36.92,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,半分に割れた太陽が
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.18,0:03:39.26,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,朝を連れてきて
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.45,0:03:44.41,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,闇に慣れた神経を　じわり刺激する
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.77,0:03:49.60,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,置き忘れたの愛は　あえてそのままで
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.08,0:03:54.47,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,シナリオの消えた物語は
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.57,0:03:59.74,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,自由に　自由に　舵をとって
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.08,0:04:06.24,OP_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　高くへ　舞い上がって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.82,0:02:47.82,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,在无法入眠的夜晚 听到的那个故事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.20,0:02:52.58,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是天马行空的妄想的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.45,0:03:09.34,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,与其探求永远的奥秘 不如把握当下的欢乐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.69,0:03:13.16,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,别让此时此刻成为一生的悔恨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.89,0:03:19.86,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是为了逃避盘踞在内心深处的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.11,0:03:23.71,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,那片黑影的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.41,0:03:29.45,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此 我还能发自内心地
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.59,0:03:33.06,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,爱着自己的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.27,0:03:36.92,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,分成两半的太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.18,0:03:39.26,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,带来了明媚清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.45,0:03:44.41,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,微微刺激着已经习惯黑暗的神经
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.77,0:03:49.60,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,把忘了带走的爱原封不动地摆在那
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.08,0:03:54.47,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,缺了剧本的故事就会..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.57,0:03:59.74,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,自由地 自由地  操起船舵
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.08,0:04:06.24,OP_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,一起飞向更高的地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.66,0:22:28.67,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ　叶うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.64,0:22:40.70,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,君の手の中 揺れる小さな花でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.52,0:22:47.25,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,はじめてみる眩しいこの世界で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.73,0:22:52.67,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,君ともしはぐれたとしても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.67,0:22:55.09,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,きっと　
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.18,0:23:05.79,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,見つけだして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.70,0:23:23.78,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,目覚めたら　そばにいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.48,0:23:31.65,ED_jp,,0000,0000,0000,,明日も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.66,0:22:28.67,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,如果只能实现一个愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.64,0:22:40.70,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,我想成为在你手中随风摇曳的小花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.52,0:22:47.25,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,在这个陌生 而又炫目的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.73,0:22:52.67,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕和你走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.67,0:22:55.09,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,一定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.18,0:23:05.79,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,会找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.70,0:23:23.78,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,醒来的时候 就在你身边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.48,0:23:31.65,ED_cn,,0000,0000,0000,,明天也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.75,0:04:21.56,title,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(360,600)}{\fad(250,150)}#0 「命运...这个东西...」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.20,0:00:06.36,Default2,,0000,0000,0000,,七个月前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.89,0:00:14.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经准备好了 老爷
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.56,0:00:29.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.57,0:00:31.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来 过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.02,0:00:32.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我来帮你拍照吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.72,0:00:34.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要在这里拍吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.49,0:00:36.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,父亲大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.78,0:00:37.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那当然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.61,0:00:40.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不正是为此而来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.58,0:00:42.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把处于中学生最后阶段的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.26,0:00:45.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永久保留在这个大自然的景色之中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.29,0:00:48.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是作为一个父亲理所当然的想法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.85,0:00:51.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不知道会不会被别人看到
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.03,0:00:55.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁会看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.50,0:00:58.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只属于我们啊 礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.68,0:01:01.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是只属于我们的世界啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.10,0:01:13.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来 脱掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.07,0:01:14.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.74,0:01:45.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了礼弥！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.21,0:01:46.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.24,0:01:48.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想拍的就是这个！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.21,0:01:50.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你明白吗 礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.64,0:01:52.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.23,0:01:55.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这才是..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.68,0:02:00.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这才是仅仅属于我的你啊！礼弥！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.86,0:02:02.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的礼弥..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.71,0:02:04.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.25,0:02:10.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对这些事情浑然不知
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.43,0:02:14.13,Default2,,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅是被满足还远远不够吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.41,0:02:19.28,Default2,,0000,0000,0000,,自由地 自由地  操起船舵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.71,0:02:24.55,Default2,,0000,0000,0000,,变成小鸟朝着更远的地方飞去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.92,0:02:29.76,Default2,,0000,0000,0000,,自由地 自由地  操起船舵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.30,0:02:37.52,Default2,,0000,0000,0000,,变成星星朝着更高的地方飞去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.09,0:02:34.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.53,0:02:38.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是我还完全不认识礼弥的时候的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.54,0:04:16.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呀 唱得还真是相当地悦耳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.04,0:04:19.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,萌路妹妹的歌喉也是出奇地好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.93,0:04:26.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs48}因为近来小学生的社交 如果缺了卡拉OK可真是说不过去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.03,0:04:28.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,千紘 你听到了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.76,0:04:32.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是小学生就这么积极地发展人际关系了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.36,0:04:34.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是你看你啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.42,0:04:36.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烦不烦啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.90,0:04:44.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔啊 你好歹也说一说他呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.37,0:04:45.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兰子酱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.68,0:04:49.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别看我这样 我可是放任主义的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.60,0:04:51.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看上去就完全是放任主义的样子啦..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.39,0:04:52.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且还放任过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.79,0:04:54.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是稍微收一下缰绳比较好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.16,0:04:55.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算啦算啦..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.16,0:04:57.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难得出来旅行一次嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.59,0:04:58.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难得出来一起外宿嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.39,0:05:03.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是只有你的周围散发着一股你房间的味道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.93,0:05:05.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么办法嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.60,0:05:07.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都说了我讨厌旅行..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.43,0:05:09.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都说了我喜欢自己的房间..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.57,0:05:11.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都说了我最喜欢僵尸了..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.00,0:05:13.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暂时放一放啦 求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.24,0:05:15.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.74,0:05:16.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说老爹
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.91,0:05:17.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没到吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.66,0:05:19.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还早呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.22,0:05:21.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是个很凄凉的地方哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.97,0:05:22.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做好觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.61,0:05:26.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幽凄的风情反而让人别有一番期待呢..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.33,0:05:30.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪里都随便啦 总之先伸个懒腰..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.74,0:05:34.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那天为了前往住在东北的亲戚家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.15,0:05:36.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们摸黑起早地就开车出行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.65,0:05:40.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亲戚家的叔叔决定把留在仓库里的数量庞大的藏书
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.04,0:05:43.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部捐赠于京都资料馆
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.78,0:05:46.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以老爹和我们就被请过去帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.52,0:05:51.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而爷爷和巴布留着看家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.45,0:05:53.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是不知为何又多出了这个家伙..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.95,0:05:55.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.69,0:05:56.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么说呢..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.67,0:05:59.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好像六墓村和恶魔的蹴鞠歌哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.67,0:05:59.31,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}《六墓村》《恶魔的蹴鞠歌》：这里指的是《八墓村》《恶魔的彩球歌》，两者均为横沟正史的\N长篇推理小说。
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.76,0:06:02.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了啦 我超喜欢立沟的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.76,0:06:02.65,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}立沟：这里指的是横沟正史，日本推理小说家，以讲述金田一耕助的侦探故事的一系列小说而闻名。
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.34,0:06:06.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个讲的不是东北 而是冈山啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.73,0:06:08.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要挑刺啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.54,0:06:09.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.54,0:06:11.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,荒无人烟指的就是这种感觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.06,0:06:16.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是我也觉得刚才那个发言有问题哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.85,0:06:22.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.72,0:06:23.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.86,0:06:25.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不..好像..
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.02,0:06:26.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.46,0:06:27.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说萌路
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.36,0:06:30.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那座桥是不是在哪里见过？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.68,0:06:33.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不清楚 我没什么印象耶
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.39,0:06:35.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.18,0:06:37.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得好像在哪里见过..
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.21,0:06:39.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正又是电影里的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.78,0:06:54.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当时萦绕在我心头的东西到底是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.41,0:06:57.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等我弄明白又是蛮久以后的事情了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.24,0:07:04.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吓了一跳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.59,0:07:06.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,荒废成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.93,0:07:08.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欸..还好啦..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.72,0:07:10.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为想开发也无从下手呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.33,0:07:13.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就像是个被抛弃的孤岛般的村子一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.31,0:07:16.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是..真是个很美的地方呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.52,0:07:18.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要住下来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.58,0:07:20.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欸..这就..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.67,0:07:23.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么回事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.31,0:07:25.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然偶尔回来看看不错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.06,0:07:27.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是住起来就很不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.87,0:07:30.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过对我们这些上了年纪的人来说倒是刚好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.32,0:07:36.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走到学校要花两小时还真是辛苦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.69,0:07:39.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没个租片店日子难过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.77,0:07:43.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你们在自说自话些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.19,0:07:47.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两个人都这么精神真是太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.29,0:07:51.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生那个事故的时候我还以为会出什么事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.05,0:07:53.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我做的是这行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.00,0:07:58.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过从没有像那时候那样认真地想要倚靠神佛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.96,0:08:00.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,柚菜也真是可惜啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.24,0:08:03.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在孩子们面前还请您见谅一下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.00,0:08:06.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊..啊..对不住对不住
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.03,0:08:12.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,柚菜小姐是你们的妈妈对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.56,0:08:14.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.66,0:08:18.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过父亲就如同刚刚那样不太愿意提及母亲之事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.63,0:08:21.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎样的一个人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.12,0:08:25.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在小时候见过一小面而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.48,0:08:29.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本人的记忆也是十分之模糊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.99,0:08:32.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为实在是年纪太小了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.47,0:08:36.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是个很好的人呢..这一点是可以肯定的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.20,0:08:40.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让您为我费心真是过意不去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.07,0:08:42.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会..我只是..
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.97,0:08:47.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有些模糊 但是本人的记忆中她也确实是个好人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.96,0:08:51.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是细节的部分无论如何都..
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.60,0:08:55.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊 老爹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.11,0:08:57.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.14,0:08:59.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知怎么的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.20,0:09:02.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总是不太想得起来妈妈的事情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.38,0:09:04.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.54,0:09:06.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.34,0:09:08.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常喜欢她啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.14,0:09:10.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常温柔啊之类的..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.11,0:09:12.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明还记得对她的那些感情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.42,0:09:16.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是对老妈本人的事情却怎么都想不起来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.14,0:09:19.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样不也蛮好的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.57,0:09:21.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.15,0:09:23.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这样就好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.58,0:09:26.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好喜欢 好温柔..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.30,0:09:28.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论哪一点都是事实
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.02,0:09:30.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你一点都没有搞错
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.83,0:09:31.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.35,0:09:32.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.65,0:09:37.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,柚菜曾拜托我不要告诉你们关于她的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.30,0:09:40.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她也有她的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.15,0:09:42.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就顺着她的意思去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.20,0:09:43.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.71,0:09:46.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老爹..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.83,0:09:49.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我不知道到底发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.30,0:09:53.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过那天的老爹有一种让人不敢多言的威严
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.39,0:09:56.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我也没能再问下去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.85,0:10:00.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说到母亲..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.20,0:10:06.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没有睡吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.28,0:10:08.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有点睡不着
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.13,0:10:15.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喝吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.03,0:10:17.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.98,0:10:20.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真傻呢 开玩笑啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.42,0:10:31.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个啦 那种表情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.39,0:10:33.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让人不痛快的就是那种表情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.50,0:10:36.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像只有自己是受害者一样的那种表情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.25,0:10:39.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我最看不过去的就是这个！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.79,0:10:44.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请住手 母亲大人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.61,0:10:47.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你 根本就没有考虑过我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.26,0:10:49.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,满脑子想的全是你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.86,0:10:54.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果觉得只有你自己不幸那就大错特错了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.31,0:10:56.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这世上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.94,0:11:00.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不幸就像台球一样在互相撞击着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.78,0:11:05.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就因为你的那种感受让我成为了这样一个坏妈妈啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.10,0:11:06.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你明白吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.66,0:11:08.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请..请住手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.84,0:11:14.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想变得幸福的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.41,0:11:16.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就先让我幸福吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.62,0:11:20.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么做才可以呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.35,0:11:24.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从这里消失之类的？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.04,0:11:28.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,..还有这种妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.26,0:11:44.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.66,0:11:46.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呀..只是兴趣太广了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.55,0:11:49.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然也有一部分是从父辈那传下来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.26,0:11:52.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还真是攒了不少呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.24,0:11:56.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想与其攒在这里 不如捐赠资料馆
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.12,0:11:59.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样更能发扬光大造福大众
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.42,0:12:01.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,车子已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.95,0:12:04.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么就开始遵照马场先生的指示
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.25,0:12:06.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帮我把书籍都装箱打包吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.85,0:12:11.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样看来 车子也得往返好几次呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.77,0:12:14.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定一天还干不完呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.78,0:12:19.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 这个 给
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.08,0:12:33.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,平时的烂成绩开始作怂了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.49,0:12:35.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 给我闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.51,0:12:39.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上午就这样 到了傍晚就变废人了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.81,0:12:43.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是归到捐赠类呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.94,0:12:46.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而这个是重复资料
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.74,0:12:48.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以请装进那边的箱子里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.81,0:12:50.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只看封面就知道了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.06,0:12:52.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我就是靠这个吃饭的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.92,0:12:54.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是资料管理员的长处啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.17,0:13:05.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该吃午餐了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.28,0:13:07.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连下午都撑不到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.42,0:13:09.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.02,0:13:10.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要我来背你吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.03,0:13:13.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用啦 你们先走
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.27,0:13:15.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一会就去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.91,0:13:17.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说我连吃饭的力气都没了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.63,0:13:19.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.11,0:13:21.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果过了30分钟还不来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.10,0:13:23.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就把饭拿过来给他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.85,0:13:26.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了吗 哥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.83,0:13:27.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.16,0:13:30.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 总之好好歇一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.48,0:13:32.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暂别一会罗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.30,0:13:40.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是躺着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.22,0:13:56.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.58,0:14:10.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老..妈？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.02,0:14:40.01,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}把以上列举之物置入研钵捣碎混合
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.02,0:14:40.01,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}枯叶碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.02,0:14:40.01,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}河豚的肠子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.02,0:14:40.01,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}不死之水
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.47,0:14:41.49,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9}蚯蚓数只
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.47,0:14:41.49,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9}薄翅蜻蜓的翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.47,0:14:41.49,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9}芥末之子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.47,0:14:41.49,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}杉叶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.47,0:14:41.49,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}蜗牛壳
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.47,0:14:41.49,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}钴的粉末
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.93,0:14:56.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老妈..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.15,0:15:02.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不..这个是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.77,0:15:04.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,假书那一类的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.62,0:15:06.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,假书？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.93,0:15:08.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,简单地说就是骗人的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.38,0:15:11.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且虽然弄出一副很像古文书的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.41,0:15:14.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但好像也并不是那么有年头的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.88,0:15:18.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该是某个人因恶作剧而制作出来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.10,0:15:22.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个没有价值
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.18,0:15:24.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请放入处理品的箱子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.98,0:15:26.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.50,0:15:28.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.44,0:15:38.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.11,0:15:45.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,母亲大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.64,0:15:50.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,母亲大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.41,0:15:51.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.08,0:15:54.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚您说的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.25,0:15:55.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你指什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.53,0:15:58.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我消失的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.41,0:16:00.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的会幸福吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.50,0:16:02.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.77,0:16:05.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您不记得了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.07,0:16:07.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我累了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.22,0:16:09.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能不能让我一个人清静一会
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.81,0:16:11.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.45,0:16:14.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,皐月 给我拿头痛药来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.48,0:16:16.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 马上就来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.19,0:16:17.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,动作快
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.22,0:16:27.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,消失..吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.88,0:16:33.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干脆就这么做说不定更好..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.74,0:16:36.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.27,0:16:40.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,露天浴池的清扫已经完毕了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.03,0:16:42.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.12,0:16:46.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呀 托各位的福
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.92,0:16:48.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用了今天一天就整理完毕了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.22,0:16:50.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的辛苦各位了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.29,0:16:53.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可能这阵子都不会想看书了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.70,0:16:57.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到书是这么沉甸甸的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.29,0:17:01.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会再买书了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.61,0:17:05.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,萌路妹妹 那是我的台词啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.22,0:17:08.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,千紘君也已经没事了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.96,0:17:11.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？啊 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.87,0:17:12.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.15,0:17:14.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全恢复了 是..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.56,0:17:15.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.80,0:17:18.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果能在这里再休息一天就好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.46,0:17:21.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我们很想这么办
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.82,0:17:23.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是施主那边的事也抛不开
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.73,0:17:24.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以明天再怎么可得赶回去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.42,0:17:27.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有不少地方想带你们参观
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.96,0:17:30.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也好想再观光观光呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.76,0:17:32.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这有一座纱红瀑布啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.62,0:17:36.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是个国家指定文化财产的大瀑布呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.19,0:17:40.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道！在电视里看到过！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.47,0:17:41.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,电视里可不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.17,0:17:43.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个得亲眼看一看才行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.64,0:17:47.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,气势相当惊人呢 像..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.98,0:17:48.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们去吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.98,0:17:49.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.89,0:17:52.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们就去嘛 难得都来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.02,0:17:54.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.81,0:17:55.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我赞成哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.16,0:17:57.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了长见识一定要看一看
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.75,0:18:00.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,千紘 你就陪她们去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.94,0:18:01.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.65,0:18:02.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.64,0:18:04.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就算了啦 我很累了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.56,0:18:07.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能让两个女生自己去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.22,0:18:10.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是要在大山里走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.74,0:18:12.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概走个一小时吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.56,0:18:13.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算了啦..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.56,0:18:14.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走嘛 千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.10,0:18:16.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.61,0:18:17.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根据你的回答
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.74,0:18:20.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作为男生的评价会大大提升哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.82,0:18:22.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很烦耶你们两个！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.20,0:18:30.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你们这么有精神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.52,0:18:34.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小学生的体力不可小觑也
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.78,0:18:37.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说是你的体力太差了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.83,0:18:40.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那点小事就累成那样你真是嫩毙了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.15,0:18:46.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？这么怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.61,0:18:50.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这路还真是复杂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.11,0:18:54.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想应该是这边
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.27,0:18:56.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 应该是这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.51,0:18:58.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.77,0:19:02.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？..复活是指..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.86,0:19:10.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啥？小狗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.53,0:19:12.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,萌路？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.63,0:19:14.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不妙..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.18,0:19:26.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才说不要 的说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.16,0:19:35.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？为什么..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.96,0:19:42.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好想消失
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.10,0:19:47.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,至少..想投胎做别人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.83,0:19:53.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,行不通吗..这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.87,0:19:58.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个难不成..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.99,0:20:02.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,写的是关于如何唤醒死者的方法？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.95,0:20:06.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,复活..丸？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.57,0:20:31.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌讨厌讨厌讨厌讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.89,0:20:50.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.46,0:20:54.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然发生了这样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.53,0:20:58.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感动~
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.90,0:21:03.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感时之境迁而不觉泪沾襟下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.90,0:21:03.33,Zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}時の移るまで涙を落としはべりぬ：出自于日本俳圣松尾芭蕉的纪行文集《奥の細道》，值得一提的是\N该句引用了我国唐代诗人杜甫著作《春望》中的"感时花溅泪"一句。
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.32,0:21:09.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果我也没能看到瀑布
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.19,0:21:14.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这样离开了叔叔家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.17,0:21:18.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,联想到之后的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.51,0:21:21.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定这世上真的存在命运这个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.43,0:21:26.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么..是谁在冥冥中指引了我们的命运呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.10,0:21:42.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我每次想起那段旅行..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.72,0:21:44.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,母亲的记忆就会浮现于脑海之中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.00,0:23:43.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是降谷千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.53,0:23:45.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是一名热爱僵尸的高中生
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.67,0:23:49.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在机缘巧合之下和楚楚可怜的大小姐散华礼弥邂逅了 可是..
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.67,0:23:51.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我成了僵尸的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.89,0:23:52.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,散华礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.10,0:23:54.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请试着为我负责吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,

