[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-11-01 12:28:26
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:恶魔岛字幕
Original Script:恶魔岛字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,20,20,12,1
Style: Warring,微软雅黑,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H282D2D2D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Zhushi,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,12,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H28000000,&HF0C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title2,方正准圆_GBK,60,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default3,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ED_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: ED_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.95,0:02:31.95,Warring,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,300)}翻译 TL旧民  后期 aoi  恶魔岛字幕组制作 仅供交流试看之用 \N请勿添加广告 相关资源和讨论请访问恶魔岛动漫世界：http://bbs.emland.net
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.81,0:00:58.81,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眠れない夜に　聞いた物語が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.19,0:01:03.57,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絵空事だとしたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.44,0:01:20.33,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永遠を知るより　快楽を求めて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.68,0:01:24.15,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今を悔やんでしまうのは
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.88,0:01:30.85,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心の深くに　住み着いた影から
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.10,0:01:34.70,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃げるためだとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.40,0:01:40.44,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでも　あたしはあたしを
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.58,0:01:44.05,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛していられるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.26,0:01:47.91,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半分に割れた太陽が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.17,0:01:50.25,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝を連れてきて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.44,0:01:55.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闇に慣れた神経を　じわり刺激する
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.76,0:02:00.59,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,置き忘れたの愛は　あえてそのままで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.07,0:02:05.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シナリオの消えた物語は
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.56,0:02:10.73,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由に　自由に　舵をとって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.07,0:02:17.23,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　高くへ　舞い上がって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.81,0:00:58.81,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在无法入眠的夜晚 听到的那个故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.19,0:01:03.57,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是天马行空的妄想的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.44,0:01:20.33,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与其探求永远的奥秘 不如把握当下的欢乐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.68,0:01:24.15,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让此时此刻成为一生的悔恨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.88,0:01:30.85,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是为了逃避盘踞在内心深处的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.10,0:01:34.70,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那片黑影的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.40,0:01:40.44,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此 我还能发自内心地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.58,0:01:44.05,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱着自己的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.26,0:01:47.91,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分成两半的太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.17,0:01:50.25,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带来了明媚清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.44,0:01:55.40,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微微刺激着已经习惯黑暗的神经
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.76,0:02:00.59,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把忘了带走的爱原封不动地摆在那
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.07,0:02:05.46,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缺了剧本的故事就会..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.56,0:02:10.73,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由地 自由地  操起船舵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.07,0:02:17.23,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起飞向更高的地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.30,0:22:28.31,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ　叶うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.28,0:22:40.34,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君の手の中 揺れる小さな花でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.16,0:22:46.89,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はじめてみる眩しいこの世界で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.37,0:22:52.31,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君ともしはぐれたとしても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.31,0:22:54.73,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと　
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.82,0:23:05.43,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見つけだして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.34,0:23:23.42,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目覚めたら　そばにいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.12,0:23:31.29,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.30,0:22:28.31,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果只能实现一个愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.28,0:22:40.34,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想成为在你手中随风摇曳的小花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.16,0:22:46.89,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个陌生 而又炫目的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.37,0:22:52.31,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕和你走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.31,0:22:54.73,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.82,0:23:05.43,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.34,0:23:23.42,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒来的时候 就在你身边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.12,0:23:31.29,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.79,0:02:35.68,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(902,600)}{\fad(250,150)}#7 「青梅...竹马...」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.29,0:24:09.47,title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(660,490)}#8 「虚伪的...自由...」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.75,0:00:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 千紘那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.74,0:00:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要拜托我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.24,0:00:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.81,0:00:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.32,0:00:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 丢下你了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.42,0:00:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你坏啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.47,0:02:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.50,0:02:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好好吃的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.29,0:02:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真漂亮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.58,0:02:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 味道好香
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.50,0:02:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.00,0:02:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫左王子兰子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.14,0:02:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是私立散华女子学园的二年级生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.29,0:02:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母亲是这里..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.41,0:02:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,京怀石左王子的老板娘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.44,0:02:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲是料理长
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.09,0:02:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我也就是生下来就是料理店的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.79,0:02:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从小时候开始就经常帮家里的忙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.62,0:02:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔碰到人手不足的话 就会变成随叫随到的帮手
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.82,0:02:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.29,0:03:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 手脚再利索点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.90,0:03:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 不要突然冲着我喊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.76,0:03:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会切到手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.69,0:03:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且为什么我必须来你们店帮忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.24,0:03:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得的周日假期的说..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.33,0:03:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说那么绝情的话嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.90,0:03:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都认识这么久了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.72,0:03:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 手停下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.32,0:03:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你让我停的吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.81,0:03:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你在那磨磨蹭蹭的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.39,0:03:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 这么一看就像登对的年轻夫妇呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.81,0:03:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.18,0:03:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的哦 千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.15,0:03:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算结了婚我也不会叫你继承这家店的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.33,0:03:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到机会就赶紧推了吧 不用给我面子的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.46,0:03:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说是吧 亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.31,0:03:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.70,0:03:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.43,0:03:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.12,0:03:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.85,0:03:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.86,0:04:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好火热的一对哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.07,0:04:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不用这么慌忙放手啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.82,0:04:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.31,0:04:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.37,0:04:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和千紘第一次相遇 是在我读幼稚园的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.62,0:04:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在恋爱偶像剧里经常能看到那种..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.51,0:04:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为糟糕的邂逅而非常讨厌对方
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.10,0:04:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经历了不少事之后又渐渐喜欢上的情节
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.37,0:04:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我和千紘的相遇是..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.17,0:04:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最棒的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.46,0:04:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不害怕吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.40,0:04:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不害怕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.41,0:05:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我的白马王子出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.03,0:05:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而那个白马王子的真实身份..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.17,0:05:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隔天呶恩叔叔就告诉了我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.34,0:05:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子 这是我的儿子千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.24,0:05:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然小你一岁 不过要好好相处哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.97,0:05:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.27,0:05:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.39,0:05:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.02,0:05:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来玩吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.13,0:05:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时我决心一定要和他交上朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.62,0:05:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要看电影吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.02,0:05:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很有趣哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.84,0:05:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 埃莉娅诺？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.51,0:05:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做噩梦了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.62,0:06:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃莉娅诺？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.83,0:06:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.79,0:06:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.90,0:06:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.02,0:06:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到外面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.85,0:06:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.00,0:06:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外面玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.61,0:06:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.40,0:06:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到外面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.01,0:06:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘平时都玩些什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.82,0:06:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看僵尸电影
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.51,0:06:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了僵尸电影呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.55,0:07:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,读僵尸的书
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.86,0:07:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,..除了僵尸呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.98,0:07:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.88,0:07:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那和玩不一样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.94,0:07:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.87,0:07:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘 用这个来玩办家家酒吧..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.90,0:07:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.91,0:07:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.49,0:07:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱花树下据说会埋着尸体呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.26,0:07:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.58,0:07:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定埋着僵尸呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.68,0:07:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.44,0:07:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.75,0:07:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事好吓人的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.85,0:07:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？是寺庙家的千紘嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.64,0:07:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.24,0:07:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 居然在和女人玩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.87,0:07:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真丢脸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.40,0:07:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们不肯跟你玩 所以你去找女人跟你玩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.86,0:07:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好恶心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.30,0:08:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.03,0:08:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和女孩子玩有什么不好？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.83,0:08:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.93,0:08:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.79,0:08:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.03,0:08:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵 又哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.62,0:08:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙真的没两下就要哭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.01,0:08:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是觉得一哭就能解决问题了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.68,0:08:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看中的白马王子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.93,0:08:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实只是个喜欢僵尸的怪人..
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.72,0:08:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕麻烦又不会和人互动的爱哭可怜虫
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.94,0:08:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不害怕墓地只是因为这是他家而且在僵尸片里也看惯了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.83,0:08:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以到了回家的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.81,0:08:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的爱恋之心也被浇灭了一大半
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.71,0:08:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能款待您什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.78,0:08:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里 每次来这里我都会不小心玩太疯真对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.84,0:08:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方便的话 就算不是逢年过节也经常来玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.75,0:09:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.64,0:09:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？柚菜小姐呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.92,0:09:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛 由于萌路发烧了所以带她去了医院
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.34,0:09:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是..是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.02,0:09:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你们根本不用特地来送我们的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.49,0:09:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 并没什么大不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.58,0:09:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么哥哥 再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.02,0:09:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.50,0:09:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子 不用和千紘说再见吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.78,0:09:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.58,0:09:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 被叫去帮厨的我为什么还要帮忙外送？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.32,0:09:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为你帮厨不力嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.28,0:09:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么办法啊 我根本没怎么用过菜刀啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.71,0:09:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.04,0:09:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 为什么小狗也跟过来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.48,0:09:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果千紘一个人去的话 根本不会好好招呼客人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.88,0:10:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样可牵涉到我们店的信誉问题
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.60,0:10:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有这么没常识呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.74,0:10:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得到啦 打招呼之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.43,0:10:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.12,0:10:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少说话多干活
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.51,0:10:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子 今天也谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.84,0:10:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会不会 哪里的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.58,0:10:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘就让你随便使唤了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.07,0:10:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟一直都劳你们家照顾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.69,0:10:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.67,0:10:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就没有拒绝的权力吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.00,0:10:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.46,0:10:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.98,0:10:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有几家？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.78,0:10:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.25,0:10:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 就这么不情愿帮忙？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.46,0:10:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是这样啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.97,0:10:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你看..礼弥的事我会在意嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.84,0:10:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 礼弥同学呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.28,0:10:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 所以说不是你想的那样啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.47,0:10:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明白的事还有一堆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.25,0:10:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况还不稳定..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.78,0:10:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.53,0:10:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.14,0:11:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真放心不下呢 礼弥同学好可爱的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.25,0:11:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你完全没有懂嘛！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.98,0:11:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这难不成是约会吗？！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.53,0:11:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是约会吗？！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.52,0:11:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？是..是约会吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.61,0:11:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们傻啊 那怎么可能嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.95,0:11:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 也用不着这么全盘否定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.63,0:11:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为本来就不是约会嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.48,0:11:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛？就这么讨厌被人说你和我相好？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.19,0:11:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是讨厌之类的问题啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.82,0:11:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下等下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.14,0:11:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这难不成就是..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.99,0:11:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情侣之间才会出现令人向往的打情骂俏？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.37,0:11:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.33,0:11:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊~咧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.33,0:11:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.62,0:11:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥小姐也好兰子小姐也好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.50,0:11:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么只有你这么受欢迎啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.07,0:11:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且关键的本人还宣称什么自己独爱僵尸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.08,0:11:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游刃有余？是游刃有余吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.31,0:11:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在愚弄我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.39,0:11:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是这样吧你这混蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.18,0:11:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,康孝同学你冷静一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.39,0:12:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么冷静的下来嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.71,0:12:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是懒得陪你演下去..
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.52,0:12:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.57,0:12:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要选这种家伙？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.71,0:12:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙根本就是长相平平的僵尸宅 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.92,0:12:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱闹别扭又怕麻烦的顽固废柴 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.65,0:12:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是没错啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.49,0:12:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不否认啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.43,0:12:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你不也是个宅美少女的死变态嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.36,0:12:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.25,0:12:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于这一点我反而觉得很光荣！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.44,0:12:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果你也不受欢迎的话我就没话说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.07,0:12:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说我没受欢迎啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.12,0:12:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还要说么 你这个装模作样的家伙！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.73,0:12:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩都冷静一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.45,0:12:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很冷静啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.45,0:12:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和千紘的再会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.73,0:12:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是第一次相遇的两年之后
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.60,0:12:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我六岁的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.29,0:12:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在父亲的坚持下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.84,0:12:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家之前开在千叶的店被搬来了紫阳町
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.36,0:12:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家和千紘家的寺庙成了邻居
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.33,0:12:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是 没过多久
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.97,0:12:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于母亲的邀请 千紘被请到我们家玩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.33,0:12:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然两年前的恋情泡了汤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.49,0:13:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过由于我们是堂姐堂弟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.47,0:13:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想这次要好好陪他玩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.87,0:13:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.46,0:13:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.38,0:13:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.52,0:13:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来玩游戏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.35,0:13:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不玩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.20,0:13:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就到外面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.45,0:13:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.51,0:13:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有变
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.75,0:13:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我把点心拿来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.14,0:13:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘 我们好不容易做了邻居
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.27,0:13:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要和兰子好好相处哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.39,0:13:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 好一个怕羞的小朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.17,0:13:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.68,0:13:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要这样..不要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.65,0:13:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知为何母亲从以前开始就很中意千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.30,0:13:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直想让我们俩的关系变好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.79,0:13:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也让我的心情迅速冷却
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.19,0:13:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是好可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.17,0:13:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 兰子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.30,0:13:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 兰子 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.02,0:13:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.56,0:13:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在上面看书
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.78,0:13:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不一起玩呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.59,0:14:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘说他不要玩嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.93,0:14:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是不玩游戏也不要到外面去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.85,0:14:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就去附近的租片店
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.48,0:14:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你前一阵子不是说有一部卡通很想看吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.07,0:14:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那个租过来一起看嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.11,0:14:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.29,0:14:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子是个把难得来玩的堂弟一直晾在一边的孩子吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.29,0:14:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.28,0:14:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.38,0:14:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.22,0:14:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.04,0:14:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.92,0:14:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.02,0:14:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去租卡通吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.64,0:14:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一部很有趣的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.04,0:14:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个才有意思呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.01,0:14:55.81,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僵尸学院 惨剧的文化祭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.35,0:15:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僵尸学院 惨剧的文化祭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.19,0:15:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不愧是千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.16,0:15:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个的话 我店里好像有从美国买来的最新作
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.07,0:15:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要看吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.01,0:15:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.88,0:15:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.70,0:15:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 千紘真厉害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.95,0:15:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明才五岁就能看没有国语配音的恐怖电影
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.40,0:15:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.79,0:15:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内容有点刺激 要跟爸爸妈妈保密哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.03,0:15:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.71,0:15:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 刺激是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.98,0:15:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说里边的僵尸比较血肉模糊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.92,0:15:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血肉模糊是..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.24,0:15:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎样呢 血肉模糊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.16,0:15:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么自己决定要看什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.12,0:15:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 这个一定很有意思的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.38,0:15:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个系列可是很有口碑的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.37,0:16:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢恐怖片这类的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.01,0:16:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是看了以后一定会喜欢上的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.20,0:16:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是是英文的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.69,0:16:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算听不懂里边的话也很有意思的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.85,0:16:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我觉得没意思啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.07,0:16:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要看卡通啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.51,0:16:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 绝对比卡通有趣多了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.96,0:16:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起恐怖片 我就是想要看卡通啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.27,0:16:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把这个拿去还掉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.95,0:16:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？兰子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.41,0:16:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.01,0:16:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到别地方去啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.76,0:17:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.90,0:17:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘 谢谢你救我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.21,0:17:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在回想起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.05,0:17:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然在墓地的时候就已经一见钟情了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.68,0:17:32.65,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意保护我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.26,0:17:34.15,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.11,0:17:37.77,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解决这场灾难之后我们就一起生活吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.14,0:17:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我在10岁左右
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.07,0:17:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就已经完全喜欢上了千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.27,0:17:40.13,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 就这么决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.25,0:17:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊 千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.04,0:17:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.46,0:17:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘啊 初吻喜欢什么样的？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.88,0:17:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么样的是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.98,0:17:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看啊 不是有很多种吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.36,0:18:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以夕阳的大海为背景之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.82,0:18:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即将踏上旅途的情侣离别之际..之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.54,0:18:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.54,0:18:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是想和这种僵尸娘亲亲呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.82,0:18:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又..又是僵尸娘？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.09,0:18:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真以为这世上有这种女孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.55,0:18:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定就是有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.37,0:18:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你更认真的想一下啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.07,0:18:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接吻是很重要的事情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.55,0:18:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.45,0:18:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.57,0:18:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.28,0:18:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天你会遭天谴的！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.55,0:18:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想的话就介绍女孩子给我吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.44,0:18:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 好烦人的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.09,0:18:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 去最后两家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.88,0:18:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.03,0:18:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牵..我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.17,0:19:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.63,0:19:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管啦 叫你牵就牵
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.41,0:19:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛痛痛..我知道啦我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.18,0:19:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.69,0:19:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.99,0:19:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.31,0:19:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.38,0:19:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们第一次牵手是什么时候你记得吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.27,0:19:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是..第一次见面的时候吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.16,0:19:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在墓地里哭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.00,0:19:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迫不得已我只能拉着你的手走
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.70,0:19:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？我记错了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.03,0:19:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正确答案是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.17,0:19:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得啦 这么早以前的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.48,0:19:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.08,0:19:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道你什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.16,0:19:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,配送完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.08,0:19:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们还外送这种大户人家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.15,0:20:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 前年这家祖母办法事的时候吃的是我们店的便当
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.51,0:20:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后就成了我们的忠实顾客
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.13,0:20:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以经常会来订餐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.16,0:20:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘的工作到此结束
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.63,0:20:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以回去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.51,0:20:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高峰阶段也已经过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.62,0:20:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用再特意回去帮忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.45,0:20:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家那些人就忙得过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.28,0:20:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.60,0:20:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,LUCKY~
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.83,0:20:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再见了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.83,0:20:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.81,0:20:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你..怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.08,0:20:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.94,0:21:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在情势所趋之下就闭上眼等着被亲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.19,0:21:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.29,0:21:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再认真考虑一下啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.85,0:21:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接吻是很重要的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.16,0:21:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然..不想输给她
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.58,0:21:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对绝对..不会输给你的！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.16,0:23:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.56,0:23:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换我来..
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.07,0:23:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟萌路酱事先讲过了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.37,0:23:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好..
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.11,0:23:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回 散华礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.75,0:23:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第八话 虚伪的...自由...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.74,0:23:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.36,0:23:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌路酱？！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.33,0:24:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制作人..制作人在哪呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.33,0:24:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌路酱 这个啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.63,0:24:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制作人 
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.73,0:24:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么一回事给我说明一下吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
