[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-11-01 11:00:42
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:恶魔岛字幕
Original Script:恶魔岛字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,20,20,12,1
Style: Warring,微软雅黑,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H282D2D2D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Zhushi,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,12,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H28000000,&HF0C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title2,方正准圆_GBK,60,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default3,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ED_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: ED_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.95,0:02:29.95,Warring,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,300)}翻译 TL旧民  后期 aoi  恶魔岛字幕组制作 仅供交流试看之用 \N请勿添加广告 相关资源和讨论请访问恶魔岛动漫世界：http://bbs.emland.net
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.81,0:00:56.81,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眠れない夜に　聞いた物語が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.19,0:01:01.57,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絵空事だとしたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.44,0:01:18.33,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永遠を知るより　快楽を求めて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.68,0:01:22.15,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今を悔やんでしまうのは
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.88,0:01:28.85,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心の深くに　住み着いた影から
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.10,0:01:32.70,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃げるためだとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.40,0:01:38.44,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでも　あたしはあたしを
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.58,0:01:42.05,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛していられるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.26,0:01:45.91,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半分に割れた太陽が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.17,0:01:48.25,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝を連れてきて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.44,0:01:53.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闇に慣れた神経を　じわり刺激する
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.76,0:01:58.59,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,置き忘れたの愛は　あえてそのままで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.07,0:02:03.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シナリオの消えた物語は
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.56,0:02:08.73,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由に　自由に　舵をとって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.07,0:02:15.23,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　高くへ　舞い上がって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.81,0:00:56.81,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在无法入眠的夜晚 听到的那个故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.19,0:01:01.57,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是天马行空的妄想的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.44,0:01:18.33,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与其探求永远的奥秘 不如把握当下的欢乐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.68,0:01:22.15,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让此时此刻成为一生的悔恨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.88,0:01:28.85,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是为了逃避盘踞在内心深处的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.10,0:01:32.70,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那片黑影的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.40,0:01:38.44,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此 我还能发自内心地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.58,0:01:42.05,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱着自己的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.26,0:01:45.91,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分成两半的太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.17,0:01:48.25,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带来了明媚清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.44,0:01:53.40,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微微刺激着已经习惯黑暗的神经
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.76,0:01:58.59,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把忘了带走的爱原封不动地摆在那
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.07,0:02:03.46,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缺了剧本的故事就会..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.56,0:02:08.73,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由地 自由地  操起船舵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.07,0:02:15.23,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起飞向更高的地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.56,0:22:28.57,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ　叶うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.54,0:22:40.60,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君の手の中 揺れる小さな花でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.42,0:22:47.15,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はじめてみる眩しいこの世界で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.63,0:22:52.57,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君ともしはぐれたとしても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.57,0:22:54.99,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと　
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.08,0:23:05.69,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見つけだして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.60,0:23:23.68,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目覚めたら　そばにいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.38,0:23:31.55,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.56,0:22:28.57,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果只能实现一个愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.54,0:22:40.60,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想成为在你手中随风摇曳的小花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.42,0:22:47.15,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个陌生 而又炫目的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.63,0:22:52.57,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕和你走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.57,0:22:54.99,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.08,0:23:05.69,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.60,0:23:23.68,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒来的时候 就在你身边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.38,0:23:31.55,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.84,0:02:36.68,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(930,580)}{\fad(250,150)}#5 「僵尸...也就是说...」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.38,0:24:09.68,title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(660,500)}#6 「因为...与你相遇了」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.10,0:00:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想个办法的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.09,0:00:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.88,0:00:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要保护好礼弥的身体！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.94,0:03:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.82,0:03:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了死后硬直的礼弥的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.64,0:03:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去的话 肉体会逐渐腐烂..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.70,0:04:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 在硬直解除之前
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.30,0:04:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须找个法子来维持住礼弥的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.39,0:04:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于遗体保存方法的书？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.28,0:04:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 你之前好像有读过吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.22,0:04:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那本书..我想跟你借一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.36,0:04:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 关于防腐处理的书籍吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.36,0:04:39.47,Zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(600,660)}Embalming
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.24,0:04:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那本书借给学友尚未归还
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.86,0:04:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学友..你是哪门子中学生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.37,0:04:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小学生之上 高中生之下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.49,0:04:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不..这个我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.64,0:04:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥才是 为何要读那样的书？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.96,0:04:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.20,0:04:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊..那个..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.66,0:04:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有的话就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.00,0:05:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不打扰你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.32,0:05:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近好奇怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.57,0:05:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最常用的还是福尔马林吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.83,0:05:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是味道好像很呛人..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.04,0:05:27.12,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准随便进来！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.80,0:05:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让家人和邻居发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.14,0:05:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样看上去..就好像普普通通地在睡觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.50,0:05:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 千紘 萌路
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.50,0:05:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不快点起床
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.97,0:05:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.02,0:05:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她睡床还是不太妙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.89,0:05:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搬到壁橱里去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.02,0:06:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.66,0:06:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过话说回来..眼睛都不知道该往哪里看呢..
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.73,0:06:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛..
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.60,0:06:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘 你在干吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.67,0:06:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是的..
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.74,0:06:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.81,0:07:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想到了今天晚上硬直应该就会解除了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.19,0:07:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然窄了点有些不好意思..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.54,0:07:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过拜托你乖乖待在这里 明白吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.18,0:07:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚..刚才的声音是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.91,0:07:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.42,0:07:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成你..肚子饿了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.12,0:07:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那..等你能动了以后
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.16,0:07:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再拿点东西来给你吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.16,0:07:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸 我这就来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.01,0:07:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.68,0:07:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.69,0:07:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一如既往的早餐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.60,0:08:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！味噌汤里别放鱼板啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.54,0:08:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 那个是豆腐啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.95,0:08:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？！诶...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.52,0:08:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是我家一如既往的情景
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.13,0:08:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请让我经历一下 作为普通女孩子的所有体验
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.48,0:08:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说..什么叫普通呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.77,0:08:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这没头没尾地是要问什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.42,0:08:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不..没事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.27,0:08:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！味噌汤里别放鱼板啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.04,0:08:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 那个是豆腐啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.26,0:08:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？！诶...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.59,0:09:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.24,0:09:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯..礼弥同学她..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.67,0:09:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.51,0:09:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 这不是兰子学姐吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.59,0:09:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.82,0:09:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐你在这里干什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.90,0:09:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家的工作啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.05,0:09:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来你又是来这里干嘛的？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.74,0:09:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 关于这个嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.87,0:09:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为同班的礼弥大人没有来学校上课..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.90,0:09:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我很为她担心 于是就来她家看看情况
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.08,0:09:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.05,0:09:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说..可以从正门进去嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.78,0:09:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.24,0:09:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你也真闲呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.61,0:09:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为礼弥大人可是我的偶像哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.93,0:09:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过兰子学姐对我来说也是一样耀眼的偶像哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.95,0:09:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用奉承我啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.19,0:10:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得最近的礼弥大人样子有点怪怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.98,0:10:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不..虽然依旧是那样的美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.39,0:10:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过好像总带着一些淡淡的忧伤..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.59,0:10:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶~
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.11,0:10:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还是无故缺席哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.17,0:10:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我实在是在意到不行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.12,0:10:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.95,0:10:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 以兰子学姐来看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.45,0:10:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是学妹 对她并没有太大的兴趣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.32,0:10:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是在我们一年级里 礼弥大人可是所有人关注的目标呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.68,0:10:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为她真的很美啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.28,0:10:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 来看看她的照片吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.05,0:10:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..有好多版本呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.39,0:10:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么第一张先看我觉得最美的抓拍..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.52,0:10:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.67,0:10:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉稳高贵的气质让人不由地就看呆了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.31,0:10:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这个是三人照
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.21,0:10:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一张是我最宝贵的双人照
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.41,0:11:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.24,0:11:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是礼弥家的女仆们看起来都是一副匆匆忙忙的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.34,0:11:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟发生什么事了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.84,0:11:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好像闹腾得很厉害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.16,0:11:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟是怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.16,0:11:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成礼弥大人出事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.96,0:11:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子学姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.42,0:11:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.76,0:11:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是休息日
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.00,0:11:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校不上课
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.47,0:11:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家人全体出动的..大扫除
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.71,0:11:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶..现在明明就不是干这个的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.37,0:11:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘 你好像又想养猫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.28,0:12:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前阵子才刚刚失去了巴布 到底怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.83,0:12:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦 老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.37,0:12:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布复活了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.45,0:12:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的什么莫名其妙的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.70,0:12:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷你也看到巴布了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.41,0:12:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 那个是巴布啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.14,0:12:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞧 爷爷也这么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.91,0:12:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊是啊 阿贞和巴布都复活啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.78,0:12:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊是啊 阿贞和巴布都..
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.46,0:12:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿贞是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.83,0:12:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的是巴布啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.73,0:12:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 两个人都傻在一块了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.10,0:12:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.21,0:12:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做的复活丸应该要受到世人更多的赞叹才是！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.22,0:12:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊是啊 复活丸..
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.54,0:12:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.01,0:12:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爷..爷爷！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.53,0:12:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才说了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.49,0:12:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？阿贞吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.27,0:12:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对啦 那后面那后面
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.98,0:12:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.13,0:13:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复活丸是..难不成是在说那种药吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.18,0:13:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是爷爷做的？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.95,0:13:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有说过这种话吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.31,0:13:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说过啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.58,0:13:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道 那种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.85,0:13:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去洗个澡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.06,0:13:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等..等下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.40,0:13:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 还没打扫完吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.92,0:13:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是没做两下就想开溜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.30,0:13:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不像话 哥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.78,0:13:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵~
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.62,0:13:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴~布巴~布~
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.14,0:13:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂喂 如果那服药真的是爷爷做的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.26,0:13:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不..我那爷爷绝对干得出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.87,0:13:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.02,0:13:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于复活后肉体的维持方法..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.36,0:13:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他应该知道点什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.94,0:13:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.91,0:13:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦！你冷不防地出什么声啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.80,0:14:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥的房间还是没在打扫吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.02,0:14:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待会我要顺便打扫一下哥的房间哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.25,0:14:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 麻烦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.27,0:14:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 萌路 等一下..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.39,0:14:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.26,0:14:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的房间啊 今天不用你打扫了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.56,0:14:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敢问您何出此言？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.70,0:14:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃..哎呀..那啥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.88,0:14:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近我忽然开始喜欢打扫了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.31,0:14:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的啦 所以打扫什么的不要紧的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.16,0:14:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 不骗你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.46,0:14:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.01,0:14:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真难琢磨啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.58,0:14:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.55,0:14:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.48,0:14:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？小狗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.74,0:14:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是兰子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.76,0:14:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 小狗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.95,0:14:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这阵子天天来报到..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.33,0:14:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送外卖顺便绕过来看看啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.95,0:15:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 萌路酱 这个拿去当做午餐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.91,0:15:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不胜感激 兰子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.99,0:15:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 每次都帮大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.48,0:15:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然没错啊..你看这家伙只会想着自己
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.27,0:15:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是该找个兰子这样的老婆..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.01,0:15:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像姐姐一样照顾着他才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.20,0:15:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么老婆呀..叔叔您真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.43,0:15:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊对了对了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.60,0:15:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘你知道吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.61,0:15:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.04,0:15:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散华家的大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.00,0:15:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎从昨天开始就离家出走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.27,0:15:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没事..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.32,0:15:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而呢 散华家是我们家的老主顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.86,0:15:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我去送外卖的时候闹得很厉害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.66,0:15:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的大小姐原来也会有烦恼呢..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.81,0:15:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦..哦...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.32,0:15:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定是..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.69,0:15:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和生死两别的恋人再次重逢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.94,0:16:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坠入一场禁断之恋..于是就私奔了呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.56,0:16:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生死两别是..不是死了吗..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.12,0:16:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后两人在面海的小民宿中共度良宵..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.05,0:16:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命中注定不能结合的两人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.54,0:16:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是对此浑然不觉的他们..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.46,0:16:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身心都渴望着与对方结合在一起..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.46,0:16:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说 千紘果然也喜欢那种类型的女生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.56,0:16:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.78,0:16:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？可是你那奇怪的朋友不是也说了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.86,0:16:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说千紘和那个叫礼弥的女生很熟..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.03,0:16:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦..所以说那是..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.22,0:16:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是晚上出门的时候在路上偶遇
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.40,0:16:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后稍微聊了点有的没的而已..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.75,0:16:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.95,0:16:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 为什么我必须跟你报告啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.72,0:16:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.45,0:17:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为姐姐果然还是该掌握一下弟弟的交友状况呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.12,0:17:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说不是那样的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.88,0:17:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.71,0:17:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我家里还有事要忙先回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.34,0:17:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.04,0:17:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么嘛 那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.70,0:17:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底想说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.30,0:17:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.47,0:17:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不快点去擦后面的地板
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.34,0:17:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.50,0:17:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊对了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.85,0:17:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来都来了 借一碟僵尸DVD再走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.99,0:17:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥的家里 现在乱成一团了吗..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.56,0:17:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.48,0:17:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个爸爸好像很吓人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.25,0:17:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在这幅样子也不能还给人家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.72,0:17:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.58,0:17:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.42,0:17:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.82,0:17:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个季节就开冷气了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.54,0:17:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我瞧瞧..哪个还没有借过？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.94,0:18:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僵尸电影的名字每一部都好像啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.71,0:18:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.21,0:18:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃..这个封面和碟子对不上嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.12,0:18:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴~布
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.02,0:18:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选 哪 个 好 呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.74,0:18:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老 天 爷 说 了 算
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.70,0:18:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 这个前阵子才刚看过
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.90,0:18:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.95,0:18:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长长的..黑发？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.93,0:18:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个怎么想都不是千紘的呢..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.82,0:18:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.37,0:18:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的错觉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.99,0:19:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 刚才礼弥看起来好像肚子饿了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.59,0:19:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子里都一塌糊涂了还想吃什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.04,0:19:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僵尸..也就是说...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.01,0:19:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.59,0:19:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等..你是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.66,0:19:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.10,0:19:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事..这个力道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.71,0:19:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等..！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.00,0:19:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.43,0:19:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散华家的..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.82,0:19:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.82,0:19:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌..等..等下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.92,0:19:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.91,0:19:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.29,0:20:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.58,0:20:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你..伤得很重啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.53,0:20:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么还笑得出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.75,0:20:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 救护车..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.99,0:20:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像..有点奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.86,0:20:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难..难不成 这孩子..！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.22,0:20:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狗！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.58,0:20:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.76,0:20:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的声音是从家里传出来的 也就是说..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.65,0:20:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成是..！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.80,0:20:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狗！你没事..吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.94,0:21:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.06,0:21:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬直已经解除了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.78,0:21:01.33,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.76,0:21:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千..千紘
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.20,0:21:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狗..你..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.81,0:21:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.38,0:21:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.64,0:21:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.19,0:21:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欸？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.06,0:21:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.45,0:22:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.07,0:23:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要加料？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.67,0:23:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.73,0:23:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得千篇一律不好的话换个表达方式就好了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.19,0:23:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.66,0:23:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个内容就可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.32,0:23:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回 散华礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.90,0:24:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第六话 “因为...与你相遇了”
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.98,0:24:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs48}知不知道萌路的名字是出自于哪一位著名僵尸电影导演呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.46,0:24:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正确答案是..大家都要看哦罗梅罗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.46,0:24:09.16,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗梅罗：乔治·A·罗梅罗，美国电影导演，僵尸电影的一代宗师。
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
