[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-11-01 10:32:21
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:恶魔岛字幕
Original Script:恶魔岛字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,20,20,12,1
Style: Warring,微软雅黑,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H282D2D2D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Zhushi,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,12,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H28000000,&HF0C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title2,方正准圆_GBK,60,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default3,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ED_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: ED_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.92,0:03:13.92,Warring,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,300)}翻译 TL旧民  后期 aoi  恶魔岛字幕组制作 仅供交流试看之用 \N相关资源与火爆讨论专区请访问恶魔岛动漫世界：http://bbs.emland.net
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.78,0:01:40.78,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眠れない夜に　聞いた物語が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.16,0:01:45.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絵空事だとしたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.41,0:02:02.30,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永遠を知るより　快楽を求めて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.65,0:02:06.12,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今を悔やんでしまうのは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.85,0:02:12.82,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心の深くに　住み着いた影から
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.07,0:02:16.67,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃げるためだとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.37,0:02:22.41,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでも　あたしはあたしを
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.55,0:02:26.02,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛していられるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.23,0:02:29.88,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半分に割れた太陽が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.14,0:02:32.22,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝を連れてきて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.41,0:02:37.37,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闇に慣れた神経を　じわり刺激する
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.73,0:02:42.56,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,置き忘れたの愛は　あえてそのままで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.04,0:02:47.43,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シナリオの消えた物語は
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.53,0:02:52.70,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由に　自由に　舵をとって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.04,0:02:59.20,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　高くへ　舞い上がって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.78,0:01:40.78,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在无法入眠的夜晚 听到的那个故事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.16,0:01:45.54,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是天马行空的妄想的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.41,0:02:02.30,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与其探求永远的奥秘 不如把握当下的欢乐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.65,0:02:06.12,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让此时此刻成为一生的悔恨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.85,0:02:12.82,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是为了逃避盘踞在内心深处的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.07,0:02:16.67,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那片黑影的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.37,0:02:22.41,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此 我还能发自内心地
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.55,0:02:26.02,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱着自己的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.23,0:02:29.88,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分成两半的太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.14,0:02:32.22,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带来了明媚清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.41,0:02:37.37,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微微刺激着已经习惯黑暗的神经
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.73,0:02:42.56,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把忘了带走的爱原封不动地摆在那
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.04,0:02:47.43,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缺了剧本的故事就会..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.53,0:02:52.70,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由地 自由地  操起船舵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.04,0:02:59.20,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起飞向更高的地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.58,0:22:28.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ　叶うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.56,0:22:40.62,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君の手の中 揺れる小さな花でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.44,0:22:47.17,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はじめてみる眩しいこの世界で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.65,0:22:52.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君ともしはぐれたとしても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.59,0:22:55.01,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと　
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.10,0:23:05.71,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見つけだして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.62,0:23:23.70,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目覚めたら　そばにいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.40,0:23:31.57,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.58,0:22:28.59,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果只能实现一个愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.56,0:22:40.62,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想成为在你手中随风摇曳的小花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.44,0:22:47.17,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个陌生 而又炫目的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.65,0:22:52.59,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕和你走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.59,0:22:55.01,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.10,0:23:05.71,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.62,0:23:23.70,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒来的时候 就在你身边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.40,0:23:31.57,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.00,0:03:12.74,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(935,580)}{\fad(250,150)}#4 「普通的...女孩子...」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.30,0:24:09.67,title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(660,500)}#5 「僵尸...也就是说...」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.00,0:00:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎大人！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.09,0:00:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.41,0:00:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.04,0:00:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎大人！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.96,0:00:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 你为我活下来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.52,0:00:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是..你怎么浑身是血？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.22,0:00:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 一起去医院吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.08,0:00:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问..有什么问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.20,0:00:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有脉搏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.42,0:00:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这简直就像..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.94,0:00:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我死了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.87,0:00:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我也获得了重生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.90,0:00:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.01,0:01:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 不要走
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.02,0:01:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.01,0:01:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不..我已经不是你的女儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.95,0:01:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问我为什么的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.34,0:01:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我已经不是人了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.44,0:01:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么..变成了这样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.31,0:03:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 你听说了么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.99,0:03:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.91,0:03:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近礼弥大人的私自外出
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.75,0:03:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是跟男人有关哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.79,0:03:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真火星..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.79,0:03:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要地球上的第一手资料？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.24,0:03:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.32,0:03:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥大人 据说离家出走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.89,0:03:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 真的假的..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.33,0:03:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话..该怎么讲？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.48,0:03:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚..亚里亚大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.82,0:03:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎您回家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.60,0:03:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.89,0:03:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥离家出走是怎么一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.17,0:03:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..先您一步到家的团一郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.06,0:03:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说“礼弥已经离开了” 所以..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.97,0:03:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他人呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.11,0:03:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎大人他自从归家之后就一直没有离开过浴室..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.52,0:03:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浴室？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.39,0:03:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.76,0:03:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也不要楞在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.47,0:03:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事也去整理一下庭院吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.06,0:03:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大白天的就一身酒气
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.38,0:04:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为最近的牛郎俱乐部..开业到白天嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.93,0:04:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牛郎俱乐部？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.33,0:04:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想啊 团一郎大人完全都不理她..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.44,0:04:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定憋了不少吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.47,0:04:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.08,0:04:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥离家出走是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.79,0:04:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明死了..却又站了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.75,0:04:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.52,0:04:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她站起来..离开了我的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.31,0:04:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.01,0:04:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之让孩子离家出走的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.46,0:04:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为学院理事长的我的立场就全完了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.13,0:04:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么..礼弥人在哪里你知道吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.99,0:04:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕..跟一个名为降谷的紫阳高中男学生在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.32,0:04:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷？这家伙是谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.06,0:04:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降..谷
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.10,0:05:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 是那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.17,0:05:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个男人骗走了礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.97,0:05:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人是诸恶的根源！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.71,0:05:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.84,0:05:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着吧 礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.80,0:05:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把你从他手中解放出来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.99,0:05:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一次用我的爱..来净化你的全部吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.71,0:05:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在私立散华女子学院
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.82,0:05:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个特殊的科目叫做瞑针
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.38,0:05:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是一项全校学生在第一节课之前的10分钟内..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.60,0:05:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不断用针线缝制碎布的科目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.15,0:05:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目的除了让她们锻炼裁缝技术之外..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.80,0:05:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更重要的是用这种冥想方式来锻炼学生们的精神
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.52,0:05:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而那也是她们每天清晨的必修科目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.68,0:05:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我在入学之前还很小的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.55,0:05:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天早上都一定会习惯性地练一练暝针
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.92,0:06:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 原来如此啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.06,0:06:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才能这么熟练地缝自己的伤口啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.86,0:06:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,..啊个屁哇！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.06,0:06:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 请你好好按着嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.93,0:06:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就差一点了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.29,0:06:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉不到疼痛真是好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.49,0:06:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你知不知道自己已经死了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.47,0:06:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮肤冷冰冰的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.94,0:06:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有脉搏而且瞳孔放大了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.56,0:06:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你还笑得出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.59,0:06:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为..因为我第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.39,0:06:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次进到男生的房间里 所以..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.07,0:07:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得好高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.89,0:07:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.11,0:07:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束了结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.05,0:07:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子学姐~
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.53,0:07:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.21,0:07:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去的时候要不要去吃个甜点？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.23,0:07:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现了一家好时髦的露天咖啡馆呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.72,0:07:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 今天我要直接去一个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.52,0:07:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦啦 是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.77,0:07:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘那家伙..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.80,0:07:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算一心想去追巴布..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.65,0:07:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可居然把本小姐晾在那个窄得要命的洞里..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.16,0:07:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.55,0:07:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要好好收收他的骨头！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.16,0:07:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？您要收什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.33,0:07:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊..没有啦~没事没事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.52,0:07:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雨歇时分的黄昏也不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.06,0:08:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙难不成今天..
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.18,0:08:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 从今往后打算一直赖在我家？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.01,0:08:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 降谷同学
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.93,0:08:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看得见吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.21,0:08:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀 我没看到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.91,0:08:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看啊 那边的树上
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.78,0:08:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布酱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.55,0:08:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.24,0:08:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.09,0:08:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.60,0:08:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 让我担心死了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.92,0:08:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 巴布
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.64,0:08:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.88,0:08:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑眼珠显出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.45,0:08:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴~布
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.95,0:08:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布酱好像有点鼻塞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.91,0:08:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.09,0:08:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 头一回遇上它就是那样了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.34,0:08:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也带它去看过动物医院
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.97,0:08:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可就是治不好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.14,0:08:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫声一直就是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.87,0:08:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以叫巴布
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.12,0:08:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.35,0:08:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 瞧它悠哉悠哉的 一点不知道我花了多大心思
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.69,0:08:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴~布
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.15,0:08:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它说这颗树最舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.81,0:09:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？你知道巴布讲什么吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.09,0:09:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总感觉它好像是这么说的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.90,0:09:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.60,0:09:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成僵尸之间可以沟通？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.33,0:09:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.38,0:09:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成了僵尸以后也没有什么性情大变的情况呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.51,0:09:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.20,0:09:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.60,0:09:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不啦..没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.94,0:09:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 难不成..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.52,0:09:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得我的行为举止应该更像僵尸一点？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.64,0:09:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像这样..降谷同学喜欢的那类？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.12,0:09:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说 现在这样就已经够萌了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.62,0:09:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.78,0:09:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于自己变成僵尸还真是一点不安都没有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.69,0:10:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 因为降谷同学会负责的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.01,0:10:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.84,0:10:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的“负责”具体上来说是想让我怎么做？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.00,0:10:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般来说 负起责任的话就是..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.78,0:10:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..说的也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.16,0:10:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起出去买东西..去逛美术馆之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.51,0:10:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.59,0:10:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 还要一起去看僵尸电影哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.26,0:10:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..其他的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.65,0:10:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了对了 游乐场
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.49,0:10:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天去庙会也不错呢..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.24,0:10:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.19,0:10:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这完全就是普通的..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.03,0:10:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说请让我经历一下..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.18,0:10:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为普通女孩子的所有体验
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.77,0:10:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..明明成了僵尸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.22,0:10:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却想体会普通女孩子的生活..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.14,0:10:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？有什么奇怪的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.27,0:11:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.43,0:11:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不..不是不行啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.80,0:11:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害的力道..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.81,0:11:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,..降谷同学
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.59,0:11:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我..忽然想..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.12,0:11:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！这么突然..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.10,0:11:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.51,0:11:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘！ 给我滚出来！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.27,0:11:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好 是小狗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.51,0:11:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.91,0:11:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上你还真敢把我晾在后面不管呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.01,0:11:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？你房间里现在是不是有别人？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.64,0:11:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啦 我一个人啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.68,0:11:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我要去你房间了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.13,0:11:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等下等下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.31,0:11:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要聊在外面聊就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.11,0:11:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.94,0:11:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人有男人的问题啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.82,0:11:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今搜出一两册A书我也不会吃惊啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.60,0:12:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之你在那等着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.22,0:12:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.88,0:12:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要出去一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.42,0:12:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要出房间哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.76,0:12:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.96,0:12:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要谈事到河边去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.90,0:12:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥 为什么要去河边啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.77,0:12:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我的啦 来啦来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.61,0:12:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我想对降谷君做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.54,0:12:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个..感觉是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.15,0:12:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起啊 我完全忘了你在我后面
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.89,0:12:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘记了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.68,0:12:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借口只有这个？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.09,0:12:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很火大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.30,0:12:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛好痛好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.22,0:12:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我不好我错了还不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.70,0:12:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布酱呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.04,0:12:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.55,0:12:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有去袭击别人啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.52,0:13:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 你好歹拿个手机啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.24,0:13:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种时候真的让人很伤脑筋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.70,0:13:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不需要呢 手机什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.74,0:13:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是巴布酱今后会怎样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.56,0:13:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直就这样保持不死之身？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.26,0:13:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题就在这呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.07,0:13:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 降谷！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.69,0:13:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.86,0:13:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次换康孝
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.40,0:13:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降..谷！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.51,0:13:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这混蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.82,0:13:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把礼弥炭也介绍给我吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.01,0:13:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.15,0:13:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷 你就是神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.97,0:13:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来既然认识她怎么也不告诉我一声啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.04,0:13:42.27,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啦 住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.74,0:13:43.45,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.71,0:13:45.21,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.44,0:13:50.37,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这！你这！..嫉妒羡慕恨啊 我也要 我也要妹子啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.09,0:13:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.52,0:13:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,康孝同学你太激动了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.39,0:13:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 礼弥是指散华礼弥？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.34,0:13:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对对 就是那个散华礼弥炭
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.93,0:13:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 你不是认识嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.17,0:14:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前还煞有其事地问我认不认识散华礼弥呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.51,0:14:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.01,0:14:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是认识..不如说偶然就..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.55,0:14:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.89,0:14:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么“偶然就”..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.08,0:14:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能这么若无其事的就这么和妹子就好上了涅！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.15,0:14:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.75,0:14:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是只对僵尸娘感兴趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.50,0:14:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不对不对 我是绝对铁杆的僵尸娘命啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.90,0:14:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我和她不是那样的..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.21,0:14:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.51,0:14:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.37,0:14:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那样是怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.41,0:14:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的她正是我朝思暮想的僵尸娘啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.04,0:14:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这个僵尸娘现在在我的房间？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.36,0:14:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 仔细一想这是多么让人鼻血的梦想状况啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.98,0:14:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？你笑嘻嘻的是怎样啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.54,0:14:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没..没有笑啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.07,0:14:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学..好慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.68,0:14:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人是谁呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.24,0:15:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿的是散华女子的制服
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.06,0:15:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很亲密呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.47,0:15:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是降谷同学的..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.53,0:15:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今搜出一两册A书我也不会吃惊啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.11,0:15:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 好像也没人在家
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.76,0:15:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 僵尸洗澡应该也没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.05,0:16:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这什么呀 好奇怪的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.59,0:16:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 我感觉不出是冷是热呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.52,0:16:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是感觉好新鲜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.24,0:16:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次看见这么小巧的浴室呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.01,0:16:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.88,0:16:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.45,0:16:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用在什么上面的呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.48,0:16:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点硬硬的有点弹弹的..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.24,0:16:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.12,0:16:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像这样用来做运动？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.88,0:16:44.99,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撒菱（忍者道具？）
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.37,0:16:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.25,0:16:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.08,0:16:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶~~有人在家？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.07,0:16:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？阿贞！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.70,0:16:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是阿贞吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.82,0:16:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 阿贞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.23,0:16:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 你复活了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.81,0:17:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对..我是..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.40,0:17:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿贞啊 是我错了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.92,0:17:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..你认错人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.38,0:17:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.31,0:17:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿贞
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.38,0:17:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了啊 老爷
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.47,0:17:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复活了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.39,0:17:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿贞又回到了我的身边啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.46,0:17:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道有没有复活
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.88,0:17:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是去世的奶奶的名字不叫阿贞而是阿清吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.64,0:17:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗？咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.66,0:17:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才干了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.51,0:17:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.15,0:17:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该没有被发现吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.89,0:17:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和父亲共进晚餐的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.00,0:17:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种时候 我居然在别人家里..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.92,0:18:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是男生的房间里..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.15,0:18:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真的是发生了好多事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.75,0:18:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于..自由了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.81,0:18:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今往后也要..一直..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.73,0:18:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.41,0:18:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算是忽悠过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.45,0:18:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 康孝那家伙真缠人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.19,0:18:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神真是够充沛的..就不能用在其他地方吗..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.24,0:18:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 哥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.93,0:18:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的晚餐是动物内脏锅哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.51,0:18:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.43,0:18:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像没什么食欲
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.18,0:18:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌路好像还没发现
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.16,0:19:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起..我回来晚了..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.04,0:19:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.34,0:19:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 你这样子太超过了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.34,0:19:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我借用了一下浴室
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.97,0:19:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那啥..你身子都还是湿的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.98,0:19:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会感冒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.32,0:19:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没事的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.85,0:19:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家是僵尸嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.17,0:19:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会感冒的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.58,0:19:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 对了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.24,0:19:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？喂喂等一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.34,0:19:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的对话难不成是..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.27,0:19:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止在我脑内重现无数次的和僵尸娘的萌对话嘛！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.69,0:19:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那那么..也不会闹肚子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.26,0:19:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？因为是僵尸嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.87,0:19:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子里早就是一塌糊涂的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.59,0:19:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,止不住止不住止不住！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.48,0:20:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学..？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.32,0:20:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.99,0:20:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于梦想实现得过于完美
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.57,0:20:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一时进入了忘我状态..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.87,0:20:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 你也快点换上衣服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.86,0:20:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这个嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.52,0:20:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实啊 我好像诶来诶动不了了..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.46,0:20:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体..好像变..酱硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.22,0:20:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？你说僵硬？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.84,0:20:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得口齿不清也是因为这个缘故吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.61,0:20:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊..好像素诶..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.57,0:20:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么情况 难不成药效过了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.56,0:20:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我摸一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.56,0:20:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成..这个是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.35,0:20:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死后硬直..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.29,0:20:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死后..硬..叽？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.68,0:20:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 应该是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.80,0:20:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 是自然现象
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.83,0:21:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯~~不愧是..酱谷..童鞋..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.51,0:21:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尊素清楚呢...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.16,0:21:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然礼弥自己很开朗所以一点没有察觉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.77,0:21:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然拥有意识 但是她的身体和死人的状态是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.86,0:21:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话..礼弥她..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.79,0:21:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样放任不管的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.61,0:21:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉体会渐渐..变得腐烂..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.68,0:21:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不出一个月就..白骨？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.03,0:21:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要想个办法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.38,0:21:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请让我经历一下..作为普通女孩子的所有体验
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.66,0:21:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.13,0:22:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护礼弥的身体！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.96,0:23:40.88,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准随便进来！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.71,0:23:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.74,0:23:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让我低调一点？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.02,0:23:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么意思呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.08,0:23:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？角色不对？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.17,0:23:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么不对的..
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.85,0:23:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我本人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.36,0:23:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一回 散华礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.09,0:24:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第五话 “僵尸...也就是说...”
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.54,0:24:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都要看哦萌路~
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.92,0:24:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都已经接受了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.14,0:24:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们反而说出这种泼冷水的话我也很困扰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
