[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-12-09 13:15:38
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:恶魔岛字幕
Original Script:恶魔岛字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,20,20,12,1
Style: Warring,微软雅黑,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H282D2D2D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Zhushi,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,12,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H28000000,&HF0C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title2,方正准圆_GBK,60,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default3,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ED_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: ED_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.96,0:03:22.96,Warring,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,300)}翻译 TL旧民  后期 aoi  恶魔岛字幕组制作 仅供交流试看之用 \N请勿添加广告 相关资源和讨论请访问恶魔岛动漫世界：http://bbs.emland.net
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.82,0:01:49.82,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眠れない夜に　聞いた物語が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.20,0:01:54.58,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絵空事だとしたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.45,0:02:11.34,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永遠を知るより　快楽を求めて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.69,0:02:15.16,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今を悔やんでしまうのは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.89,0:02:21.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心の深くに　住み着いた影から
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.11,0:02:25.71,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃げるためだとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.41,0:02:31.45,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでも　あたしはあたしを
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.59,0:02:35.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛していられるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.27,0:02:38.92,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半分に割れた太陽が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.18,0:02:41.26,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝を連れてきて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.45,0:02:46.41,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闇に慣れた神経を　じわり刺激する
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.77,0:02:51.60,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,置き忘れたの愛は　あえてそのままで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.08,0:02:56.47,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シナリオの消えた物語は
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.57,0:03:01.74,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由に　自由に　舵をとって
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.08,0:03:08.24,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　高くへ　舞い上がって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.82,0:01:49.82,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在无法入眠的夜晚 听到的那个故事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.20,0:01:54.58,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是天马行空的妄想的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.45,0:02:11.34,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与其探求永远的奥秘 不如把握当下的欢乐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.69,0:02:15.16,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让此时此刻成为一生的悔恨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.89,0:02:21.86,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是为了逃避盘踞在内心深处的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.11,0:02:25.71,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那片黑影的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.41,0:02:31.45,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此 我还能发自内心地
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.59,0:02:35.06,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱着自己的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.27,0:02:38.92,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分成两半的太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.18,0:02:41.26,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带来了明媚清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.45,0:02:46.41,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微微刺激着已经习惯黑暗的神经
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.77,0:02:51.60,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把忘了带走的爱原封不动地摆在那
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.08,0:02:56.47,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缺了剧本的故事就会..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.57,0:03:01.74,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由地 自由地  操起船舵
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.08,0:03:08.24,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起飞向更高的地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.49,0:22:28.50,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ　叶うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.47,0:22:40.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君の手の中 揺れる小さな花でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.35,0:22:47.08,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はじめてみる眩しいこの世界で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.56,0:22:52.50,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君ともしはぐれたとしても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.50,0:22:54.92,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと　
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.01,0:23:05.62,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見つけだして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.53,0:23:23.61,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目覚めたら　そばにいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.31,0:23:31.48,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.49,0:22:28.50,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果只能实现一个愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.47,0:22:40.53,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想成为在你手中随风摇曳的小花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.35,0:22:47.08,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个陌生 而又炫目的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.56,0:22:52.50,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕和你走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.50,0:22:54.92,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.01,0:23:05.62,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.53,0:23:23.61,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒来的时候 就在你身边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.31,0:23:31.48,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.56,0:03:47.48,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(372,600)}{\fad(250,150)}#11 「才不是...特别的...呢」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.15,0:24:09.62,title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(660,490)}#12 「那个瞬间...我...」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.00,0:00:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 这是要去哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.17,0:00:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会想就这样把我丢进滚油里烫..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.77,0:00:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不..还是准备把我推下悬崖？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.58,0:00:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问..女仆小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.77,0:00:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以借个厕所吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.59,0:00:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要趁这个机会开溜！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.54,0:00:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 您要方便啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.21,0:00:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之后会打扫的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.59,0:00:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以请你随便尿出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.74,0:00:48.71,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无限之间
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.11,0:00:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么的 我又不是为了严刑拷问而带你来这
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.14,0:00:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.94,0:01:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道场？！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.93,0:01:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武具这里一应俱全
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.34,0:01:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武具?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.43,0:01:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挑个你称手的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.86,0:01:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然赤手空拳也可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.38,0:01:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.67,0:01:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是要..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.80,0:01:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底谁更有资格保护礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.49,0:01:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这里分个高下如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.10,0:03:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来能拿到钱了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.80,0:03:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.40,0:03:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把父亲..请把父亲叫过来！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.65,0:03:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.46,0:03:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎大人现在有要事在忙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.27,0:03:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学也在那对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.18,0:03:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要到父亲那里去！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.67,0:03:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.23,0:03:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还请礼弥大人暂作歇息
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.51,0:03:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.76,0:04:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里亚大人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.32,0:04:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥大人好像已经被保护起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.44,0:04:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.88,0:04:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问您要见她吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.64,0:04:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.28,0:04:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我非得见那孩子不可？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.28,0:04:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？为什么要做这种事..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.66,0:04:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.68,0:04:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这是团一郎大人的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.46,0:04:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话我也要命令你们！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.38,0:04:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就把这个解开！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.11,0:04:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 礼弥大人居然摆出一副可怕的脸想来命令我们
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.68,0:04:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是离家出走了几天
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.16,0:04:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然就变了这么多..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.75,0:04:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还真是不应该呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.94,0:04:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞒着团一郎大人稍微惩罚一下应该也可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.37,0:04:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的对呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.83,0:05:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么难得的机会 也不可能有第二次..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.41,0:05:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？你们要干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.73,0:05:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不..不要..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.69,0:05:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.97,0:05:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.36,0:05:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊 这到底是要干什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.04,0:05:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直想找机会让礼弥大人穿一次看看的说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.58,0:05:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道一定很适合的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.11,0:05:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卑鄙小人！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.30,0:05:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然趁别人动弹不得
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.61,0:05:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用恶作剧来肆意玩弄
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.57,0:05:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们知不知羞啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.08,0:05:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害羞的礼弥大人也好可爱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.33,0:05:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个让她穿什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.95,0:05:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女忍装？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.56,0:05:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩偶服？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.82,0:05:48.70,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是穿这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.70,0:05:51.82,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？穿这个好看吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.02,0:05:53.29,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱~
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.81,0:05:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在..明明不是干这种事的时候啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.72,0:05:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心里完全静不下来..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.58,0:05:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.53,0:05:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.65,0:06:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.58,0:06:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经说了只要你能刺中我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.94,0:06:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是你赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.63,0:06:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得很赖皮吗..
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.58,0:06:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本不会击剑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.02,0:06:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你有什么擅长的剑术或者格斗技就随便使出来吧..
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.29,0:06:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种东西我完全一窍不通啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.82,0:06:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 真是个羸弱的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.54,0:06:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连护身术都没有学过吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.00,0:06:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么礼弥会想去这种..没才没艺的男人身边呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.95,0:06:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？你连这种事都不知道吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.17,0:06:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.43,0:06:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连这种事都不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.22,0:06:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连这种事都不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.49,0:06:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个可以有啊 可以有！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.61,0:06:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超~可爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.15,0:07:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个 快帮我解开
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.78,0:07:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说我们无法听从您的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.66,0:07:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做不到~
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.72,0:07:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一套还是换女忍装吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.95,0:07:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再下一套一定要换玩偶服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.34,0:07:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吗 到底该怎么办呢~
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.87,0:07:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？不是轮流吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.74,0:07:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办呢~
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.64,0:07:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪一件..都不穿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.04,0:07:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.50,0:07:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得不去！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.98,0:07:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 我也是这么想的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.62,0:07:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.86,0:07:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.55,0:07:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底想说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.01,0:07:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以啊 也就是说..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.62,0:07:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.26,0:07:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.31,0:07:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一对一分出高下？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.84,0:07:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.06,0:07:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不顾礼弥的想法 自个在这里用胜负决定她的归属
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.33,0:07:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是你把别人硬拐到这里 还说要分什么高下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.38,0:07:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就叫自以为是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.63,0:07:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.21,0:08:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做父亲的兴趣居然是在女儿生日那天拍她裸照？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.77,0:08:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙为什么知道这个！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.43,0:08:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般没这样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.48,0:08:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么父女爱 这也太超过了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.21,0:08:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这当然论谁都会想从这种糟糕老爹的身边溜走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.30,0:08:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是正常人的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.63,0:08:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.59,0:08:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说 玩笑先开到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.67,0:08:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与其讨论谁来保护礼弥或者谁更有才能？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.12,0:08:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这些 最重要的是礼弥想怎么做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.55,0:08:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于她自己的人生 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.99,0:08:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要她不在场我们就不能做出任何决定
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.68,0:08:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的观点从这里就已经不对劲了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.80,0:08:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你说要保护礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.25,0:08:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实只是你不想放走礼弥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.77,0:08:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从那位母亲那里听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.08,0:08:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想礼弥一定也不好受哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.17,0:09:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你一直把过世妻子的影子叠加在她身上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.92,0:09:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你就..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.24,0:09:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷啊 你似乎有点小看我了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.89,0:09:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这微不足道的存在..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.65,0:09:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要动用散华一族的力量就能轻易地抹去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.04,0:09:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说是吧 礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.81,0:09:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.73,0:09:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 插进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.28,0:09:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦 降谷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.25,0:09:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我不敢真的刺你吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.00,0:10:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这怎么可能！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.58,0:10:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对~
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.51,0:10:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报了一剑之仇了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.53,0:10:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷..同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.41,0:10:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？礼弥？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.00,0:10:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.55,0:10:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你..这身打扮..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.91,0:10:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这样的搭配啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.21,0:10:24.53,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死灵之僵尸兔女郎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.78,0:10:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,值得与僵尸护士娘一战..不对.. 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.57,0:10:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的“魔萌”程度有过之而无不及！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.29,0:10:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 这是女仆长硬让我穿的..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.16,0:10:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学 血！血！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.61,0:10:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降..谷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.37,0:10:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.14,0:10:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你会没事！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.54,0:10:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊..是为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.06,0:10:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是很明白
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.56,0:10:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为过度兴奋使肾上腺素大量分泌..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.06,0:10:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.85,0:11:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成..因为那时候被礼弥舔了伤口..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.23,0:11:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 看来我感染了礼弥的毒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.70,0:11:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毒？感染？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.79,0:11:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然痛觉麻痹了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.71,0:11:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是心脏还在跳动 也就是说..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.34,0:11:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感染到的毒还不足以致死么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.06,0:11:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么从结论上讲..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.90,0:11:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就是半僵尸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.57,0:11:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是僵尸？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.82,0:11:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.23,0:11:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我把你的头给削飞！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.39,0:12:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请..住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.73,0:12:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲大人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.31,0:12:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的那一击 应该胜负已分了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.34,0:12:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此您还想继续战斗的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.20,0:12:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次就由我来当您的对手！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.32,0:12:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么啊 礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.24,0:12:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想拯救你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.58,0:12:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你患上的那种未知之疾 我只是想治好它而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.94,0:12:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起移居美国吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.58,0:12:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远渡重洋的手续我都准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.93,0:12:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要拜托那些我从世界各地请来的名医和研究学者
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.05,0:12:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能...不 一定会找到治疗的方法才对！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.63,0:12:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人真的能救得了你吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.32,0:12:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个财力和知识都相当有限的小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.19,0:12:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底能做到什么程度？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.62,0:13:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 父亲大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.80,0:13:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实..就算不治好也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.04,0:13:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.62,0:13:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去的话 你的身体会..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.84,0:13:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果为了治好它而要远离这个城镇的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.23,0:13:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得现在这样就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.81,0:13:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便是很短暂的时光
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.53,0:13:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能和降谷同学一起生活在这个城镇
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.72,0:13:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅是这样就足够了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.36,0:13:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.08,0:13:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.46,0:13:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你..只要有眼前这小小的自由就满足了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.76,0:13:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明明是那么特别..那么高雅的一个存在..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.53,0:14:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不明白吗 父亲大人！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.46,0:14:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.80,0:14:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥真正追求的..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.60,0:14:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是什么“特别”啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.33,0:14:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止 你有实现过礼弥自己的愿望吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.45,0:14:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你强加给她的愿望！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.63,0:14:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 我在庭院里抓到了一只蜗牛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.36,0:14:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.42,0:14:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不可以碰那种肮脏的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.90,0:14:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和朋友一起出去购物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.41,0:14:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用那么费事 我来买你喜欢的东西吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.89,0:14:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说想买什么 嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.81,0:14:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥已经是高中生了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.90,0:15:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让那些低俗的怪胎靠近那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.82,0:15:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为礼弥应该接受的遗传因子只有一种..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.16,0:15:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥只是想..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.42,0:15:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为普通的女孩子而已啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.03,0:15:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是只为了这个理由..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.27,0:15:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅为了这个理由
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.02,0:15:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就选择了死亡吗..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.86,0:15:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.56,0:15:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.53,0:15:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我..对于你所说的话还是有一部分赞同的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.41,0:16:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭我一个人的力量..有些事情可能确实是无能为力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.85,0:16:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以到时我希望你也能帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.73,0:16:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我希望礼弥今后也一直待在这里..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.41,0:16:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.99,0:16:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.11,0:16:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的不后悔了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.51,0:16:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.37,0:16:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.78,0:16:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.43,0:16:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就把礼弥托付给你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.56,0:16:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.71,0:16:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲大人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.78,0:17:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过仅仅介于我在海外寻找治疗礼弥的方法的这段期间
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.28,0:17:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是一直托付给你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.60,0:17:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.71,0:17:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.22,0:17:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算这样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.60,0:17:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也没有准你夺走礼弥的贞操哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.83,0:17:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有那种事啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.44,0:17:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？他对你说了什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.41,0:17:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？啊不..没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.33,0:17:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没那回事啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.23,0:17:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 总之太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.53,0:17:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样总算..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.64,0:17:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又能和礼弥生活在..一起了..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.30,0:17:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.56,0:17:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学？！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.17,0:17:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.03,0:17:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.94,0:18:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问要喝些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.02,0:18:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.46,0:18:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.03,0:18:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛..痛痛痛！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.82,0:18:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.93,0:18:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？痛觉恢复了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.01,0:18:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊..体内的毒已经消失了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.10,0:18:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.11,0:18:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们做的应急处理
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.23,0:18:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是活过来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.03,0:18:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我可没死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.54,0:19:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.41,0:19:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为出了好多血
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.14,0:19:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你再也醒不过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.95,0:19:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 让你担心了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.74,0:19:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.64,0:19:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.52,0:19:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 你这身打扮..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.07,0:19:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？这个是..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.42,0:19:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女仆姐姐们说这么穿你一定会高兴的..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.59,0:19:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..不行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.10,0:19:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僵尸护士娘 实在太..棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.82,0:19:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥还真是容易摆平啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.98,0:19:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.80,0:19:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？小狗？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.69,0:19:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋笨蛋笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.76,0:19:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听萌路妹妹说你受了严重的伤
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.69,0:19:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就赶过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.04,0:19:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然知道我伤了你就别扑过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.02,0:19:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.85,0:19:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 到底是发生什么事才变成这样..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.40,0:19:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.80,0:19:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实..实在对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.82,0:20:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是我的..不好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.37,0:20:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？为什么是护士装？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.80,0:20:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这是因为大家说这个能让降谷同学高兴..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.85,0:20:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？你让人家小姑娘干些什么啊 变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.76,0:20:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是我让她穿的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.66,0:20:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是高兴是真的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.26,0:20:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那自然是..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.59,0:20:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你套你哥什么话啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.14,0:20:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欸......
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.23,0:20:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 降谷同学变成这样都是我的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.98,0:20:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥 不用说这些的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.56,0:20:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫散华是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.38,0:20:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是作为僵尸住在降谷家的..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.87,0:20:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.35,0:20:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我还没正式的自我介绍呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.23,0:20:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是大你们一岁的左王子兰子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.15,0:20:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.64,0:20:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是千紘的姐姐 也是他的未婚妻
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.08,0:20:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦喂！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.23,0:20:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 是“人类”的..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.87,0:20:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.04,0:21:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.11,0:21:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那个是开玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.12,0:21:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 小狗..小姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.12,0:21:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别随随便便乱讲话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.94,0:21:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欸——？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.90,0:21:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是小学的时候不是约好了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.58,0:21:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千紘！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.84,0:21:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.42,0:21:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要当我的未婚夫吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.63,0:21:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.32,0:21:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管啦 总之要你当就当
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.22,0:21:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦..那我就当吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.68,0:21:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼才记得啊 那时候的扯皮！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.24,0:21:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑啦 对不起哦 散华小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.37,0:21:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你看到了吗？刚才千紘惊慌失措的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.28,0:21:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好纯情哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.46,0:21:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 你刚才不也差点哭出来吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.72,0:21:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？我那是在演戏啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.92,0:21:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这话说得太假了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.95,0:21:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也是演戏的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.60,0:21:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是你演得太挫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.33,0:21:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 该让我好好听一下来龙去脉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.63,0:21:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手拿开我就说给你听啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.80,0:21:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个我恕难从命
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.20,0:21:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛痛痛痛！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.07,0:21:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 这个人..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.28,0:22:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢降谷同学呢..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.70,0:23:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 萌路妹妹换掉了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.49,0:23:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么办法
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.90,0:23:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙也还只是个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.90,0:23:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.89,0:23:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.11,0:23:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回 散华礼弥 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.51,0:23:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十二话 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.73,0:23:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「那个瞬间...我...」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.92,0:24:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 都要看哦萌路！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.74,0:24:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌路！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.65,0:24:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌路妹妹！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.25,0:24:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会再逃了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
