[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-11-03 16:28:41
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:恶魔岛字幕
Original Script:恶魔岛字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,20,20,12,1
Style: Warring,微软雅黑,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H282D2D2D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Zhushi,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H14FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140D0D0D,&H3C1C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,12,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H28000000,&HF0C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title2,方正准圆_GBK,60,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default3,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ED_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: ED_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC8C0C0C0,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_jp,Arphic Roman-Mincho Ultra JIS,42,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: OP_cn,方正大标宋_GBK,48,&H124080FF,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&HC8C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.76,0:01:56.76,Warring,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,300)}翻译 TL旧民  后期 aoi  恶魔岛字幕组制作 仅供交流试看之用 \N请勿添加广告 相关资源和讨论请访问恶魔岛动漫世界：http://bbs.emland.net
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.62,0:00:23.62,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眠れない夜に　聞いた物語が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.00,0:00:28.38,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絵空事だとしたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.25,0:00:45.14,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永遠を知るより　快楽を求めて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.49,0:00:48.96,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今を悔やんでしまうのは
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.69,0:00:55.66,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心の深くに　住み着いた影から
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.91,0:00:59.51,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃げるためだとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.21,0:01:05.25,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでも　あたしはあたしを
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.39,0:01:08.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛していられるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.07,0:01:12.72,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半分に割れた太陽が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.98,0:01:15.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝を連れてきて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.25,0:01:20.21,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闇に慣れた神経を　じわり刺激する
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.57,0:01:25.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,置き忘れたの愛は　あえてそのままで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.88,0:01:30.27,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シナリオの消えた物語は
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.37,0:01:35.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由に　自由に　舵をとって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.88,0:01:42.04,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　高くへ　舞い上がって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.62,0:00:23.62,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在无法入眠的夜晚 听到的那个故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.00,0:00:28.38,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是天马行空的妄想的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.25,0:00:45.14,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与其探求永远的奥秘 不如把握当下的欢乐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.49,0:00:48.96,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让此时此刻成为一生的悔恨
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.69,0:00:55.66,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是为了逃避盘踞在内心深处的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.91,0:00:59.51,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那片黑影的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.21,0:01:05.25,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此 我还能发自内心地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.39,0:01:08.86,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱着自己的话..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.07,0:01:12.72,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分成两半的太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.98,0:01:15.06,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带来了明媚清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.25,0:01:20.21,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微微刺激着已经习惯黑暗的神经
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.57,0:01:25.40,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把忘了带走的爱原封不动地摆在那
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.88,0:01:30.27,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缺了剧本的故事就会..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.37,0:01:35.54,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由地 自由地  操起船舵
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.88,0:01:42.04,OP_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起飞向更高的地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.40,0:22:28.41,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ　叶うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:40.44,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君の手の中 揺れる小さな花でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.26,0:22:46.99,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はじめてみる眩しいこの世界で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.47,0:22:52.41,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君ともしはぐれたとしても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.41,0:22:54.83,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと　
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.92,0:23:05.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見つけだして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.44,0:23:23.52,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目覚めたら　そばにいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.22,0:23:31.39,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.40,0:22:28.41,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果只能实现一个愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:40.44,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想成为在你手中随风摇曳的小花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.26,0:22:46.99,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个陌生 而又炫目的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.47,0:22:52.41,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕和你走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.41,0:22:54.83,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.92,0:23:05.53,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.44,0:23:23.52,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒来的时候 就在你身边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.22,0:23:31.39,ED_cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.88,0:01:53.21,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(332,600)}{\fad(250,150)}#10 「强烈的...感情...」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.82,0:24:09.77,title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(660,490)}#11 「才不是...特别的...呢」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.30,0:00:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.60,0:00:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就趁这个机会..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.30,0:00:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来分个高下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.63,0:00:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 降谷啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.83,0:01:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布~
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.14,0:01:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绿色的墙壁能让人放松呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.71,0:01:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷少爷
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.75,0:01:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎您的大驾光临
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.30,0:02:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先送上接风小饮一杯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.67,0:02:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正好口渴了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.63,0:02:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种对话放在现在有点奇怪吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.07,0:02:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么请慢用
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.10,0:02:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.39,0:02:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我松绑啊 喂！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.86,0:02:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等一下..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.66,0:02:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.71,0:02:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 别开玩笑啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.33,0:02:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是完完全全的诱拐犯罪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.67,0:02:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是绑架啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.39,0:02:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有在听吗 给我解开啊混蛋..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.15,0:02:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚皮发痒了怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.14,0:02:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 痒起来了痒起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.78,0:02:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痒好痒好..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.74,0:02:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 终于回来了吗..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.14,0:02:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.01,0:02:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音都传到走廊外面了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.95,0:02:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？你是谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.74,0:02:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑到人家家里 这口气还真没礼貌呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.85,0:03:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又不是自己想来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.54,0:03:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.61,0:03:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是散华团一郎的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.39,0:03:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散华亚里亚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.22,0:03:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那..你是礼弥的..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.71,0:03:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是..降谷千紘？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.43,0:03:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥承蒙你照顾了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.27,0:03:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.15,0:03:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没你说的那么夸张啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.76,0:03:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你和那孩子进展到哪一步了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.78,0:03:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.78,0:03:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还停留在接吻阶段？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.27,0:03:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的..那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.23,0:03:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前被压抑了这么久
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.61,0:03:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想必现在一定没节操地整天发情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.68,0:03:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.49,0:03:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥才没有这样..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.96,0:03:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？那么你和那孩子一次都还没..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.18,0:03:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 说的也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.32,0:03:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟对方是个怪物呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.01,0:03:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吧 僵尸这玩意..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.81,0:04:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体会不断腐烂发出恶臭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.20,0:04:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮肤也会越变越脏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.20,0:04:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然忍心把自己的亲生女儿说成这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.88,0:04:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲生？我生的？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.52,0:04:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我从来没出产过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.99,0:04:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.88,0:04:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你是..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.05,0:04:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是团一郎的第二任妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.48,0:04:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 那孩子是他和前妻生的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.04,0:04:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我完全没有血缘关系
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.51,0:04:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥可没有说过这种事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.87,0:04:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那当然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.71,0:04:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事是散华家最大的禁忌
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.05,0:04:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道的只有很少的一部分人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.21,0:04:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就顺便跟你说了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.28,0:04:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原来只是这个散华家的女仆
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.68,0:04:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.69,0:05:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你不要以为是我出身下贱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.87,0:05:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥出生之前
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.76,0:05:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个宅子里服务的女仆们全都是..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.86,0:05:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了将来要继承家业的散华家之子而准备的新娘候补
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.96,0:05:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家世 教育 乃至个人素养
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.18,0:05:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过了各种科目的人才有资格在这个宅子里服务
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.55,0:05:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里好像不会挂上那孩子的照片呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.22,0:05:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以今后就挂上我的照片吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.47,0:05:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从团一郎还小的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.74,0:05:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多女仆们为了嫁入散华家就千方百计要讨他的欢心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.52,0:05:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是团一郎从未倾心于任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.67,0:06:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我作为女仆来到这个宅子 是在团一郎读研究生的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.81,0:06:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易成为了散华家的女仆 可是真遗憾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.97,0:06:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下任当家对女人没有兴趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.51,0:06:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也要在这里赔上自己的青春呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.59,0:06:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是对女人没有兴趣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.63,0:06:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是对你们没有兴趣而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.79,0:06:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时的我自信满满
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.10,0:06:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为长这么大还没碰到过我不能攻陷的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.05,0:06:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请进吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.28,0:07:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道我要加咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.17,0:07:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想您差不多也该喝完了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.67,0:07:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我也帮您拿来了盖膝毯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.00,0:07:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字是？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.87,0:07:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小女名叫亚里亚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.00,0:07:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开始越来越频繁地被团一郎叫到身边
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.87,0:08:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果团一郎也没有倾心于我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.48,0:08:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎大人 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.80,0:08:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.45,0:08:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也渐渐地开始认为团一郎对女人没有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.35,0:08:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是情况一下子改变了..
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.97,0:08:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这天 作为公益事业的一环
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.51,0:08:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有残疾的人和福利院的人们被邀请到散华家
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.51,0:08:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里举办了一场击剑大赛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.53,0:08:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而选手阵容中当然也少不了团一郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.72,0:09:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎大人赢了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.76,0:09:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎大人太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.29,0:09:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好的一场比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.24,0:09:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不拿出全力来比！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.60,0:09:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我会输吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.64,0:09:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散华家给国际击剑协会捐了非常多的钱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.80,0:09:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是最大的赞助商
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.45,0:09:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每年举办的这场大赛 团一郎的胜出已是不成文的规矩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.28,0:09:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎是个不懂察言观色的人 所以好像不喜欢这种惯例
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.29,0:09:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这场大会即将结束 大家欢送来访者离去的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.85,0:09:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女孩向团一郎搭话了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.66,0:09:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.88,0:09:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.66,0:09:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.12,0:10:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊..啊..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.49,0:10:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你好像对比赛有所不满
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.80,0:10:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果不爱惜东西的话 会被神训斥的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.94,0:10:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕今天的比赛并不真实
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.42,0:10:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你积累到现在的练习以及努力如果是真的的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.25,0:10:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就更不用说了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.02,0:10:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数天之后
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.98,0:10:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎就对那位年仅15岁的女孩求婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.20,0:10:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散华家有史以来最大的稀罕事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.11,0:10:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把门当户对的我们丢在一边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.41,0:10:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然选择了一个来历不明的病弱少女作为妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.22,0:11:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是礼弥真正的母亲..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.91,0:11:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的婚事 当然受到了散华一族上下的强烈反对
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.65,0:11:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是团一郎大人没有屈服于任何人的反对
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.38,0:11:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说家世是问题？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.61,0:11:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那当然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.97,0:11:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种来历不明的丫头..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.45,0:11:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就放弃家督之位
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.33,0:11:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话结婚就没有任何障碍了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.44,0:11:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.30,0:11:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊 团一郎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.43,0:11:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么糊涂话！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.08,0:11:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的意思是要为了那种丫头舍弃散华家吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.33,0:11:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种丫头..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.76,0:11:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请注意你的言辞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.03,0:11:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是将要成为我的妻子的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.87,0:11:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我舍弃散华家 和你们形同陌路之前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.84,0:11:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更是要让你们搞搞清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.10,0:11:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妻子如是被人指指点点 本人将感到极为愤慨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.59,0:11:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把所有亲戚说得哑口无言的团一郎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.33,0:12:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那个女人结婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.17,0:12:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是生下礼弥之后
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.60,0:12:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女人马上就死了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.98,0:12:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时的团一郎大人失魂落魄的样子让人惨不忍睹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.12,0:12:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至让人觉得他说不定会就这样随她而去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.07,0:12:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而在这个情况下 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.06,0:12:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的悉心照料才让他一点点振作了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.33,0:13:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是 我得到了团一郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.63,0:13:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是结婚之后 哪怕过了一年两年
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.90,0:13:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎也从来没有把我当成妻子来对待
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.36,0:13:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是..什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.75,0:13:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真迟钝呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.77,0:13:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有过肌肤之亲的意思啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.36,0:13:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎他..只是认为那个孩子需要母亲而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.53,0:13:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且事实上连母亲都不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.52,0:13:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为根本没有我插手的余地呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.16,0:14:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是永远在远处望着他们两人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.24,0:14:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从没感受到一丝作为家人的羁绊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.01,0:14:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.31,0:14:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不想偶尔出去旅行一下？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.44,0:14:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.86,0:14:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细想想 我们连新婚之旅都没有去过呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.92,0:14:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.35,0:14:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥说不定是时候体验一下外面的世界了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.15,0:14:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要带礼弥去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.01,0:14:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.84,0:14:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.34,0:14:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仍相信团一郎选我做妻子 是因为其中还包含着爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.43,0:15:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.11,0:15:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和爸爸一起拍照吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.45,0:15:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.44,0:15:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仍相信团一郎对那孩子的爱 是出于父女之爱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.32,0:15:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.83,0:15:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我跟你来到底是有什么事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.89,0:15:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.70,0:15:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让亚里亚大人放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.47,0:16:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让您放弃在团一郎大人身上寻求爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.03,0:16:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.98,0:16:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦您务必不要发出太大的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.73,0:16:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.43,0:16:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姿势是这样哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.20,0:16:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把脚这样抬起来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.26,0:16:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.35,0:16:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您这样就肯放弃了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.80,0:17:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果团一郎大人对那孩子的溺爱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.79,0:17:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是因为他在她身上追逐着那个女人的影子啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.14,0:17:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然说那孩子是我的女儿？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.82,0:17:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说这种令人恶心的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.44,0:17:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥被逼入绝境看来不仅仅是那个老爹的缘故呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.52,0:17:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.59,0:17:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 降谷
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.01,0:17:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得我是个很可悲的女人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.86,0:17:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能用你的身体安慰我一下？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.38,0:17:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 是僵尸身上无法体验到的炙热胴体吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.72,0:18:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.77,0:18:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只对僵尸娘感兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.83,0:18:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都只关注那个孩子..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.87,0:18:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么没有人肯看我一眼啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.24,0:18:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴~布~
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.05,0:18:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴~
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.10,0:18:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布~
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.23,0:18:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小猫猫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.46,0:18:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要来安慰我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.40,0:18:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于如此可悲的我..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.05,0:18:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么惹人疼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.38,0:18:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好温柔的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.34,0:18:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是那只也是僵尸哦？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.92,0:18:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.32,0:18:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.51,0:18:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来人啊 快把这两只无礼的生物撵出去！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.60,0:18:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那啥..如果能出去的话我倒是很乐意..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.76,0:19:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.38,0:19:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎大人有找
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.32,0:19:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.52,0:19:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊 刚才也说了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.79,0:19:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是完完全全的绑架行为啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.57,0:19:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们那位团一郎大人 管他是不是什么散华家当主
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.39,0:19:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他也没权利对我这么做哦？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.65,0:19:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说呢..能不能至少把这个解开再说？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.48,0:19:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.94,0:19:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.60,0:19:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.86,0:19:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真羡慕你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.57,0:19:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能被那个人视为眼中钉..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.98,0:19:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我这样..还从来都没有被他当回事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.96,0:19:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.73,0:20:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请..请问
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.21,0:20:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷气能不能再开强一点呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.76,0:20:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嘞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.85,0:20:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天有这么热吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.94,0:20:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.28,0:20:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那些人一定是爸爸派来的手下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.88,0:20:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷同学有危险了！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.67,0:20:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.65,0:20:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能请你开快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.90,0:20:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嘞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.43,0:20:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子有带钱吗..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.85,0:20:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请在这里等候片刻
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.56,0:20:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.74,0:20:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的团一郎大人不是找我有事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.52,0:20:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以请你等待片刻
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.94,0:20:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.73,0:21:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都是我拍的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.59,0:21:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.58,0:21:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论在哪一个瞬间按下快门
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.74,0:21:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镜中的礼弥都是那么美丽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.04,0:21:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为她是用虚幻脆弱的美交织而成的纯真本身
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.47,0:21:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把礼弥的纯真守护到现在
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.64,0:21:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要感谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.65,0:21:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过这一次失去礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.69,0:21:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再一次强烈地感受到了内心中对礼弥的爱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.10,0:21:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我更想要保护她
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.96,0:21:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.80,0:21:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.98,0:22:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不可饶恕..
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.54,0:22:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷千紘！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.38,0:23:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.37,0:23:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作归工作
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.15,0:23:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以这样赌气闹别扭啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.93,0:23:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然接受了就要好好干
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.24,0:23:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.15,0:23:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.74,0:23:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回 散华礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.80,0:23:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十一话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.17,0:24:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「才不是...特别的...呢」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.81,0:24:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是没干劲的话就换人啦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.46,0:24:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快说“大家要看哦萌路”啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
