This is an exciting memory of mine where Morishima-senpai and I went to a family restaurant one day, after school.
It happened a few days before Christmas.
Amagami SS
Morishima Haruka Chapter
What's wrong, Tachibana-kun?
You seem really uneasy for some reason.
I-It's nothing.
I'm actually having tea with you in a family restaurant, Morishima-senpai...
Um... I'm really grateful!
Oh, come on!
You don't have to be grateful for that!
But this is something that would never happen to me...
Well, I guess it actually is happening...
I mean, I just can't believe it!  I'm so happy!
Geez, you're making it such a big deal!
I'm happy that I can have tea with Senpai...
But we had to come to where Kaoru works, of all places...
What'll happen if she sees this?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing!
Senpai, have you decided on what you'd like?
Yeah, I have.
You know, Tachibana-kun, are you okay with eating sweet stuff?
Yes, to a normal extent.
Then... will you share a parfait with me?
A parfait?
This one.
This one?
Yeah.
May I take your order?
Tachibana-kun, can we?
Yes, go ahead.
I'm glad it wasn't Kaoru.
BIG SIZE
For lovers
Shining
Lovers
Parfait
This one, please.
Okay, understood!
Restaurant
Totosu
It must be the one that girl's carrying.
Crap, it's Kaoru!
Tachibana-kun, do you know her?
Yes.  She's my classmate.
I see.
So students from our school actually work here.
I didn't know.
Yeah.
I see.
So it'd be bad if she sees the two of us alone together.
That's not true!
All right, I have a great idea!
Senpai, what are you doing?
Well, nobody'll know you came with me if I hide myself like this, right?
You don't have to do that...
It's fine, it's fine.
It's more fun this way!
Look, here she comes.
Here you go.
A Shining Lovers Parfait!
Shining Lovers Parfait
Y-Yo, Kaoru.
It's rare for customers to order this, so I was wondering who it was...
And it was you.
Who cares?!
That's right, that's right!
So who are you having this special parfait meant for lovers with?
You came with someone else, right?
I saw on your ticket.
W-Well...
Now who could it be?
Senpai's totally amused by this.
U...
U?
...Umehara.
I knew it!
Who cares?!
Is there a problem?!
Nope, I have nothing else to say!
Please enjoy!
Senpai, you can come out now.
So you're having a parfait with Umehara-kun.
That's because you hid yourself, Senpai.
But I was interested in what excuse you'd come up with.
I'm sorry.
Come on, let's have the Shining Lovers Parfait together.
Bye-bye!
The Shining Lovers Parfait I had with Senpai was delicious...
But I get the feeling I lost something...
Christmas will arrive soon.
I wonder if I can spend a happy
Christmas with Morishima-senpai?
Amagami SS
Tanamachi Kaoru Chapter
Kaoru said she has a shift today.
I shouldn't disturb her, so I guess I'll go straight home.
I know!
I'll go read books in the bookstore!
It's almost Christmas.
A date with Kaoru, huh?
Would you like a Christmas cake?
We're taking orders!
Huh?
Our Christmas cakes are delicious!
Kaoru?
Junichi!
W-Why are you here?!
Uh, I was thinking of going to the bookstore for a bit...
Your costume...
Can't you tell?!
It's obviously a Santa costume.
I know that...
Then what?  Is there a problem?!
N-Not really...
It's for my job, so I had no choice!
Shopping
District
Sale
Did you quit your job at the family restaurant?
Of course not.  This is just a temp job.
It pays well.
Man, how many jobs are you working?
Five.
That many?!
Are you doing okay?
I'm totally fine.
But you know...
The man who might become my
new dad said the same thing you did.
You told me that I didn't have to work.
I see.
So are you gonna stop?
I'm still thinking.
I see.
Yeah.
Wait, where do you think you're looking?!
No, I wasn't!
I was thinking your Santa hat with cat ears is really cute!
Liar, that wasn't where you were looking!
It was somewhere lower down!
Well... uh...
Perv.
So what?
You'll buy one, right?
You can have this cake for the cheapest price of 2,500 yen.
It's a loss-incurring discount!
I'm saying that price is too low for viewing my costume.
So that's your loss-incurring discount.
Are you feeling cold from wearing so little?
I know!
Junichi, pay me back with your body.
Help me finish selling these.
How much longer do you want me
to stand here in such cold weather?
F-Fine.
Would you like a Christmas cake?
We're still taking orders!
They're delicious!  Would you like one?
Would you like a Christmas cake?
Would you like one?  They're delicious!
Take care in carrying them.
Thank you for buying!
We sold them all!
Yay!
I'm beat.
Viewing your costume is pretty pricey.
Really?
That wasn't anywhere near enough to pay for it.
Hey now.
Well, whatever.
I got my fill of looking at Kaoru in a Santa suit.
Oh yeah, I should ask where she'd like to go for our Christmas date.
Oh, maybe I should talk to him about our Christmas plans.
You know-
What?
U-Um...
Can I go home now?
Oh... right.
Yeah, that's right.
I see.
Yeah.
S-See you.
Junichi.
What?
Thank you for today.
I'm looking forward to Christmas!
O-Okay!
Don't be sick on Christmas!
Gotcha!
Amagami SS
Nakata Sae Chapter
This is something trivial that happened one December night.
That day was an important anniversary for the boy.
Yet...
Nobody's home.
That's right.  That day was his birthday.
But when he returned home, neither his family
nor a birthday cake was anywhere to be found.
The boy, disappointed that he'd have to spend his birthday alone, quietly shut himself in his closet.
Leave me alone!
I've been abandoned by my family and my goddess of luck anyway.
Hello.
A girl was standing before the boy.
It appears that the goddess of luck
had not abandoned the boy just yet.
Sae-chan.
I-I'm sorry for visiting so late.
What is it?  Are you looking for Miya?
I'm sorry, she's not at home.
Ah, I'm not.
I'm looking for S-Se... no, I-Instructor...
For me?
Y-Yes.
What is it?
Um... uh...
Ha...
Happy birthday!
How'd you know it's my birthday?
Well, Miya-chan told me.
Um... here's your present.
A present?
Y-Yes.  It's nothing grand, though...
Thank you.
I'm really happy.
You must be cold.
Come in.
O-Okay.
I'm sorry there isn't much to do, since nobody else is home.
It's fine...
The boy's phrase, "nobody else is home",
resounded in the girl's head and sent her heart racing.
"Nobody's home", "Nobody's home", "Alone together"...
Boy, I believe in you.
I believe you aren't the type to commit foul play.
Can I open it?
Y-Yes.
A book?
Huh?  An album?
The girl's first birthday present to the boy turned out to be quite the curveball.
What's more, it was a risky high-inside pitch.
W-What's this?!
It was an upper-diagonal pitch that far exceeded the boy's imagination.
"W-What is this?"
"Wooh!", the boy gave a masculine roar in his heart.
T-This is... Sae-chan's...
Yes.
...swimsuit photo, right?
I'm sorry.
This is Sae-chan's qipao photo, right?
And this is Sae-chan's nurse photo, right?
And this is Sae-chan's miniskirt policewoman photo, right?
It truly is a melting pot of excitement!
And this is Sae-chan's n-n-negligee photo, right?!
The boy's thoughts had gone completely berserk.
It was now a berserk train nobody could stop.
Unstoppable.
W-Why...
Why would you give this to me?!
W-Well...
I asked Miya-chan about what you like, Senpai.
She said that you often read photobooks of women wearing swimsuits and other stuff...
S-So you...
U-Um... it's embarrassing after all to have you see them...
Well, I think you look really cute in these photos.
But... no!
No, no!
W-Wait!
Don't look!  Don't!
A-Are you okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Ah, the boy's face was buried in the girl's breasts.
That warmth was the best possible present for the boy, one that warmed both his body and soul.
Sae-chan.
Y-Yes.
Thanks for the present.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
I'm glad.
Miya took those photos?!
Yes, she said she knew all about what would please you.
Miya, you're unbelievable!
Ten more days until Christmas Eve.
Will the Goddess of the Holy Night smile upon them both?
At any rate, Boy...
Happy birthday.
I wonder if Nii-nii liked Sae-chan's present!