I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
I told you so.
Let's go there next time.
Who are you?
Sorry, Miss.
This probably isn't a very amusing place for a woman.
No bother, but I do prefer quieter places.
The Kousa Council is on the move.
We won't stand out here at Roppongi.
Our goals are being met at a satisfactory rate.
However, the Kousa Council is a large organization.
We need to move to stage two to finish them off.
We will shift gears.
Shift gears?
Yes, we shift gears.
We will clamp down on the stores, brothels, and industrial waste collectors which are their source of funds.
They aren't amateurs. If we keep this up, they'll notice what we're doing.
This is just to rattle their cage.
Our main target is something else.
What do you mean?
We shall resort to a tactic that works in every country.
Abduction. Abduction, Mr. Bando.
We target the family of Masami Kousa, the Kousa Council chief.
B-Boss!
This may sound like I'm butting in.
What we want is a fight that'll ease the pressure from the Kousa Council.
If you guys go on a simple rampage, we can cover it up later,
but please don't do anything different to mess this up.
Did you hear that, Sergeant? They don't get it at all.
Rock, translate this carefully. Ready?
Mr. Bando...
we will employ any measures necessary to secure profits.
And we are taking much of the risk.
Therefore, the decision-making lies not with you but with us.
W-wait a minute...
Oh it's you, Rumi.
I told you not to call me around this time.
Prada? I don't want any. We've got enough to sell.
You talk too much. I'm taking out two teeth later.
Then get false teeth.
I'm hanging up now.
Chaka! You bastard, what the hell are you doing?
Don't you realize what we're talking about here, you idiot?
Sorry.
That stupid bitch.
Get out of here, asshole!
Yoshida, let it go.
I apologize for making a scene.
Oh, senpai, you're still here?
Oh, Maki.
Oh, is it already this late?
What are you reading now?
This?
Martin Heidegger.
Martin Heidegger: highly influential 20th century German philosopher  who pondered about human existence
It's philosophical but very powerful. I like it.
I'll pass. I like skin-care and modern horror books.
You did say you liked Anne Rice.
What do you like for light reading?
Lets see... well....
Never mind, never mind.
What you were just thinking of probably wasn't light reading at all.
Do you think so?
I like any book that makes me feel like I'm in a sea.
Swallowing in knowledge and emotion and everything else.
Endlessly expanding...
but somehow different from reality. I think that's what I like.
I see.
I can't handle hard ones. How about King?
I can't read scary ones.
That's kind of surprising, senpai.  I would have thought you'd have liked Poe.
I don't like the ones that make you imagine the night.
So dark and lonely and painful.
I don't like the night.
I'm scared I might be sucked into the darkness.
It's not romantic at all.
Not at all.
I hear we've got big trouble.
They are waiting for you.
Target 012 confirmed.
012 confirmed.
Can't I have a little more time before you do that?
Of course I will wait, as along as it does not interfere with the operation.
So we can raise a toast to each other.
Hey, Mr. Taka.
What's with this girl?
Idiot, haven't you learned your lesson yet?
No, no, that's not what I meant.
She's that skinny translator's bodyguard. From Roanapur.
She's a woman and she can do it?
Are you serious?
Chaka, you idiot!
Cut it out! They're guests!
I know, Mr. Taka.
But don't you want to see?
Can't we go home yet?
It's time for socializing now.
What a waste of time.
Don't complain, Revy.
It's a method of keeping things moving smoothly.
If this takes care of things then it's worth it.
I don't understand. It'd be faster making them drink...
a detergent cocktail.
There she is.
So, I hear you're a gunman?
So, have you ever shot anyone?
About ten guys...
Romeo, can I tell you one thing?
Your breath stinks, fuckhead.
I can smell it over your cologne. Your insides are rotten.
Revy.
Revy, let's go.
Miss Balalaika is waiting. Come on.
Hey, Mr. Translator. Can't you tell we're talking?
Please don't cut in.
Revy, go on ahead.
Go back and get Mr. Bando...
Hey, who do you think you are?
Don't you ignore me.
When I snap, I can't control myself.
Hey, you hear me?
Yo Sis.
He's just getting his ass whipped, not very cool, huh?
Why don't you give me a try?
I bet a wuss like this can't keep you satisfied in bed.
You bastard!
Say something!
What the hell are you doing, Chaka?
What the hell are you looking for?
Take a look at when and where you are!
Wait, we were just playin' around, Mr. Yoshida.
I'm very sorry. I'll give him a talking later.
An incompetent officer and a soldier who ignores orders.
I can hardly stand it, Sergeant.
It would have been better if it were a battlefield.
They would have been killed, and we would not have to deal with them.
Sorry, Rock.
He had his hand on his gun the whole time.
He wasn't after me, he wanted you to draw.
You're starting to get better at this, Rock.
You're absolutely right.
I may need Cutlass after all.
Hey, Revy!
I don't plan on starting anything, but at some point, he'll turn his gun on us.
He is a dumbass who doesn't know his ass from his elbow.
Let's take his challenge. Just wait till then, Rock.
When that time comes, I'll kill him.
Boss.
Would you pass the miso?
Yeah.
We don't have enough power to shut the Kousa Council up.
It was a good plan, despite the Peacekeeping Council's decision,
but if we established some reason, we could take care of it later with force or money.
But those Russians....
Boss, the sweet rice vinegar.
Here you are.
Honestly, this isn't good.
Are you missing anything else, Benny?
Thanks a lot. You saved me.
I couldn't really get to the black market in Bangkok.
Oh yea, Revy wanted something too.
She says, send Sword Cutlass.
That's not a very nice thing to say.
Is a storm brewing?
I don't know yet...
but I hope not.
So do I. I'll take care of it.
Later.
No good. I guess I'll get a cab.
From the other day...
It's been a while since I've been cold.
It is in a subtropical zone.
Have you gone home yet, Mr. Okajima?
My home... well...
To be honest, I don't really want to go.
Mr. Okajima, you're like the old me.
As for me, I used to hate my home.
But that was my place to return to.
I have a family that raised me.
You have your head on straight for you age.
My friends say I act like an old lady.
That's not what I mean.
I was kidding.
I don't have anything like that.
I just feel like I'm hanging between places.
I have too many attachments to them just to throw them away,
but I don't have the resolution to go forward.
People are like dice, a certain Frenchman said that.
You throw yourself...
in the direction of your own choosing.
People are free because they can do that.
Everyone's circumstances are different,
but no matter how small the choice, at the very least, you can throw yourself.
It's not chance or fate.
It's the choice you made.
What do you think?
You're pretty harsh.
Excuse me a moment.
Yes, it's me, Yukio.
Oh, it's you Mr. Gin.
I know. You worry too much, Mr. Gin.
I'm out of the snow with Mr. Okajima.
The one we met at the festival.
Miss...
Yes, what is it?
Today...
Oh, Mr. Bando's there?
Then I better hurry home.
I understand.
I'm sorry, Mr. Okajima. Goodbye.
Ms. Yukio... um, well...
Yes?
Your last name... I still don't know it yet.
It's Washimine.
It sounds pretty solemn, right?
I'm against this.
This doesn't involve the Miss.
Imagine the Peacekeeping Council hearing about this.
Not only will they not let us rebuild our group, but they'll throw us out of the region.
Miss!
You're already home.
I apologize for not noticing.
Mr. Bando, what were you talking about just now?
Goodnight, Miss.
As soon as the old man passed away, they came onto us about not having a boss.
They said they would accept anyone of direct relation.
Idiots, they knew who it would have to be.
You mean...
Yes, a direct relation.
And you, Miss, are the only one.
They're dirty bastards.
And they'll slowly come to strangle us with it.
That you, Yoshida?
Boss! Is that you, Boss?
I got a tail behind me.
And it's not anyone local.
Boss!
They're from the capital.
When I have a chance, I'll lose them and head to a hideout.
Boss! The Russians aren't holding back!
They blew up a car in front of a police station when a man from Kousa tried to turn himself in!
Yeah.
I thought you asked them to calm down!
I know.
I'll contact you again.
Boss!
Prepare for some trouble and clean up.
Anything from the Washimine Group?
Nothing yet.
A waste of time.
Earlier, at 06:00, a detective approached the Washimine office for information.
It's only a matter of time until we're discovered.
Tell the main unit to move to the Mariazeleska.
Affirmative. What about Laptev?
There's no need to tell him.
Uh, Miss Balalaika.
What is it?
What if... the Washimine Group abandons the agreement?
Rock.
Does it concern you?
No...
That's right. Don't mistake where you should be.
Sis, that's not too nice.
It's not really a secret, so why don't you tell him?
You're certainly taking his side, Two Hands. Silence is golden.
That's true, but Rock's family.
Trusting each other is important, too.
You've gotten to be a much better talker.
All right then.
Let's just say if they do something stupid like that,
we'll just have to add one more name to our target list.
Our job won't change, and the world will go on.
That's all.
Yuki!
I'm sorry, we'll stay late next time to help!
Goodbye!
Don't worry about it. Have fun at work.
So senpai, my last finals were so bad,
and Mom made a big deal about me quitting my job.
Mr. Gin, I am involved in this.
I was raised in this house.
I am the daughter of Washimine Ryuzo.
And Mom just won't drop it about me quitting my job...
About that guy, Okajima.
He is involved in this...
on the Russian's side.
Senpai? Senpai!
Are you listening to me at all?
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is a big concern for me.
Um, Maki.
Yes?
It's nothing. Now that I think about it, talking about it won't help.
Don't fade out with a line like that!
Boss!
Oh, it's you, Yoshida.
I'm just out for a walk. Nothing exciting's gonna happen.
Bro! Are you meeting the Russians?
Yoshida, it's been a long time since you've called me bro.
Bro! I'll go too!
Yoshida, take this.
Ask Gin about what to do next. You might not like him, but he's a good man.
Bro!
Later!
Or something like that.
When?
This morning...
there was a suitcase just sitting in front of our office.
Those god damned Russians!
Yoshida, no matter who did it, it would have ended like this.
We had to do something about Kousa.
Boss was just too smart for his own good.
That was all.
What do we do now?
Dark and lonely...
the snowy night sky.
Hold up!
You lowlife!
Rock!
I want you to translate as bluntly as you can in Japanese.
B-But!
Tonight, I'll tell you about the truth.
What I seek is destruction and domination.
I don't have interest in anything else.
I'm only interested in how much I can dance in the pit of Hell.
See you another day.
Hey!
Hey, Rock! Are you all right?
You were sweating like crazy.
Was I asleep?
You were breathing like a Buick engine.
It's not good to drink that much.
It's about to get wild.
We're moving.
Moving?
The Visotniki are splitting up between the Russian embassy and a cargo ship.
So there really is going to be war.
Yeah, Hotel Moscow is serious.
A storm is coming, Rock. A storm of steel and blood.
Mr. Gin, do you plan on going?
If I choose to walk a path in the sun.
the rest of you will be forced to wallow in darkness.
Miss, that's no good.
I can't run from this.
Right now, Mr. Gin, I feel the night inside of you.
That's very sorrowful, but it's not cold, it's warm.
Miss...
I...
I wanted you to walk the path of a human and get a hold of true happiness.
That is why I have lived to this day.
Kousa's rats, the Russian lowlifes,
They're all trying to ruin us!
We will do what we can.
If they will accept me on equal terms, then I shall go.
Hey, Mr. Ginji...
The snowy night is beautiful.
This is the first time I've thought that.
Mr. Ginji.
Mr. Ginji, will you protect me?
Master, as acting boss of the Washimine Group,  I, Matsuzaki Ginji...
As my master, please let me protect you...
Please allow me to serve.
People are just like dice,
we throw ourselves into our lives.
Mr. Gin, your fist job. Please work carefully tonight.
Let's take of this quickly.