I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
Me, Uncle? To the Olympics?
One day you should aim for something like that.
It's all right, you have the skills for it.
If I do that, can I regain my father's honor?
As a member of your father's family, that is what you can do.
If I do that I can...
But before that, you may need to prove yourself worthy, at least a bit.
Kapitan, Kapitan!
Menshov, the Dragunov!
Excellent. If this was Los Angeles you'd get the gold medal!
The first lieutenant has paved the way!
Everyone, move out! Leave the chemicals!
Let's go!
Women's 50m Rifle, position three.
The gold medal goes to America's Launi Meili.
Meili was in sixth place four years ago...
And what would you have me do?
Kapitan.
I've been stripped of my military rank. I'm no longer a kapitan.
And you aren't in my company anymore.
The Soviet Union, the country we fought for, no longer exists in this world.
No matter what battlefield we're on...
as long as we're under you, the path will open.
I believed that once.
Even through this shameful poverty.
I never thought my second-in-command would lose his life because of dirty money.
Comrades, raise your fists!
From this moment we will return to our own active military duty!
We've charged through many battlefields since that time at the cemetery.
Yes.
What we're doing now is just a check point.
Let's take care of it quickly.
As for the Washimine Group, she's next in line after Bando.
A little girl.
The sun has been setting a lot earlier recently.
But senpai, what's wrong? You sorted all those library cards by yourself.
I'm glad you finished, but...
It's snowing too!
It's a good night.
But senpai, I thought you didn't like snowy nights.
Maki-chan.
Get along with your mother.
You're a very good girl.
S-Senpai?
Come on senpai, you sound like you're about to die.
Senpai!
Deputy, we've come for you.
Thank you.
In that case, let us begin.
Senpai...
I... Umm...
Stay healthy.
I-I... what's going on...
Senpai.
Senpai!
Senpai...
Have you found Balalaika's location?
Not yet. It won't be easy to figure out where they're coming from.
We've got people looking for them now.
No matter what, someone must have seen a group of Russians running around.
Azabu: Area in Tokyo with many embassies and a large foreign population
Send people to Azabu as well.
And to the Russian embassy, as well as other places they could be using as an entrance point.
There's a political group in that area that we know well. I'll ask them to investigate.
Shouldn't we send soldiers to Narita and Haneda as well, Deputy?
They must know that we will counterattack.
I don't believe they will try to flee from Japan.
That woman plans on fighting.
Deputy, shall I stop somewhere?
No, I'm all right.
I must get accustomed to this.
Mr. Yoshida.
Y-Yes?
I haven't thanked you yet.
Thank you for that time at the meeting.
Deputy, that was nothing!
That time...
Don't act so dim!
The Miss is here because she can't stand to see you taken by Kousa's bastards and thrown out!
The Miss is putting her own life on the line!
If there's any time to show your chivalry, it's now!
Miss, even though you had nothing to do with us, you wanted to avenge our boss.
What kind of yakuza wouldn't put their life on the line for you?
So then Deputy, I'll begin now. I will see you at home.
Mr. Gin!
Your first job tonight... please work carefully.
Please leave it to me.
No one's answering, Boss.
I can't contact Balalaika or any of the other members.
Call again. Keep calling until you get a hold of someone, Makalushka.
The hotel's been vacated, and there's no sign of them.
Perhaps we should ask for direction from Moscow...
Don't you say anything stupid like "ask for direction" again!
When I say do it again, I mean do it again!
Damn it. Damn it, damn it! That woman must have worked them up against me.
There's no other way the Slevenin would betray me!
Why would she frame us?
Not you, it's me!
She hates the KGB!
Not just the KGB, the GRU, and the Nomenklatura too!
There are plenty of others who were crushed by that woman!
What did Slevenin say about this woman?
Get down!
It's the yakuza!
Is it over?
Sukeroku the Souga has come to play.
Sukeroku and Ikyu: Reference to the play Sukeroku Kuruwa no Hatsuzakura where Sukeroku arrived in teahouse to battle Ikyu
Now, where is Ikyu the Bearded?
His only weapon is that sword!
Kill him!
Old man.
Where are you headed?
Now then, I have quite a few questions for you.
What's that woman's phone number, Boss?
Wait, don't kill me! It wasn't me, someone set this up!
Oh, you don't understand Japanese.
I see, then I can't use you.
Tell the Ivans to give us more in chips.
The higher-ups have been annoying lately.
We need to compensate them a little more.
Tell them yourself, bro.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Rock. She'll be mad. Let's get going.
I finally get to ditch that Tokarev.
I can't go far without him.
What's wrong?
It has started.
Shooting incident at store, several foreigners killed, Russian
Yeah, the struggle.
I bet she's laughing her ass off.
It's a big ol' fight, just like she wanted.
That girl...
Revy, I can't leave things as they are.
Will you go to that girl with me?
Don't be stupid. You better think about what we are to them.
We're the worst enemy they've got right now.
Please, Revy!
If she's related to the Washimine, then she's going to get dragged into this!
Now that I've seen how Miss Balalaika does things, we have to go!
That girl is different from us!
Rock.
She's just a normal girl!
Rock!
And this isn't Roanapur!
How is it different?
How is it any different, Rock?
She's already living this kind of life.
And Balalaika will take care of things here in Roanapur style.
There is no difference.
But I...
Please, Rock. This is a division.
If we pass over it here, we'll have nowhere to go back to.
Our Ameripass will be expired and the Greyhounds won't come down this road anymore.
Ameripass: bus pass to many North American destinations for Greyhound bus service
What I'm saying is that this is your country.
Do you understand me?
I understand. But...
It's all right. I'm sorry.
Forget about it, Rock.
I forgot something important.
Where we are now, I'm your gun.
My job is to protect your life, not to interfere with it.
I'll follow you, Master.
So don't connect any phone calls unless they're from the Russian embassy. Is that correct?
Miss Vlatinera?
Yes. Thank you.
If there's anything else, please call on me.
A boy that age is the most adorable.
Now, Sergeant.
Yes, Kapitan?
A report from the recon team.  Attack Point 2 is situation yellow.
The offices around the Kousa Council are completely protected.
The police in this country are skilled.
Police who don't accept bribes are always skilled.
It's a matter of quality, Sergeant.
Have you seen the news?
Yes.
Comrade Laptev did a fine job.
So he did. For a KGB agent, he probed the enemy very well.
The next head will be Bulgazivi the Priest. He's very skilled with the abacus.
But we'll handle the violence.
Let us begin our job.
Very well done, Miss.
I've told him to contact the office with his results.
Right. Good work, Mr. Yoshida.
Umm, Miss...
I'm sorry about what happened at your school.
I knew it would cause you trouble, but...
I know.
I always assumed she would know about this at some point.
Now that I think about it, this may have been the best time.
Thank you, Mr. Yoshida.
That's much too kind! Uhh...
It's cold tonight so let's...
Eh? You got here sooner than I thought you would! I figured it'd take a little longer.
Chaka! Why the hell are you here? You have your station!
What happened?
The times are the times.
Right, Miss?
Chaka! You need to know your place!
Who told you... Are you listening to me?
Chaka? These are your allies?
Mr. Yoshida, you know what?
You're... too trusting.
Did that hurt? Sorry, Mr. Yoshida.
God damn it!
You see, we don't take the side that won't earn us anything.
We don't care if it's the Kousa Council or the Russians.
But if we have her as a present, nothing bad will happen to us.
Right, Miss?
Miss! Hurry up and run!
You're so god damned loud, punch-head.
Hurry up and die.
Here's some more!
That hurt!
Geez.
Hana's real scary when he snaps.
I feel bad for that girl.
You running into me hurt.
I said it hurt, you bitch! Fuck off!
Don't you have something to say?
Like "sorry" or "I apologize"?
Stand up!
Hey, hey, Hanada.
Who told you to beat the shit out of her?
If you act up too much...
I'll kill you.
Sorry, Ms. Yuki.
We have a lot of guys here who get out of control when they snap.
You look stupid, Hana!
Forgive me!
So you better listen to us and follow orders, or it might get dangerous.
Rock, is this the only entrance?
We're uninvited guests.
I thought the backdoor would be...
That's not it. Haven't you noticed it yet, Rock?
This place only smells like what we've gotten used to.
Footprints?
Oh no! Ms. Yukio!
Don't rush in, Rock!
Ms. Yukio!
Was it Balalaika?
It wasn't her, or that girl would be lying here too.
The girl doesn't have enough value as a hostage to Hotel Moscow.
She uses a Stetchkin. The others use a Varyag or other military autos.
AKs too.
But look at the floor. Why aren't there any cases?
A revolver.
That's it.
Too bad for Yoshida, but he's more aerodynamic now.
Look at this huge hole. It was high caliber.
Guys who happily use this type of gun are either show-offs or idiots beyond salvation.
I've got one guess.
It's that guy! But, why did he betray him?
I don't get it.
You don't smell like gun powder.
Get it, Jumbo? My gun had nothing to do with how Yoshida bought the farm.
Mr. Ginji, we didn't do this. Hotel Moscow hasn't come this far.
We came to take Ms. Yukio away from the fighting and happened to find this.
Please trust that... we have nothing... to do with Hotel Moscow...
Wait, Mr. Ginji! We're not done talking.
I didn't hear a car when you arrived.
You came here on foot, alone.
There are tire marks everywhere out front.
Judging from the footprints here, it looks like they came in numbers from a distance.
Do you plan on going alone?
It doesn't matter.
We don't have time.
The one who did this is one of yours.
He knows you'll be coming to take her back, and he'll be waiting.
But what if a skilled gunman was at your side?
It'll be outside of his estimation.
So you want to know where he is?
It's all Japanese talk.
Don't you play any music? I don't get what they're saying.
What about FEN?
The DJ keeps playing shitty songs.
Yeah, it's Guitar Wolf! I know these guys!
They put out a cool sound.
Mr. Translator, left at the next road.
I don't understand why you're helping.
Mr. Ginji,
she's not the kind of person who should be on this side.
That's what I think.
I hate it when kids who should grow up normally, can't.
If someone had allowed her to,
that would have been well enough.
If someone allowed her to...
Strike!
If I get one more point, take more off. What do you think, Okazaki?
Top or bottom?
How about the bottoms.
Well, if she's completely naked then the bet's over.
If that happens, let's do that! Let's shave her.
It'd be hilarious!
It's a dark tower.
The knights are here to save the princess.
Rock, we're charging in from the front. You go in from the back.
What should I do?
Just cover our backs when we need you to.
Revy, can you two work together? You don't understand...
No problem.
Once the fight starts, our bodies will move on their own.
We're made to be that way.
This is Hell's motel.
Run as hard as you can or the boogeyman will get ya!