I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
Even if it's 150,000 dollars?
It doesn't matter! After I kill these brats, don't forget to grab the cash on the ground, Eda!
R-Right! Don't move, you two!
I suppose... that's the end of negotiating.
Why you!
There they are!
This is Jodorovsky. I've encountered the enemy at Point Puskov.
Understood.
Those bastards!
Don't, Eda! It's Hotel Moscow!
They've come out, nee-sama. The Russians.
Yes.
Hey, nee-sama, let's confuse the Russians.
If we start killing them, they'll return to their base.
I understand, nii-sama. Let's split up and hunt down the Russians.
I wish you luck, nee-sama.
Yes, nii-sama.
I love you.
Yes, I love you too.
They lost the target in combat.
But it clearly showed the enemy who we are.
Proceed as if the enemy has taken our bait.
Yes, ma'am.
All units, continue your assigned tasks.
Lavochec's and Jodorovsky's squads have finished the second set of orders.
Moving to the final location.
Discovered target two behind Jodorovsky's squad during the retreat.
Confirm the number of targets. Hurry!
This is Polanski.
Only target two has been sighted. I repeat, only target two has been sighted.
This is Private Eugene.
Confirming the enemy pursuing Jodorovsky.
I can only see one as well.
The target is on Jodorovsky's tail.
We will drag it to the planned location.
So only target two has taken the bait.
Yes ma'am.
Very well. Drag that one in.
Don't let it know what you're doing. Those kids are pretty smart.
Let it to believe it has the upper hand.
Keep that in mind, and move to the next phase. Act confused and chaotic.
My subordinates will follow through in mafia style. Please do not be concerned.
We will be at the park gate momentarily. Once there, we will attack the target.
Focus on confusing and angering it.
If it's angered, its senses will become dulled. That will be the turning point.
Roger.
Sergeant, it's time. Take command of the last squad.
Yes, ma'am.
Good luck then, Kapitan.
Yes. You be careful as well.
Now...
let's end this... pathetic racket.
Damn!
How do you expect me to go back to the church?
We should have gone along with the trade! You're so damned greedy!
Bitch...
Who the hell do you think saved you from having your balls ripped off by Hotel Moscow? Huh?
I haven't had balls since I was born! Monkey-faced dumbass!
That's it, you fucking bitch, draw your guns!
Very funny, Revy. It'll be even funnier when I rip you a new asshole!
I just don't care anymore.
We didn't make a cent.
I'm going back to the office.
Call me if anything happens.
H-Hey! What about me?
What about you?
I don't want to go get the car by myself in the middle of a fire-fight!
Come with me, Revy! We're friends, right?
Do it yourself. Geez, you're not a kid anymore.
What...
You cold-hearted bitch!
Hello, miss.
How long have you been there?
I was waiting for you to be alone.
I didn't want to take on the both of you by myself.
I want you to help me with something, miss.
We need to get out of here after nii-sama kills the Russian woman.
But we've already killed our hosts, the Verrocchio family.
Dumbass. You knew that, but you killed the boss anyway?
Now that Verrocchio's dead, there's no reason to kill Balalaika.
Why do you continue? Why?
Why? You're asking why? That's... funny.
Because we want to. There's no other reason.
We want to, so we do it.
It doesn't matter.
We just want to know about our get-away driver.
We want someone who takes their job seriously.
Come on. Tell me, miss.
There's no reason to hide. Come on out.
You noticed me. As expected of you, madame.
Your subordinates are quite skilled as well.
As much as I chased them around, I couldn't kill a single one.
So, what shall we do, madame?
Since I came all the way here, would you like to talk?
About the man we killed, maybe?
A normal person would have died sooner, but he lasted quite a while.
And he kept yelling out "Kapitan! Kapitan!" until the very end.
Even while bubbling so much blood.
Hmmm? I see.
You're cold, madame.
But madame, you'll become like that man soon enough.
It's just a shame that we don't have much time.
It's a real shame.
I'm sorry, boy, but this is the end for you.
But before that, you need to apologize for your mischief.
Right, boy?
So go ahead and kneel right there.
That's not...
Kneel!
It's the end of the line for you, boy.
If you still had an ounce of sanity left, you would have noticed...
...that you jumped right into the feeding grounds.
So, in the end, you're just a helpless, broken, piece of shit brat.
And you're going to die here.
That's funny. What are you talking about?
I'm not going to die. I can't die.
I killed so many people.
Many, many,
many, many people.
We can live for that many...
lives.
We can... we can increase our lives.
We shall never die.
Thus,
we're eternal.
So that's what your belief is? It's a very wonderful thought.
"No One Lives Forever": 1980s song by Oingo Boingo
But, the truth is in the song, "No One Lives Forever". Just like it says.
Now, I could torment you before I kill you.
Considering what you did to my subordinate, that would be most appropriate.
However...
I'm not as perverse as you are.
So I'm just going to sit here and watch you die.
With that bullet wound, you'll only last ten minutes at best.
I dedicate these last few minutes before you leave this world to Sahalov and Menishof.
I'm...
certain that you wouldn't understand.
Don't cry... you fool.
Kapitan!
Sergeant, we're done here.
That was horrible, Kapitan. My guts were frozen the whole time.
I apologize.
I made you put up with my selfishness.
Kapitan...
I must be getting old.
I'm...
I'm a little tired.
She's got a nice voice, doesn't she.
That's not the voice of a psychopathic killer.
Her voice, at least, is the voice of an angel.
But things sure have gone crazy.
No kidding.
To think, that the gal who orchestrated the "night of terror" in Roanapur is our client...
But it's still a job. Where's Revy?
She's been in a bad mood over that girl.
But right now, she's keeping watch outside of the cabin door.
To be ready, just in case, for Rock.
That was a beautiful song. Where did you learn it?
I saw it on TV.
I really love this song.
But apart from letting nii-sama hear this song...
you're the the first, mister.
Hey!
Mister, you seem different.
Like someone that's in a different place, a different world.
Maybe I just haven't gotten used to this job yet.
You're a good person.
I'm good at telling who's a good person.
It's me. Is this Balalaika?
You know what I'm calling about, don't you?
Yeah.
I thought you would've called sooner.
Dutch, do you understand what you're doing?
Of course.
We've been paid enough.
It's not because of a sense of obligation or attachment, is it?
Do I look like a philanthropist?
I just had to find out.
Our position depends on yours.
We both have things we have to do. Right, Balalaika?
Dutch, we're heading south...
You're right, Dutch. I've already prepared a few hands.
Yeah.
I think I saw a few of them.
No sorrow or regrets. Good luck, then.
Roger, Kapitan.
Sergeant.
Yes, ma'am.
Bring me the E-File of the Trouble List.
"E"?
Just a clever insurance policy.
It's the Vietnam Navy.
Good answer. They're impressive.
The power of Hotel Moscow.
Are we going to fight them?
Don't be stupid.
We're a torpedo boat, they're missile boats.
It sucks, but the South Seas route is out.
How about Brunei? Melody Li's place?
No good, pain in the ass to get there.
Well, the only place we can go, that's in the range of this boat, is Pangkal Pinang's Elroy.
"Bighorn" Elroy?
Okay, let's go with that.
I'll go contact him.
Ah, the sea. We're out at sea, but I can't even have a look!
What a shame.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I'm used to it.
Haven't you seen the ocean before?
In Sicily, and at the orphanage...
all we ever saw were grey walls.
Carpathian Mountains: eastern wing of the European Central Mountains
We were born in the rocky Carpathian Mountains.
It was always a cloudy and lonely place.
A certain dictator prohibited abortions...
in order to create a work force for a poor country.
But if they're poor, there's no way to raise those children.
Abandoned children were placed into state orphanages.
They became slaves to the secret police.
The dictator was killed. Only the orphans were left.
When we were taken to Sicily, we were put into blood and darkness.
We were kicked so hard that some nights we couldn't stop peeing red blood.
I talked with my nii-sama a lot.
"Why does God make us suffer so much?"
But then, nii-sama and I noticed it.
When...
when we were brought in front of the other children,
and had to beat another child repeatedly with a bat,
the adults were all laughing.
Nii-sama and I were laughing.
We thought, while we laughed, that this is how it worked.
Yes. If the world will keep turning because someone is killed,
that must be the reason why we're here.
To kill, be killed, and kill again.
That's how the world creates a ring.
Aren't you...
sad that your brother died because of that?
What are you talking about?
I'm right here.
I'm always with nee-sama.
That's why we will never die. We will always kill above this ring.
The world keeps existing in order to kill.
Everyone's here and we're here. That's why we're not sad.
The scent of blood, the screams, the warmth of organs...
we love it all, now.
No!
You're wrong. The world really exists to make you happy!
Listen to me. Blood and darkness are just a small part of this world!
It's not everything!
Please don't cry, mister.
This is the first time I've met someone as kind as you. So this...
is a reward.
Rock?
Benny! Make sure he's all right!
I'll take care of the brat.
Got it!
Hmph, so even the likes of you still has red blood.
Listen up brat, the sis isn't the only one.
I'm disappointed that you didn't die.
You have the same smell... blood and gun smoke.
The smell of rotten blood and mud.
You and I are the same thing!
That doesn't matter.
If you fuck with him again, I'll kill you.
And if you say something unpleasant to me, I'll kill you.
Damn it! Shit! Why?
The world came together and turned them into tigers!
Man-eating tigers! Damn it!
Rock, don't look stuff like this in the eye.
This is that kind of place. It's for the best.
I'll, I'll... !
Are you going to take care of that child? Impossible.
That girl can't stop killing.
If someone had just showed them a little kindness, they would have gone to school,
they would have made friends and they would have lived happily.
But, that didn't happen, Rock.
So the story ends here... Rock.
Dutch, it's been a while.
Yeah, it's been a while.
Is this the cargo?
Yeah.
I'm sorry for the rush, but did you get a passport ready?
I somehow managed. I'm used to it.
Mister, let's meet again!
Let's meet again sometime!
Just the two of us, with a picnic basket!
Yeah, that sounds wonderful.
Really wonderful.
It's beautiful.
The sky...
It was Hotel Moscow, Dutch. What else is there?
You're done as a get-away man.
Yeah, I'm done.
My son is in South Africa.
I got a letter from his wife. He's only 34, but he has already contracted cancer.
Either way, I'm tired of walking the tightrope.
This was my last job.
I got a nice amount from Hotel Moscow.
Later.
"The sky is beautiful", right at the end...
Fuck.
Rock, get the canvas. We've gotta cover the body.
Someday I want to run away...
We don't need it, Dutch.
She's fine as she is...
...to the world of midnight...
Facing the blue sky...
watching the sea while sleeping.
Where the darkness fill the air...
Where it's icy cold...
Where nobody has a name...
Where living is not a game...
There, I'll hide my broken heart...
Dying to survive...
There, no one can see me cry...
The tears of my lonely soul...
I'll find peace of mind...
In the dark and cold world of midnight...
Midnight...
I took this job because I heard I could make perfect counterfeit money.