I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
Don't put us in a tight spot with your selfishness, little lady.
There's nothing wrong with being a perfectionist.
But, all things have a time limit.
Soccer, baseball, stocks and even fucking.
Stupid people.
It's half-asses. Far too half-assed.
There's no way we can release these.
We're not saying we want to fool the mint.
The only ones saying that, are you and your friend on the PC.
And you've already gone over the expenses we specified by 200,000 dollars.
The due date was over two months ago.
I don't think it's a big deal, but some of my subordinates think you're trying to pull a fast one on us like we're dumb reptiles.
Leo, keep working.
It's rude of them.
Ah, I'm sorry. I don't agree with them at all.
But if it were true, I really would have to turn you into tiny little pieces.
Hmph. Do I look like a man who'd strike a woman?
I don't, right?
I can't do great things.
Geez, think about the ones who have to clean up after you.
Why did you do that?
Now we can't... can't...
Now, now... don't cry.
We're not bored enough to put up with your hobby.
And we're not so extravagant that we can waste money.
Get it done within 48 hours, little lady.
It's hot! Ow!
Damn it's hot. How much did I drink last night?
Miss Revy never shoots when she's drinking, but...
Good Lord.
Shit, it's so fucking hot, and this is how the day starts?
How about this?
I'm taking it all.
Damn it. I'm going to the can. Then we're starting over.
It's not as if I cheated on you. I just...
Open up! Hey!
What's with this city?
I've never seen anything more suspicious.
What's the shepherd's weapon?
Psalms Chapter 23 Verse 15.
"Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death."
The story is about what the shepherd took with him.
Jericho 941: high capacity pistol created by Israeli Military Industries
Model Jericho 941 FBL.
What the hell is that?
Then what's your answer?
It's this, of course.
You stupid shit.
He's a Jew, right? Obviously he's gotta have an Israeli model.
Don't you argue with me, you monkey.
It's so hot.
I wouldn't have come if I knew your AC was broken. The boat at the dock too. I'm so unlucky.
I know, I don't need to hear you whine about it, either.
You're not a broken jukebox you know.
So how about that pretty sailor boy of yours?
It's been almost a year, right?
Rock is just pathetic.
He won't take off that stupid business suit. He gets taken hostage by enemies. And on top of that, his jokes suck.
Damn it.
Who asked about that?
Have you done it with him or not?
Come on, come on. You're being boring.
It's hot!
Hello!
Hello! I'm being chased! Help me!
You're being called upon.
We're closed!
Hurry! Open up! Open up!
Please open the door!
Do you know what Jesus said in John, Chapter 5, miss?
He said, "Don't bring me any trouble, bitch."
Isn't this a church?
So what? God isn't home.
He's on vacation in Vegas.
Please! I'm being chased!
I can't count on anyone in this city!
I'm not from this city! Isn't a church supposed to do something!
I can't believe it! You call yourself a sister?
Come back on Judgment Day.
Then God will...
Jane, don't make us go through all of this.
It's time to go home.
Mr. Elvis, don't do that.
How many times do I gotta tell you, you don't know this city...
Sister, I have to speak with that girl, so...
Eda!
All right!
Son of a bitch!
Any idiot who tries to attack us...
Had better prepare themselves!
God damn it! Shoot them! Kill 'em!
Stop! Don't shoot back, no matter what!
Shoot, you idiots!
Damn it, I can't calm down!
Sis, I'm here to help!
Call me "sister" you moron!
I don't recognize the face. Is he new?
Yes, I'm an apprentice priest, Ricardo.
I've heard all about you from sis. Please call me Rico...
Rico! I said, don't call me sis!
Revy! Revy, can you hear me? It's me, Nobushi!
Put your guns down! It was a mistake! I beg of you!
This is just a little misunderstanding...
Don't fuck with me!
Who cares if it was a mistake!
Got that, piss-ass bastard?
You think you're going to be able to go home in one piece after putting a bullet in the church?
Oh Lord! It was useless after all!
Oh my, oh my... what's this?
My, my. Eda!
Eh?
Haven't I told you not to have these in the chapel?
Uh, well, sister...
Oh well, we'll deal with that later. We'll put these non-believers through the same thing as the Etimeshi.
Damn it! Fall back! You too, Elvis!
God damn, those bitches! I'll remember this!
I'll turn you into mincemeat!
My, my.
Who's handling the repair fee? The bullet fees?
Money just keeps running out the door. It's not a joking matter.
Now then, let's hear what you have to say, little lady.
They are the Neveral Cartel, the Florida branch of the Gerolam Familia.
The cartel hired me to make counterfeits of the old dollar bills.
The design team for the counterfeit bills are all over the world, so that hasn't been a problem thanks to the net.
I keep the team together. I'm pretty much the leader.
And? What did you screw up to be chased by them?
No one screwed up.
They just didn't have any taste. How rude.
Listen.
I took this job because I heard I could make perfect counterfeit money.
The Super Z was a big shock for me.
The paper was perfect, but it was the mixture ratio that was brilliant.
We made sure that the cotton to linen pulp ratio was exactly 23 to 76.8.
There are some folks who'd settle with using a laser printer.
To me, that's outrageous!
But these guys were good. They had a specialized Swiss-made printer.
I could kill for one of those, but they're monitored so carefully.
Incidentally, we used a Heidelberg MF521 printer. But it has its limits.
Isn't it terrible?
If you call it support to attack a hostile country, you get funding just for that!
I could make it on a much smaller budget. Honestly!
But even that has its problems. The pressure around the serial numbers on the faceplates.
But we use a method where we alter the ink pressure in certain places with rubber.
But this isn't a very clever method.
That's because if we use an ultraviolet ink, we can make a more natural looking red blow ink.
There's no problem where there's a coat of green and black.
But with that method we need to be careful with the Treasury mark.
Or the area around it becomes uneven. So then...
Hey, hey, hey, I got a question.
Er, yes?
Sorry to interrupt you in the middle of your speech, but...
What is it?
When will this be over?
Battle of the Bulge: 1965 film about the famous WW II battle
Are you gonna put your review of "Battle of the Bulge" in there too?
You're the ones who asked. What, are you bored?
Eda, her attitude reminds me of someone.
She's just like that old hag from the Child Welfare Center.
Anyway, research like that takes time and money, time and...
That's enough. I think we understand.
So you tried to pull one over them like that.
You say the same thing as those idiots did.
Fine, solid proof over theory.
You want us to check the goods? This'll only take a second, you idiot.
Look, the print is off by half an inch and the Department of Treasury mark is too green.
And the rose-work on this one is more refined.
Am I right?
Oh really?
So you plan on enjoying a shopping spree at Sear's with the bill in your right hand?
Ah, you poor thing. You'd be going straight to prison.
Take a closer look at the Federal Mint mark. I figured you'd be fooled by that.
Odd colorations and slips are not uncommon for bills made in the 70's.
But there's no Federal Reserve that starts with an M.
So, you've proven that Miss Revy's eyes are just glass balls.
All right, we'll believe you.
Well then, let's hear the important part.
I went over the deadline.
But I wouldn't yield, as long as I had a purpose.
And then they shot my German operator!
It was his job to manage the information given to us by our online members.
All our efforts up until then were wasted!
They don't get it!
So I finally got fed up and said goodbye to those wild gorillas. That's all of it.
That's all your fault.
Seems like you have lots of time of time on your hands.
What? I knew you wouldn't understand me!
NYPD Blue: 1990's American TV police drama set in New York City
Playing with your stupid guns all day! People who waste their time watching NYPD Blue!
Would you believe me if I told you that I watched the Oprah Winfrey Show?
The correct answer coming up after the gunshot.
Little lady, this must be the guidance of God.
You are very fortunate.
The girl who has the gun pointing at you is a getaway person.
You could handle the costs with the plates you have there.
I don't want to hand over anything that's incomplete!
But this is an emergency, and I can't be picky.
How about you buy it for 30,000 excluding the getaway fee?
Well, you have no choice. You'd better ask a different God.
Wha...? Don't you serve God?
As Luke said, "It's better to make friends, albeit with unlawful money."
I don't care, Eda. Just go and die, lady.
I don't want your help anyway.
I'm thankful that you saved me from a tight spot.
Well, goodbye.
Hey, hold on a sec. Where are you staying tonight?
I'll find a place.
If you stay at any old motel, you'll have yourself a brand new asshole even before you take off your socks.
So, here's the deal.
There's a cheap place called the "Ramsap Inn", just past the Charkwan Market.
If you tell them that you're from the Church, they should let you in.
That seems odd.
I didn't say it was free. Please donate 300 dollars as you're leaving.
I see. A church to the very end.
Then it's a deal.
Hey, hey hey. What are you thinking, Eda?
Hmm? What?
Nicely done, Sister Eda. Never forget the importance of money.
Yes, Sister.
Country bumpkins are so easy to use.
Y-You!
Yo, Leeroy! It's been a long time!
Chero: Salvadorian slang for "friend"
You know the girl that the Cheros are chasing? Yep, the Indian.
You bitch.
How much is her location worth?
That's dirty!
You found out where Jane is?
Yes, Boss.
Lobos is a cowardly idiot. You go in his place.
Listen, Russel! The bastards in this town are just shithead monkeys with clothes on!
Can you believe it? Even those nun bitches at the church were shooting at me!
Boss!
Damn it, I want to leave this godforsaken shithole of a place and go back to civilized Florida!
Yes, Boss.
Russel, capture that Indian woman and bring her to me no matter what.
Dachau: first large-scale Nazi concentration camp opened in 1933
I'll punish her so bad, it'll make Dachau look like a field trip!
Yes, Boss.
I came with you from Florida for just this reason.
In three days, you'll be able to watch the sunset with Don Gerola in Calib, Boss.
Leave it to me, "Groovy Guy" Russel, the Trouble Buster.
What's up? Got a thorn or something?
I'll kill you! Earning dirty money like that!
Give me half!
That's why I keep calling you an idiot.
You gotta let girls like that sleep before you take'em.
Let them sleep?
What do you mean, let them sleep?
It's just like the slots at a casino. Wait a while and coins will start pouring out.
Hey, what on earth...
We're here, passenger lady.
You're making an ugly face, Eda. What on earth did you do?
What do you mean? I work for the master trickster.
Sea of Galilee: Israel's largest freshwater lake where many of Jesus Christ's miracles were said to have occurred
The man who walked across the Sea of Galilee.
A trick like this is a breeze.
So, Rock's bringing the car, right? Let's go.
Hey, tell me! Where're we going?
Bye bye.
Eda! Hey, Eda!
A nun?
Hey, hey, Eda!
Damn it.
Which of you were called here by Lobos?
Everyone at this table.
All right, then. I'll be giving the orders.
1,000 dollars a head.
She's staying at the Ramsap Inn.
Your job is to capture her alive.
If she causes trouble, then you can rough her up.
Hmph, it's an easy job that any punk on the street could do.
No needing unneeded words, you idiot bastard!
If I not bored, why would I hang around pathetic money.
You...
It's just like Shenhua said, cowboy!
How about you go back to Austin and fuck a cow?
You bastards...
For a guy who got here yesterday, you're too damned bossy!
Go call Lobos, you're too...
Go call Lobos, you're too... Listen to what I have to say, you bastards!
Listen to what I have to say, you bastards!
Just introduce us to the new face.
That will be enough.
Who are you?
I don't recognize her either.
Who has she been working with?
What do you mean, Shenhua? Last week, you came to me with a job.
Eh? Me?
I'm late, I'm late! Sorry!
Are you ready?
So, the method of taking care of this. Boss Chang said to make example of it.
Tear up or to mince? Boss didn't say.
Either one works.
Well, I dropped it off. Rest up to you.
Sawyer the Cleaner!
So that's what you look like?
You always had the white mask and goggles on!
No wonder we didn't recognize you!
You all done? Let's get to work!
Over there is a new face.
Oh yeah, you're right. Never seen them before.
You two, what are your names?
I am Claude "Torch" Weaver.
Rotton...
the Wizard.
Hey, I hate to interrupt the introductions, but are you two drinking milk?
I can't drink. Beer makes me vomit.
Because of my faith.
Not very fitting...
More importantly, what kind of weapons you have?
This.
How about you? It doesn't look like a gun.
Idiot! You plan on roasting the store?
Y-Y-You... cut it out!
So, we all understand what weapons we all have.
Everyone OK with that?
Let's go take care of this and then have a drink.
Is Ramsap Inn far?
Let's split up in cars and go.
The tab's all yours.
Shit!
Cowboy? What doing? You be left here!
All right, this street'll be fine. Pull over and stop.
Yes, thank you, nii-san.
Is it really okay, this place?
I don't get her logic.
Just shut up. If we wait here awhile, something very convenient will happen for us.
Somehow, that doesn't sound right...
All right, you bastards! Let's go!
To a senseless 1,000 dollars a head job!