I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
What's with those eyes?
You had all that done to you, and you still act like nothing's wrong.
Go ahead, keep looking down on us.
Hey, after we've taken care of sword-boy, and if we can't find a buyer for you,
I'll send you to perverted fucks from dusk till dawn every day.
Those guys who can't get a hard on without hardcore S&M.
I think you'll change your mind after you're pumped full of drugs and wiggling your ass, eating shit every day.
Right?
Relax. If the video gets out, I'll buy a copy.
Dumbass. You can't win that much with Mahjong, idiot.
Shut up! You wanna fight?
Hey, any of you got Zippo oil?
Oh, did you hear? Someone pulled off a robbery at New Ookubo.
Yeah, an Iranian with a knife chased 'em down.
And then he was arrested and...
What the hell?
You're too fucking noisy!
So he really came.
You never can tell.
Well my dearest Revy, what are you doing here?
So you did want to watch, eh? Cool.
Mr. Gin...
Mr. Gin!
So you did it. You really did it.
Did you want to see my sword that badly?
You can all make the march to Hell together!
Kill 'em all, baby!
Look! Check it out! I've never seen a fight like this!
Don't fucking hide! Show your manliness!
Now run! Run!
Amazing! Amazing!
I'd better get serious.
Come here, Yuki!
Miss!
You'd better chase me!
O-Ow! Ow!
That woman's amazing! Amazing!
I never thought I'd have a chance to do it with her in a place like this!
I'd better prepare the stage!
God damn it! Who did this?
Cleaning fluid?
It's a strike!
W-Wait!
I give up! I give up!
Give! Give! Give give give!
Give? Give me what?
I... I can not speak... uh...
You're gonna give me something, right? Well, come on!
What the fuck are you trying to say, huh?
Seriously! I give, give!
Quit yapping you goofball.
You wanna give it to me or not? Come on!
Hey Jumbo, the game's up.
Boy, we made a mess.
All we got left is to mop up the glass.
Let's split up and look for our princess and that sack of shit.
We'll go around the hallway and meet at the pool, OK?
If you see Rock, drag him along with you.
If we're lucky, he might be with the princess.
All right. I'm counting on you, partner.
What a stiff.
Now then...
You're shit out of luck. I pity you.
No one is getting out of here alive. Not a single one of you.
This is Hell's motel.
Run as hard as you can, or...
the boogeyman will get ya!
Perfect.
Time to live forever, baby.
I don't hear anything any more.
Mr. Chaka could the others be...
Mr. Chaka!
I can hear you! God damnit.
What? They're probably dead.
Fuck you! How can you talk like that?
I'm sick of following you!
If you've got time to bitch, find the girl.
What are you going to do? The plan's fucked.
Come on now!
You're turning tail? Fine!
Fucking shit.
Wow, this is surprising.
You shot your own subordinates.
Despicable to the end.
Seeing as you're still hopping around, you must have not met up with Jumbo yet.
Well, who cares? I've been waiting to meet you.
I've never met a female gunman before.
We've finally got our chance. Sleep with me, Ms. Revy.
Uh huh, yeah.
I see how it is. Don't make me laugh.
When this can hits the floor, it's the signal, miss kitty-cat.
Ready?
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven...
Huh?
You wanted to fight like a gunman?
Don't make me laugh.
Who'd fight a third-rate sack of shit like you?
I do want to kill you,
but if you're happy to die, that's a different story.
I'll let Jumbo finish you off.
Fucking bitch, stop! Bitch!
Sack of shit.
You bitch, stop!
Stop, god damnit!
Stop!
Bitch!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Jumbo.
I brought you your prom date.
This ain't no fun. You're in the fucking way, sword-boy.
The miss isn't here any more. I shot her.
You're done here, right? Go home and cook some takoyaki or something.
A treacherous little dog like you wouldn't kill your own paycheck.
Am I right?
All right then, you bastard!
Now, let's see how you do.
Draw in any fashion you like.
You bastards! I'll kill you bastards!
I'll kill you!
It's gotten quiet.
Revy and Mr. Gin must be doing well.
Let's stay here a little longer, just in case.
Mr. Okajima,
why are you here?
I couldn't leave you alone.
Because I found out that you were being dragged into this incident, our affairs.
I see.
You didn't know.
I see. You mentioned that I was being dragged into this.
That's not true, Mr. Okajima.
I'm...
I'm in the center of all this,
and...
you are my enemy.
I'll say it again. You are my enemy.
Ms. Yukio, what are you saying?
Mr. Okajima, I...
succeeded as the 14th Washimine Group deputy.
Right now, for all intents and purposes, I hold the highest rank within the Washimine Group.
I...
I wasn't dragged into this. I am in the center of it all.
And you...
are my enemy.
You're...
You knew what kind of place this was and stepped forward?
You've seen it! They're filled with evil and without a shred of decency!
This world, where people like that betray and kill one another!
Mr. Okajima, I'll ask you again. Why did you come here?
I said it before.
I couldn't just watch you become dragged into this.
Couldn't just watch?
I don't believe Mr. Bando committed suicide.
You must have been there too.
With the group's momentum gone, tormented by our parent group,
when it was necessary to stand up against a stronger power,
what if you were the only one who could save them from that plight?
To renew the brotherhood, someone from the family had to be involved.
That was the rule.
But...
You don't have to say it, I know.
No matter how you look at it, it was just an excuse.
But no matter how ridiculous the deal is, making it happen is the only way we know.
That is how we keep order.
What is that?
Then what happens to your life?
No one wanted this!
Not Mr. Bando, not Mr. Gin, and not you!
They were all desperate to keep you away from the fighting, right?
To make sure that you didn't stand in this spot!
If I had been standing here sooner, this wouldn't have happened.
No! The Kousa Council are to blame!
You are...
You are trying to bear this burden by yourself.
That's the only way I can see it.
Do you remember what we talked about at the café?
That people are like dice.
People are like dice, a certain Frenchman said that.
You throw yourself...
in the direction of your own choosing.
I wasn't forced into this. I threw myself into it.
I chose to do what I could for my father and the people who loved him.
No! You didn't have a choice!
If you don't see that, you'll be forced to live with a burden that you don't have to carry!
You are in the twilight...
You can say those things because you're staying in the twilight!
I had no choice but to come here! If I don't believe that I chose this, I wouldn't have the strength!
If someone's life, honor... If their future is counting on me,
what can I do but fight for them?
Like tonight. If I didn't believe that I had chosen this responsibility, there's no way I could've endured it!
Revy...
I believed him, until one night, when the cops beat the shit out of me for something I didn't do.
If you ever turn these stories on me, you stop being one of us.
Nothing's changed since then.
Revy.
Against the experience she has endured tonight, I am powerless.
I have no words to give this girl in front of me, who's stumbling towards your side.
I...
I am... I am where I'm standing.
Nowhere else.
That's a lie.
My legs aren't standing anywhere!
You bastard!
Bastard, are you the devil?
For your death, this is a little easy on you.
But it's at your level.
Everything that happens, the painful and the terrible. I decided to carry it all.
I decided that if it saves everyone's... Mr. Gin's life, then I would do it.
Ms. Yukio, do you...
Mr. Okajima, answer me.
Why did you try to make a stand here?
I didn't honestly understand what you were talking about in the café,
but I think I can say it clearly now.
Why you submerged yourself in the southeast Asian underworld,
your Japanese life... no, you may have been seeking something outside of your normal life.
But in the end, you haven't chosen anything.
You aren't returning to the normality of the sun,
yet you're not going deeper into the evil of the darkness.
You're just... hesitating between them.
No... I...
You said it earlier, you wanted to save me.
Then save me!
Save the Washimine Group, Mr. Gin, the members, everyone!
There's no way you can.
Because you don't actually want to save me.
You just don't want to lose the normal life that you thought you threw away.
If you just watch me die, then you lose the very last of your memories of Japan.
To choose is to lose something, to leave something behind.
You don't want to lose anything, even that which you've thrown away.
You still hang on to a piece of yearning.
Who could you possibly protect like that?
Who could you possibly save like that?
Answer me! Answer me now!
I wanted to live normally.
I should be in the same place as you, not desiring a life of pain.
Ms. Yukio...
Stay away.
I know.
But I'm angry.
I can't help but be jealous of you.
That's why I...
hate you.
Wait a sec.
You did something amazing.
The bullet, baby. You sliced the bullet.
Won't you show that to me again?
Please?
Don't be short tempered.
I owe you and the translator.
There's no need to waste that.
If you're lucky...
No, if you're unlucky, there will be a chance to fight.
Ms. Yukio.
Thank you very much for tonight.
But I pray...
I pray we never meet again.
Rock still hasn't returned to his room.
What could he be wasting his time on?
It's just as well. There's nothing for him to do for a while.
The assault on the Washimine Group will begin at 0750.
Destroy all confirmed headquarters, offices, and hideouts with two teams.
The attack team has already moved out.
We shall destroy all of the Washimine forces immediately.
Teach these Japanese the etiquette of war.
I don't know what you're thinking.
You shouldn't seek the same life as him.