I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
Did you change your clothes, nee-sama?
Yes. We won't return here.
Let's take everything we need with us.
I know, nee-sama.
Here you go, nii-sama.
Please become nee-sama.
Yes, nii-sama.
Shall we go, nee-sama?
Don't forget your ticket and passport.
Of course, we can't go anywhere without them or pass through any place.
Now then, let's go, nii-sama.
Nee-sama.
Yes, yes. That's correct. That's what I remember.
Yes.
Thank you, Rock. Until next time.
Rock gave us an answer.
Those brats are from Dracula's homeland.
Romanians.
Damn it, Romanian!
If I remember correctly, the Romanian
military in Kabul used to speak like that.
Of course.
It gets harder to remember things with age.
Don't worry about it, Sergeant.
The same goes for me.
A pink shop or pink salon is a type of whore house
Sergeant, I recall that Rowan, the owner of the pink
shop on Lachada Street, was selling illegal videos.
You're correct.
Did Rowan do something?
Did you clear this place out, Chang?
Yeah. This is a delicate meeting.
If this is a date, I more then welcome it.
We can't enjoy a movie and drinks
while stinking of blood, now can we?
Chang, I found out who they are.
I see.
That's a very interesting story. How did you find out?
In the end,
we found the answer in Rowan's goods.
"Pink Shop" Rowan?
You invited him to your office? I bet he was scared to death.
He was about to shit his pants.
How unpleasant for him.
I asked him about child pornography
that had Romanian twins in it or snuff videos.
He gave us 250 videos.
That's unpleasant as well.
It took an entire night looking through
those 250 videos for fucked up perverts,
but then "bingo", we found it.
Hansel and Gretel.
That's what those brats were called in the video.
Brats sold onto the black market by institutions that couldn't
afford them anymore after the Romanian revolution.
Children of a dead dictator.
Made into the toys of perverts and ending up as pig food.
That was meant to be those brats' fate.
How did they avoid it?
Idiots made them finish off their
victims as a form of amusement.
Finishing off sacrificial lambs,
not much different from themselves.
To survive, those brats desperately learned
ways to kill that pleased the perverts.
One night after another...
And at some point, they just accepted it.
They turned their backs on the blue sky,
and entered into the shadows of darkness.
They decided to become show dogs on video, eh?
What a horrible story.
Yet appropriate for our world.
Sometimes I feel like I'm walking over a huge pile of shit.
"Morality" and "Justice" don't really suit me.
Words like that and what comes
out of asses are surprisingly similar.
Having sympathy for those kids is on the same level
as idiots who wield missiles and talk about peace.
I only told you what I know.
We don't need justice. We just need profit and trust.
After Rowan, it was easy.
Just needed to follow the purchase routes.
I see. So this is the source.
If one of his relatives had died,
it would've been a great alibi.
It was just for show.
They can't possibly be disciplined.
They are trouble to everyone around
them and shit on them in the process.
Your men were hit by their wake.
No matter the reasons...
a line must be drawn.
What's going on god dammit?
They should have just taken care of that bitch,
but the corpses just keep piling up!
Boss.
Why don't we end it here?
We can make it look like we took care
of the guys who messed with this city!
Now's the time to take care of them
without creating a bigger mess!
For a shrimp, you sure talk big to your boss!
But boss, they're too much...
Why do you think I called those
damn brats here in the first place?
Don't you think it's about time to
change this city's color, Chang?
Then there'd be no reason for the committee to exist.
Are you going to bring us to war again?
I like to call it a controlled conflict.
The reason and motive will stand.
It's a justified war then?
I didn't think you were the type to say sugarcoated words.
If they're the right words for an excuse.
Why don't you feed this "justice" to the dogs?
Join me, or forget about this. It's up to you.
Well now...
I suppose there's no reason to
report back to headquarters.
The only thing you can trust in this world is brute force.
So, I'll get to see you as a gunman again?
I'm looking forward to it, babe.
I don't mind being in gunfights, but since I have
to maintain my reputation, it's a pain in the ass.
Oh, and don't call me "babe"!
I hate that nickname.
Kapitan.
Sergeant, Chang has agreed to the proposal.
From now on, the Hong Kong Triad will be our allies.
Roger.
Please notify our comrade soldiers.
Immediate standby from 1905.
I predict Lesson 217, Case 5.
Repeat.
Immediate standby from 1905.
You predict a snatch mission
within enemy combat territory.
"Da" means yes in Russian
Da. I predict chaos. It's a carnival in the city at the moment with all the bounty hunters.
It's better that it's lively, Kapitan. There's nothing better than the roar of gunfire.
That's right, Sergeant.
Right now, this is the only war that we have.
Let's use it carefully.
The Palermo bosses have great
interest in this shithole of a city!
They're on edge because I can't do a single thing out here!
Listen up, you piece of shit!
If we don't do something right now,
at the next officer's meeting, I'll...
Shit.
Um... Um, Boss.
Shut up!!
But... those twins are...
T-Those punks.
I-I told them never to come here. What are they here for?
We talked about it and decided.
What are you saying?
Yes.
Borscht: a vegetable soup usually red in color from beet roots.
We decided that Borscht will be the main dish,
They're referring to the order of the mob bosses being targeted
and we'll start with the macaroni.
D-Don't you f-fuck around!
The macaroni has boiled over.
God damned brats! Do you wanna die?
Boss Chang.
We've completely surrounded the building.
We await your orders.
Cho.
Yes?
You should lower your head.
The job has changed to a hunt.
Contact Hotel Moscow. I want to make them owe me.
Revy, the cops are on the move.
They blocked off the entrances to the central road.
It seems like something has
happened with the Verrocchio family.
Revy, we won't get any of the
bounty if we stay on the sidelines!
I got it. Don't yell, Eda.
Where are we meeting up?
Joey's got a room at the Barkana Square. Hurry it up!
Geez.
The fuse got lit.
Now we just wait for the bomb.
Attention!
Comrades, the Verrocchio Family
has been attacked tonight.
But there will be no change of plan. Do everything as planned.
From this moment, we begin.
Courageous comrades...
to us, Warrant Officer Sahalov and Corporal
Menishof were irreplaceable comrades in arms.
We are the ones who should offer a light for their souls.
With our lost comrade's souls,
our guns become Goddesses of Vengeance!
Kalashnikov refers to the Avtomat Kalashnikova 1947 or AK-47
Give them punishment through our AKs and
rip their jaws open with 5.45mm rounds!
Boss Chang, we have word from Hotel Moscow.
"The situation is dangerous, retreat from the location."
She's smart.
However, it's too late.
Cho, get your pistol.
The Chinese on Chang's pistol is tentei literally Heavenly King.
Get down!
Great! You're pretty good!
Thanks, little girl!
It's unfortunate, but we can't deal with you right now.
Till next time!
That puts me at ease.
The source is the Verrocchio family.
Watsup is interrogating the Triad.
Our route's about to pay off.
The carnival night is about to start. Hallelujah!
Listen, it's a black Japanese sedan.
But we won't know it's them if they ditch the car!
Who cares. Shoot anyone that passes by.
Hey, don't push.
Revy, come here.
What is it, Eda?
Hey, I just noticed something's strange, Revy.
What is it? Don't hold out on me again.
It's Balalaika.
The woman with the biggest grudge hasn't appeared yet.
Now that you mention it...
Right? If this was the real deal, it'd be weird if we weren't shut out.
Revy, where will those twins go?
They're not rational, but their target is Balalaika.
The others were diversions...
no, they were just in their way.
If Balalaika mobilized the Visotniki
to completely annihilate the twins.
Military people are all pragmatists. They won't move carelessly.
The twins will definitely hit a blind spot.
All these guys think they're deer hunting in Montana.
Those twins are more like coyotes, it won't be this easy.
If they fell for this kind of trap, they'd be six feet under by now.
For an uneducated girl, you sure are quick, Revy.
So, what's the fastest back-street to Hotel Moscow?
Through Chalquam Market and
straight down Sautanam Street.
More importantly, you're the uneducated one, you whore.
I'm sorry for your loss, Chang.
If I had known those kids were here,
I would have brought more men.
Thanks to them, I have to walk home. It's just my luck.
Ah, I got rid of Watsup.
I figured you didn't want to give it to those greedy pigs.
He's off on a wild goose chase, till the day after tomorrow.
So, just pay me back someday.
Shrewd as always.
I owe you one.
Things are going smooth over here, Chang.
The first march is about to begin.
It's coming! It's their car!
There's no mistake. A black Japanese sedan!
Are the twins inside?
It's tinted... I can't see.
Who cares? Blow it up!
Go to hell!
Did we get 'em?
They're not white!
They're local brats, damn it!
Shit, we missed!
Watsup is heading towards the south port.
After them!
Just you wait, you damn punks!
We'll smoke those brats out! Fuck yeah!
You were absolutely right, nee-sama.
Making a fake for only 5,000 baht was a bargain.
But I feel a little sorry for them.
They said they were orphans.
It couldn't be helped, nee-sama.
It's kill or be killed.
That's all there is in this world.
That's right, nii-sama. It couldn't be helped.
That's right, nee-sama.
So, let's kill. Let's kill even more.
Enemy spotted.
The team behind Charkwan Street
has spotted the hated enemy.
They have engaged in combat.
Good.
Where did they move next?
East, just as predicted.
Momentarily, they will be at Radoga Point.
Target is out of sight.
They're moving along the course nicely.
Team 3 has attacked once and has broken away
from Radoga Point, moving toward Livinsk now.
Standing by.
Place a team on Hamipon Street.
Yes, ma'am.
Leave only one spot on the floodgate. Notify all teams to fall back after engaging the enemy.
The main mission is to divert the enemy.
Which team was that?
We did not deploy in that area yet.
It's possible that those are bounty hunters.
Team captains, report.
Deal with those who interfere.
Whoa now, don't move you damn brats!
Bad things will happen if you hang out around here.
Especially when the entire city is on a manhunt.
Hurry up and say your prayers.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Can I ask you something?
How much money is on our heads?
80,000 dollars!
Don't move!
That's a very good price.
Then I have one question.
I have the money from Verrocchio's office here.
I don't mind fighting you here,
but we still have something that we want to do.
How does 100,000 sound for having not seen us?
Don't fuck around. We're not punks on an errand.
Then, how about 150,000?
How about it?
Well...
What should we do, Revy?
Don't panic, Eda.
We'll take it all. The 80,000, the 150,000, and their lives!
We have confirmed the target's location.
It's the Chinese from the Lagoon Company.
And the sister from the Church of Violence is with her.
It doesn't matter.
If necessary, crush them underfoot.
The scent of rotten blood and soil.
You and I are the same thing!