I
have
a
big
gun
I
took
it
from
my
Lord
Sick
with
Justice
I
just
wanna
feel
you
I
am
your
angel
Only
a
ring
away
You
make
me
violate
you
No
matter
who
you
are
It's
lives
forever
Been
burn
in
the
hell
By
all
those
pigs
out
there
It's
always
been
hell
from
when
I
was
born
They
make
me
violate
them
No
matter
who
they
are
Get
down
on
your
knees
Get
a
good
head
on
shoulders
If
it's
for
your
guys
earth
Do
what
you
think
Give
it
with
dedication
I'll
put
out
your
misery
You
made
a
mess
For
Crist
sake,
this
rotten
world
Shit
out
of
luck
Go
with
my
vision
Light
on
the
fire
Ride
on
your
power
Weapon...
I
have
it
all
The noose hanging at the edge of town...
warns all who wish to go further.
If you pass through this gate, you will be automatically marked as a reckless one.
Villains among villains from around the world gather, butting up against each other in this city.
An evil city born between the East and West...
during the Cold War, and fed by the invasion of a continent that uses drugs as its secret weapon.
The end of this world...
this crucible of hypocrisy...
resides the living souls that have already been destroyed and sent to Hell.
The only reason I have survived is because I am with the fairly well known Lagoon Company.
The name of this city is whispered amongst all the villains of the world.
But many of those who come to make a name for themselves, never set foot in their homeland again.
A cruel fate awaits any small-time crook, accidentally stepping foot into Roanapur.
Right now, there is a sacrificial lamb who has wandered into this city.
All right then, guys! The night's just right.
To a senseless 1,000 dollar-a-head job!
Alright, let's head out!
Hey.
What are we waiting here for?
By my calculations, about one million dollars.
Like there's really such a great deal.
I bet it's just gun-fighting. A gun-fight is coming.
I'd be grateful for a gun-fight.
That rotten nun's just blinded by her own greed.
Who's gonna come? No one's coming.
Don't get all tough just because you're bored, Revy.
This is a  no-problem situation.
Right, pretty boy?
But it's going to be a gun-fight, right?
Come on Rock, it's not like you're going to get a new hole put in you.
Hey Eda, can I crack your jaw?
Oh my, jealousy isn't like you.
But, it's about time. I guess I can tell you what's going down in a certain place in Roanapur.
You bitch.
Of course, that certain place is the Ramsap Inn.
The place I told that girl about.
Right about now, a bunch of scoundrels are rushing right in there.
Probably something like this.
But the room they raid will be the one next to hers.
Why would a convenient thing like that happen?
That's because I told them it was the room next to hers.
The stupid woman will hop up because of the gun fire, and she'll run to the hallway to see what's going on.
Well, in that situation, of course she would.
That woman's sense of observation is devastatingly bad.
Right?
Especially since that room is the only one behind a fireproof wall.
When she opens the door, she'll be directly facing those bastards.
The scoundrels wouldn't have realized that there's a room behind the fireproof wall, or so I think.
It's like you've collected all the "ifs" in the world for this story.
Come on now. If she gets killed now, that's the end of the story.
Despite being useless, she'll shut the fireproof door.
It'll buy her time,  but only a little.
But when the guys break through the door and burst into the room,
it'll be empty.
Why? Like it'll be that convenient, you moron.
I told her how, you see.
If you sprawl back on the bed even once...
you'll be able to see.
Although you only understand its meaning when the time comes.
That's way too simple. Like the graffiti in bathrooms.
Look up.
Look down.
Jackass.
What? It's way better when it's simple!
Brett Favre: Record-holding NFL quarterback for the Green Bay Packers
Anyway! After that, she'll be able to make a touchdown like Brett Favre.
As long as she escapes like the signs tell her.
How's that sound?
I shouldn't have come with you.
Let's go home, Rock. Turn the key.
All right.
Wait a sec, Revy,  that room's worked four times out of seven!
See, see, see? Bingo! Go after her, Rock!
Hey Sis.
Jogging this late at night? How hard working of you.
You! Y-you tricked me!
How disrespectful. How can you talk like that to your guardian angel?
Screw you! I thought I was going to die!
Oh really? Do you want us to save you?
Think hard.
If you don't want to hand over the plates, I guess we don't have a choice.
You'd better run to a mosque next time. Whaddya think?
How low can you go, really?
30,000 dollars!
Rock, it's almost my bedtime. I'm going back to the church.
You monster! 100,000!
Don't insult me.
Look, they're after you.
All right! I'll go with your conditions!
All right, contract complete.
If you don't actually save me...
I'll haunt you.
If I did anything more evil, I'd only scare away customers.
Hey Eda! What are you doing here?
What's up?
You guys going for a late night walk too?
We have business with that woman there!
A senseless 1,000 dollar-a-head job.
That's a nice way to get pocket change.
How about it Eda, you want...
You bitch!
What do you mean bitch, dipshits?
This is a big million-dollar job.
From here on out, she's our job.
We're her recently purchased get-away driver and bodyguard.
Revy, eat 'em up!
Get the cars! After them!
Get 'em!
We're getting onto the main road!
This is our job, Rock! We're going to the ocean!
God damn it!
Look like things get complicated.
Complicated doesn't cover it.
It's the Church of Violence and the gun-woman from the Lagoon Company.
This isn't the same as going after one little amateur.
Deer hunting's turned into tiger hunting.
What are you doing? You need to get after them!
Cowboy! The situation's changed.
Unless you up to 30,000 a head, we all leave.
What? Fuck off!
I heard two punks are on her side. 30,000 for that?
You're all unbelievable pussies!
Cowboy, this no Florida. This Roanapur.
Understand what I say?
The enemies are not like punks you know that graffiti all over the walls and get excited.
That includes us.
We kill and be killed for food.
If you want stay stingy, then do it with your men alone.
Understand what I say?
So you're full of confidence. I hope it's not just bravado. But wait a second.
The way you go on, it sounds like you know them.
Of course I know them.
Anyone who doesn't know about those two is just a mole, yes you are Cowboy!
You better hurry and call Lobos.
Got it?
If you do, then we have deal.
Where? Where are you taking me now?
Is it another trap?
Even if you want to add more conditions...
I won't do anything so roundabout.
I'll take you directly to the get-away vehicle.
Once you're in, you get to say goodbye to wonderful Roanapur.
As soon as you can, please.
Eda, you promised me cash.
Yeah, it's been ready.
The ocean? A port? A boat?
Is that boat fast?
Why don't you ask the handsome man in the necktie?
Eda...
Well, you'll see it in a minute.
Don't be amazed, it's a torpedo...
I'm sorry Eda, but you won't see the boat.
This isn't what you promised!
The most important thing isn't here!
Yeah, we're in the middle of receiving an order.
They got a rush job in, a little while ago.
Want something to drink?
It's all piss.
Ardbeg: a single malt Scotch Whiskey produced on the island of Islay
I see that you've got Ardbeg Providence. Gimme that.
Don't be stupid. That's Dutch's
You lick that even once, I'll headbutt you and shove a beer up your ass.
Stingy.
How about Jim Beam? We have plenty of that.
If you're going to keep on being picky, then drink toilet water, you idiot.
Revy, is Eda there too?
Yeah, she is.
Sorry for interrupting.
That's fine. Let's start where we left off.
So the situation is neither good nor bad, right?
OK, we've got all the goods.
Yeah, that's it.
We have Eda and we have weapons.
I've even accounted for the two useless lumps.
Worse and worse. Wait a sec, Benny's here.
I know we just got it, but lets dump what we've got. We'll be able to get to the port a little faster.
I guess we have no choice. We'll have to pay for breaking the deal, too.
I'll contact Isaac about that from here.
Anything and everything will be covered by the Church of Violence.
It's not much. It'll be fine.
What is that woman up to?
Her? She's been in the storage room since she got here.
She hasn't been out for a moment since.
Space. Box.
TSIG root authority.
Auto-I.
192, 168, DNS Server?
Is this it?
No good. The boat shell's being rebooted.
I can't believe I can't get into my own bank.
Way to go, Teo. I'm in big trouble, thanks to your skills.
Sorry Dutch, I'm really sorry.
It's okay, Lobos.
He's from my country, and I'm having trouble with him too.
The don't realize they're just country bumpkins in the world of the lawless.
Of course they don't.  Villains among villains come to Roanapur.
Hell, even we've been tainted by it enough.
The need to be refined by real villainy.
So please, give me more time.
All right.
Benny boy, did you hear that?
Yea, everything.
They're playing with fire around the demonic energy of that city. It's dangerous.
Let's just hurry.
Of course.
But, everyone and anyone is tainted by the villainy of this city.
I always thought Rock and I were exceptions.
What are you saying, Benny?
I sensed it all along... what's deep down inside you guys.
Thanks a lot.
Shit! How long is this going to take?
One more try.
TSIG, root authority.
It's from here that...
You forgot to say, "good evening."
You fucking idiots.
Damn it!
What's up with that? They're using our car as a shield!
Sorry for your loss.
God damn it!
We only just got it fixed after that god damned maid tore it up!
Hey! It's leaking gas!
You did it.
Rock!
Damn it, new guys!
Rock, can you make it to the back door with that woman?
I'll give it a try. As long as you hold them there.
Leave it to me!
All right, let's go!
Wait!
Come on!
That's pretty manly of him!
He's still got a long way to go.
Over here!
It's no good, Revy!
What's wrong, Rock?
What are you doing?
Hurry up! Hurry up and shoot her!
I can't! I don't have a gun.
Are you stupid or something?
I've often wondered...
Rock!
Rock! God damn it!
Hey, Revy!
Rock!
Damn it.
Are you all right?
No comment.
No, come back! That door leads down to the dock!
You've got to be kidding!
If I stay up here...
it wouldn't matter...
how many lives...
Hi! I've got a favor to ask.
Will you let me pass?
Do you like grill parties, missy?
Rock!
Rock, get away from her!
Shoot! Shoot 'em up!
Revy, the guys across the street are getting loud.  Isn't there anything you can do?
Hey, woman! Give that box to her!
What's this?
If you've got something this nice, bring it out to begin with, you monkey.
It was for sale!
Doesn't matter! We've only got one life!
Damn it!
Now, hurry!
You too, Revy!
Go on ahead, Rock!
Damn. If we stick our heads out, we'll just be targets.
The same with the font door, too.  There were two or three snipers just waiting.
Something smells burnt.
Damn it. That's just not fair.
Some idiot set fire to the dock exit.
We really have no choice but to go to the roof.
Bad idea, that'll be our last stop.
I know. But, it's the same for the bad guys.
Their money maker will be burnt down to the ground along with the building.
And what would you do if you were them?
Go in and take out the guards, of course.
What about the timing?
They'll spray us all at once any second now.
Once we're pinned down, they'll rush in.
Now, we're not just going to sit and wait.
Revy!
That you, Shenhua?
Oh! Good guess!
Who's that? A friend of yours?
She's the worst to have as a cut-in.
"Yes it is" lady, is your partner here?
Oh, Legarch? He relaxed too much and finally couldn't get back home from Mars.
He's living happily with his live-in nurse.
That's a shame!
Eda, listen up.
Then tell him "hi" for me!
OK!
She's using the duct as a foothold.
Yeah, but we still have other problems.
The fire down below isn't a joking matter anymore.
Damn it. It's only a matter of time.
We won't last forever.
I hate endurance contests.
I'll draw her out before she draws us out.
I'll chase out the fox on the duct to the front door.
Can you nail her?
Of course, blockhead. If you draw her out, I could do that before breakfast.
Then, here I go.
Got it.
She's headed that way!
What do we do now?
I'm thinking about it.
We can't go up any higher. Do you have a plan?
So that was your plan? How dependable of you.
How about we pray and pray and pray to make a golden chain rain down?
Shut up.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm here to take your life!
My name is Wizard, Rotton the Wizard!