We're going live in...
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Ribbit?
Ri... Ri–Ri–Ri–Ri~
Ribbit Ri~bbit!
Everyone watching Frog-chan TV,
thank you for waiting!
Everyone's favorite show,
"Gero-Gero Kitchen"
starts right after the news, ribbit!
Ribbit ri~bbit.
Ribbi-pah!
All right, the program blurb is done.
Okay! The show's going to
start soon, so go get changed.
Gero Gero Kitchen
Members of 765 Pro
Right!
It's so hot!
This is the first time I've
worn a costume like this.
Ganaha-san, what are you doing?
It kind of smells a bit.
H–Hey, Hibiki-chan!
Don't smell that!
To think they would have us
wear something so strange...
I would never have dreamed.
Takane-san...
But don't you like it?
Ribbi-pah.
Look, what we want out of newbies, see
is this kind of gah!  and like guh!  and then like bam!  sorta thing.
So make sure they really give it to me.
Okay! I understand.
You got that? You gotta like, surprise me!
Kinda like 765-sa~n, see.
I'm coming in.
You're not dressed yet?
No, not yet. I'm sorry, Producer-san!
We need you ready soon, please.
Look, just get changed. Quick!
What's wrong?
We can't get changed because
you're here, Producer-san!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I’m sure, I can’t fail, I’m number one
Start hajimaru kyou no Suteeji
Start, today’s live is beginning
Check maiku meeku ishou ni Showtime
Check my mic, makeup, outfit, then it’s showtime!
Try challenge!
I’ve got to challenge myself
Stardom hikari hikaru Spotlight
The light of stardom, the shining spotlight
Mabushii kagayaki massugu Debut
It sparkles brilliantly like the path before me
Yume wa kanau mono
A dream is something that needs to come true
Watashi shinjiteru
That’s what I believe
Saa ichi ni tsuite Let’s go
So get on your mark, let’s go
Yeah!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Uta wo utaou!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s sing a song!
Hitotsu hitotsu egao to namida wa
Every last smile and tear
Yume ni naru Entertainment
make up the entertainment that becomes a dream
Are you ready? I’m ready! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I’m sure, I can’t fail, I’m number one
Episode 4
To Change Yourself
Got it?
Even if it's a cable TV program with only a couple of affiliates,
TV is TV.
This modest first step
will surely one day lead
to the pinnacle of idoldom!
Probably!
Only probably...?
Right, Producer!
Right?!
Just stand out the best you can here.
We've got to show everyone that 765 Pro exists!
Yeah!
...and that's where you gah!  and like guh! and then like bam!
Like that, okay?
Okay!
Okay...?
Okay, thanks!
Thank you very much!
All right, let's do our best!
Haruka, did you understand how the program will go from that explanation just now?
U–Um, I didn't really understand it.
Haruka, you didn't get it at all?
I can't believe you.
I'm sorry.
...Huh?
Hibiki, you said "okay" too, didn't you?
Ah, no, I didn't get any of that, either.
Then what should we–
Hamuzou...
Me and Takane, Haruka and Chihaya form two teams and compete in a cooking battle show.
I get it. So the one who wins the game gets bonus ingredients.
Then we have to put everything into that game, huh?
All right!
Hamuzou is kind of amazing, huh?
Sure. Hamuzou loves this show, so he watches it every week.
We're live in five minutes!
Girls!
Don't get too nervous, okay?
J–Just be your usual selves.
Right!
Chihaya, what's wrong?
It seems like they cut the song after all.
That's right, sorry.
It looks like the composition of the show got changed in a hurry.
But in exchange it seems they'll extend the cooking segment, so make do with that.
What, you don't like cooking?
Not particularly...
It must be tough like that
when you're living alone, too.
Chihaya, you live alone?
Producer-san, you didn't know?
No...
Stand-by, please!
I–In any case, loosen up before you go!
Look, it's starting.
Kuma-chan
Burger Set
Limited time offer!
Kuma-chan
Burger Set
I can't settle down.
O–Otonashi-kun, are we ready to record?
Yes, we're fine.
Is that right!
A–Ah, O–Otonashi-kun, it's recording in high-resolution mode, right?
It's not often everyone appears on TV,
so it would be a waste in long-play mode!
It's okay!
Gero-Gero Kitchen!
I really love this show! I watch it every week.
I should have known, Kotori-san. You love these niche shows.
Not more than anyone else!
That's right!
We need Yoshizawa-kun to watch, too!
I'd like him to write up a real
hot article for us, after all.
Otonashi-kun, could you contact him for me, please?
Chief, would you please calm down a little?
We can't watch the TV in peace!
Chief, it's starting already, so let's just watch quietly.
A–Ah, I suppose you're right.
Now then, this week's guests are
these fine ladies right here from 765 Pro!
Okay...
Then let's get started!
Bonus fight!
Go~!
I got it, ribbit~!
We have a winner!
The Toad Team is victorious!
Our first bonus ingredient is...!
Wha–Wha–Wha–Wha–Wha
What a shock, it's lobster!
On the other hand, the losing
Team Tree Frog's ingredient is...?
Oh my. What a let-down, it's sakura shrimp!
Tiny!
Chihaya-chan, don't let it get to you!
Otome yo taishi wo idake!!
Young lady, aim high!!
Young Lady, Aim High!
Lyrics: yura  Composition: Shirato Yuusuke  Arrangement: Kageie Jyun
Yume mite suteki ni nare
Dream your dreams and become lovely
Otome yo taishi wo idake!!
Young lady, aim high!!
Koi shite kirei ni nare
Fall in love and become beautiful
Tachi agare
Rise up
Onna shokun
Ladies
Hai!
Yeah!
All right! I'm gonna take this big ol' lobster and slather it with bitter melon sau–
Whoa, Nellie! Don't finish that sentence, contestant Ganaha!
Mezamashi jirijiri
The alarm clock goes ring, ring
We don't want any spoilers!
Gakkou ni mata girigiri
Barely on time for school again
But it looks like you're in high spirits, Team Toad!
Hamigaki Meiku
Brush my teeth, make-up
Yep!
How about it?! Think you can win?
...tte chikoku shichau
...I'm going to be late
Ittekimasu!!
I'm heading out!!
Dasshu chuu ni Meeru chekku
Check email while dashing
Only God knows who shall be the victor.
Rasshu chuu ni Burogu chekku
Check some blogs while rushing
I can only do the best I can.
Nakanaka yo no naka mo
isogashikute taihen
It's tough when the world is so busy
Hm! Either contestant Shijou is one big mouse, or she's got time to spare!
It's hard to tell from that poker face!
Watashi-ryuu kakugen sono ichi!
A proverb straight out of my book, number one!
"Isogaba massugu susunjyaou"
"If you're in a hurry, run forward
and don't stop"
Chihaya-chan! Beat the eggs, please!
Mou sugu nakama to kimi ni aeru yo
Soon I can see my friends and you
What's on the menu?!
E–Egg custard.
Otome yo taishi wo idake!!
Young lady, aim high!!
Well then! Red egg custard,
yellow egg custard, blue egg custard!
Jyugyouchuu Zzz... tto yume michae
I'm dreaming all class long
Can you say that?
...Huh?
C'mon, c'mon! Don't be such a stick in the mud!
Otome yo taishi wo idake!!
Young lady, aim high!!
Okorare rouka de koi bana
Talking about love after being sent
to the hallway
Let's see, the shrimp are...
Where were the shrimp?
Otome yo taishi wo idake!!
Young lady, aim high!!
Weren't they in the pot?
Ah, that's right!
Tesuto wa Chatto soudankai
Tests are the time to consult all my friends
Otome yo taishi wo idake!!
Young lady, aim high!!
Asobi mo manabi nandayo
Playing is learning, too
Tachi agare
Rise up
Onna shokun
Ladies
Whoa, nice reaction!
I did it again...!
Houkago wa Baito
After school is my part-time
How about it, contestant Kisaragi?
Your partner is making herself out to be the Rajah of Reaction over there!
Micchiri shuu go de Faito
Packed tight in five days a week, let's go
Excuse me, but just what's so funny?
Raigetsu kimi no Birthday
Next month is your birthday
...Eh?
S–So sorry about that!
I keep tripping, even when
the ground is perfectly level...
Amami Haruka, still going strong!
Oh~ I like that positivity!
Instead of a Dojikko, let's call you a Posikko!
And so, the completion of Team Toad's shrimp steak
and Team Tree Frog's egg custard finishes dish number one!
Judge 1
Judge 2
Judge 3
It's evaluation time for the judges!
Judge 1
Judge 2
Judge 3
There's a brief moment of commercials for everyone in their living rooms.
Following that we'll have you
watch our touching melodrama,
the gardener's teacher-student affair, "Red Shears of Passion."
We'll be back after that!
It'll be Gero-Gero Kitchen again!
That's right!
This week, the student is
approached by a client's wife...
I wonder if Chihaya is all right...?
But in fact, his teacher was–!
...And we're clear!
Let's take a short break!
Hey, Chihaya.
What happened, Chihaya?
It was nothing, really.
Was there some kind of problem?
Something happened, right? Tell me about it.
I just thought
I'd get to sing.
Oh, is that it.
But you know, if we make an impression here,
even a music show wouldn't be–
Do you really think so?
I just can't see this job
tying into a chance to sing.
Chihaya...?
765-san?
You're putting me on the spot, here.
It doesn't feel like it has any energy.
I'm sorry.
Put everything you've got into the second half, okay?
Kinda like 765-sa~n, see.
Where's Chihaya?
Huh? Wasn't she in the dressing room?
...Takane?
...Sorry for interrupting.
Chihaya...
Where did you go?
You didn't leave, did you?
Do you know what that would do to us?
Aoi tori
Bluebird
Moshi shiawase
Even if happiness
Chikaku ni attemo
Were to be close by
Ano sora he
I would fly
Watashi wa tobu
Into that sky
Mirai wo shinjite
Believing in the future
Anata wo wasurenai
I won't forget you
Demo kinou ni wa kaerenai
But we can't return to yesterday.
...Producer!
I was looking for you, Chihaya.
U–Um...
You really love to sing, don't you, Chihaya?
I fell in love just listening.
So? Feel any better after singing some?
Yes.
Just a little, though.
Well, I guess
I need to work hard enough that
more singing jobs come your way.
It might be too much to ask for right away...
but one day, for sure.
Producer...
We should probably get back.
Um...
Please watch over us in the second half, too!
I'm expecting a lot from you.
Kisaragi Chihaya.
Do you know what the ultimate spice in an exquisite dish is?
It is the heart.
I mean to put your heart into it.
Is putting your heart into making a delicious meal
not similar to singing a song?
I believe that trying to express one's feelings to the recipient with all your might
is just the same.
Hey, hey, did you know?
They said we can eat the food we make after the show!
So I'm going to make all three of you my best cooking!
Right, Hamuzou?
You just wait!
Yeah!
Chihaya-chan! Let's go!
Um... Haruka.
To be honest, I can't cook very well...
No problem, no problem!
Leave it to me!
I'm pretty confident when it comes to coo–
I tripped again...
Um... Haruka.
What is it?
Thanks for covering for me earlier.
Sure.
And here's our turbulent start!
Here comes dish number two!
The theme is Testing Patience!
...I mean, Mom's Cooking!
Chihaya-chan, get the soy sauce for me?
Here!
...Huh? Isn't this Worcestershire?
What do we do?
We're fine.
We're just fine!
Salsa sauce, and...
Sliced Cheese
melted cheese make...
Tah-dah!
Western-style meat and
potato stew, ready to serve!
Haruka, that's amazing...
Okinawa Slice!
Oh?
Tree Frogs
Toads
Yahoo!
Once again, it's Beach Flag Time!
Chihaya-chan, could you?
Yes!
Last out of the gate...!
Hup!
Haruka, I got it!
Chihaya-chan, say it! You know, that!
Huh?
The show's one-liner!
Chihaya! You must say it!
You can say it. Come on.
I–I–
I got it, ribbit~!
You did it!
Now then! Team Tree Frog's bonus ingredient is...?!
Eh? What is this?
Is it alive?
What if it starts moving...?
I did it again...
Wha–Wha–What is this!
Their bonus ingredient is durian!
Just how will they prepare this
temperamental uncrowned King of Fruits?!
Final dish... start!
But... this smell...
Yeah...
It... It stinks!
Haruka, is this enough?
Yeah, that's fine.
Cooking time is up!
Okay~!
We of Team Toad have made
a Lively Lobster Bake, a Bitter Melon Champloo,
and Takane's Southern Paradise Steamed Mango Buns.
Well, Team Tree Frog made Wobbling Egg Custard,
Mistakes are the Origin of Success Meat and Potato Stew,
and a Dripping Durian in Coconut Milk for dessert!
Now then,
who will the Goddess of Cooking smile upon...?!
Toad
Tree
Oh–
Team Toad wins!
We did it!
Magnificent, Team Toad! Just magnificent!
That's a shame, huh, Chihaya-chan?
I guess so.
Let's meet again next week!
Ready, and...!
Frog-Channel
Ribbit ribbit~!
Ah, that was fun!
Members of 765 Pro
Gero Gero Kitchen
765-san!
Hey, that was great!
There was this kind of... ga-ga-ga-ga!
rise to the excitement in the second half.
Do you think so?
Nice going, 765 Pro-san!
You made me a fan!
Thank you very much.
Give me a call any time.
Well then, see ya! Thanks!
Thank you very much!
Producer-san!
Good work, everyone.
Takane...
You can't bring that back. Just so you know.
Haruka... Sorry about today.
Did you do anything you'd need to apologize to me for? I forgot.
I caused a lot of trouble for you.
No, not at all.
I made a lot of mistakes too, after all.
Tehe.
I had a lot of fun cooking with you, Chihaya-chan.
Chihaya-chan?
I guess in the end, I really...
Really?
That is truly a wonderful idea.
What, what?
Producer said he'll treat us to dessert!
All right! I'll come!
You all worked hard today, after all.
Let's see, what would be good...
H–Hey, let's keep it inexpensive, okay?
Chihaya-chan, you should come too!
No, I'm going home. I'm sorry, Producer.
I see.
I'll be going, then.
Good work today.
Oh, that's right.
Here, put these on.
Thank you.
Chihaya lives alone, right?
Yes. I heard she lives alone due to circumstances with her family.
I don't really know anything about any of you, do I?
Naku koto nara tayasui keredo
Though it would be simple to cry
Kanashimi ni wa nagasarenai
I won't be swept away by sorrow
Koi shita koto
That I was in love
Kono wakare sae
Even parting this way
Eranda no wa
Was a choice
Jibun dakara
I made myself
Mure wo hanareta tori no you ni
Like a bird separated from its flock
Asu no yuki saki nado shiranai
I know not where tomorrow leads
Dakedo kizutsuite
But even hurt
Chi wo nagashitatte
And shedding blood
Itsumo kokoro no mama
I simply follow my heart
Tada habatakuyo
And take wing
Aoi tori
Bluebird
Moshi shiawase
Even if happiness
Chikaku ni attemo
Were to be close by
Ano sora he
I would fly
Watashi wa tobu
Into that sky
Mirai wo shinjite
Believing in the future
Anata wo wasurenai
I won't forget you
Demo kinou ni wa kaerenai
But we can't return to yesterday
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
This is Kisaragi Chihaya.
If possible, I'd actually prefer
you didn't watch next week,
but I couldn't possibly
ask such a thing...
Um, everyone, at least
close your eyes half-way!
Summer Break with Everyone
Look forward to it!