Idol: Kisaragi Chihaya's hidden secrets.
"Onee-chan."
Her little brother, attempting to reach his older sister, Chihaya,
was hit by a car and
departed this world.
Chihaya was eight at the time.
According to testimony
from those at the scene,
Chihaya didn't even try to
help her little brother.
She merely watched from afar.
Why did she simply
watch her brother die?
Chihaya
CosX
CM rec
KISARAGI CHIHAYA'S HIDDEN SECRETS
Kisaragi Chihaya truly seems to have simply watched her little brother die...
A cursed idol...
Affiliated with 765 Pro
KISARAGI CHIHAYA
Domestic collapse... What
has our princess of song
GONE THROUGH!?
The picture is of
Chihaya and her mother,
arguing before the eyes
of that very brother.
Incidentally, Chihaya's parents are divorced as of several months ago.
Death in an accident.
Domestic collapse. Divorce.
Misfortune builds upon
itself around her.
Placing a mask over that cursed reality,
Kisaragi Chihaya sings today once more,
in front of fans who know nothing.
What the hell?!
They say it like everything's
Chihaya's fault!
The very writing is
filled with malice.
I never knew Chihaya-san
had a little brother...
Haruka-chan, did you know?
No...
It's all true.
That I had a little brother.
That it's my fault he lost his life.
I had heard about your
brother from your parents,
but they said that you were simply there by
coincidence, and that you were not to blame.
Whatever my parents say,
it doesn't matter.
Sketchbook
If I– If I hadn't been there,
my brother wouldn't have
been in that accident.
Kisaragi-kun...
Chihaya...
I must  keep on singing.
On my brother's behalf, too.
Episode 20
Promise
They couldn't have imagined
a trump card like this.
765 Pro's– No, Takagi's bitter face is dancing before my eyes!
So this is how you do things?
What are you trying to say?
You already know!
I'm telling you not to
pull this petty crap!
The only one playing dirty
here is you, old ma–!
Who do you think you're talking to?
I thought I told you...
You lot just need to
shut up, follow orders,
and watch from the sidelines as Third-Rate Pro destroys itself.
There are no abnormalities in her throat,
nor is there anything
preventing her from vocalizing.
When it comes to this, "voice will not emerge when trying to sing,"
the origin is most likely
psychological in nature.
Though there are cases where
symptoms disappear with time,
this isn't something I can...
Yuu...
Sing!
Sing, Onee-chan!
My little brother was
the only audience I had.
Until that day.
"I must  continue to sing."
"I've got to keep singing. For Yuu."
That's how I felt.
But I can't sing for him anymore.
I'm a failure.
Both as an idol
and as an older sister.
Chihaya-chan...
Chihaya, you shouldn't
pressure yourself so much.
Let's put singing work on
the back burner for a while.
First, we'll give your
emotions a good rest–
Now that I can no longer sing,
I don't intend to continue
in this line of work.
Chihaya...!
But you might be able
to sing again, right?
No, I know you will!
So–
I apologize for all the disturbance.
Chihaya!
Chihaya-chan!
Wait!
I don't care anymore.
Are we live?! Sunday!
Are
We Live!?
Sunday
Chihaya's out with a cold today, so the two of us are coming to you live!
Yay! We're pulling out the stops!
Okay then! We're starting
today with this  segment!
Cameras have switched!
Chihaya won't pick up?
No.
When I go to her flat, she won't
even answer the door.
I do leave food so that
she keeps eating, but...
What about her parents?
Even when I explained
the situation to them,
they'd just repeat,
"We can't do anything."
Even though this is exactly the kind of time I'd like them to be her support.
Missed calls
At this rate, Chihaya won't even
make next month's regular concert...
KISARAGI CHIHAYA'S PAST, EXPOSED
Rumors of retirement surface with latest trouble!
765PRO AT THE CENTER OF MORE CHAOS?!
765 Pro again...
KISARAGI CHIHAYA
TROUBLE
Quarrel
in the
cemetery
Kisaragi
Chihaya-chan, are you
there? It's Haruka.
Do you need something?
Yeah!
I was wondering if you want to go to dance lessons together.
You know, it feels good when
you get your body moving!
I'm not going.
Oh, that's right!
I have some things from everyone.
Like tea, and throat lozenges
and all sorts of stuff.
I told them, "I can't carry all of that!"
but they kept going,
"And this! And this!"
I feel kinda like Santa Claus!
Just leave me alone.
I can't sing anymore.
I can't respond to
everyone's expectations.
Chihaya-chan...
Chihaya-chan, didn't you say you had to keep singing for your little brother?
Can't it be a little
simpler than that?
"Because I love to sing."
Can't you sing just
because you love to sing?
I can't see it like that
after all this time.
Chihaya-chan, don't you think you're
putting too much pressure on yourself?
Y–You should just say,
"I'll sing because I want to!"
It'll be easier on your feelings!
Stop it.
And then, if we could all sing
together again, we'd all be so happy...
And I just know your little brother up in Heaven would also–
Stop it!
Haruka, my feelings aren't–
Yuu's feelings aren't
something you could understand!
Stop being such a good Samaritan!
Excuse me...
Yes?
You're Amami Haruka-san, aren't you?
Yes...
I'm Kisaragi Chihaya's mother.
Huh...?
Um, if you'd like, the office is–
No, that's all right.
U–Um...
Um...
Pardon me.
Um, could you
Kisaragi Yuu
Sketchbook
pass this on to Chihaya?
Is this...?
It's my departed son's sketchbook.
Chihaya-chan's little brother's?
My son truly loved
to hear Chihaya sing.
He'd go on and on... "Sing! Sing!"
If she recalled the period
when they were close,
then maybe Chihaya could...
Um...!
Um, rather than having
me give it to her,
I think her mother
should give it to her!
I'm sure that way she would–
No. I–
If we were to see one another,
we'd surely just end up fighting.
B–But even when I tried to
cheer her up, I couldn't do it!
So instead of me,
I'm sure her mother could–
That's impossible.
I couldn't expect to regain
her trust after all this time.
Our relationship has
always been like this.
Stop being such a good Samaritan!
This is just about all I can do.
Please watch over her in my stead.
So she gave this to you and left?
Sketchbook
Kisaragi Yuu
I see.
We'll have to take care
of Chihaya after all.
Haruka?
You look pretty down.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Um... do I come off
as a "good Samaritan"?
Where'd that come
from all of a sudden?
Chihaya-chan said so...
She said to "Stop being
such a good Samaritan."
I'm always saying, "Let's do
our best!" "Let's do our best!"
Not just to Chihaya-chan,
but to everyone else, too.
I was just wondering if everybody
wanted me to mind my own business...
That's not true!
Your optimism is your strong point!
You can't be considerate all the time when you cheer someone up!
But...
I was really happy when you gave me that caramel back then.
I really just wanted to start
over as everyone's friend.
I appreciated that, Haruka.
Producer-san...
You know, Haruka...
Chihaya might be a little awkward,
but I think she's someone who really does understand peoples' feelings.
Right!
Then everything's fine.
Your feelings have definitely
gotten through to her.
Go ahead and hit her with
everything you're feeling!
Okay!
Chihaya-chan's in every last one, holding a mic and smiling.
Did you draw those, Haruka?
Miki...
Not me.
Chihaya-chan's brother did.
So these are Chihaya-san?
Yeah.
But...
I don't think I've ever seen
Chihaya-san sing like this.
You haven't either, Miki?
Yeah.
"I must continue to sing."
"I've got to keep singing. For Yuu."
No. I want to leave Chihaya's
spot until the last minute.
But if she loses it in front of the fans,
won't that really make
her lose all confidence...?
I know.
But I think we have a chance before
she convinces herself she can't do it.
And if it's the regular concert,
the risk won't be too...
Producer-san!
Haruka...
Um... I want your opinion on something.
It seems Kisaragi Chihaya
is still on a leave of absence.
THE TRUTH BEHIND
KISARAGI CHIHAYA'S SILENCE
Well, let's see...
When things stretch into
this long a time-frame–
Chihaya-chan...?
It's me.
Haruka.
Actually, there's something
I wanted to give you today.
Could you open the door?
Kisaragi
I don't want anything.
Just leave me alone.
I won't leave you alone.
I won't leave you alone!
Because I want to keep
working with you, Chihaya-chan!
I want to stand together
onstage and sing!
Maybe I am a "good Samaritan."
But even then!
I want you to stay an idol!
Then I'll leave this in your mail slot.
Make sure you look at it!
Dear Chihaya-chan,
It's a little sudden,
but we have a new song.
Everyone at 765 Pro
pitched in to write the lyrics,
and we asked a composer
to set it to music.
We all thought of how we could convey our feelings to you,
and "Of course! Let's put it in music!"
Everyone was happy to help.
It's our first time writing lyrics,
so they might not be very good.
But each of us, one by one, placed our honest feelings for you into this song.
If we could all sing this
song we wrote together,
and if we could get you to smile,
like the girl in the pictures
your little brother drew...
Sketchbook
Kisaragi Yuu
Also... you might get mad at me again,
Onee-chan
but I wonder if your brother didn't
necessarily just want to hear you sing,
but if he just wanted
to see you smile.
Onee-chan
A girl who loves to sing,
and when she sings, she smiles.
Don't you think that's
the big sister he loved?
And finally, a P.S.
from Producer-san:
"You're in the schedule
for the regular concert.
"The fans, and we, are waitin' for ya."
Or so he says.
~Poker face
~a poker face with my lips
Yo toudai moto kurashi Do you know!?
Yo! It's dark at the bottom of the lighthouse! Do you know!?
Girigiri de oazuke Funky girl
That funky girl cuts bait just at the last moment
Yes. That was fine for me.
Roger that!
Um, excuse me!
Right here, I'm constantly
on the verge of tripping up...
Roger. We'll check.
Okay! Please do!
Heart of the Marionette
Promise
Pre-encore pause
Encores
Producer!
Has Chihaya...?
No. Not yet.
So Chihaya won't–
Hey, everyone!
Let's circle up like always!
Okay?
Yeah!
Here we go!
765 Pro–
Wait a second!
S–Sorry I'm late.
Chihaya!
Chihaya-onee-chan!
Chihaya. I'm so glad you came.
Producer...
So... Think you can do it?
I'm not sure.
But at the very least, I–
Haruka...
Chihaya-chan.
Now let's get that hand.
Here goes!
765 Pro–
Fight–
Yeah–
Everyone! You having a good time?!
Haruka?
Um... I said such terrible–
Let's not get into that! Okay?
I thought, "I want to sing,"
when I saw the lyrics everyone
wrote together and Yuu's drawings...
Yeah.
I wonder if I'll be able to smile?
I'm not sure if I'll be
able to sing, though.
I thought to myself,
"I want to give it another chance."
Yeah.
Thank you.
Chihaya.
It's almost time.
Okay.
Everything's fine.
Just stay relaxed.
Okay.
You're on.
Yeah.
It's Chihaya-chan!
Chihaya?
She's coming on today?
Is that even safe?
Sketchbook
Chihaya...!
I knew she couldn't...!
Excuse me! Please stop
everything for a moment!
H–Haruka!
W–Wait!
Stop!
Just let her.
Please let them keep going!
I knew it.
I knew I couldn't...
Nee ima
You know, right now
Promise
Mitsumete iruyo
I'm watching you
Hanarete itemo
Even if we're apart
Haruka...
Mou namida wo nugutte waratte
So wipe your tears and smile
Hitori jyanai donna toki datte
You're never alone
Yume miru koto wa ikiru koto
To dream is to live
Kanashimi wo koeru chikara
The power to overcome grief
Everyone...!
Arukou
Let's walk
Hatenai michi
The unending path
Utaou
Let's sing
Sora wo koete
And overcome the heavens
Omoi ga todoku you ni
So that our hearts reach one another
Yakusoku shiyou
Let's promise
Mae wo muku koto
To face forward
Thank you for smile
Okay.
Arukou
Let's walk
Yes!
Hatenai michi
The unending path
Utaou
Let's sing
Sora wo koete
And overcome the heavens
Omoi ga todoku you ni
So that our hearts reach one another
Yakusoku shiyou
Let's promise
Mae wo muku koto
To face forward
Thank you for smile
Nee me wo
You know, if I close my eyes
Tojireba mieru
I can see
Kimi no egao
Your smile
Kikoeteru yo kimi no sono koe ga
And I can hear that voice of yours
Egao misete kagayaite itteta
Your smile would shine when you told me
Itami wo itsuka yuuki he to
"Turn your pain into courage
Omoide wo ai ni kaete
"And turn your memories into love"
Arukou
Let's walk
Modorenu michi
The path of no return
Utaou
Let's sing
Nakama to ima
Together now with our companions
Inori wo
So that
Hibikasu you ni
Our prayers will roar out loud
Yakusoku suru yo
I promise
Yume wo kanaeru
Our dream will come true
Thank you for love
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
My, today's was
such a nice story!
I was so touched!
Chief! A review is
great, but right now–
Now then, let's drink the
night away at Taruki-tei!
Come on!
Like a Flower Blooming
Salarymen
have it tough!