Kimi ga fureta kara nana iro Button
Because you touched it, it's a rainbow button
Rainbow Button
Lyrics: Endou Fubito  Composition/Arrangement: Uchida Tetsuya
Ami! Stop wobbling there!
Subete wo koi de someta yo
It dyes everything with the color of love
Right. Iori! Fingertips!
Donna dekigoto mo koete yukeru tsuyosa
And gives strength to overcome any event
Azusa-san, you're behind! Match them!
Kimi ga boku ni kureta
You gave it to me
No!
Get this. Don't let it get tedious.
Treat each run like the real thing.
And look at your surroundings.
Ami. You know what went
wrong just now, right?
Yep.
And Iori needs to watch her fingertips.
But I stretched them out just fine!
They weren't stretched!
They were! See?
More! Crisply!
Like this!
That's our former idol!
Showin' us how it's done!
Just beautiful!
Nihihi! Really, that's our former  idol!
Anyway, once more!
Next, we're doing a runthrough
of the top three songs!
All three of you together there!
Ami, don't lower your hand!
Ritsuko's strict as always.
But doesn't she look even
more pumped up than usual?
Otonashi-san was talking about it.
She says Ryuuguu Komachi
has a secret concert coming up.
So that's why.
'Scuse me a second.
What? I'm at work.
Wrong!
Once more, from the top.
Hey, how about a break?
Not yet.
And Iori. Your fingertips.
What's your problem?
What's wrong with them?
I told you, like this!
I'm doing that!
My, my.
No, you aren't. Like this!
I'm doing that!
Those four really get along well.
CHANGE! Ima wa kawaru sekai kagayake
Change! It's a changing world, shine!
CHANGE! Ima wa watashi no sekai
Change! It's my world
Watashi no mono CHANGE
It belongs to me! Change!
Kirameku Stage
The shining stage
Event gurabia CM
Events, photo shoots, commercials,
Terebi de Show time
Showtime on TV
Hajimaru tsuzuku Story
A beginning, a continuing story!
Nando eru chii demo
No matter how many times we attain this position
Donna Rival datte
No matter the rival
Makenaide Try again!
Don't give up and try again!
Tachi agaru Story
It's a story about standing up
Encore wa My life
My life is an encore
Ichido no Live
A once-upon-a-live
Susume dokomade mo
Keep moving forward and never stop
Show must go on!
The show must go on!
Three
Two
One!
CHANGE! Ima wa kawaranai yume egaite
Change! It's an unchanging dream we're drawing
CHANGE! Ima wo suki ni jiyuu ni
Change! It's a time to do what you want and be free!
Try lady!
Aim to be a lady!
CHANGE! Ima wo atarashii ni Live
Change! It's a time to start a new show
Oikakenagara
While we chase after
Watashi rashii watashi de
A me who's really me
Motto motto Your dream come true!
Keep trying, keep trying! Your dream will come true!
I love you all!
Episode 18
Lots of, Everything
It's no use. I can't move an inch.
My legs are so swollen!
Were you practicing your
choreography this whole time?
You girls are working hard!
It would seem you're
on track for finalization.
We're not close at all.
She keeps jumping at our
throats for every little thing.
Yeah, yeah.
In Ricchan's case, she's most
alive when she's drumming us.
I can hear  you.
There she is!
The Demon Drill Sergeant!
Who's a Demon Drill Sergeant?!
My, my.
I might be repeating myself...
Just five more days until
the secret concert, I guess.
How's the response looking?
Well, the fans are very  excited.
Let's see...
"I'm looking forward to the show!"
"I'll definitely be there!"
"I'll follow Ryuuguu forever!"
See?
These are all fan letters
for Ryuuguu Komachi?
Yes, from this month.
Ritsuko-san has been
working very hard, after all.
You're right.
She's steadily building–
Huh?
A picture?
Is this from Ritsuko's idol days?
Let's see here.
Give Grandpa a look!
Hey!
Wait a second!
Wait, this is from that mini-concert...
Where did you find it?
It was in this letter.
Looks like it's a fan letter
from a "Petit Bellpepper-san."
Just don't look anymore without asking!
Petit Bellpepper?
That's one of Ritsuko-san's diehard fans.
Knowing that Ritsuko-san
became a producer,
he's following Ryuuguu Komachi now.
That's some devotion.
Isn't it nice that he's been
behind you for so long?
Yes, I suppose so.
What's this?
Is that the face of someone who
wants to make an idol comeback?
Don't be ridiculous!
More importantly, we're going to put the
finishing touches on your dance tomorrow!
'kay–
Um, I'm feeling a little feverish.
I'm going to excuse myself first.
Will you be okay?
The concert is soon,
so please take care of yourself.
I will.
Make sure to take a lot
of vitamin C, and sleep!
Rest up as best you can.
I will.
Ritsuko-san is completely
in Producer-mode.
Yeah.
Hey, have you seen Azusa-san yet?
Not yet.
Isn't she just lost again?
Probably.
Yes, hello?
Azusa-san, where are you right now?
I'm sorry.
My fever just wouldn't go down,
so I went to the hospital just in case.
They said it's the mumps.
Mumps?!
Yes.
Then what about the show...?
It seems she has no choice but to rest until the fever and pain subside.
That normally takes four or five days.
We should probably think that
she can't come on stage.
Are we going to cancel the show?
We couldn't do that.
The fans are really looking forward to it.
The two of you will just
have to make do in her place.
That being the case, I'm sorry,
but we have an emergency situation.
We'll put on this show
with Iori and Ami,
just the two of them.
I hope you can all
help us follow through!
Kimi ga fureta kara nana iro Button
Because you touched it, it's a rainbow button
Subete wo koi de someta yo
It dyes everything with the color of love
We'll take out Azusa-san's solos for now,
Donna dekigoto mo koete yukeru tsuyosa
And gives strength to overcome any event
and increase the overall
number of songs instead.
But then I need to
rethink the order–
Kimi ga boku ni kureta
You gave it to me
Geez!
Be careful!
But–!
Are either of you hurt?
What happened?
Since Azusa isn't here,
we need to fill up the stage, right?
We were just trying to
emphasize our movements...
It's true that with the
dance the way it is,
the empty space will stand out.
We'll need to alter it somehow.
You're probably right.
But with so little rehearsal time,
it's just going to end up
feeling unnatural.
Hey.
Shouldn't we just get someone
to stand-in for Azusa?
That way we could use the
choreography the way we have it now.
Impossible!
There are only four days
until the concert!
We'd need someone who could memorize the entire song and choreography.
I guess.
Can memorize the song
and choreography...
And has experience
standing on stage.
Someone whose schedule fits...
And knows Ryuuguu Komachi inside and out.
Of course!
It'd never work!
Never never never!
Well, it's an emergency
situation, so just give up!
The fans are waiting, Ricchan!
M–Maybe, but–
I have to consider my
position as a producer–
Just ask Nii-chan to fill in!
You're the only person who can do it!
Resign yourself!
W–Wait a second!
This is the request of
a lifetime, Ricchan!
Please...
Give me some time to think...!
Ryuuguu Komachi Secret Concert Set List (1105 Revision)
Order
Song Name
SMOKY THRILL
Here we go!!
Start Star..oOO
Clear..
Their Memories
YOU ARE MY GUIDING STAR!
9:02pm
RIZORA
Daybreak Star Line
Mythmaker
Sweet Smile! First Bite
DIAMOND
L<>R
Lovely
Grab Her Heart!
Positive!
Beside Me...
Rainbow Button
Performer
Ryuuguu
Iorio
Amio
Azusa
Iorio
Amio
Azusa
Iorio
Amio
Azusa
Ryuuguu
Iorio
Amio
Azusa
Iorio
Amio
Azusa
Ryuuguu
Daybreak Star Line
Mythmaker
Sweet Smile! First Bite
Azusa
Ryuuguu
Mythmaker
Azusa
Daybreak Star Line
Sweet Smile! First Bite
DIAMOND
L<>R
Lovely
Grab Her Heart!
Positive!
Beside Me...
Rainbow Button
Ryuuguu
Iorio
Amio
Azusa
Iorio
Amio
Azusa
Ryuuguu
Keep the number of songs we
have and load up on talk time...
But doing just that
is really pushing it...
How was Azusa-san's condition?
I just called,
but it sounds like she's
just taking it easy for now.
I see.
So things like this really happen.
I suppose it's a good
experience for us, though.
You know, Ritsuko...
I heard from Iori and the others,
but why don't you go
perform at the concert?
Now even you're getting in on this?
Is it that surprising?
You've actually stood in
front of fans as an idol,
so if you'd like, I'd take on
your duties as Producer.
Stop that!
Let's forget this whole
thing ever happened.
Sheesh. You all act like
it's not your problem.
Okay, Honey.
I'm going home now.
Okay. Thanks for coming in.
Were you able to
memorize the song?
Yeah, for the most part.
That's right!
Hey, Miki. Would you want to perform in the show as Azusa's stand-in?
If we went with you, you could
memorize the song and dance in a flash.
And didn't you say a while ago that you wanted to join Ryuuguu–
I'm sorry.
What on Earth am I saying?
How convenient would that be?
I wouldn't mind doing it.
Really?!
But
the way I see it, it would be best if you did it, Ritsuko...san.
Why?
Because I think Ritsuko...san would fit better in Ryuuguu Komachi than Miki would.
Okay, I'm heading out!
Yeah. Good night.
When I became a Producer, I decided to stop splitting up my resources.
Because Ryuuguu Komachi was
the precious unit I first produced,
I decided I didn't want to be irresponsible by having a side job like being an idol.
Then why don't you think
about it like a producer would?
In order to make Ryuuguu
Komachi's concert a success,
who is the most viable
candidate at this point in time?
Don't you already
have your answer?
Donna dekigoto mo koete yukeru tsuyosa
And gives strength to overcome any event
Okay, stretch your fingertips!
You're behind! You're behind!
Next, we should go through
it with all three of us.
I guess so!
I can't! I can't! I can't!
But it's only been thirty minutes!
W–Well, yeah...
Kimi ga fureta kara nana iro Button
Because you touched it, it's a rainbow button
Subete wo koi de someta yo
It dyes everything with the color of love
Donna dekigoto mo koete yukeru tsuyosa
And gives strength to overcome any event
I get it already! Sheesh!
Kimi ga boku ni kureta
You gave it to me
I knew it. It's impossible.
In the first place, putting me on-stage in Azusa's place is just–
Yes?
Azusa-san!
I'm really so sorry.
I've caused you so much trouble...
N–No, don't say that...
But, even though you might
get mad at me for saying this,
I'm a little happy.
That you're going on
in my place, I mean.
Really, it's Iori-chan, Ami-chan,
then me and Ritsuko-san.
Diligence
The four of us make up
Ryuuguu Komachi, right?
Azusa-san...
We're just fine here,
so get better soon, okay?
I'll do my best,
so please leave the show to us!
Hey, Ricchan!
About your entrance at the concert...
Wouldn't it be great to storm
on-stage and then sing a solo?
No thanks!
I'm just a stand-in,
so I don't need a solo!
Not happening! We need impact!
Is there some song you want to sing?
No, there isn't!
I bet nobody even remembers
my songs from when I was an idol!
Ryuuguu
Komachi
-
Shoot
for
Top
Idol!!
What?
Well, it's not like I
don't have a single one...
See? I knew you had one.
Then that's settled.
W–Wait!
I just meant if  I was going to sing–
Okay, we're starting dress
rehearsal for tomorrow's show!
Please go ahead!
Kimi ga fureta kara nana iro Button
Because you touched it, it's a rainbow button
Subete wo koi de someta yo
It dyes everything with the color of love
Donna dekigoto mo koete yukeru tsuyosa
And gives strength to overcome any event
Kimi ga boku ni kureta
You gave it to me
Kimi ga fureta kara nana iro Button
Because you touched it, it's a rainbow button
Ritsuko?
Ricchan?
Excuse me!
Subete wo niji ni ka
It changes everything
Please stop the music!
What is it, Ritsuko?
Is there something wrong?
U–Um, no.
S–Sorry. It's my first rehearsal in
a while, so I got a little stage fright.
Sheesh. What are you getting
stage fright during rehearsal for?
Of course. Sorry, Iori, Ami.
One more time, please!
You're okay, right?
Yes.
"Otona ni nattara ne"
"When you become an adult"
Chotto yudan shiteru
You let your guard down
Ritsuko-san.
Ah, Kotori-san.
Kimi no yokogao wo ne
And I see your face
Practicing your steps?
But you might want to rest
your body for tomorrow.
Miteiru no yo mada ima demo
From the side, even now
Did they come again today?
Those fan letters for Ryuuguu.
They did.
They've been increasing
as the concert approaches.
Isn't it incredible?
I think it finally hit me today.
That Iori and Ami have gone so far ahead of me when I was an idol.
When I started thinking that I was going to stand on stage with girls like that,
I just...
Ritsuko-san...
What?!
Just what I said!
There are people we want
to invite to tomorrow's show!
Can you do something
about reserving their spots?
I think I could manage a few, but–
They hung up...
Yes?
Azusa-san!
Um, I have a request
regarding tomorrow's concert...
Just look at all of them!
They're all nice and pumped up.
This is it. Break a leg.
Of course!
We'll give 'em a kick in the teeth!
You too, Ritsuko.
Leave it to me!
W–What now?
I–I totally want to go home.
Okay. We're going on ahead.
We'll get them all
warmed up for your entrance!
S–Sure.
Everyone–!
Welcome to Ryuuguu Komachi's
Secret Concert!
We have a bit of disappointing news.
To be honest, due to a bout of sudden illness, Azusa couldn't come tonight.
We have a message straight
from her, so listen up!
A Message from Azusa
from
Everyone! Um, I'm sorry I
wasn't able to come tonight.
I can't stand up on stage, but I'm
sending all my love to you from here!
Azusa-san...
Did she do this herself?
Yeah.
She called yesterday to
say she'd recorded it,
and wanted me to come pick it up.
Additionally,
standing in for me today, a very
special guest has decided to join us,
so I hope you all enjoy the show!
Uh oh! Did those words
set off any alarm bells?
A special guest!
That's right!
Perfect for a "secret" show,
a very secret guest will arrive
on stage right after this!
When they get their hopes up,
the pressure just builds and builds...
This person is a precious someone whose existence keeps Ryuuguu Komachi afloat!
Though she's mega-scary
when she's mad,
she's always really thinking about us.
It's because of her support that we're standing here right now!
Our precious friend!
Iori... Ami...!
So let's introduce her!
Ryuuguu Komachi's producer,
and today, an idol from 765 Pro!
It's Akizuki Ritsuko!
My name is Akizuki Ritsuko!
I'll sing w–with all my heart today!
I hope you enjoy yourselves!
Okay, Ricchan!
Let's give this a shot!
The song is "Lots and Lots"!
Lots and Lots
Composition/Arrangement: Sasaki Hiroto
Lyrics: Nakamura Kei
My voice is so shrill...
My hands and legs are shaking...
Hanaseba wadai ni tsukinai kurai ni
We'd never run out of topics if we talked
I was nervous back then, too, wasn't I?
Tanoshiku futari no jikan sugoseru
We could enjoy spending our time alone together
It was my first stand-alone mini-concert.
Aa doushite watashi
Ah, why can't I
I managed to keep singing until the end because everybody got into this, my first song.
Kokoro gamae nashi dewa aenai no?
See you without steeling myself?
Though none of those
fans are here today,
if I just put my heart into it–!
Nee ippai ippai ippai ippai
Hey! Lots and lots and lots and lots
Aren't those...?
Anata no koe wo
I want to hear
Sou ippai ippai ippai ippai
Yeah! Lots and lots and lots and lots
Kikasete hoshii
Your voice
Mou zettai zettai zettai zettai
I'm sure sure sure sure
Petit Bellpepper-san brought
a good number of them!
Hokano hito yori
That my feelings for you
Nihihi!
Un zettai zettai zettai zettai
Okay! Sure sure sure sure
It was the right choice
to contact her fan club.
Suki dato omou
Are stronger than anyone else's
Mada sonna koto ienai kedo
But I can't tell you that yet
Saa saa
Come on, come on
Saa kigaru ni
Come on, take it easy
Saa saa
Come on, come on
The shaking stopped...!
Saa kamaezu
Come on, don't stiffen up
Saa saa
Come on, come on
Saa tsuyoki de
Come on, be confident
Saa
Come on
Saa ikouyo
Come on, let's go
Nee ippai ippai ippai ippai
Hey! Lots and lots and lots and lots
Anata no koe wo
I want to hear
Sou ippai ippai ippai ippai
Yeah! Lots and lots and lots and lots
Kikasete hoshii
Your voice
Mou zettai zettai zettai zettai
I'm sure sure sure sure
Hokano hito yori
That my feelings for you
Un zettai zettai zettai zettai
Okay! Sure sure sure sure
Suki dato omou
Are stronger than anyone else's
Nee ippai ippai ippai ippai
Hey! Lots and lots and lots and lots
Anata no koe wo
I want to hear
Sou ippai ippai ippai ippai
Yeah! Lots and lots and lots and lots...
Nice work out there.
Producer. Nice work yourself.
It was a great show.
How did it feel to see what
it's like to be an idol again?
Let's see.
Singing my lungs out on stage,
listening to the screaming fans...
To be honest, it might
have been pretty fun.
But this isn't the place I belong.
It's their job to bathe
in the light and sparkle.
My job is to make them
sparkle even more.
That became very clear to me.
I see.
Or something like that.
You never know what'll happen.
If I suddenly decide, "I can't forget how it feels to be on stage.
"I'm gonna make a
comeback as an idol!"
If that happens, I'm counting
on you to produce me.
See? The same place as before!
Iori! Stop making the same
mistake over and over!
I get it already!
Once more from the top!
What's her problem?!
She was shaking like a leaf on stage!
And now she's regressed into
the Demon Drill Sergeant.
I can hear  you.
Oh my, my.
Being a Demon Drill Sergeant is fine with me.
I'm going to train you
harder than ever before.
How does that work?!
Because I believe Ryuuguu Komachi will stand at the top some day!
Ryuuguu Komachi - Shoot for Top Idol!!
Right?
Cast a spell on me!
W–Well yeah, but...
Cast a special spell on me!
When you put it like that,
we can hardly afford to complain.
Okay, here we go!
Okay!
Kagami no naka tame iki ga hitotsu
I sigh into my mirror
"Kyoukashou ga Boyfriend?"
"Is that textbook your boyfriend?"
Minna iu kedo
That's what they all say
Tsukue no naka kakikake no Love letter
In my desk, there's a love letter I started writing
Mada minu anata ni omoi wo haseru
To show you my feelings, though you haven't seen it yet
Tsumaranai ko dato omou kashira?
Would you think I'm boring?
Hontou wa kono mune no doki doki sagashitainoni
In reality, I want to go off in search of the excitement in my heart
Koi wo yume miru ohime-sama wa
A princess who dreams of love
Itsuka sutekina ouji-sama ni meguri aeru
Will one day come across a handsome prince
Hayaku sonna hi ga kimasu youni
So that day will come sooner
Sotto hitomi wo tojiru kara
I'll close my eyes softly
Mahou wo kakete!
Cast a spell on me!
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
We had a real
Ritsuko-Fest this time!
W–Wait, Miki!
Let's talk about
next week instead, okay?!
The performance scene
was especially awesome!
Start talking about
next week already!
Like the Moon Hiding Between the Clouds