Okay!
Perfect weather!
It's the perfect–
day for a concert, isn't it?
Ch–Chief!
Hey! 'Morning.
Good morning.
I didn't know you were already here.
Of course I am.
It's the biggest show 765 Pro
has put on its history, after all.
Yes.
But how do I put it...?
Now that we've finally reached the
performance we've always dreamed of,
I'm as happy as can be!
I just can't put it into words!
No, we're just getting started.
This is the start point.
Is that right?
It's about time for our idols to arrive.
You're right.
It's about time...
What about Ritsuko-kun and her girls?
The four of them are coming
directly here from their recording.
Ah. I see.
Good morning!
'Morning!
Let's do our best today!
Of course!
We're aiming for the top!
Ryuuguu Komachi
Minase Iori
Futami Ami
Miura Azusa
Futami Mami
Takatsuki Yayoi
Shijyou Takane
Kikuchi Makoto
Amami Haruka
Kisaragi Chihaya
Hoshii Miki
Hagiwara Yukiho
Ganaha Hibiki
Dressing Room
Hey, hey, Yayoi-cchi!
Take a look at these!
They're so sparkly!
It's so big!
We're on the screen!
She was right.
What do you mean?
A long time ago,
my dad took me to a concert.
I was sitting in the very back.
Yeah.
And then,
the idol on stage said,
"We can see you all in back, too!"
You really can  see them.
I want to make today's show one the people in the very back
and the people in the very
front can enjoy just the same.
You're right.
Miki?
Producer.
What're you staring into space for?
I wasn't.
Really?
I wonder
if I can sparkle?
You'll be fine.
Hello?
Ritsuko? What is it?
A typhoon?
You're kidding, right?
It's sunny over here.
I mean it.
The rain and wind are already terrible here.
Yes, the bullet trains have all suspended service.
Look at that wind.
Looks like it would blow you off your feet.
'Tis the storm!
The storm cometh!
Sheesh. Why did it have to be today of all days?
Anyway, once we find a running train, we'll head your way.
We'll make sure we make the dress rehearsal.
Okay. Got it.
Huh? Because of a typhoon?
Yeah.
But even though they're going to be late,
we're going according to schedule, okay?
R–Right!
Everyone!
Take this opportunity to put something in your stomachs!
Thank you!
I wonder if Ritsuko-san and the girls are all right?
Yukiho, if you start worrying, we won't get anywhere.
But when I get nervous, I start
thinking about all kinds of things...
Yukiho, there exists an expression
relating to the "power of language."
I believe it would be wise to refrain from speaking of unlikely circumstances.
And also,
when I texted Ami a second ago,
see?
This is the reply I got back, so it's all good!
Received Message
Ami
What does that say?
Huh?
"The typhoon's crazy, but Ricchan is working hard,
so we're fine," it says.
They're fine, right?
They must be.
Yup!
Excuse me!
Everyone who's performing!
We'd like to do a dress rehearsal,
so please gather up in front of the stage.
Okay!
Excuse me,
could you turn the volume on my voice up?
Okay!
It's finally time.
Yes.
I wonder where Ritsuko-san's group is now?
I wonder, too.
Ah, Ritsuko?
How's it look? About where–
A car?!
Why?
All the trains are stopped,
so we got a rent-a-car, but...
now we have a flat tire.
A flat...?
Are you all right?
Yes, we're all fine.
I'm sorry. It doesn't look like we'll be able to participate in the rehearsal.
Yes, we'll get on the highway
and leave right now.
Got it.
I might be repeating myself,
but don't do anything danger–
Drive safely!
I'm sorry for causing such a headache for all of you.
We're going your way at full tilt!
Sorry for worrying you!
Well! If the super-idol Iori-chan doesn't go,
there just wouldn't be a point, right?
Anyway, just get here safely.
Okay!
All right!
Let's start rehearsal!
Right!
Thank you for waiting!
We'll be opening the doors in a moment!
Anyone buying goods, please enter from this way!
Hall-Exclusive Goods List
Show Pamplet
Hall-Exclusive
Glow Sticks
Ryuuguu Komachi Set
Special Use
light set
Ryuuguu Komachi
Debut Single
Hall-Exclusive Version
I'd like a Ryuuguu glow stick set, please.
Thank you very much.
From Ritsuko again?
They opened the doors!
Lots of people came to see you.
So they already let people in...
I'm starting to get nervous!
Sh–She said there are lots of people!
Yes.
One more hour until the show starts.
Producer!
Are Iori and the others here yet?
Tell us!
Can't forehead and the others perform?
It doesn't look like they're going to be in time for the main event.
I knew it!
Hey, what are we going to do?
It's bad if Ryuuguu Komachi isn't here, right?
The audience will be so disappointed.
Hey, Nii-chan!
We aren't going to cancel the show, are we...?
We won't cancel it.
Until Ritsuko's group arrives,
let's do whatever we can.
Miura
Azusa
Minase
Iori
Futami
Ami
We offer our sincerest apologies,
but please allow us to inform you of a change in the performance start time.
We are delaying the scheduled start of show by thirty minutes.
We will begin at 6:30PM.
What on Earth...?
Producer, excuse me!
What comes after My Best Friend?
It's I'm An Idol!
Thank you very much!
So we'll change the song order here...
Let's see, would it be possible to use this one first?
This is a real rush job of a set list.
But we don't have a choice but to do it like this.
Is there anyone here who can sing I'm an Idol?
Ryuuguu Komachi was supposed to sing it.
I can do it.
Mami can, too!
But Mami-chan, you're in Start Star right after that.
Oh, you're right!
Then if Yuki-pyon sings Start Star–
I can't!
I'm not sure if we can last until Ryuuguu gets here anymore...
I understand the circumstances.
Right.
We'll do something about it.
I see.
Then I'll place my trust in you.
Well, if it gets too bad, I'll do some magic tricks!
Start getting ready, please!
Everyone. Listen for a bit, please.
We may be performing under circumstances like these,
but let's use this opportunity to show the audience
that 765 Pro isn't just about Ryuuguu Komachi.
On behalf of the people who came to enjoy this show,
let's give it everything we've got!
I'll do it.
We've finally come this far.
I want to test how far we can go!
Miki...
All right!
We're going on standby!
Okay!
Everyone with us here today,
thank you for waiting!
765 Pro's first concert, Those Aiming for the Top, will begin shortly!
All right!
Get going!
Lyrics: Nakamura Megumi  Composition-Arrangement: Sasaki Hiroto
Quite the predicament, eh?
Mou fushime gachi na kinou nante iranai
Don't need more unstable days like yesterday
I'm not worried.
Every last one of our idols is exceptional.
Well, I guess this is a chance to show that to the world, too.
Kyou korekara hajimaru watashi no densetsu
Today marks the start of my legend
Kitto otoko ga mireba
From a man's eyes it probably
Young Lady, Aim High!
Lyrics: yura  Composition: Shirato Yuusuke  Arrangement: Kageie Jyun
Otome yo taishi wo idake!!
Young lady, aim high!!
Yume mite suteki ni nare
Fall in love and become beautiful
I can't find my ribbon!
Otome yo taishi wo idake!!
Young lady, aim high!!
But you're up next!
What do I do?!
Okorare rouka de koi bana
Talking about love after being sent to the hallway
Hey!
Can't you use this scarf instead?
Otome yo taishi wo idake!!
Young lady, aim high!!
Thank you, Hibikin!
We're going!
Tesuto wa Chatto sou
Tests are the time to consult
Spark Sparkle
Lyrics: yura  Composition-Arrangement: Kousaki Satoru
Kiramekirari zutto chu tto (chu chu)
Spark Sparkle!  Just like a peck on the cheek
Huh?! You gave it to Mami-chan?!
Chikyuu de kagayaku hikari (kirari)
Light shines down on Earth
S–Sorry!
I didn't think it was yours...
Kiramekirari motto More tto (More tto)
Spark Sparkle!  Just more and more
Wh–What do I do?!
Watashi wo watashi to yobitai
I want to be able to call myself, me
I–I said sorry!
Yukiho, calm down.
Tokimekirari kitto kyun tto (kyu kyu)
Heart-pounding Sparkle!  I know it'll amaze you
Who did it?!
Who used my make-up box and messed everything up?
Kagami wo mireba chou Lovely
If you look in the mirror you'll be super lovely
Tokimekirari gutto gyu tto (gyu tto)
Heart-pounding Sparkle!  The grip on your heart doesn't let up
I'm back.
Nice work out there, Haruka.
Watashi wa watashi ga daisuki
I love being me
How was the audience?
Guitar solo, come on!
I don't think I got them very worked up.
But we're just getting started, right?
Hey, Ricchan!
Can't this car fly or something?
If it could, we'd have been flying long ago.
Yes, I'm sorry.
We haven't been able to move whatsoever.
Yes. I'm told it's right there if we could get off the highway, but...
Lyrics: uRy  Composition: Ookubo Hiroshi  Arrangement: Ooue Shouko/Ookubo Hiroshi
Marude Jet coaster mitai ne
It's like a roller coaster, isn't it?
Itsudemo dokidoki Happy
Everything is so exciting and happy
Isn't Ryuuguu on yet?
Isn't the opener a little too long?
Sarigenaku kureru sonna
You casually give me that feeling
W–We're fine.
No problems here.
Kihon teki ni wa ippongi dake do
I've usually got a one-track mind
I'm an Idol
Lyrics: Nakamura Megumi  Composition-Arrangement: Sasaki Hiroto
It just won't zip, Yuki-pyon!
Toki to baai de utsurigi na no
But from time to time I'm fickle
What do I do?!
Sonna jyuunan tekiou ryoku
You need that kind of flexibility
Huh...? Where was I supposed to go next...?
Umaku ikashite tsunawatari
To walk a tightrope right
Where's the set list...?
Suki na hito ni wa nikoniko shite
I'm all smiles for the person I like
Ah! Makoto, hand me the set list for a second?
Sou de nai hito mo sorenari ni
And I guess for everyone else, too
Sotozura yokute uchibenkei
I look nice on the outside, but I'm a devil inside
What do you think you're doing, Hibiki?!
Yowatari dake wa jyouzu
Making my way in the world is all I'm good at
My outfit is drenched!
S–Sorry...
What were you doing all of a sudden, anyway?
Kiryou to sainou dake de karuku
This isn't a job you can do
Shouldn't the two of you calm down a bit?
Sorry! I just wanted to borrow the set list!
Mami! You're up next, so you should probably–
Konaseru shigoto jya nai no dakara
On beauty and talent alone
Then you didn't need to come all the way over here!
It–It's your fault too for not capping your water bottle!
Hito ni mienai doryoku nante
I work harder behind the scenes
In the first place, you're always so clumsy, Hibiki!
Hakuchou nami ijyou
Than any swan
Mami, you can't pull on it that hard!
You've been messing everything up since we got here!
Kitto watashi ga ichiban!
I know I'm number one!
That's got nothing to do with this!
Demo anata mo sokosoko kamo
But you might be okay, too
H–Hey, everyone–!
Everyone, calm down a little!
Sorya watashi to kuraberu kara
When you compare yourself to me
Chotto bun warui no yo
The odds are just against you
I can't go on like this...
I'm sorry, Yuki-pyon...
For now, let's just calm down some.
You're right.
Once I calmed down, I started getting jittery...
I think I might have forgotten some of my lyrics, too.
And the audience isn't really getting into it.
Maybe we really can't do it alone...
Hey, everyone...
Instead of worrying about how the audience sees us,
why don't we think about what we want to tell them?
We've always seen singing in front of a big audience as our objective,
and today that dream finally came true!
Even if we look a little stupid,
let's show the entire performance hall what we can do!
After all, we practiced so hard!
I just know we can reach them!
I guess you're right.
It doesn't get anything done when we all panic.
Yeah.
And I bet
Iori and the others are panicking even more.
So let's make sure we show them everything we can sing!
Yeah!
All right! Let's do it!
I can, too!
Yukiho-san, I'll fix your skirt in a jiffy!
Thank you!
Start Star
Lyrics: yura/Ookubo Hiroshi
Composition-Arrangement: Ookubo Hiroshi
Miracle
Start star
Start star!
Thank you for the Memories
Lyrics: Nakamura Megumi
Composition-Arrangement: Sasaki Hiroto
Omoide wo arigatou
Thank you for the memories
Lyrics-Composition-Arrangement: Toyama Akitaka
Shinken na manazashi wo zutto
Always watching me with that earnest gaze
Flower Girl
Lyrics: Yoshi&Kyon
Composition-Arrangement: Yoshi
Yume no naka de mata tsutsunde
Envelope me once more in a dream
Yep. Everyone's got some life in 'em.
But still...
Yeah. If you can make it by then, we'll manage.
Yeah. Got it.
We're cutting it close.
Um, Producer.
Anata ga kita! Machi
You've come! I waited
Do you have a moment?
Futami Mami
Takatsuki Yayoi
Shijyou Takane
Kikuchi Makoto
Amami Haruka
Kisaragi Chihaya
Hoshii Miki
Hagiwara Yukiho
Ganaha Hibiki
Dressing Room
We've got a problem, Producer!
Right after Miki's Day of the Future,
it's Miki's Heart of the Marionette!
Even Miki can't keep doing all these heavy dance routines!
You're right. Shit.
We can't alter the set list any more, either.
Nobody but Miki has practiced either of those songs, either.
Well, let's see.
It'll be tough if we consider having to hold out until Ryuuguu arrives,
but we'll need to cut one song and move on to the next–
Producer.
Could you let me try?
Miki!
Y–You can't!
That's right!
You already have a lot of numbers in the second half!
Do you think you can?
I don't know.
But...
I want to try!
I want to test myself!
Hibiki, Makoto.
Could I ask you to be her backup?
P–Producer!
Is that really okay?
I might mess up.
If that happens, everyone will cover for you.
Don't worry and go in guns blazing!
You want to sparkle on stage, right?
Yeah!
Everyone!
You having fun out there?!
It kinda feels like you're all bored
because Ryuuguu Komachi isn't here!
But you know, to be honest,
the three girls from Ryuuguu Komachi
are a little late getting here
because they're stuck in a typhoon.
Really?!
They can't come today?!
Bzzt!
They'll definitely be here, so don't worry!
So you know, until then, the other girls and I will work just as hard–
No, we'll work even harder than they would!
So keep your eyes on us!
Lyrics: Omi Oriha  Composition-Arrangement: Tatsh
Now then. We're at a crossroads here.
It's from Mami!
She says Miki-Miki is working super-hard to give us time!
Miki is?
My!
We can't lose to them!
I see.
Her smile and body(?) soothe us!
A calm, big-sister idol!
Birthday: July 19th, Cancer
Hobbies: Walking her dog, trying cafes
"I need to have a level head.
On behalf of everyone at the office!"
Can't do without singing and baking and friends!
A girl with unflagging energy!
Birthday: April 3rd. Aries.
Hobbies: Baking, karaoke, long phone calls
"I'm Amami Haruka! My dream is to be Top Idol!"
An aggressive "little demon"-type girl with
overflowing talent
Birthday: November 23rd. Sagittarius.
Hobbies: Chatting with friends, nail art
"I'm pretty serious about being an idol, you know?"
Betting everything on her music.
A quiet and solitary young girl.
Birthday: February 25th. Pisces.
Hobbies: Music appreciation (Classical), getting in shape
"To me, singing is the only–"
Miki looks like she's in pain.
Nee kiete shimatte mo sagashite kuremasuka
Even if I disappeared, would you look for me?
Heart of the Marionette
Lyrics: mft  Composition: Hashimoto Yukari  Arrangement: Miyazaki Makoto
Kitto isogashikute Meeru utenai no ne
You must be too busy to text me
Samishii toki ni ha yozora mitsumeru
When I'm lonely, I look up into the night sky
Motto furimuite hoshii
I want you to look my way
Mukashi mitai ni
Like you did in the past
Sunao ni iitaku naru no
I simply want to tell you
Dakedo ima nande
But why now?
Suki suki suki itai
Love, love, love, hurt
Doki doki doki kono omoi ga tsutawaru
Throb, throb, throb, my feelings reach you
Nani mo dekinai
I can't do a thing
Sore ga Marionetto
That's what a marionette is
Anata ni kimochi todokanai
My feelings won't reach you
Aa modokashii!
Ah! It's so frustrating!
Hora ne namida hito tsubu mo denai
Look, I can't even shed a single tear
Kokoro ga kowaresou dayo
It feels like my heart might break
Yeah. I think I can make a great article out of this.
Looks like they didn't need my magic tricks.
You were amazing, Miki.
Chihaya-san...
Now it's my turn.
Hey, Miki!
Are you all right?
Did I do it right?
The stage was so bright...
Hey... did I sparkle, too?
Yeah.
You sparkled.
Ubatte hoshii
Steal me away
When Our Eyes Meet
Lyrics: Kaida Yuriko  Composition-Arrangement: Jesahm
Me to me ga au shunkan suki dato kizuita
When our eyes meet, I realize I'm in love
Miki. Here.
Ah, Haruka.
Thanks.
Producer was right.
My heart was beating so hard, and I got so excited...
The lights sparkled,
and the voices of everyone in the audience reverberated in me like they were roaring.
It made me think that I really want to keep being an idol.
Are you all ready?
Until Ryuugu Komachi
gets here
we've got
to sing
to dance
and give it our best
until the
very end!
Let's go!
765 Pro!
Let's do it!
REST@RT!
REST@RT YOURSELF
Lyrics: Sasaki Hiroto  Composition-Arrangement: Tanaka Hidekazu
Kinou made no ikikata wo hitei suru dake jyanakute
I didn't just deny the way I lived life until yesterday
Korekara susumu michi ga miete kita
I can see the road I want to take into the future
Yowai dake no onna yori
Even if I endure or outstretch my arm further
Gaman toka senobi shitemo
Than a woman who's nothing but weak
Kakko tsuketa jibun ga suki dakara
I really like the "me" who pretended to be strong
Ima sugu kokoro no Doa chotto hiraite
Open the door to your heart a little right now
Tabi ni dete mitai kibun
I feel like going on a journey
Boyaboya shiteru to taisetsu na Chansu
If I sit around, it feels like I'll miss out
Nogashite shimaisou
On this precious chance
Kagayaita Suteeji ni tateba
If we stand on this sparkling stage
Saikou no kibun wo ajiwaeru
We can enjoy the greatest feeling
Subete ga mukuwareru shunkan
The moment we're repaid for all our effort
Itsumademo tsuzuke
Will last forever
Yume nara samenaide ite
If this is a dream, I hope we never wake
Oozora wo tobu tori no you ni
Like a bird that flies in the open sky
Tsubasa wo hirogete habatakitai
I want to spread my wings and soar
Donna ni tookutemo ikou
Let's go as far as it takes
Akogare no sekai
To the world we dream of
Yume dake dewa owarasetakunai
I don't want this to end as just a dream
Hey! Where is everyone?!
What's going on right now?!
Iori and the girls made it!
What are you crying about?
Don't cry!
Looks like it went well.
Sure did. Good going.
Sorry about all that.
But you can leave the rest to us!
Okay, let's get ready!
We can't trail behind them!
Everyone!
Thanks for waiting!
Ryuuguu Komachi won't lose to them!
So here's our first song!
Smoky Thrill!
Everyone!
My...
Great job!
Episode 13
And So,The Girls Rise to the Shining Stage
Atarashii fuku kigaete dekakeyou
Let's put on some new clothes and go somewhere
Kutsu mo kaban mo kaitate oroshitate
My shoes and bag are brand new off the rack
Aoi sora niwa taiyou mabushii na
The sun shines brilliantly in the blue sky
Hitome ki ni sezu uta demo kuchi zusamou
Don't let other people bother you and maybe hum a song to yourself
Itsumo wasureteta tagoto ni ki wo torare
I'd always forgotten, distracted by other things,
Sugoku taisetsu na hito tachi no sonzai wo
About the existence of the people who are so important to me
Jibun hitori dake kurou shita ki ga shiteta
I got the feeling that I was suffering all by myself
Dakedo sore wa chigau ima dakara wakarukedo
But I can see now that wasn't true
Minna tanoshiku egao de butai ni tatou
Let's all enjoy ourselves and smile when we stand on stage
Uta ya Dansu de jibun wo tsutaeyou
Let's tell everyone about us through our song and dance
Kotoba dake dewa ienai atsui kimochi wo
We have these burning feelings that don't fit in just words
Sukoshi dake demo todekerareta naraba shiawase
So if we can deliver even a few of them to you, I'd be on cloud nine
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
This is Amami Haruka!
Next week, we at 765 Pro
advance to a whole new stage!
Everyone, we're going to
keep making waves, so
Look forward to it!
The World that Began to Change!