Beautiful flowers.
A magnificent fountain.
And an extravagant mansion!
Ah, I want to be rich!
Today we impose upon the household of the famous Minase Group's President.
Cute dog, huh?
Hello there!
You were broadcasting?
Sorry!
Are you a member of the family here?
Yes! My name is Minase Iori, and I'm 15 years old.
I'm an idol in a unit called Ryuuguu Komachi.
An idol?
Yes!
You're right.
It's written in fine print right here.
I see. Iori-chan is the young lady of the Minase Conglomerate.
You must be so proud to have such a fine father and big brothers!
O–Oh yes, I sure am.
What is your father usually–
More importantly,
let's give everyone a great big introduction
to the private life of the super idol, Minase Iori!
Milady!
H–Hey, stop that!
Cut, cut!
Leggo already!
We're on the air!
Milady!
Not bad, Iori.
But when are they gonna go to Iori-chan's house?
I think I wanna see that more than some garden.
That's no garden, Yayoi.
That place on the screen right now is Iori's house.
Okay, everyone!
Let's all be Iori-chan's fans!
Cleaning that place must take a lot of work!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I’m sure, I can’t fail, I’m number one
Start hajimaru kyou no Suteeji
Start, today’s live is beginning
Check maiku meeku ishou ni Showtime
Check my mic, makeup, outfit, then it’s showtime!
Try challenge!
I’ve got to challenge myself
Stardom hikari hikaru Spotlight
The light of stardom, the shining spotlight
Mabushii kagayaki massugu Debut
It sparkles brilliantly like the path before me
Yume wa kanau mono
A dream is something that needs to come true
Watashi shinjiteru
That’s what I believe
Saa ichi ni tsuite Let’s go
So get on your mark, let’s go
Yeah!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Uta wo utaou!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s sing a song!
Hitotsu hitotsu egao to namida wa
Every last smile and tear
Yume ni naru Entertainment
make up the entertainment that becomes a dream
Are you ready? I’m ready! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I’m sure, I can’t fail, I’m number one
Episode 6
Things One Loves,
Things One Holds Dear
And just what was the problem with that?
Isn't it a Producer's job to praise effort at advertising?
That's true,
but if you do it poorly, it has a negative effect on your image.
I just thought I'd make the best of an opportunity.
At least discuss these things with us before they happen.
As a producer, some advice is the least I could–
Ritsuko is in charge of Ryuuguu Komachi!
It's none of your business!
That's not true!
We all work together at 765 Pro.
I want to be of help to everyone.
And if you have worries or need advice on something,
I want to be there for you.
I'd like to be everyone's Producer.
I don't need your advice!
If you want us to rely on you, you've got some work to do!
That show was ridiculous anyway.
Just who is "so proud to have such a fine father and big brothers"?!
Right?
Iori-chan, are you on bad terms with your father and brothers?
Not really.
But they're convinced I could never be an idol.
I just want to prove them wrong.
I feel that way, too.
My big bro's always making fun of me.
Just because they were born a little
earlier, they think they're so special.
Yayoi-cchi, how about you?
Don't you fight with your siblings?
Not at all!
There are six of us, so we fight
over little things every day
but everyone gets along real well!
I see.
I want to relax and get something good to eat.
Hibiki, Yayoi, want to come?
It'll be my treat.
Really?!
All right!
I want to go, but I have to get back and make dinner.
If you want, you could have dinner at my house!
That sounds kinda interesting!
At your house, Yayoi?
So this is the commoners' supermarket.
It's my first time here, but they have a pretty good selection!
Iori-chan, don't you go grocery shopping?
Meal preparation is the cook's job, right?
I'll treat you guys to some Okinawan cooking!
I can't wait!
I don't see bitter melon...
Here.
No, Iori-chan!
You have to pick carefully!
But they're all the same!
That's not true!
See? These all look good.
This head of broccoli looks fresher
and cucumbers with lots of bumps taste better!
Taro isn't just cheaper with the
skin on, it's more nutritious, too!
You have to pick carefully!
Okay...
Oh, Yayoi-chan!
You're working hard, as always.
It's no trouble.
Okay!
It's a little early, but let's go a little crazy with the half-off stickers.
Thank you very much!
What do you want?
Um...
I'll have this, please.
Thatta girl.
You've got an eye for quality.
So? What're you going to do with all these beansprouts?
Since today's Thursday, it's our weekly Beansprout Festival.
What a dull-sounding festival.
That's not true!
It's a lot of fun.
Do you always make dinner, Yayoi?
Dad and Mom are always home late because of work,
so making dinner and taking care of the younger kids is my job.
I see. So you're a good girl!
Iori and I are gonna help out with everything today!
Right, Iori?
O–Of course!
Thanks!
Tah-dah! Welcome to our humble home!
It's a two-story!
It's smaller than our horse stable...
I'm home!
Were you all good kids?
Welcome back!
I'm a good boy!
Yayoi nee-chan, welcome back.
Welcome back!
Ah, strangers!
Welcome back.
Yeah. They're my idol friends.
Thanks for having us.
Let's get along!
Welcome!
Hurry, come this way!
You're so strong!
Yayoi nee-chan, where's the formula milk?
I have it right there.
Got lots of beansprouts, too!
I got Hibiki-san and Iori-chan to help.
He's not a mouse, he's a hamster.
His name is Hamuzou.
Boom!
Is that a challenge?!
Take this!
Boom!
Hey, don't be rude to our guests!
This ain't nothin'!
Okay, let's get cooking!
Furee furee Ganbare saa ikou
Hurray, hurray, do your best!! Now let's go
Spark Sparkle
Lyrics: yura
Composition/Arrangement: Kousaki Satoru
Furee furee Ganbare saikou
Hurray, hurray, do your best!! It can't get any better
Donna tane mo makeba medatsun desu
Whatever seed you plant will sprout
Maru maru Super Star
just like a super star
Donna me demo hana ni narun desu
No matter how it sprouts it'll become a flower
Hanamaru Super Start
It's a Gold Star Super Start
Hare ga atte
It's because there are clear skies
Ame ga atte
and rain
Saa niji ga dekiru
See, they made a rainbow
Kokoro to yume de
It's with heart and dreams
Mirai ga dekiru
that we make the future
Miracle doko kuru matteiru yori mo
Where's our miracle? Instead of waiting
Hajimete mimashou Hop Step Jump!
let's just get started Hop Step Jump!!
Kiramekirari zutto chu tto (chu chu)
Spark Sparkle!  Just like a peck on the cheek
Chikyuu de kagayaku hikari (kirari)
Light shines down on Earth
Kiramekirari motto More tto (More tto)
Spark Sparkle!  Just more and more
Watashi wo watashi to yobitai
I want to be able to call myself, me
Tokimekirari kitto kyun tto (kyu kyu)
Heart-pounding Sparkle!  I know it'll amaze you
Kagami wo mireba chou Lovely
If you look in the mirror you'll be super lovely
Tokimekirari gutto gyu tto (gyu tto)
Heart-pounding Sparkle!  The grip on your heart doesn't let up
Watashi wa watashi ga daisuki
I love being me
Furee furee Ganbare saa ikou
Hurray, hurray, do your best!! Now let's go
Furee furee Ganbare saikou
Hurray, hurray, do your best!! It can't get any better
Furee furee Ganbare saa ikou
Hurray, hurray, do your best!! Now let's go
Furee furee Ganbare saikou
Hurray, hurray, do your best!! It can't get any better
Shake!
I don't think he can shake.
Then sit!
Sit!
He's already sitting.
He's so fluffy!
Aren't you going to go play?
I will,
but I want to start helping, little by little.
Yayoi nee-chan's busy with being an idol and all.
Okay, looking good.
Dinner's ready!
Thanks for waiting.
All right!
Hey, I don't see anything besides beansprouts in there...
Yeah. It's the Beansprout Festival, after all.
Don't worry.
Even if there are only beansprouts, they taste great!
Yeah, yeah!
I hereby declare the beginning of Beansprout Festival!
Switch, on!
Now's your chance, YakinikuMan!
Yakiniku Punch!
It's pitch black!
Pitch black!
The breaker fell!
What's going on?!
Sorry!
I just wanted to see YakinikuMan!
Nobody move!
Sheesh. You never know what's going to happen in this house.
Full points for thrills.
Thank you for the food!
Iori-chan, if you don't eat, there won't be any left.
I–I will...
It's a lot better than it looks!
I know, right? The secret is in my special sauce.
It's totally great!
Ah... Bitter melon...
There was one left, so I bought it!
Thank you, Yayoi!
I'm so touched!
I was really happy you could both come.
You helped out a bunch, too.
If only you could come over every day!
Just kidding!
Okay, here comes round two!
Chousuke nii-chan, aren't you gonna eat?
I'm gonna take it!
Hey!
Onii-chan hit me!
Chousuke, why did you make him cry?
But Kouji–
You didn't need to hit him, did you?
Apologize to him.
Why? It's Kouji's fault.
Chousuke, you're the oldest boy here.
Aren't I always telling you to be kind to everyone?
Now, apologize!
What the heck!? You talk like you're so special.
Even though you're running around
being an idol like you always wanted!
I hate you, Nee-chan!
...Chousuke!
I wonder what's wrong with Chousuke.
Let's continue the Beansprout Festival!
Is it okay to just leave him like that, Yayoi?
Sure! When he gets hungry, he'll come right back.
Chousuke sure is taking his time, isn't he?
Maybe he's at a friend's house?
I called, but they said he hadn't come by.
I'm a little surprised.
I never thought Chousuke would say something like that.
I had always thought that if I became an idol
I might be of some help to everyone.
I don't think he meant it.
He said "Onee-chan is busy being an idol,
"so I want to help as much as I can," after all.
Chousuke did?
Yeah.
Yayoi, the animals get out from time to time
but I always go right after them.
Wouldn't it be terrible if something happened to your precious family?
If something...
Let's split up and search.
Yeah.
Iori-chan, can you look after the little ones?
Leave it to me.
Okay.
Think they'll find Chousuke?
Did he run away from home?
It's called "disappearance."
Come on, now.
You all need to get inside.
'kay–
What's "disappearance"?
That's not what it is.
Look, "disappearance" is–
And if you have worries–
I'd like to be everyone's Producer.
Just in case.
Chousuke–!
Find him?
Nope.
Maybe he went a little farther.
There couldn't have been an accident or something...
O–Of course not!
If something happened to Chousuke, I...!
Yayoi!
Hibiki!
Producer!
Why are you...?
I got a call from Iori.
Where's Chousuke-kun?
I see.
Don't worry, Yayoi.
We'll definitely find him.
Okay!
Okay, let's split up and look for him.
Understand? Go to sleep the instant you get in bed.
If you stay up late...
ghosts will pay you a visit!
Good night!
Okay, good night.
Nope. Don't think I've seen him.
I see. Thank you very much.
Yes?
Hey! Haven't you found him yet?!
Hello?
No. We just split up and we're looking now.
I see.
I'll contact you as soon as we find him.
Okay.
Even I, Iori-chan, am relying on you,
so make sure you do your job!
Yeah, I know.
Hey... If it were you, where would you go?
Who knows... I haven't the faintest
understanding of these commoners.
There are so many places to hide even in my own house.
I see...
In my own... house?
Found you.
How'd you know?
When I fought with my big brothers, I'd go hide in the storage shed, too.
You have big brothers?
That's right.
They're both such boy scouts,
we'd fight all the time because they kept making fun of me.
Though things aren't much different now.
So you're just like me.
Just like you?
Yeah.
Yayoi nee-chan's an idol
and she does all the housework by herself.
I want to work hard and help out, too.
But in the end, someone's always getting mad at me.
The way I feel is something onee-chan could–
never understand.
Never.
You want Yayoi to respect you, right?
Then instead of skulking around and running away
you need to confront her with those feelings.
At least, that's what I do.
See, no matter what happen to her,
Yayoi always does her work smiling like an idiot.
I've never once seen her make a face that said
"taking care of things at home is so hard!"
That's Yayoi's pride.
If you have your own pride,
then you need to become a man who can help your big sister on your own.
By "pride," you mean–
Be confident and take action.
Chousuke!
Thank goodness!
Thank goodness...
Thank goodness...!
I'm sorry,
Yayoi nee-chan!
I'm so sorry!
Siblings really are great.
Maybe I'll send big bro a text once in a while.
I won't.
Until I become Top Idol, I'd never do such a thing.
Thanks, Iori.
F–For what?
For calling.
I was pretty happy.
Wh–What are you saying?!
You're about the only conveniently available guy I could think of.
And in the end, you didn't do a thing.
Well, I can't really argue with that.
You need to put more effort in.
Then I'll call you next time, too.
Sure, I'll do that.
You can do it!
I'll go wake everyone.
Why are you up, Chousuke?
I'll wake up by myself starting today.
I'll go wake the others.
Thanks...
Chousuke, you seem kinda reliable!
Pride! It's pride, got it?
Hey! Get up!
Breakfast is ready!
Mabuta wo akete sawayaka omezame
Open my eyes, what a refreshing morning
(Rararara asa da! Rararara okiyou!)
(La la la la it's morning! La la la la let's get up!)
Kirakira asa hi chikyuu ni ohayou
The sparkling sun, good morning, planet Earth
(Rararara asa da! Rararara okiyou!)
(La la la la it's morning! La la la la let's get up!)
Ara ara onaka ga guruguru utatteru
My, my, my tummy's singing the rumbly song
Arerere atama ga kurakura odoru
Huh?  My head's dancing the dizzy dance
Wasurezu tabeyo kyou no asagohan
Let's not forget to eat this morning's breakfast
(Rararara gohan! Rararara tabeyou!)
(La la la la breakfast! La la la la let's eat!)
Washoku ni youshoku nani ga deru kana?
Western or Eastern food, which will we get?
(Rararara gohan! Rararara tabeyou!)
(La la la la breakfast! La la la la let's eat!)
Gohan ni nattou misoshiru nori tamago
Rice and nattou, egg and seaweed in miso soup
Toast Salad ni Omelette Milk
Toast, salad and an omelette, milk
Saa ippai tabeyou yo
Well, let's eat a lot
Hayaoki dekita gohoubi
As a reward for waking up early
Hora minna de tabeyou yo
Come on, let's all eat together
Ohiru made motsuyou
So we can last until lunch
Milk wa Calcium ga
Milk has calcium
Yasai wa Vitamin houfu
Vegetables are chock full of vitamins
Daizu wa tanpakushitsu
Soybeans are a source of protein
Balance mo taisetsu
Balance is important
Ichinichi no hajimari ni
When the day starts
Harapeko jya monotarinai
You can't go on with an empty stomach
Karada wo ugokasu ni wa
To move your body
Oishii asagohan
You need a yummy breakfast
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
This is
Akizuki Ritsuko.
Honestly speaking,
next week is a must-see
soothing party
for all the
gentlemen in the nation!
You there, the one who's
been feeling tired recently!
And you, who
we've yet to meet!
The Indirect Route to Happiness
Look forward to it!