City event frenzy
A wild hit with housewives
and students!
Rocketing in popularity
Kikuchi Makoto-kun
(765 Pro Affiliate)
--OP2|02:27|CHANGE!!!!--
Everyone's eyes are on her!
She's a girl who looks like
a boy, Kikuchi Makoto-kun!
Her bearing is truly that of a prince!
The explosion in her core fandom of women is perfectly understandable!
Makoto-sama came today?!
Yeah, that's what I heard!
I wanted to see her! My prince!
Prince Makoto, you're so handsome!
I love her so much,
I think I might go crazy!
Makoto-kun is so great!
Oh? I thought you were
in Jupiter's Touma camp?
Oh, come on! I'm in both!
Thank you very much.
S–Sorry!
If you could just let me through here...
We say it all the time,
but you've got it tough.
Aspire
I won't last if it keeps up.
That's for sure.
But doesn't that mean you're
just that popular now?
Actually, I don't want to be a prince.
I want to be a princess.
CHANGE! Ima wa kawaru sekai kagayake
Change! It's a changing world, shine!
CHANGE! Ima wa watashi no sekai
Change! It's my world
Watashi no mono CHANGE
It belongs to me! Change!
Kirameku Stage
The shining stage
Event gurabia CM
Events, photo shoots, commercials,
Terebi de Show time
Showtime on TV
Hajimaru tsuzuku Story
A beginning, a continuing story!
Nando eru chii demo
No matter how many times we attain this position
Donna Rival datte
No matter the rival
Makenaide Try again!
Don't give up and try again!
Tachi agaru Story
It's a story about standing up
Encore wa My life
My life is an encore
Ichido no Live
A once-upon-a-live
Susume dokomade mo
Keep moving forward and never stop
Show must go on!
The show must go on!
Three
Two
One!
CHANGE! Ima wa kawaranai yume egaite
Change! It's an unchanging dream we're drawing
CHANGE! Ima wo suki ni jiyuu ni
Change! It's a time to do what you want and be free!
Try lady!
Aim to be a lady!
CHANGE! Ima wo atarashii ni Live
Change! It's a time to start a new show
Oikakenagara
While we chase after
Watashi rashii watashi de
A me who's really me
Motto motto Your dream come true!
Keep trying, keep trying! Your dream will come true!
I love you all!
Episode 17
Makoto, A True Prince
"Wh–What?! What are you all doing here?"
"It's nothing personal,"
"but we we're just
doing someone a favor."
"H–Help! Someone!"
"Stop right there!"
"The–"
"The prince?"
"You're kidding, right?"
"Who cares if he's a prince?"
"Kick his ass!"
"Shit!"
"We'll be back!"
"All bark and no bite."
"Kyun!"
"This might be..."
"love...!"
She's so lucky!
I want an encounter like this, too!
With a horse?
With a prince!
First of all,
why is that prince or whatever
going to school on a horse?
Isn't that violating school regulations?
It seems the horse is a student, too.
Everyone judges based on appearances.
Even I have a feminine side.
But nobody even tries to see it.
Well,
I guess that's true.
I'm very grateful that they support me.
But I'm a girl, too, you know?
Kisaragi Chigusa
I guess I want them to support me as a girl?
I'm not at all saying that I
just want male supporters.
How should I put this?
I think it's too lopsided!
Hey, are you listening? Producer!
I'm listening!
If I wore some frilly clothes and did a totally girly pose, even I could–
The inside of your mouth can
be absolute zero any time.
Prince Makoto's South Pole Toothpaste!
Aspire
If you did a pose...?
That was so cool...
I knew I could never–
Don't let that bother you!
You're fine that way, Makoto!
Haruka, how do you
want people to see you?
You do, don't you?
Don't you have a way you want people to see you as an idol?
I think...
I'm not sure, actually.
Don't worry about it, Makoto.
Everyone's been saying
you've gotten sexier recently.
I–Is that right?
Yeah!
Everyone's been saying it.
Is–
Is that right?
I sure hope so!
I see!
So everyone's saying it!
Thank God she's easy to please.
Okay!
It's about time to get going.
I've got Producer all to myself today.
You're so lucky, Makoto!
Come on. Stop fooling
around and let's go.
Okay–
A prince, huh?
What, you're still thinking about that?
Well, I became an idol so
I could become a princess.
And then I went and became a prince.
Prince's Early
Afternoon
46th Composite Script
Special: Congregation of
Hot Young Noblemen~!
It just feels weird.
What's wrong with that?
Not just anybody can be a prince.
For now, let's just focus on today's job.
Special: Congregation of
Hot Young Noblemen!
First we have the
ever-popular three from Jupiter.
Boy, you're as popular as ever.
Thank you.
Next, we have Kikuchi Makoto-kun.
Hello!
You're a real hit with
your nickname, "Prince"!
You're also this segment's first female guest.
What an honor.
She's so handsome!
She most certainly is!
How about it?
How does it feel to be called
"handsome" or "Prince" by other women?
Well, let's see.
I'm really just happy to
be supported by others.
A breath of fresh air!
Next, we have something of a unique guest–
Hey, 765 Pro.
Ignoring me?
So the Prince won't speak
with the commoners?
I have nothing to talk about with 961 Pro.
What's with that tone?
That's something coming from an office full of dirty cheats.
Wh–What?!
We won't run or hide.
If that pissed you off, fight us with talent.
What do you mean, talent?!
You  guys were the dirty–
Dirty what?
Oh, no. I...
I really want to go get dirty
exploring uncharted regions.
Exploring! What a manly comment.
We have quite the trusty prince with us!
I don't even understand!
They  were the ones playing dirty!
Hibiki almost got kicked off her show!
Well, calm down, Makoto.
You're playing into their hands if
you let the blood go to your head.
I will never  give in to those creeps!
Who aren't you giving in to?
In the first place,
how do you intend to compete?
A prince-off?
I'd look better in tights, anyway.
Don't mock me!
You again.
Stop provoking our idols.
Do you even know what President Kuroi has been doing to us?
The old man?
When did you boys start paying
attention to a low-level office's rugrats?
Prince's Early
Afternoon
Members of Jupiter
Just what I'd have expected from a
third-rate office's producer and idol.
They're indecent just by standing there.
Old man...
Don't you think you're
being a little immature
for the President of a
major production office?
I'm not exactly sure what you mean,
but it's perfectly natural.
After all, if we don't exterminate the rabble from this office I know
they'll keep popping up
everywhere like cockroaches.
L–Like cockroaches?!
Recently, it seems like there's some
very manly-looking idol running around.
She's getting all sorts of attention, being called "Prince" and so on.
It's so absurd!
In the end, she's just a
cockroach that learned a trick!
She's no match for us.
Don't you think that's going too far?!
Stop, Makoto!
Low-Society Pro barks
almost like a real dog!
Just stay out of our way and do your work quietly in some corner of the Industry.
Whatever the old man does,
it's none of our business.
We'll take you on
head-to-head any time.
See ya, "Prince."
Bye-bye–
Ciao!
Why you–
You!
You, you, you, you!
Why?
Why does it keep coming?!
I'm shooting! I'm shooting!
Makoto!
Reload, reload!
Don't screw with me!
Producer!
I didn't grow up like a
guy because I wanted to!
Sure. I know.
Look, the zombie tank
is coming from the left.
Makoto?
This and that... It's all Dad's fault!
Makoto!
The zombie tank! To the left!
You must like to take risks.
Sorry.
If you want to keep going, I'll put in a coin.
That's all right. I'll watch.
I thought you'd be
good at these, Makoto.
Dad says playing with "those flashies"
makes people wimps, so he never let me.
He really sounds strict.
Yes.
I like having fun playing
games with everyone, though.
You're really good, Producer.
You think?
Well, I played a lot when I was younger.
It's kinda like, "This is a man!"
The heck?
Oh, right!
Hey, Producer!
Are you free after this?
Me? Yeah, if it's just for a bit.
Okay...!
H–Hey!
Makoto! The zombies
are still attacking town!
Tah-dah!
Could you be a little more impressed, please?
Do it for the skirt!
Well, yeah, it's unusual, but...
What's the occassion?
I decided I'd have you really treat me like a girl for the rest of the day!
So let's go!
Huh?
Where?
Isn't that obvious?
Bicycle
Lyrics: Shirose Sai  Composition/Arrangement: Itou Shintarou
On a date!
"Chotto matte!!"
"Wait a minute!!"
"Boku wa kimi wo..."
"I think I lo–"
Gyutto dakishimeta Cushion
I was clutching tightly at my pillow
Aa~ mata yume da
Ah~ it's that dream again
Nando me darou
I wonder how many times this makes
Yappa chanto tsutaenakya
I guess I've just got to tell you
Saa soto dete mitara
So when I tried going outside
Mabushisa ni me ga Wink
It was so bright I couldn't help but blink my eyes
On tha phone
P & Makoto
Matchi
MY P!
Chain hazushite
Took of the lock
Stopper agete
Raised the kickstand
Kogu tabi tanoshiku yureru Short hair
Every time I pedal, my short hair sways merrily
Donna michi de datte
Whatever the road
Makenaide
I won't lose
Susunde miseru
I'll show you I can keep going
Suki da yo
I love you
Kokoro komete
Put your heart into it
Suki da yo
I love you
Chikara komete
Put some volume in it
Omoi kiri mawaru Pedal
Push those pedals as hard as you can
Propeller mitai tobesou dane
They're like propellers. It feels like I could fly
Suki da yo
I love you
Koe wo agete
Raise your voice
Suki da yo
I love you
Sokudo agete
Speed up
Kono mune ga kurushiku naru
My chest starts to hurt
Dakedo ikeru
But I can do it
Datte kimi ga suki da!!
Because I love you!!
Isn't this fun, Producer?!
Makoto, couldn't you take my
stamina into consideration here?
I won't last if I keep going at your pace.
Oh, come on!
We're just getting started!
Hey, Producer.
Dates are just like this, right?
I wonder if we look like we're in love?
Don't be ridiculous.
Then would we look that
way if we got some crepes?
Be it crepes or ice cream,
it'd be siblings at best, right?
Come to think of it, is this
supposed to be a date?
Sheesh, Producer.
You've got to get more into it.
Easier said than done...
Not good, Makoto.
I think you've been noticed.
It's all right.
If you act confident, you get
seen a lot less than you'd think.
So it seems.
Maybe they thought
we're on a date after all?
"Kikuchi Makoto, on a date at the
amusement park in broad daylight!"
I can see the headline now!
Hey, hey.
If that happened, your fans
would hunt me down.
Not a problem.
When that happens, I'll carry you over my
shoulder and help you escape at full speed.
There, there.
That must've hurt.
It seems Dad wanted to raise
me as a boy no matter what.
I never got to wear a skirt once,
and there's not one cute
thing anywhere at home.
I got teased a lot for being a "man-woman."
So that's why I admired princesses.
Long hair, pretty dresses,
an encounter with a handsome prince.
It's because I had dreams like those
that I wanted to become an idol!
Congratulations!
You've successfully exterminated the ogres!
Here's your prize!
Hey, Producer!
What do you want to ride next?
How about that one over that goes real high?
Or do you want to ride the coaster again?
You know, Makoto...
If you want to be a princess, maybe you
should consider something more peaceful.
Hey! Where do you think you're walking?
Your shoulder bumps me
and not a word of apology?
You've got some real guts.
That's not true.
You bumped into us.
What was that, woman?!
Producer. I'll be right back.
H–Hey, Makoto!
Wait!
Underestimate us and
you're cruisin' for a bruisin'!
Hey! Stop that!
Look how scared they are!
Let them go!
The hell's with you?
A skirt?
Hey, hey, it's a woman!
Where'd you get that, bitch?
Hey, stop! Look at the situation!
Producer, get back.
I just can't stand people like this.
You've got some real guts.
Makoto-sama!
I knew it was you, Makoto-sama!
I'm so touched I can meet you in person!
Thanks...
But now's not really the time...
I can't believe you actually came to rescue us!
You really are our prince!
I'll never forget today!
What the hell?
You're a woman, but you've got them calling you a prince?
Oh, princey, you're so handsome!
Real hip!
Makoto-sama, could I get your autograph later?
Makoto-sama, could I get a pic?
U–Um, girls...
Hey!
Don't ignore us!
Who do you think we are?!
Makoto-sama!
Prince!
Uh... Could you get back...
Damn it!
Don't you make fun of us!
P–
Producer!
Are you all right?
Somehow.
I'm more amazed those guys just left quietly.
After that, more of my female fans
who recognized me gathered around.
So that's how...
I see.
I'm just glad it worked out.
I'm sorry, Producer!
I wasn't thinking straight.
You're telling me.
I don't think they could've beaten you,
but it would've been terrible if
they hit your face or something.
You're right.
I'm an idol, after all.
Not just that.
You're a girl, too.
You're a princess today. Right, Makoto?
Though you might not feel much like a princess with your precious prince in this shape.
That's not true!
But unlike me,
you can do that.
You became those girls' Prince.
You really showed them their dream of being saved by their Prince.
Showed them
a dream...
Right.
You said that you became an idol dreaming of becoming a princess.
I think it's wonderful to
have a dream of your own.
But I also think it's an idol's precious job to show others their dreams.
You can make someone somewhere a princess.
I think things like that are an idol's role.
Right?
It's not too bad to become
someone else's support.
We haven't ridden this one yet, have we?
You're right.
It's so pretty.
Would you like to have a ride,
Princess?
Plan well my jaunt.
That's  the king of the castle!
I guess so!
Princess. You've mistaken your mount.
Very well. You shall be the Prince, and ride yon white horse.
Me?
I mean, nobody else can do it.
I'll put up with it just for today.
We're back!
Welcome back, Mako-chin!
Oh, and Nii-chan, too.
Don't say it like I'm some extra!
Hey, did you two go somewhere together?
Didn't recording end a long time ago?
Yeah. Just around.
It was a date. At the amusement park.
A– A date?
Honey, what's that supposed to mean?
Makoto! Don't exaggerate things!
Hey! Hey already!
But it's true!
Honey! Don't take away my Makoto-kun!
Huh? Makoto-kun took Honey away?
I think I'll do my best as a prince.
Instead of going along half-heartedly,
I'll face things head on.
I see.
You're done with princesses, then?
Well, I still admire them.
But if someday a single person arrives
who really treats me like a girl,
then for now I'm fine just like this.
Blazing Washboard
Chests
Prince Congregation!
A Hundred Consecutive
Shining Smiles!
Another job like this today!
Oh, come on, Makoto.
Just the other day you said
you'd do your best as a prince.
I said that, but...!
Hey, Producer!
Can I go on in a skirt today?
I think a prince in a skirt
would be original and–
Denied.
Knew it.
Genki ni shiteimasuka
Are you well?
Aikawarazu tsuppashitte imasuka
Are you still living at full speed?
Choppiri terechau kedo
It's a little embarrassing
Kono tegami wo kaite miyou
But I thought I'd write you a letter
Moshimo ikizumatta nara
If you find yourself stuck
Sono toki Best tsukuseba ii
Just do the best you can
Ima dekiru koto kangaeyou
Think of the things you can do right then
Sunao na kimochi de
If you take your honest feelings
Ari no mama yatte ireba
And do things the way those feelings tell you
Minna ni todokuyo
Everyone will understand
Dakara nayamanaide
So don't worry yourself
Itsumo yume miteita
I always see in my dreams
Kakko ii otona ni
A person who is becoming a handsome adult
Kizukanai uchi ni
Before I knew what had happened
Natteru anata he
And that's who this letter is for
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
I can't wait for
next week either, Mom!
I misspoke!
So cute...
What did you just–
Everyone!
Look forward
to next week!
Lots of, Everything