Good morning, Producer-san.
Good morning, Otonashi-san.
You've been looking
a lot better recently.
Yes, thanks to everyone.
It's enough to make me want
to be discharged right away.
Producer-san, you're so
dedicated to your job.
It's so nice out.
Indeed. It's a perfect day
to hold a concert.
Otonashi-san, don't you need
to be there with them?
It's fine. The Chief is
helping out on-site today.
I'm always weighing
everyone down, am I not?
You've been looking after me
all this time, too, Otonashi-san.
We have to look out for one
another in times like these.
For the time being, it's your job to get
well, so just concentrate on that. Okay?
Otonashi-san.
Um...
I'd like to ask you a favor.
Changin' my world!! Kawaru sekai kagayake
Changin' my world!! The changing world shines
Changin' my world!! Watashi no sekai
Changin' my world!! It's my world
Watashi no mono Change!!
It belongs to me! Change!!
Kirameku Stage
The shining stage
Event gurabia CM
Events, photo shoots, commercials,
Terebi de Show time
Showtime on TV
Hajimaru tsuzuku Story
A beginning, a continuing story!
Nando NG demo
No matter how many times we NG
Donna Rival datte
No matter the rival
Makenaide Try again!
Don't give up and try again!
Tachi agaru Street
It's a path you pave by standing up
Encore wa nai Life
Your life doesn't get an encore
Ichido no Live
It's a one-shot performance
Susume dokomade mo
Keep moving forward and never stop
Show must go on!
Three
Two
One!
Changin' my world!! Kawaranai yume egaite
Changin' my world!! It might be an unchanging dream we're drawing
Changin' ima wo!! Suki ni jiyuu ni kaeru Ready!!
Changin' right now!! But change it however you want! Ready!!
Changin' mae wo!! Atarashii mirai oikakenagara
Changin' what's in front of us!! While we chase a new future
Watashi rashii watashi de motto motto
I'll just be myself to keep on, keep on
Dreams come true
I love all
Episode 25
Everyone, Together!
Did you see how
big the stage was?
It's so exciting.
Time is hard won and easily lost.
Let us proceed
with focused hearts.
It kind of sucks that Producer
can't be here, though.
What's that, Hibikin?
It sounds like you miss
Nii-chan an awful  lot.
Th–That's not what I meant!
It's just that Producer was looking forward to the show so much–
Come on, Ami.
If you have the time to
tease Hibiki, go stretch with...
What's that bag?
Ricchan, I think you should
get to your  stretches, too.
What's that laugh supposed to mean?
Nothing, nothing!
Don't worry, don't worry!
Ms. Futami Ami
Ms. Futami Mami
Ms. Takatsuki Yayoi
Ms. Shijou Takane
Ms. Kikuchi Makoto
Ms. Miura Azusa
Ms. Amami Haruka
Ms. Kisaragi Chihaya
Ms. Hoshii Miki
Ms. Hagiwara Yukiho
Ms. Ganaha Hibiki
Ms. Minase Iori
You came for water too, Miki?
Yup.
Here.
Thanks.
It's finally time.
Hey, Miki.
What?
Remember a while ago, when we were talking about what makes an idol?
Yeah.
Back then, both you and
Chihaya had an answer.
I was the only one who
didn't have a clear answer.
But now I can say what I
think it is with confidence.
I really do have the most fun
when I'm on-stage with everyone.
All of our fans are there,
and everyone from 765 Pro is there.
That's the moment when
I feel most like an idol.
It's just like you to
think that, Haruka.
Yeah.
I think I'm okay with that, too.
Yeah!
Rehearsal Room
Members of
765 Pro
Ladies! Are your
preparations complete?
Yes, sir!
An excellent response.
Today's is the biggest event
in the history of 765 Pro,
and I applaud the effort you've put
towards today despite your busy schedules.
I'm sure the young man who isn't with us today
would've liked to extend his own well-wishing to you all.
But unfortunately,
he is not yet...
No, no.
That got a tad gloomy.
That's right!
To brighten up the mood, why don't I perform some magic tricks to raise everyone's spirits?
Honey!
Wh–Why are you...
What happened?!
Here I am.
Producer!
It's Nii-chan!
I was so worried!
Is it okay for you to
come outside now?
Hey! You don't have to force yourself
to come if you're in such a pitiful state!
Well... I was pretty
confident in my reflexes, too...
You have my apologies.
Rehearsal Room
Members of
765 Pro
I'm mostly surprised the hospital gave you permission to leave.
He said he wanted to see everyone's finest performance no matter what...
Huh? Does that mean you
came without telling them?
Well... I guess you
could put it that way.
Huh?!
Now, now! We were told that they planned to let him go out next week anyway.
So it must be fine!
Sheesh. Even the Chief...
Everyone... allow me to
apologize more formally.
I ended up leaving your
lessons entirely to you.
I didn't even know what kind
of condition you'd be in today,
and to be honest,
I was worried.
Seeing all of you
has relieved me.
Today's will be the greatest
show you've ever had!
I guarantee it!
I think you all already know the huge number
of people who helped to put on this show today.
Let's show them our appreciation
today by giving them all you've got!
Kisaragi Chihaya
Amami Haruka
Takatsuki Yayoi
Ganaha Hibiki
Shijou Takane
Kikuchi Makoto
Fan letters and presents for the idols
Please place in boxes
We have Haruka.
Miki.
Makoto.
Yukiho.
Ami.
Mami.
Iori.
Yayoi.
Hibiki.
Takane.
We have Azusa-san...
...and Chihaya.
And then there's Ritsuko,
as well as the Chief
and Otonashi-san,
who've always been
there for us, supporting us.
Removing any one
person ruins the whole.
I think it's because each of
us is here that we're 765 Pro.
I'm sure 765 Pro is unbeatable
with everyone together!
Let's make this the
best performance together!
Okay!
Haruka.
Yes?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't do anything for you
when you needed it most.
I'm so sorry...
But it looks like you found the answer you were looking for back then
all on your own.
Yes.
I see.
Great job!
Okay!
Everyone, if you don't want
to leave regrets behind,
go knock 'em dead!
Okay!
Here we go!
765 Pro!
Fight!
Yeah!
Are you ready? I’m lady! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m a lady! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I know it! I can’t fail, I’m number one
Lyrics: yura  Composition: Kousaki Satoru/Uchida Tetsuya
Arrangement: Kousaki Satoru/Hashimoto Yukari/Uchida Tetsuya
Start hajimaru kyou no Suteeji
Start, today’s live is beginning
Check maiku meeku ishou It's showtime
Check my mic, makeup, outfit, then it’s showtime!
Try challenge!
I’ve got to challenge myself
Stardom hikari hikaru Spotlight
The light of stardom, the shining spotlight
Mabushii kagayaki massugu Debut
A brilliantly sparkling, straightforward debut
Encore wa nai Life
Your life doesn't get an encore
Ichido no Live
It's a one-shot performance
Susume dokomade mo
Keep moving forward and never stop
Show must go on!
Three
Two
One!
Changin' my world!! Kawaranai yume egaite
Changin' my world!! It might be an unchanging dream we're drawing
Changin' ima wo!! Suki ni jiyuu ni kaeru Ready!!
Changin' right now!! But change it however you want! Ready!!
Changin' mae wo!! Atarashii mirai oikakenagara
Changin' what's in front of us!! While we chase a new future
Watashi rashii watashi de motto motto
I'll just be myself to keep on, keep on
Dreams come true
Are you ready? I’m lady! Uta wo utaou!
Are you ready? I’m a lady! Let’s sing a song!
Hitotsu hitotsu egao to namida wa
Every last smile and tear
Yume ni naru Entertainment
make up the entertainment that becomes a dream
Are you ready? I’m lady! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m a lady! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I know it! I can’t fail, I’m number one
Already!! We're all lady!! Odori odorou
Already!! We're all lady!! Let's dance a dance!
Ippo ippo deai ya wakare wa
One step at a time, our meetings and partings
Ai ni naru Amusement
make up the amusement that becomes love
Already!! We're all lady!! Hajimetai
Already!! We're all lady!! I want to get started
Yukeba nareru
If you try, you can do it
Motto zentai minna Only one
So we can all become one
Everyone at the back!
We can see you just fine, okay?!
And everyone on the second balcony! We can see you, too, okay?!
Isn't it just incredible?
I can't believe we're singing in such a big hall, surrounded by so many fans!
It's racing so  hard right in here!
How about all of you?!
Am I sparkling?!
You are!
We were able to work hard
enough to come all this way
because all of you are here,
cheering for us just like this!
Really and truly, each and
every time! Thank you!
Hey now! Isn't it a little
early to look at the past?
Yeah, yeah! This is
just our starting line!
We've got to try harder
and harder, don't we?
That's right.
But first, we must make today's
performance a tremendous success!
All you big boys and
girls in the audience!
Let's all play together and have
fun until the very last minute!
In order to reach all of your hearts, I,
too, will sing to the best of my ability!
Let's get going, then!
But before that...
Here's today's surprise guest!
Go for it!
Hey, you girls!
What's this supposed to mean?!
Nobody told me about this!
Ryuuguu Komachi's Producer
and  idol, Akizuki Ritsuko-san!
Ricchan–!
It turns out she's going to be
on stage with all of us tonight!
Right?
Ritsuko! Thank you!
Ricchan! Come out here already!
I–I get it already.
Sheesh.
I walked right into this one.
Everyone wants to be on
stage with you, Ritsuko.
I mean, you're a member
of 765 Pro too, right?
I guess I could go out
there for just a little.
Sure! Go enjoy yourself.
I think we're approaching our goal.
Those girls might be the very shape of the
perfect idol I started this company to search for.
And you showed them the way.
No.
It's only just begun
for me and the girls.
I see.
Of course.
Well then! Let's get going, too.
Yes, sir!
Okay! We're really
starting this time!
It's our new song!
Please listen!
However Long, However Far
Lyrics: Hata Aki  Composition/Arrangement: Sasaki Hiroto
Honki ga mitai? Ah ah!!
You want to see me get serious? Ah ah!
Honne de kyou mo odorou
Let's dance from the bottoms of our hearts today, too
Yubi wo ugokashitara...
If we move our fingers even a little...
Chiisaku I love you
A little "I love you"
Jyouzu ni nareru? Ah ah!!
Will I improve? Ah ah!
Jyoushou don don susumou
Climb higher and get better and better
Ude wa hane mitai ni...
My arms are like wings...
Tooku he Fly with you
I'll fly far away with you
Erabarete mitai
I want to be chosen
Hikari no Stage
For that stage made of light
Doryoku wa miryoku?
Effort is appealing?
Ganbare watashi! Ima!!
I can do it! Right now!!
Deshou? Kitto kagayaite
Right? I'm sure I'll shine
Deshou? Doko made made mo
Right? However ever far
Deshou? Yume no hajimari wa
Right? A dream starts
Futo shita guuzen deshou!
With an unexpected coincidence, right?!
Kono akogare wa motto
I want this aspiration
Itsu made made made mo
To last however ever long
Kibou nosete hohoemi wo
To place my hopes on a smile
Todoke ni iku no deshou!
And deliver it to you, right?!
Shichau?
Shall we do it?
Deshou? tte koto wa
Right? Which means
Shichau?
Shall we do it?
Deshou? tte koto ne
Right? That's what it means
Watashi-tachi no mirai
We have to go
Sagashi ni ikanakucha
Searching for our future
Watashi-tachi wa akiramenai
We won't give up
Kokoro ga yobu mirai
On the future our hearts call for
Deshou? Kitto kagayaite
Right? I'm sure I'll shine
Deshou? Doko made made mo
Right? However ever far
Deshou? Yume no hajimari wa
Right? A dream starts
Futo shita guuzen deshou!
With an unexpected coincidence, right?!
Kono akogare wa motto
I want this aspiration
Itsu made made made mo
To last however ever long
Kibou nosete hohoemi wo
To place my hopes on a smile
Todoke ni iku no deshou!
And deliver it to you, right?!
Ah ah!
Yay!
Encore! Encore! Encore!
You can keep going, right?!
Of course! Piece of cake!
Excuse me! One more song, please!
Encore! Encore! Encore!
Can you play it for us?
Then we'll keep going!
765 Pro!
Fight!
Yeah!
Encore! Encore! Encore!
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Honey! I missed you so much!
Are you okay now?
I can lend you a shoulder.
Thanks.
I'm just fine now.
It really is easiest to relax here.
You sound like
some old geezer!
That's right! It's dead boring when we can't toy around with you!
Yeah, yeah!
Everyone... I'm sorry I've
been away for so long.
Don't worry. We used that opportunity to take a good look at ourselves.
It also taught us how
important you are to 765 Pro.
I see.
You know, Honey,
about "Are We Live!?"
They're renewing us, and come spring, we're all cast to be on "Are We Live!? Revolution!"
Nobody told me about that!
Also, Miki's and my musical
will be performed nation-wide!
Th–That's incredible!
Way to go!
Don't be surprised
just yet, Producer.
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
Tah-dah!
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
The finest office space, just for you!
Roughly
4 mins walk
from the
station
「Project Announcement Meeting」 to be held
Complete Proposal
A spacious building
overlooking the city
I–Is this...?
How is it?
This will be our new office.
New office?!
This?
Well, as luck would have it, I caught wind that we could get in here cheap, you see.
So I went out on a limb
and decided to move us!
And thanks to that, the office
safe is now completely empty.
Chief! This really is  cheap!
Isn't it?!
Let's see... what's the
company's name...?
Blackwell Company?
I don't think I've
ever heard of them.
O–On TV!
Construction firm Blackwell Company has stated an intent to halt their latest building project.
Blackwell Company bankrupted?
Mr. Kuroi Takao denies involvement
This signals the firm's
evident bankruptcy.
However, the man thought to be involved, Mr. Kuroi Takao,
What does that mean?
Blackwell Company bankrupted?
Mr. Kuroi Takao denies involvement
has denied any involvement.
P–President Kuroi?!
Which means...
Well, sorry everyone!
It looks like I've been had...
Issho ni utaou
Let's sing together
And I thought we'd finally
get to move into a big office...
Issho no toki naraba
If it's when we're together
Oh well.
Issho de yukou
Then let's go together
That's so dumb.
A total let down.
I thought it'd turn out like this.
Issho no yume wo miyou
Let's dream about being together
Shouldn't we just appreciate how going up
and down the office stairs keeps us in shape?
Issho ni miyou
Let's see that dream together
But it really is
pretty disappointing.
Issho ga ii motto zutto
Let's be together forever
You think so? The way I see it,
it's not so bad where we are now.
Taisetsu ni shiyou isshou
And let's treasure each other all our lives
It'd probably be tough to
clean such a big building, too.
It's hard to settle down when
the place is too spacious, anyway.
Nee minna ni Thank you
Hey! Thank you to everyone
The words, "Wherever I lay
my hat is home," come to mind.
Kokoro kara Thank you
Thank you, straight from my heart
I guess that's right. We have so
many memories packed away here.
Itsumo itsumo
Because you've always, always
Soba ni itekurete
Stood by my side
We can always just
start over from scratch.
Nee jibun ni Thank you
Hey! Thank yourself
Everyone, together!
Right!
Kokoro he to Thank you
A "thank you" straight to the heart
Huh? We're already out of drinks.
Konna suteki na
Because such wonderful
I'll go buy some, then.
Minna ga iru kara
People are here with me
Oh, that's all right. Producer-san,
you should sit back and relax for today.
Hitori (hitori) sekai ga atte
There was (there was) a single world
I'll go get them.
Haruka, I'll go with you.
Hold up a second.
Meguri aeba
If we could travel it
I'll give you the money...
Is that...?
Sore ga shiawase
That would be bliss
Yeah. I'm putting it to good use.
I'm so glad...
Issho ni utaou
Let's sing together
What? What?
Was that a present from
Haruka or something?
Issho no toki naraba
If it's when we're together
Yeah. To celebrate my
discharge from the hospital.
Issho de yukou
Then let's go together
No, no!
I won't give Honey up,
even to you, Haruka!
Issho no yume wo miyou
Let's dream about being together
Issho ni miyou
Let's see that dream together
Issho ga ii motto zutto
Let's be together forever
My, today really is
a wonderful day.
Taisetsu ni shiyou isshou
And let's treasure each other all our lives
Yes. It really is.
It begins here.
And that will become the end.
But, I'm sure one day...
...it will become a new beginning!
You can go anywhere!
Because we're all together!
So we'll be just fine for sure!
The dream we're shooting for...
...is Top Idol!
With these bonds...
...and with this wish...
...held to our hearts.
Producer-san!
Ready, and...!
Thank you! Please continue
to produce us in the future!
Okay! Now, everyone!
Let's take a picture!
Issho ni utaou
Let's sing together
Issho no toki naraba
If it's when we're together
Chief. Sorry, but if
you would, please.
Issho de yukou
Then let's go together
Of course. Leave it to me.
Honey! Hurry, hurry!
Issho no yume wo miyou
Let's dream about being together
Nii-chan! Here, here!
Issho ni miyou
Let's see that dream together
Sure...
Issho ga ii motto zutto
Let's be together forever
Well then! Smile, smile!
Taisetsu ni shiyou isshou
And let's treasure each other all our lives
There!
Daisuki dakara isshou
Because I'll love you all my life
Issho ni iyou isshou
Let's be together, all our lives
See you again!