Hey–!
Wait, Inumi!
I'll never understand
if you keep running!
You've got to tell me the reason!
Inumi!
Ganaha-san?
CHANGE! Ima wa kawaru sekai kagayake
Change! It's a changing world, shine!
CHANGE! Ima wa watashi no sekai
Change! It's my world
Watashi no mono CHANGE
It belongs to me! Change!
Kirameku Stage
The shining stage
Event gurabia CM
Events, photo shoots, commercials,
Terebi de Show time
Showtime on TV
Hajimaru tsuzuku Story
A beginning, a continuing story!
Nando eru chii demo
No matter how many times we attain this position
Donna Rival datte
No matter the rival
Makenaide Try again!
Don't give up and try again!
Tachi agaru Story
It's a story about standing up
Encore wa My life
My life is an encore
Ichido no Live
A once-upon-a-live
Susume dokomade mo
Keep moving forward and never stop
Show must go on!
The show must go on!
Three
Two
One!
CHANGE! Ima wa kawaranai yume egaite
Change! It's an unchanging dream we're drawing
CHANGE! Ima wo suki ni jiyuu ni
Change! It's a time to do what you want and be free!
Try lady!
Aim to be a lady!
CHANGE! Ima wo atarashii ni Live
Change! It's a time to start a new show
Oikakenagara
While we chase after
Watashi rashii watashi de
A me who's really me
Motto motto Your dream come true!
Keep trying, keep trying! Your dream will come true!
I love you all!
Episode 16
How It Feels to be All Alone
Inumi!
Why'd you flip your dinner bowl?
What's with those rebellious eyes?
You're the one who
kicked your dinner bowl!
Even if it's not handmade, I made sure it's part of a balanced diet!
Why are you the only
one who's so selfish?
What do you mean, you're
representing everyone?
Hamuzou, you think so, too?
Just whose side are you on, anyway?!
What on Earth is going on?
It looks like they're fighting
about breakfast this morning.
It looks like they can actually
communicate like that.
Today's a recording day for
"Break Out! Animal World," isn't it?
Every Sunday morning at 7:30AM
Watch with your who le family!
Break Out!
Hibiki and Inumi are
the leads for the show...
Are they going to be all right
if they keep going like that?
Don't be so stubborn, Inumi!
I–Inumi-chan is really
popular on that show, too.
Y–Yeah, she sure is.
By the way, Yukiho.
There's a dog right there,
but you look just fine.
Y–Yes. I'm n–not scared at all.
N–Neither am I!
Bonds
Not scared at all!
Chihaya-chan!
You look kind of down.
Are you all right?
J–Just fine. I've got to get to voice practice.
See you later.
Yeah. Work hard!
What was that?!
That's just cruel!
I can't believe you said
that! You're inhuman!
She's not human. Right?
Now I'm mad!
I don't even care!
And you don't have to come to recording!
Let's go, Hamuzou!
Hey, wait! Hibiki!
It looks like things are
going well as usual
with that animal show you oversee.
Oh yes, all thanks to you.
There are no problems
with the plan, right?
None. It's all been taken care of.
The upper levels can't
even be present for filming.
I believe we'll see Ganaha Hibiki relieved of her position by the end of today.
Excellent work.
No, no. I've been under your
wing since I started out.
I hope we can maintain relations into the foreseeable future.
I'll accompany you to the recording.
President Kuroi, you want to go in person?!
Of course. Jupiter will be working with them today, after all.
Not to mention I suddenly want to see 765 Pro's unsightly tears.
Checkmate!
You're kidding!
Inumi-chan is taking the day off?
I'm sorry. It seems like
she wasn't feeling well.
Dear me! You must be
worried, Hibiki-chan!
I–It wouldn't even matter
if that stupid Inumi were here.
I'll make the show
interesting all by myself!
She's so brave!
It's precisely because you're worried
that you're putting on such a brave front.
But this might be a problem.
We need to find another
animal to play the lead.
In that case,
let's use this guy.
Oh my, supervisie!
This is Black Falchion the Third.
I thought something like this
might happen, so I came prepared.
I do appreciate it, but...
He looks kind of unsociable
compared to Inumi-chan.
He's just nervous!
Hi there, Inuzaburou!
Excuse me, Ganaha-kun!
His name is Black Falchion the Third!
Good boy! Good boy!
Hi there, Inuzaburou!
What are you doing, Inuzaburou?!
I–Is this really all right?
That's a good question...
Four!
Three!
Two!
Hiya!
It's Ganaha Hibiki!
First off is everyone's favorite
Break Out! Animal World's
Animal Explorer Squad segment!
Today, we've got a new squad member!
Tah-dah!
Meet Inuzaburou!
Let's go ahead and
hear how excited he is!
How about it, Inuzaburou?
The mic...!
Keep
going!
A–Anyway, I can't wait to see what kind of animals we'll meet today!
So let's get a sunny start
to today's adventure!
I'm so tired...
If Inumi were here, I wouldn't
have to suffer like this.
No no no! Who cares about Inumi?!
Doesn't even matter if she's not here!
Hibiki.
We're going to change locations to film after this like usual.
It sounds like we can find some
animals close to the pond today.
Okay! Got it.
And also... I heard this from
the director a second ago,
it sounds like there was a sudden
decision for Jupiter to come as guests.
Them?
It sounds like they'll be
filming for a different segment,
so you probably won't have
to deal with them directly.
We have no idea what 961 Pro is up to.
Keep on your toes.
I'll never  give in to dirty cheaters!
Our guests, Jupiter, have arrived!
I'll go have a look.
Make sure you keep your guard up.
Excuse me. Ganaha-san!
Yes?
It seems not everyone
can fit on the transfer bus,
so the director instructed
me to take you separately.
P–Please, this way.
But my producer isn't back yet.
Yeah. He'll come later on the bus.
Touma-kun! Touma-kun!
Hokuto! Look over here!
Shouta, you're awesome!
Hey, isn't this your first
time meeting Jupiter-chan?
Huh? I don't really need to–
Let me introduce you.
This man here is the incredibly popular
765 Pro's dyna-dyna mite-mite producer–
Did you say 765 Pro?
So you're the guy.
I've heard all about you.
Like how you use all sorts of
dirty tricks to sell your idols.
What was that?!
I don't know what you've been told,
but 765 Pro isn't that kind of office.
And on top of that, we will
never  lose to 961 Pro.
What's with him?
I'm so glad you boys are getting along.
They sure are!
Y–You really think so?
I see.
So that's 765 Pro's man.
He's got a face made
for such a lowly office.
And the fact that he's
here alone means...?
Yes. The plan is already in motion.
I see.
Revolution always comes about suddenly.
Because everything changes all at once.
W–We're here.
Okay–
Huh?
Is this the place?
My producer said we'd
be filming next to a pond.
Huh?
Sorry!
Wh–What's going on?
Wait!
I'm just doing what I was told!
Told you? Who did?!
What a sorry sight.
Inumi-chan won't budge an inch.
Can't we do something about her?
I don't think we can.
But Hibiki-chan is always saying,
"I'm going to work hard today
for Inumi and the others!"
Oh? It's the phone.
Hello. This is 765 Pro.
My, Producer-san.
Huh? Hibiki-chan?
No, we haven't heard from her over here.
Isn't she with you?
Well, they're telling me she just got out of the car while we were in transit.
Just got out of the car?
That can't be right.
That's what I think, too.
Did you call Hibiki-chan's cell phone?
I still have it from when she left it with me before recording.
Anyway, I'll call back.
Bye.
How did that happen?
Why did you put her in a separate car instead of the team bus, anyway?
Well...
I was told to treat her specially because she's our main emcee.
Please, wait!
Hibiki would never–
Right?
She's the kind of girl who waits until the end
even when her part is already recorded.
But you know...
You can never understand
these modern kids.
It's kind of awkward to say this
with someone from her office here,
but once they get popular,
their attitudes all change.
You're kidding!
Our idols aren't like that!
Everyone says that.
How about it, director?
Let's use this opportunity to entrust the emcee spot to another idol.
To Jupiter-chan?
Right.
They're not only popular,
but they'd be perfect as replacements.
It must be some kind of fate that
they were here as guests today, right?
I suppose so.
Hibiki-chan would be best without a doubt,
but if we push too hard, we have to consider our on-air circumstances.
Please wait just a little longer!
Please! I'll find her somehow,
so please, just a little longer...!
If you insist, I'll wait.
But I want to finish filming
while it's still light out.
I know.
I'll be sure to make it in time!
I wonder if he'll be all right?
Who knows?
Hey!
Anyone!
Hey! Producer!
Director-san!
It's no use. Nobody's coming.
I'd climb up, but it's impossible
with the soil so loose.
I wonder if this is exactly what
Producer was warning me about...
We have no idea what 961 Pro is up to.
Keep on your toes.
What now...?
If I don't make it in time for recording, I'll...
You want me to throw you
up onto the cliff, Hamuzou?
Why?
What?!
You'll contact Inumi and the
others and have them help?!
Inumi would be able to sniff
out the recording location?
No way! I can't do it!
Inumi and I are fighting right now!
That stupid Inumi can–
Hamuzou...?
H–Hamuzou!
Lyrics: yura  Composition: Nakanishi Keimi  Arrangement: Konishi Takao
Hamuzou...
Rain...?
Ready Trial Dance
Hibiki–
Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow!
Hibiki!
Every boy do it
Every girl do it
Yeah! Yeah!
Ima ga hajimaru It's brand new stage
We're gettin' started on a brand new stage
Luckily, it looks like a passing rain.
When it lets up, let's start
filming with Jupiter as our main.
Yume wo kizandeku Pure heartbeat
Our pure heartbeat carves out our dreams
I guess so.
Stand up
The filming for the mini-segment
went splendidly as well.
Dress up
Light up
Zettai Never give up
We'll never, ever give up
Just what you'd expect from pop icons!
I guess.
Saa Step by step
Now, step by step
I do think they'd manage
without any errors.
Jibun no mama
The way we want to go
Saa Good bye dream
Now, goodbye dream
Sheesh.
Nothing's been going right since I had that fight with Inumi this morning.
Real ni Metamorphose
It's a real metamorphosis
Itsudatte I can go now
We can go whenever we want
Inumi... Why'd she get so
worked up just over dinner?
Motto Crazy burning heart
A bigger crazy burning heart
Ready trial dance
Chikaratsuyoku Life
Living a strong life
Every boy do it
Every girl do it
Hamuzou-chan!
Don't stop music
Hamuzou!
Did you come here by yourself?
Where's Hibiki-chan?
It's like he's trying to
speak to us, I know it!
He's really cute, but we have
no idea what he's saying!
Inumi-cha–?
H–Hey... Wai–
What?
Could she be telling us to
take her to Hibiki-chan...?
Come to think of it,
up until just a little while ago,
I made everyone's food
by hand, one by one.
I'd cut up the things they
didn't like real small,
and mix them in with their favorites.
But recently, it's gotten so busy...
Hey, Inumi! Nekokichi!
Everyone else, too! Food's on!
I've got work now.
Make sure you all watch the place together.
See you later!
That's right.
That's right!
Inumi wasn't just talking about the food.
Not about a balanced diet or anything.
"I want to be with you."
That must have been all she wanted.
But despite that, I blamed Inumi,
fought with her, said terrible things to her...
I'm horrible!
I–Inumi?!
Why are you here?!
And the rest of you...
You're all dirty...
I'm sorry, everyone!
I didn't understand anything!
Yeah!
I'm sorry. I still haven't found Hibiki.
I see...
I knew it.
You're just lucky it was raining.
Okay, everyone. We're going to retake the Animal Explorer Squad opening
with Jupiter as our mains!
Hurry up and get ready!
Don't make our pop icons wait!
The Sun needs to read the atmosphere.
Wouldn't have minded if
it rained just a little more.
Ciao! You've got some long eyelashes there.
Kuroi-san, we've started filming.
As according to plan, Jupiter is filling the role of main emcee.
I see!
That producer from
765 Pro looked so frustrated!
He didn't even know that in truth,
that AD fooled her and brought her out,
then left her all by herself.
I figured as much.
7–765 Pro!
I've thought you were acting
a little funny for a while now,
but I never though you'd confess everything all by yourself.
So you must be President Kuroi.
That's right.
I'm going to tell the director right away and have filming canceled.
I won't let 961 Pro
continue to have their–
Can you?
What?
Regardless the reason,
it's true that the idol from your third-rate office disappeared from the set.
Jupiter is filling that hole.
Do you really have the
right to stop them?
Right, right!
If you want to stop Jupiter's recording,
you'd better bring some idols
from your place right now!
If you can, at least!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Sorry I'm so late!
Hibiki!
Is that...?
So she made it.
I was so worried, Hibiki!
Are you all right?
Yeah!
Producer! Director-san!
I'm so sorry for worrying you both!
Don't worry about that! You're back now!
Okay, everyone. Make the proper
adjustments to your preparations.
Sorry, but Jupiter-chan's
got the rest of the day off.
What?!
What the heck.
Rehearsal went perfectly, too.
Ciao! We had fun.
Don't screw around.
Disappearing as she pleases,
reappearing as she pleases...
Wh–What could you mea–
U–Um, President Kuroi...!
There must be some sort of mistake, so–
We're through with you.
U–Um! Wait!
President Kuroi!
What happened back there, old man?
It would seem 765 Pro put one over us with their foul play.
They must have thought toying with
you would be payback for the other day.
There are limits to the
vengeance one should seek!
Those guys from 765 Pro
really are beyond help.
If you're idols, you should
fight us with your talent!
Okay then, let's get
the main event started!
Three!
Two!
Hiya!
Today's Break Out! Animal World
is brought to you with
all  of these friends!
To tell the truth, everyone here
is a part of my irreplaceable family!
You really pulled us out
of the fire, Otonashi-san.
You shouldn't thank me,
but thank Inumi and the others.
They searched all over the
mountain to find Hibiki-chan.
The bonds between HIbiki-chan, Inumi-chan and the other animals are just incredible.
I wonder what kinds of
animals we'll meet this week?
Well then, let's get this expedition started!
Okay, everyone! We're gonna run!
Itsudatte kouen de
Whenever we're at the park
Arukidaseru nanka naru nara
If starting to walk can take care of things
Kagayaite mitsumete
Shine, look
If we're all together,
everything's no problemo
from now on, too!
Ima hajimaru!
It's starting!
IT'S A BRAND NEW DAY!
CATCH UP! Mitsukemashou
Catch up! Let's go find
Hitomi no naka ni utsuru
What I see reflected in your eyes
DREAMING! Sono saki no
Dreaming! And beyond that
Tokidoki wo kanji-kai no
We'll just play it by ear
STRAIGHT na omoi tomerarenai no otome no atsui HAATO
A girl's burning heart can't be stopped with direct feelings
Deaeta kamo ne hontou no watashi kara
Because I might have finally met the real me
ALL RIGHT!
Nankurunaisa!
No problemo!
Susume! Makenai! Koko kara hajimaru!
Keep going! Don't lose! This is where we start!
Te to te wo tsunaide hashiridasu
Let's hold hands and start running
Jibun tachi no mirai ha maketari hekondari shinai
We won't lose or get down in our future
Sekai ga kyou de irun dakara
Because the world exists only in the here and now
Tobikonjyaeba tabun ALL RIGHT
If we jump in, it'll probably be all right
Ima hajimaru!
It's starting!
IT'S A BRAND NEW DAY!
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
Let's see... recording
is in high resolution,
set two decks for backup
copies, and then–
What's wrong,
Yukiho-san?
Shijou-san!
Next week I'm going
to camp out at home!
Everyone,
next week will
be a sight to see!
Even if it's just
for this week...
Makoto, A True Prince