Thanks for your help!
Nice work today.
First Laugh
This is Music Today!
Today's chart topper is Ryuuguu Komachi's "Rainbow Button"!
To Shinjuku, please.
Kimi ga fureta kara nana iro Button
Because you touched it, it's a rainbow button
Rainbow Button
Lyrics: Endou Fubito  Composition/Arrangement: Uchida Tetsuya
It dyes everything
with the color of love.
Subete wo koi de someta yo
It dyes everything with the color of love
Donna dekigoto mo koete yukeru tsuyosa
And gives strength to overcome any event
And gives strength to–
Kimi ga boku ni kureta
You gave it to me
In-Depth Report 12 Pages
Songstress with a Voice
from Heaven
Kisaragi Chihaya
10K Word Interview
Kisaragi Chihaya's shocking life story
Advances since her debut
765 Pro
and meeting her colleagues
When the new year arrives
YOU NEED SOME
RAMEN!!!
"Otona ni nattara ne"
"When you become an adult"
Chotto yudan shiteru
You let your guard down
Kimi no yokogao wo ne
And I see your face
Everyone's
favorite
765 Pro
Everyone's
favorite
765 Pro
Idol Feature!!
Their warmth and energy
won't lose to winter's cold!
Gravure &
interview
pages!
Miteiru no yo mada ima demo
From the side, even now
Hora ne kizuitara?
Haven't you realized yet?
Onaji me no takasa
Our eyes see on the same plane
Thank you very much.
Itsu no ma ni ka shoujo jyanai
I was no longer just a girl before you knew it
Odoroku–
Aren't you–
Just made it!
'Morning!
'Morning.
Good morning!
Iori's girls aren't here yet?
Traffic was pretty bad,
so I thought I'd be last.
Um...
We got a call that Iori's group was running behind schedule, so they couldn't come...
It looks like it'll be hard
to get everyone together.
You're kidding!
But it's the first day of our joint
rehearsals for the New Year's show...
Nothing we can do about it.
Let's just go through everything with the members we have here.
Yeah. You're right.
There's not much time until
the show. We have to focus!
Um... actually...
Sorry!
I'm really sorry!
We need to leave early.
Changin' my world!! Kawaru sekai kagayake
Changin' my world!! The changing world shines
Changin' my world!! Watashi no sekai
Changin' my world!! It's my world
Watashi no mono Change!!
It belongs to me! Change!!
Kirameku Stage
The shining stage
Event gurabia CM
Events, photo shoots, commercials,
Terebi de Show time
Showtime on TV
Hajimaru tsuzuku Story
A beginning, a continuing story!
Nando NG demo
No matter how many times we NG
Donna Rival datte
No matter the rival
Makenaide Try again!
Don't give up and try again!
Tachi agaru Street
It's a path you pave by standing up
Encore wa nai Life
Your life doesn't get an encore
Ichido no Live
It's a one-shot performance
Susume dokomade mo
Keep moving forward and never stop
Show must go on!
Three
Two
One!
Changin' my world!! Kawaranai yume egaite
Changin' my world!! It might be an unchanging dream we're drawing
Changin' ima wo!! Suki ni jiyuu ni kaeru Ready!!
Changin' right now!! But change it however you want! Ready!!
Changin' mae wo!! Atarashii mirai oikakenagara
Changin' what's in front of us!! While we chase a new future
Watashi rashii watashi de motto motto
I'll just be myself to keep on, keep on
Dreams come true
I love all
Episode 23
I
That's right. We're in the middle of adjusting their schedules, so...
Right. I hope that's acceptable.
Hello! This is 765 Pro.
I'm back!
Thank you for using our idols.
I'm sorry, but our schedule
for those days is so full...
That's right. We're very sorry.
Iori
Azusa
Ami
Haruka
Miki
Of course. I'll pass that
on to President Takagi.
Haruka
Miki
We look forward to your
continued patronage.
Oh! Welcome back.
I'm back, Kotori-san.
Bonds
Haruka-chan, did you have
something lined up for later on?
Nope. But if I don't come back to the office, it doesn't feel like my day has ended.
While I'm happy you
come back here,
you've got a magazine interview tomorrow morning, don't you?
You'll be recording for
TV in the afternoon,
so in order to stay rested up,
you should take it easy and just go home.
Will do.
Thank you.
Kotori-san?
What is it?
Bonds
Did anyone besides me
come to the office today?
Just you, Haruka-chan.
Well, with everyone's schedules stuffed so full, you can kind of see how they couldn't...
Of course.
I'm back!
Welcome back, Producer-san.
So cold out there...!
Oh, Haruka. I didn't
know you were here.
Yep! Welcome back.
Yup. I'm back.
How're you feeling?
Anything happen?
I didn't fall once today!
Don't you think that's amazing?
Oh? That is amazing!
It's a miracle.
Then I'll show you
something cool as a reward.
Something cool?
Here.
This is for the New Year's show...!
Hot off the press.
Everyone looks so cute!
However long, however far!
I think it turned out great.
It's our last concert of the year,
so we really have to make it a success.
Everyone seems so busy right now,
with your schedules not matching up,
but if you all work together,
I'm sure it'll be a great show.
Let's do our best, Haruka!
Right!
Let's all make it a big
success, Producer-san!
Okay, everyone!
Unity's the word! Unity!
Let's all work together and
make this a great show!
Takatsuki Yayoi's
ABC's
of Cooking
Walking Leisurely
Azusaunter
Are We Live!?
Sunday
Bullet-Speed Girls
In order to do that, we'll have to match up
our schedules and get to our joint rehearsals.
We only have a little time left, so let's do our best together!
Write message (New)
To
Subj.
Att.
so let's do our best together!!
We only have a little time left,
Everyone, the time is set!
6PM Everyone gather up!
Pro
Thank you, everyone!
Sure. Nice work.
Oh, Amami-san!
Yes?
Can we talk a little?
U–Um...
It won't take very long.
Sorry. Today's really bad for me.
I'm really sorry.
Hi, everyone!
Hi!
Hi.
Nobody else is here yet?
It sounds like Minase-san and Ganaha-san are running late at their last jobs,
so they just can't make it.
Really?
I think Ami-chan's group hasn't
finished recording, either.
She said, "Apologize
to Haruka-chan for me."
I see.
From
Subj.
Att.
Received message
Hoshii Miki
Haruka, I'm really sorry
The plane is late, and I'm still
at Haneda Airport (T△T)
Miki can't make it, either.
I guess it really will be hard to get everyone together for practice.
We got to practice
together so much last year...
Oh well!
Let's practice, even if it's just the members we have here today.
You're right. Let's give today's video to the girls who couldn't make it.
Oh! Then I'll go borrow the camera.
Thanks, Makoto-chan!
Azusa-san, can you help
me with my stretches?
Okay. Let's get you
good and limber.
Okay!
Ready?
Yes!
Ready, and... one, two, three, four.
You were up early this
morning, weren't you?
Yeah.
Huh? How'd you know?
I asked Otonashi-san.
She said you had your regular radio
recording session moved to the morning.
Yeah. If I hadn't, I wouldn't have
been able to make today's rehearsal.
The staff was nice enough to say, "Well, if that's the case...!"
Chihaya-chan?
Haruka! I'll ask Producer to try and
reschedule my recording overseas tomorrow.
I can't allow us to perform at the
show in the state we're in, either.
You can't, Chihaya-chan.
You've got to go!
Haruka...
Producer-san was telling me about it.
He said this overseas recording thing will determine where you go from here on.
You've been making all
sorts of preparations, right?
We'll be fine!
Everyone wants to practice.
Oh! But make sure you're back for the day of the New Year's show.
Well, of course!
Then, make sure you go.
Okay.
It'll be a little lonely, though.
Yeah.
Sukoshi dake demo todokerareta naraba shiawase
So if we can deliver even a few of them to you, I'd be on cloud nine
Here's a suggestion:
During the period until
our next full rehearsal,
how about people who are
working together gather up
and practice together,
even it's just a few of us?
I'm totally, totally sure things
will turn out better that way!
Let's all do our best together!
Marutsuki Udon
What the heck?!
And "What the heck?!" back at you!
Excuse me! The impoverished-looking... parent and child... oh, sorry!
What am I saying? Sorry.
One more time please!
It just won't end.
Yeah.
Next time you screw up, we're replacing you with Handsome over there.
W–W–Wait a second,
you don't need to do that!
Wanna get started with just us two?
Don't you feel bad for
Takane-chan and Hibiki-chan?
I'm sorry, Harurun!
I'll get it right!
I'm out of time...
Oh, really?
Yeah...
I see...
Then let's give it everything
at tomorrow's full rehearsal, okay?
Hello! Amami speaking.
Oh, Haruka? Today's full
rehearsal has been canceled.
We just couldn't open up
everyone's schedules.
Oh! Welcome back, Haruka-chan.
I'm back.
Um, where's Producer-san?
He's here. He's in the middle of
a meeting on the phone, though.
No, I don't think that works.
Right.
Me too.
Oh, no.
I really think we should prioritize the audience and making sure they enjoy themselves.
Yes, of course! That's the kind of
show everyone at 765 Pro puts on!
Yes! We're counting on you.
Haruka, I'm really
sorry about yesterday.
I got called back just as I was
headed for the studio, and–
It's fine!
You went on about that
all yesterday over the phone.
More importantly, there's
still time before we're on,
so let's get Yukiho and practice for the show with us three!
Haruka, first let's focus
on today's live broadcast.
Little Match Girl is a new song
being performed for the first time,
not to mention this
is a live broadcast.
Can you heat it up
We can't mess up.
Yukiho's been working hard under the pressure of being lead, too.
at frozen night like a little match girl, yeah
So let's concentrate
on the present for now!
Kiss me and burn it up
When I look into your heart
Osonai koro no chiisana Page
Like a little page from when you were a child
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: ESTi
Dare mo ga yume miteru ima mo
Everyone dreams, even now
Otona ni narezu kogoeta hibi wa
Never growing up, these frozen days
Shiawasesou ni nemutteru
Sleep happily away
Nani mo miataranai shiroi iki dake ga mabushiku
I can't see a thing, but my white breath is so dazzling
Kaze ni fumareta fuku wo sotta sasaete
Gently holding down my clothes, ruffled by the wind
Haruka-chan! I didn't screw up today!
Yeah! You were incredible, Yukiho!
Yukiho! You were totally awesome!
Thank you, Makoto-chan!
Are We Live!?
Sunday
Okay, it's time for us to
say goodbye for this week!
Okay, Are We Live!? Sunday!
It looks like it's time for
us to part this week
once more!
Let's see you again next week!
Ready, and...!
Away
on
busi-
ness
Ready, and...!
Are we live?!
Sunday!
And we're clear!
Today was quite the ride, wasn't it?
My whole body hurts.
You okay?
Miki! If you don't hurry,
you won't make it.
Sorry, Haruka.
It doesn't look like I can
make practice today, either.
Okay.
Make sure you read your script.
Everyone else needs
to stay behind for a bit.
I need to tell you something.
Canceled?
Yes.
Why?!
That "ratings" thing?
No, the ratings are good. Really.
We want to keep it
going too, to be honest.
Actually, we've been getting requests to stop blocking up all of Sunday from other shows.
No way!
I'm so sorry!
We've been treated very well by this show, so I'd hoped we'd manage something...
So that's it...
What a shame.
It was a fun show, too.
Everything that has
a start has an end.
Anyway, let's do our
best 'til the very end.
We will do our best!
That's right! 'Til the very last episode,
make it fun, and make it interesting! Okay?
Okay!
Okay...
Iori-chan, wanna go
back part way together?
Sure. Fine with me.
Are you okay, Haruka?
Yes.
Here. The schedule for the musical.
Rehearsals start tomorrow at 8:00PM.
Huh? But I just told everyone that
we have practice together at that–
I know that.
But these roles will be very important experiences for both you and Miki.
You don't need to consider which is more important between this and the show.
No matter how I wake,
surely I'll dream again.
Though there be as many dreams as the number of stars in the sky,
the dream I dream shines
like the sun, blazing hot!
Stop! Stop!
Amami. Switch in.
O–Okay!
You hear me?
I intend to have one of you two play the lead for this work.
Just let it all out! Show me
everything you've got!
Throw yourself at this role!
No Smoking
Your break is ten minutes!
Just like the rumors said.
He's a really strict director.
Yeah.
But this is nothing for me.
I'm glad you're here with me, Miki.
I think I would have broken
if I'd been by myself.
I don't know who'll get the lead, but let's do our best together!
I don't wanna.
I want to be lead,
no matter what.
I think this is a chance
Honey gave me,
and I want Honey to
watch me when I play lead.
So I think it's probably wrong
to say we should work together.
Producer?
No, I haven't seen him today.
I'd imagine he's out with
someone on location.
That's right, of course.
Did you have some sort
of urgent business?
If he comes back while I'm here,
I can have him call you.
No. It's nothing important.
Thank you for staying late.
If you'll excuse me...
I'll sing! On behalf
of my proud dream!
Spring Storm
Cast
Anna
Reira
Amami Haruka
Hoshii Miki
Hmmm...?
Energetic...!!
Villagers
Switch!
Your break is fifteen minutes!
What's this?
Someone looks down!
Provisions for the front line.
How's the stage feel? Having fun?
Yes. It's fun.
There are so many
things to learn, too.
I see.
So I hear you stopped by the
office looking for me yesterday.
Did you have something you
wanted to talk to me about?
Um...!
I–
Honey! You came?
Oh, Miki...
You know, I'm working hard!
Right, Haruka?
Y–Yeah!
I see.
Your coach done lecturing you?
Not lecturing!
It's acting training!
Sorry sorry.
Oh, Miki. Did you have
some dorayaki already?
You brought dorayaki?
Sure did. I gave them to
the staff, so have some later.
Got it! Ho~ney's~ dora~yaki~
There's no honey in them, though...
Sorry, Haruka.
Let's pick up where we left off.
No. That's all right.
H–Haruka?
It's nothing at all.
It's all right.
What do you mean,
"It's all right"?
It's all right.
It really is.
Someone fell in!
Hey! Hurry!
Call an ambulance!
Hey! Are you all right?!
Why's the lift open?!
Operating
Next Episode Preview
Was I wrong?
Was it because
I was so selfish
that this happened?
Episode 24: Dream.
Dream