Sunday
Are
We Live!?
Sunday afternoon's new find,
the ever-elusive live program
Amami Haruka
Kisaragi Chihaya
Hoshii Miki
It's Are We Live!? Sunday!
This program is brought to the entire nation's living rooms live every week
by BooBoo S Akasaka Studio.
And we're back this week!
Everyone in front of your TV's!
Look at that cheering...
Haruka, Chihaya-san!
We can't lose to them
here in the studio!
Hey, look! It seems
we're already connected!
This week's top of the order is
right here!
Are
We Live!?
Hibiki
Hibiki Challenge!
Hiya!
Will her challenge succeed!?
Ganaha Hibiki
Ganaha-san, why are you
all the way out there?
This week, Hibiki-chan's
challenge will be
reaching the goal in front of our studio by the time we finish airing!
What?!
Hibiki– You don't have much time, so you should get going!
Huh?
G–Got it!
Then here I go!
Time Remaining
No problemo!
Can she really finish before time runs out?
Hibiki! Good luck!
Well then! Let's get this week started!
Are we live?!
Sunday!
CHANGE! Ima wa kawaru sekai kagayake
Change! It's a changing world, shine!
CHANGE! Ima wa watashi no sekai
Change! It's my world
Watashi no mono CHANGE
It belongs to me! Change!
Kirameku Stage
The shining stage
Event gurabia CM
Events, photo shoots, commercials,
Terebi de Show time
Showtime on TV
Hajimaru tsuzuku Story
A beginning, a continuing story!
Nando eru chii demo
No matter how many times we attain this position
Donna Rival datte
No matter the rival
Makenaide Try again!
Don't give up and try again!
Tachi agaru Story
It's a story about standing up
Encore wa My life
My life is an encore
Ichido no Live
A once-upon-a-live
Susume dokomade mo
Keep moving forward and never stop
Show must go on!
The show must go on!
Three
Two
One!
CHANGE! Ima wa kawaranai yume egaite
Change! It's an unchanging dream we're drawing
CHANGE! Ima wo suki ni jiyuu ni
Change! It's a time to do what you want and be free!
Try lady!
Aim to be a lady!
CHANGE! Ima wo atarashii ni Live
Change! It's a time to start a new show
Oikakenagara
While we chase after
Watashi rashii watashi de
A me who's really me
Motto motto Your dream come true!
Keep trying, keep trying! Your dream will come true!
I love you all!
A–Are we live?
Episode 15
Everyone Together, It's a Live
Broadcast! A Live Broadcast!
Okay! Our next feed is...
Yayoi–!
Here–
Everyone at the studio!
Yayoi! Where are you
broadcasting from today?
Bamboo Shoot Kindergarten
I'm here at Bamboo Shoot Kindergarten.
Tah-dah!
My helpers this week are
Azusa-san and Iori-chan!
Minase Iori
Miura Azusa
Helper
Everyone!
Good afternoon!
They're all hyped up, too!
The kindergarten has the day off today,
but everyone came
specially for the broadcast!
Yayoi and Azusa and Forehead
all look really cute in that outfit!
Takatsuki-san is adorable!
Thank you very much!
W–
Wait!
We can't play that off!
Y–Yayoi and Iori don't look out of place,
but Azusa-san is...
Are you sure we can broadcast this...?
Then let's deliver smiles and
happiness to everyone this week, too!
Smile Exercises
Lyrics: yura  Composition/Arrangement: Miyazaki Makoto
Minna atsumatte
Everyone! Gather up!
Smile taisou ikkuyo!
It's time for smile excercises!
Zettai Happy!!
We'll definitely be happy!!
Ichi ni
One, two!
Zentai Happy!!
Happy as a whole!!
San shi
Three, four!
Thirty-second break!
Saa dai ichi Smile taisou hajime!!
Let's start the number one smile exercise!!
Everything's going just fine so far.
I thought they might be a little down
because of the incident with 961 Pro,
but they look fine.
Yes.
961 Pro hasn't tried anything
since then, have they?
No. Nothing yet, at least.
But...
Everyone is focusing on the work they have right now, as a pro.
Yes.
That's what's important right now.
The song is ending and we're
coming back to the studio!
See you again!
Thanks, everyone!
Thank you to the teachers
and families involved as well.
We could feel their energy all
the way here in the studio, huh?
I wanted to wear that outfit, too!
Our next segment is...
It's sure got an interesting title.
It's called
"Kikuchi Makoto – Remodeling Plan"
Kikuchi Makoto
Remodeling
Plan
Remodeling?
Let's see...
For the details, we have on-site...
Yukiho!
Ladies' Fashion Floor
Y–Yes!
G–Good afternoon, everyone!
Hagiwara Yukiho
Gonna remodel you!
This is Hagiwara Yukiho,
here at our broadcast point!
D–During this segment, w–we'll–
For just a second,
I thought I saw Ganaha-san...
Huh?
U–Um...!
Ad-lib!
Yuki... H–Huh?
I–I'm pretty sure the script said–
Haruka!
You can't say "script!"
It looks like the picture has been restored!
D–Don't let it get to you.
Th–Though Makoto-chan
always looks handsome,
Ladies' Fashion Floor
our aim is to make
Makoto-chan even more so.
So with this shop's cooperation,
we're varying Makoto-chan's
outfits to experiment–
I–I mean...!
To raise her to new heights!
That sounds like fun!
I wish I could be there, too!
First, we'll show you a set of casual
clothes Makoto-chan picked herself.
I can't wait, either!
Makoto-chan, are you ready?
Ready!
Then let's see it!
Makoto-chan, go ahead!
Kya pipipipipi–n!
Makko Makori–n!
Cheer Meter
Kikuchi Makoto
Remodel me cute!
It's Kikuchi Makoto-chan!
Huh...?
Ladies' Fashion Floor
Nobody's–
Wait! Yukiho!
Say something!
She really was pushing it a bit...
The way I see it, it's not pleasing anyone.
No! No, Makoto-chan!
Ladies' Fashion Floor
Nobody wants that!
Nobody accepts it!
Huh?!
Everyone! Leave it to me!
This time, I'll take full responsibility
and give Makoto-chan a huge remodel!
If you'll excuse me!
W–Wait, Yukiho!
Back to you at the studio for now!
Yukiho's more worked up than ever!
She was kind of scary, actually.
How will Makoto's remodeling go?
We'll continue later!
Ami
Mami-chan
AmiMami-chan.
Number 1
Number one.
Out-of-body experience.
Followed by...
Gutted mackerel.
Tiered mochi.
Followed by...
Tokyo Tower.
When the segment's done,
we're going to commercial!
We'll be back in the studio in three minutes thirty seconds.
O–Ow! Stop!
The Sky Tree.
Followed by...
Ladies' Fashion Floor
The Yamanote Line.
Followed by...
The broadcast goes by so quickly.
I know, right?
I can hardly get my bearings straight.
Nice work so far.
Hon–
Producer!
Hey, hey! How was I?
I did a good job, right?
You had me a little worried,
but that was a nice save earlier.
Let's keep it up for the second half, okay?
Okay!
It looks like you've all
gotten pretty used to it.
Chihaya, you might want to
consider loosening up a bit.
O–Okay.
Loosen up...
Ami
Mami-chan
The End
The end.
Time Remaining
LIVE This week's challenge is [Reach the studio before time runs out!]
Will Ganaha Hibiki reach the finish line!?
Are we live?!
Our next segment is
Hibiki Challenge!
Hibiki
Ganaha-san's challenge this week is
to reach our studio by the
time we finish broadcasting!
Let's see what's happening!
Hibiki–!
H–Hiya!
Hibiki-chan! How're you doing?
How'm I doing?
How am  I doing...?
Um...
You look like you're having
some trouble, but are you okay?
N–No problemo!
I'll definitely make it to the
finish line, so keep watching!
Frequent Appearance
H–Hibiki-chan! That board...
Huh?
Just where is Ganaha-san running?
What about the board?
Hibiki could deal with a bear just fine.
Bear? Watcha talkin' about?
Hibiki! Keep at it!
W–We'll bring you updates as events warrant.
Here's our next segment!
Ramen.
No longer can it simply be called food.
It is a path of daily exploration.
advance and mankind itself.
Ramen is culture.
Ramen is evolution.
Ramen is possibility!
In search of new encounters today once more.
Shijou Takane's
Ramen Expedition
Writing characters in the
blue sky with a finger, fall ends.
Shijou Takane
Ramen Hunter
The leaves of the many trees,
too, have taken color.
Everyone, how does
the day find you?
This is Shijou Takane.
Hey, hey, Princess!
Futami Mami
Futami Ami
What kind of ramen are
we going to eat today?
We didn't get lunch, so we're starving!
Mami. Ami.
Though I understand your desire to rush,
we must first calm our hearts.
Meetings are but once in a lifetime.
They must be approached
with a quiet heart.
As the Princess wishes!
Then let us go.
Just look at this line!
Here?
Yes. This is the shop
we will call upon today.
Ramen Nijuurou.
Please, Princess! This way!
Excuse me!
We must first purchase here
something called a "ticket."
Simple accounting.
Full payment up front, huh?
Princess, what're you having?
I will proceed with a double cha shu.
Dear me.
Princess, you can't buy it
if you don't put money in.
Hard noodles, slightly hot, double
vegetables, extra garlic and tallow.
Did you just cast some sort of spell?
That sounded kinda official!
Th–There's so much it turned
into some kind of monster!
Ami can't handle this much,
but Mami can finish it easy, right?
Huh?!
Mami can't eat this much, either!
Mami. Ami.
Others are waiting.
Let us partake in peace and quiet.
Should we disturb
the flow of customers,
sales will be hindered,
and we will be a nuisance to the shop.
What do you mean by that?!
Princess is kinda scary!
Does this even count as reporting?
Am I still too stiff?
Huh?
I don't think so.
I wish I could be like you or Miki, too.
Huh?
Don't be like me!
I screwed up just a
second ago, after all.
Even now, when I have to ad-lib,
my head goes all white and I panic.
Miki's amazing, isn't she?
It's like she's completely
true to how she feels...
I get so impressed, and I always
think to myself, "She's unshakeable."
But it's fun, isn't it?
When we're all doing a
show together like this,
time always just flies by.
You're right.
One more minute!
It was exquisite.
It's good.
It's good, but...
I keep eating and eating, but the bean sprouts just won't go away!
And if we leave any, I just know Yayoicchi will get mad at us!
I never thought this segment
would end up a suicide run!
Shijou Takane's Ramen Expedition.
We had a wonderful
meeting again this week.
Let us seek another magnificent
meeting next week.
Shijou Takane's
Ramen Expedition
End
Are we live?!
Takane! Thanks!
Ami! Mami!
It's okay if you take your time!
Make sure to finish everything!
Well then, what's this that
was brought to the studio?
This week's refreshments!
It's Nijuurou Ice Cream,
a new product from Nijuurou Ramen
which we introduced
just a moment ago!
Let's have a taste!
This ice cream is kinda weird.
Haruka...!
At least they seem to think it's funny...
This is...!
Maybe it looks a little funny,
but it's shockingly good!
The viscosity of the soup
and sweetness of the ice cream
melt together in your mouth...
A little more casually...!
The name is kind of awkward,
but this is the best
ice cream I know!
It's true!
Honey, you want to try some, too?
H–Honey...
It might have honey in it, right?
Miki...
I'll lecture her later.
Next is the preview for this movie!
Ami
Mami-chan
AmiMami-chan.
Number 2
Number two.
I'm Ami.
I'm Mami.
Between Ami and Mami...
We're Amami!
Producer-san!
It's a movie! A movie!
Preview
This is the final battle!
765PRO Compilation
KiRaJem, full throttle!
Go–
Kisaragi–!
Ku...!
Kisaragi
Mysterious Robot
Azuscythe
Opposing the Harustein Army
Mankind's last hope!!
Yay– Yay–
Piloted by Ami and Mami
the giant robot
Kisaragi!
All hail the ironing board!
Ku...!
Ricchain
Miki-Miki! Why?!
Betrayal!!
If you insist on going forward,
do so only
once you defeat me!
Trouble!!
Mysterious Robot
Yukidrill
I'll dig a hole
and bury you in it!
Guys!
That's enough! Just get out of the way!
Friendship!!
Impossible!
They blocked AzuScythe's bla–
Miki-Miki!
I'll entrust you
with the fate of the Earth...!
Love!!
Evil!!
Kaze wa ten wo kaketeku
The wind soars through the heavens
[Endless Combine Kisaragi] Theme Song
Lyrics: Shirose Sai  Composition: Agematsu Noriyasu  Arrangement: Nakayama Masato
Fear me, and prostrate
thyself at my feet!
Revere and worship me!
Emerged from the darkness
Her Excellency Harustein's
Hikari wa chi wo terashiteku
And light bathes the ground
nefarious robot legions!!
Hito wa yume wo idaku
Mankind embraces its dreams
I found it, Miki-Miki.
Kisaragi's final,
greatest battle!!
Sou nazuketa monogatari
That is the name of this tale
Its outcome...
This is... Kisaragi's
final form!
arcadia...
Combine
Tobe! Umi yori mo hageshiku
Fly! More violently than the ocean
Combine!
Yama yori mo takadakuku
Higher than mountains
Ima watashi wa kaze ni naru
Now I become the wind
Combine!
Yume no hate made
Until the end of my dream
Endless Combine Kisaragi. The Movie.
Hyururarira
Hyururarira–
In theaters this winter.
Motto tsuyoku nare
Become stronger
We have to use Overmaster!
We'll show you!
Hyururarira
Here we go!
Mezasu arcadia
My goal is arcadia
Kisaragi!
Advance tickets and special gift
Now on sale
at the ticket window!!
Kisaragi Cell Phone Strap
Overmaster Version
Supplies are limited at each location
Advance Ticket Prices (with tax)
Adult/Student
Middle School/Toddler (Over 3 years of age)
Parent/Child Pair
Opening Day Prices (with tax)
Adult
Student
Middle School/Toddler (Over 3 years of age)
You can get a Kisaragi
Overmaster strap, too!
This winter, we're touring nation-wide!!
Revere and worship me!
Endless Combine Kisaragi!
We hope you enjoy it!
That was so cool!
It feels like you get surprisingly
sucked into villain roles, Haruka.
That's right!
It was so much fun when
I was playing the role!
Chihaya-chan, you play a mecha, right?
Only the voice...
W–Well then!
Next is the long-awaited
Kikuchi Makoto Remodeling Plan!
Part two!
Yes!
We've finished Makoto-chan's
changes over here.
Ladies' Fashion Floor
I think I did a great job,
if I do say so myself!
You really think so...?
Then let's have her make her entry!
Newly reborn, here's
Kikuchi Makoto-chan!
Tah-dah!
Can I fall in love with you?
I'm the reborn Kikuchi Makoto.
Cheer Meter
Makoto-chan, you look awesome!
Ladies' Fashion Floor
Are you sure this is right for me...?
Yes! It's right!
Actually, it might not be enough!
More!
Like this!
Senpai.
This one's mine.
Hands off, if you don't mind.
Cheer Meter
Makoto-kun, you look
super, super awesome!
Good, good!
And then! And then!
Ladies' Fashion Floor
Double the strength...
and double it again!
Blood is thicker than water.
What's done is done.
Cheer Meter
Makoto-chan, it's too good!
U–Um...
It might sound good,
but those are just proverbs, right?
And then like this!
Or this!
W–Wait, Yukiho...
Your eyes are kind of scary...
C-Camera! Let's get back to the studio!
Makoto-kun looked great!
Um, all things in moderation, right, Yukiho?
Let's see...
"We've uploaded an image of Haruka getting walloped a minute ago
to the show's home page
so everyone stop by!"
Huh?!
Next, we have–
The weather.
As you see here,
these are the skies all over Kanto.
It's a beautiful sunset, isn't it?
Not a single cloud!
We were blessed with
good weather all weekend.
Truly... Um...
I dear weather for an ex-cushion!
Ideal weather for an excursion!
Ideal weather for an excursion, apparently!
However, in party cooler
mounty-noose ray johns...
Particular mountainous regions!
I–In particular mountainous regions,
there might be sudden rainfall,
Yayoi, Azusa, Forehead! Thanks!
Who're you calling "Forehead?!"
Well now! We're approaching the end for this week's show.
I wonder if Ganaha-san is nearby?
Let's see! I can almost
hear her coming!
Hibiki–
Time Remaining
Huh?
I–Is that rain?
H–Hibiki-chan?!
Hibiki?
Where are you right now?
I can't... I can't see a thing!
Is this really the right way?!
It doesn't seem like she can
hear us here in the studio...
But there's no way this is
anywhere near us, right?
Oh, the ending...
It would seem our
time to part has arrived.
Which means...
Yes.
This week's Hibiki Challenge is, unfortunately
unsuccessful!
Hibiki
Challenge Unsuccessful!
That's too bad!
Hibiki-chan's going to keep
trying to finish the course?
I–Is that safe?!
Watashi dake ga motteiru Voice todoiteru kana?
Is the voice that only I have getting through to you?
We'll tell everyone the results of the
Hibiki Challenge on the show's home page!
Watashi dake no Performance kandou saserareru kana?
Is the performance only I can make touching your heart?
So everyone, make sure you
stop by the show's home page!
I wonder if Hibiki-chan is all right?
Mezase Idol NO.1
My goal is Idol No.1
I just hope she doesn't catch cold.
But this week was interesting, too!
I got a precious look at Yukiho-chan
and Makoto-chan's entanglement, too.
Ganbaruyo
And I'm workin' hard!
And what a look it was!
I've got to burn it and put it
in my collection right away!
Everyone has given me some energy,
so I've got to put my
best in at work tomorrow!
Hakkiri guchi wo iwasete morau to
If you'd let me speak my mind for a minute
Geinou katsudou shindoi desu
The entertainment business is tough!
Datte mannen suimin busoku de oyasumi mitei dashi
I mean, I'm short on sleep all year long and there's no vacation in sight
Well then, everyone!
See you again!
Itsu itsu made ni nani nani shinai to
"You've got things to do all day long
Ma ni awanai kara yoroshiku chan tte!
Or else we'll fall behind, so good luck!" they say!
Dance mo uta mo oshibai mo serifu mo
I've got dances and songs and lines for a drama
Oboerarenai!
But I can't remember all that!
Demone anata ga iru to watashi kujikenai
But you know, I won't break if you're with me
"Otona no jijyoo" de kimatta
I can overcome any
Tsurai koto demo nori koerareruyo
Of the hardships decided by "grown-ups' circumstances"
Faito!
Let's do it!
Watashi dake ga dekiru Smile mecha mecha miryoku desho?
Isn't the smile only I can do totally charming?
Watashi dake no totte oki Pose dokkiri & Sexy?
Isn't my best pose surprising and sexy?
Watashi dake ga motteiru Voice todoiteiru kana?
Is the voice that only I have getting through to you?
Watashi dake no Performance kandou saserareru kana?
Is the performance only I can make touching your heart?
Mezase Idol NO.1
My goal is Idol No.1
Ouen shitene
Hope you'll root for me!
Kyou mo ashita mo Training!
Today and tomorrow I'll be training
Sorezo Pro desho!
But that's what makes me a pro!
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
I wonder
what it's about?
It's obviously all
about my brilliance!
But the script says–
Script?
Everyone, look
forward to next week!
Wait! Finish what
you were saying!
How It Feels to be All Alone