Welcome
Members of 765 Pro
Courage
Junjirou
Seven chain!
Ami, no fair!
...all squishy and fluffy...
Is that right!
You've finally landed us an event, have you?
Not bad!
That's what makes you 765 Pro's hope.
Yes, sir! It was worth the trouble promoting.
Sure was.
Help him with anything he needs, Ritsuko-kun.
Yes, sir! Leave it to me!
Wait! Yukiho!
Hey, Yukiho!
Wh–What's going on?
I'm so sorry! I... I–
I'm so sorry!
There was nothing you could have done.
It was just bad luck today's teacher was a man.
Here...
Your nose is going to run all over your clothes.
God! Thanks to Yukiho's fear of men, you couldn't even call that a lesson.
Iori! You don't have to say it like that.
Don't you feel bad for Yukiho?
Hmph! What's your problem?!
Everything I said was true!
That's right, isn't it?
Someone like me should just...
should just...
dig a hole and bury myself in it–!
There it is! Yuki-pyon's Invincible Shovel!
Hey, Yukiho...
For the time being, you need to work on being able to take regular lessons even with male teachers.
A man...!
–or more importantly, maybe we need to lessen this distance between us.
Furusato
Village
Summer
Festival
I'm sorry...
Are
you
ready?
I’m
ready!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s get started!
you
ready?
I’m
ready!
If I try, I can do it
I’m sure, I can’t fail, I’m number one
Start
sute
e
ji
Start
Start, today’s live is beginning
sute
e
ji
Check
maiku
meeku
i
shou
ni
Show
time
Check
Check my mic, makeup, outfit, then it’s showtime!
maiku
meeku
i
shou
ni
Show
time
Try
chall
enge!
Try
I’ve got to challenge myself
chall
enge!
Star
Spot
light
Star
The light of stardom, the shining spotlight
Spot
light
It sparkles brilliantly like the path before me
A dream is something that needs to come true
That’s what I believe
Let’s
go
Saa
So get on your mark, let’s go
Let’s
go
Yeah!
Are
you
ready?
I’m
ready!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s sing a song!
you
ready?
I’m
ready!
Every last smile and tear
tain
ment
Yu
make up the entertainment that becomes a dream
tain
ment
Are
you
ready?
I’m
ready!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s get started!
you
ready?
I’m
ready!
If I try, I can do it
I’m sure, I can’t fail, I’m number one
Episode 3
Everything Starts
With One Brave Step
Everyone, pay attention!
What is it?
We've made plans to hold a mini-live at Furusato Village's Summer Festival!
Everyone is participating!
In addition, this is the very first job he's gotten for us.
I'm–I'm gonna do my best!
Is this really okay?
It might be too early for Nii-chan to have this kind of responsibility.
I'm–I'm gonna do my best...
We get to sing on stage...
I've got to work hard!
Furusato
Village
Summer
Festival
765 Pro Mini-Live
Everyone who's finished loading luggage can get in the car.
Even I wouldn't touch that...
Hey, Miki... You can't just sleep in a place like this.
Couldn't we have gone yesterday?
Sorry. We didn't have the budget.
I'm really sorry!
If you say so.
Makoto-chan, isn't it incredible we get to sing on a stage?
I'm really nervous, but I just can't wait.
That's the spirit, Yukiho!
Yukiho, let's do our best!
Yeah!
Oh!
Looks like all you're ready to go, Yukiho.
She really does just hate me, doesn't she?
You're in the way!
Have a safe trip!
We will. Look after everything for us!
Leave it to me!
See you later!
Have a good time!
It kinda feels like we're going on a trip when we all go together, doesn't it?
Yeah, yeah! On trips like this, it feels like there's going to be grand dinners and stuff.
Of course there will. After all, it's big enough that they called in Iori-chan!
You're right!
My! I wonder what this Refined Handsome Man Contest is?
Look, look! It says this place is famous for its loquats.
There's all sorts of stuff. Loquat cake, loquat juice, loquat gummies and pickled loquat!
Pickled loquat sounds good, doesn't it?
Maybe I'll pick some up on the way back.
It's a little more mountainous than I'd expected.
It looks like the village is just after this next mountain.
Today is our first job for everyone in a long time!
And it comes with a stage to sing on!
We're gonna get all fired up for this!
Let's do this, 765 Pro!
Fight!
Oh–!
Where are we?
Hey, is this really the place?
S–So it would seem.
Who the heck're these guys?!
I've never seen 'em on TV!
Are you really idols?!
A dog...!
A–Anyway, let's put down our bags and get settled in.
I was so scared...
Are you okay, Yukiho?
Yeah, I think.
You're not good with dogs either, I guess.
No...
But this place has a "Mother Nature" feel to it, doesn't it?
Hey!
Stop that!
Oh, hey there!
Welcome to Furusato Village!
Thank you for coming all this way!
Um, 756 Pro.
Well actually, it's 765 Pro.
We have a waiting room and meals prepared for you.
Please, come this way!
What's the matter, little lady?
Wh–What's wrong, Yukiho?
Th–There are so... many men...
Yukiho!
Okay, everyone.
Waiting Room
Members of 756 Pro
Once you set your bags down, we're going to rehearse!
Okay~
So much...
...for the grand dinners.
The onigiri are delicious!
Are you okay, Yukiho?
Sorry, Makoto-chan.
Waiting Room
Members of 756 Pro
This is a little different from what I had expected.
But that doesn't matter!
I'm the last person who should be getting depressed!
Excuse me...
Sorry to bother you.
You girls are good with a knife, aren't you!
Thank you very much!
Keep it coming!
Why do we need to do these kinds of things?!
The equipment is so old I don't really know what to do.
It matters little.
A song is not something that is sung by a machine.
Hey, Miki-Miki, you're in the way.
Sheesh, how much longer do you plan on sleeping?
I think we should probably put out more seats.
Lots of visitors will be coming today, after all.
Lots, she said!
Yep!
Ami, Mami.
It's about time for rehearsal, so go get ready.
Roger!
Sorry about this. We don't have enough hands to cover everything by ourselves.
I can't believe we're even having the idols help out.
No, no. It's good experience for the girls, too.
I got separated from everyone else...
Are you looking for something?
U–Um...!
Is something the matter?
A–A man...!
If you don't feel well, you should get to the medical room soon.
U–Um...
I'm so sorry!
Hey, wait!
Why...
are there so many men everywhere?
Ah, there she is.
Hagiwara-san, Producer-san was looking for you.
Please, let me show you the way.
There you are. I was lookin' for ya.
No–!
Um, Producer?
Do you have a minute?
What's wrong?
Waiting Room
Members of 756 Pro
Eh...?!
Why did you bring these?
But you said to get the red one, so Mami said it was this one for sure...
Ami said it was obviously this one, too!
I get it, I get it.
But at a pastoral village live like this
we really can't have you wear these, can we?
I'm sorry, Nii-chan.
Nothing's working out at all.
...which means, for today's live, we'll need to you to go on in the clothes you're wearing right now.
Okay then, after this we have rehearsal.
Make sure to confirm where you are in the program!
'Kay–.
Where's the energy?!
Come on! Perk up and get out there!
Okay–!
Yukiho, is something wrong?
You look kind of pale...
N–No, I'm fine.
Really?
Y–Yeah!
Okay, next up!
Are you ready?
What is it? Are you okay?
Okay, let's have a quick run-through. Go ahead!
Okay!
O–Okay!
We've been waitin'!
Do your best!
Hey, hey! Sing the best you can!
Why?! It's just rehearsal!
What's wrong, Yukiho?
I... I can't take any more.
I should just...
Y–Yukiho?
dig a hole...
and bury myself in it!
Yukiho?!
You can't just dig a hole in the stage!
S–Stop the music! Please stop the music!
Everyone from Furusato Village,
thank you for coming to 765 Pro's Summer Festival Special Live.
We're going to do our best today to bring you fun song and dance...
It's stuck! I can't get it out!
Everyone, settle down!
I'll go get it real quick!
Anyway, just settle down!
Iori, go help one of the stalls until you're up, please!
Eh?! Why should I?
Here. It's tea.
Have you calmed down some?
Yeah.
I see. You must have been scared of those people from the Young Mens' Association.
But they all look like such nice people.
I wonder if it's really just impossible for me.
I'm bad with men,
and when I get nervous, I lose track of whatever it is I'm doing.
I want to work hard alongside everyone, but...
Most Refined Man Contest
Next is entry number six.
Missy, missy!
Most Refined Man Contest
Yes?
Yer a real looker, ain'tcha!
Ya wanna get hitched with me?
My! Are you sure you're okay with someone like me?
Bring in our fabulous prizes!
Uwah–! They're bucking all over the place!
Okay! Everyone, leave it to me!
Oi, oi, this is getting pretty crazy.
W–Well, at least the customers seem to like it.
So like, there's nothing  here, right? I was so surprised!
And it was so far! I had to get up real early in the morning.
I'm so, so sleepy...
Afu.
It's okay if I go ahead and sleep, right?
Miki-chan, stay awake!
Miki doesn't change, does she.
It's just not fair that they actually think she's funny like that.
Everyone's so amazing.
Even though I get scared just seeing a man...
Yukiho...
I'm sorry, Haruka-chan, Makoto-chan.
I do nothing but hold you back.
Maybe I'm really not cut out to be an idol–
Yukiho!
Why do you say things like that?
I know you always do everything you can at whatever work you're given!
That's right!
Don't say things like you're holding us back.
B–But I...
You're not the only person who feels insecure.
Just look at me. I've been so nervous that my knees are shaking...
To be honest, me too...
See? We're the same.
So the three of us should work together and make this live a success!
Okay?
765 Pro! Fight!
Oh–!
Okay, you're almost up!
Right!
It's okay. I'm not scared.
How is it? Think you're okay?
D–Dog!
No–No way!
Yu–Yukiho...!
Dogs are the only...
Dogs are the only things I just can't handle!
I knew it!
After that, we need the lighting to–
Y–Yukiho?
Yukiho!
Wait!
I'll go.
There was even a dog...
Yukiho?
Are you okay?
Pro–Producer...
Let's go.
Everyone's waiting for you.
You're not good with dogs either, are you?
I heard.
Okay, leave it to me.
It's all right.
I won't let it anywhere near the stage.
I won't let it bark, either.
B–But...
You're going to do your best together with the two of them, right?
Don't worry so much!
Even if it bites me, I won't let it near you, Yukiho.
I promise.
Woof, woof!
Not too scary compared to a dog, right?
Just kidding. I guess that was a little childish.
P–Promise me.
You bet!
I promise!
I'll definitely protect you.
Lyrics: yura
Composition: cota
Arrangement: Seki Junjirou
I wonder if Yukiho is all right?
Yukiho!
Sorry to make you worry!
Ready set go!!
Ready, set, go!!
Go on ahead!
Ikitai toko itte miyou yo
Let's go where we want to go
W–Wait, Yukiho!
Haruka, Makoto!
Go ahead and get on stage first!
Aruitari hashittari yasundari shite
Walking, running, taking breaks
Ready boy girl?
Ready, boy, girl?
Yaritai koto yatte miyou yo
Let's do the things we want to do
Okay!
Mezashite oikakete jibun shinjite
Finding a goal, chasing it, believing in ourselves
I'm beggin' you here, don't bark!
Nee kondo sora hareta hi wa
Hey, when the sky clears
Still, isn't Yukiho ready yet?
...and so...
Tooi machi he dekake you
Let's go to a distant town
Um...
Thanks for waiting!
Yuki–ho?
Yeah–!
Alright*
Kyou ga waraetara
If today smiles upon us
Alright*
Ashita wa kitto shiawase
I know we'll be happy tomorrow
Daijyoubu!!
It's all right!!
Y–Yeah–!
Dokomade datte
Wherever we go
Yukiho...
Saa shuppatsu oorai*
We're ready to depart
Yeah–!
Makoto-chan...
Let's turn up the volume!
Haruka-chan!
One, two...!
Yeah–!
Love & Peace
Love & peace
Iitai mono itte miyou yo
Let's say the things we want to say
Suki nara suki datte suki ni sakebou
If we like it, let's shout we like it however we want
Louder! Louder!
Yeah–!
Nee kondo ame ga futta hi wa
Hey, the next time it rains
What's she doing? It makes no sense.
But Yukiho-san might be really cool!
Ie de yume wo hanasou
Let's talk about our dreams at home
Indeed. Truly, a magnificent sight.
Alright*
Kyou wa naitara
If we cry today
Alright*
Ashita ga motto tsuyoku naru
We'll be stronger tomorrow
Ganbatte!!
You can do it!!
Atarashii ippo fumidasou
Let's take that new step forward
All light*
Namida no hikari de
With the light from our tears
All light*
Kokoro ni niji wo kakeyou
Let's build a bridge between our hearts
Massugu
Straight as an arrow
Itsumade datte
Everything always
Saa kekka oorai*
Turns out all right*
Yukiho!
That was amazing!
Really! You were so cool!
It–It wasn't anything like that.
But...
Even though I was really nervous,
I had so much fun!
Yeah, you're right.
It was fun!
It's Producer-san!
I think the dog got attached to him!
Thank you very much for the thrilling performance!
That costume was especially charming.
I think it might become one of the village's specialties!
Then it was worth all the preparation that went into it...
Get on TV soon!
You can count on it!
Ushi-kichi, I know we'll meet again some day!
What are you doing, naming someone else's cow?
We're cheering for you, okay?
Um, Producer!
Yukiho...
What's up?
No, you see...
Producer, you aren't good with dogs either, are you?
You got me.
Don't tell everyone else, okay?
When I was a kid, I got bitten by this big dog, see...
Ever since then, I think.
Then why did you–
That's why I did, I guess.
Well, I understand what it's like for you to not like dogs.
Oh, but it's no good to be bad with them forever.
When I saw you trying your hardest, it made me feel like I could conquer this whole dog thing.
Ah. Little dogs, I mean.
Look, Nii-chan's sleeping!
He did his best in his own way, after all.
Right, right!
Let's follow the standard routine while we have the chance!
Hey, stop that! More importantly, it's dangerous, so sit down!
Good work!
I missed buying souvenirs because I was asleep...
They could have just woken me up.
Thank you for today.
Though I think I'll probably still cause trouble for you from time to time.
I'll do what I can, one step at a time.
Please continue to look after me, Producer!
I'm not even someone
who can say what she wants to say
But if I were to be in a relationship
Iitai koto sae
I have a first candidate in mind
Ienai watashi dakere do
If I could just step a bit more forward
Moshi renai suru nara
And have him talk to me...
ba...
Daiichi kouho wa iru no
I could touch him if I just reached out
Because he's that close to me...
ni...
Ato sukoshi dake mae ni dete
Kotoba kakerareta naraba...
It's my first stage
It's
my
first
su
tee
ji
Chikai sonzai na dake ni...
Te wo nobashitara todoku hodo
Love you, love you
Love
you,
love
you
This heart that overflows
It's my first suteeji
Love you, love you
with confusion towards you
is just so irritating
Love me, love me
Love
me,
love
me
Konran shita kokoro
If you notice me
Love me, love me
Modokashikute
Anata he no afureru
Just a little
Please be conscious of me
Sukoshi dake
It's my first stage
It's
my
first
su
tee
ji
Watashi ni kizuitara
It's my first suteeji
Ishiki shite kudasai
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
This is Shijou Takane.
Next week, at the aliens'
secret base, everyone at the office finally–
...is not what happens.
Please look forward...
To Change Yourself
...to next time!