The train on line two will cease operations for two minutes
KISARAGI CHIHAYA TELLS ALL
Everything about her past
KISARAGI CHIHAYA
BREAKS THE SILENCE!
765 Pro Kisaragi Chihaya
Tells the truth about her past
Kisaragi Chihaya
Princess of Song
in order to perform a transfer
with the high-speed rail.
Kisaragi Chihaya
Explains everything!!
Exclusive
Interview
We advise passengers in a
hurry to board the first line–
Weekly
Truth of the Present
Exclusive
Interview
765 PRO in
the spotlight
Kisaragi Chihaya
everything!!
I hope a little of the turmoil
will settle down with this.
Yeah.
We owe you our
thanks for this one.
I absolutely intend to
return this favor some day.
Don't be ridiculous.
I only wrote the article
because he  asked me to.
In order to resume work as usual,
this is the conclusion that Chihaya
and I came to after a long discussion.
Not to mention, we really can't just leave gossip like that to run wild.
Indeed.
I think Kisaragi-kun was very brave to face such a difficult interview.
So, where's Kisaragi-kun?
We're having her perform
at Idol Jam, as it turns out.
She's already started
on her lessons.
Changin' my world!! Kawaru sekai kagayake
Changin' my world!! The changing world shines
Changin' my world!! Watashi no sekai
Changin' my world!! It's my world
Watashi no mono Change!!
It belongs to me! Change!!
Kirameku Stage
The shining stage
Event gurabia CM
Events, photo shoots, commercials,
Terebi de Show time
Showtime on TV
Hajimaru tsuzuku Story
A beginning, a continuing story!
Nando NG demo
No matter how many times we NG
Donna Rival datte
No matter the rival
Makenaide Try again!
Don't give up and try again!
Tachi agaru Street
It's a path you pave by standing up
Encore wa nai Life
Your life doesn't get an encore
Ichido no Live
It's a one-shot performance
Susume dokomade mo
Keep moving forward and never stop
Show must go on!
Three
Two
One!
Changin' my world!! Kawaranai yume egaite
Changin' my world!! It might be an unchanging dream we're drawing
Changin' ima wo!! Suki ni jiyuu ni kaeru Ready!!
Changin' right now!! But change it however you want! Ready!!
Changin' mae wo!! Atarashii mirai oikakenagara
Changin' what's in front of us!! While we chase a new future
Watashi rashii watashi de motto motto
I'll just be myself to keep on, keep on
Dreams come true
I love all
They've undone everything!
I'll never accept it.
I would never  lose
to those halfwits!
It mustn't be permitted!
Episode 21
Like a Flower Blooming
Today's show will be
something of a trial for Chihaya.
I just hope everyone in
the audience accepts her.
If we can get them to
listen to her singing,
then I just know...
We'll need to get her on stage in the best condition we can, right?
Of course!
Huh? You can't send someone
in your place, either?
But...! Yes. Yes...
I see.
What did the hairdresser say?
Well, it's strange.
They say they received a cancellation call
from someone claiming to be from our office.
What?!
But that's crazy!
Wait, what do you mean?
So we have to do
our makeup ourselves?
Will we make it if we start now?
Hey!
How about we try it
by ourselves for now,
and if we have trouble,
we help each other to finish up?
Not like we have another option.
With that decided,
let's get this done.
Roger!
Copy that!
Then let's get started.
Okay.
Chihaya-chan, let's go, too.
Of course.
Chihaya.
Face me.
Your complexion has improved.
It must be President Kuroi
pulling these pranks.
Probably.
But no matter what
he throws at us,
we'll prove we can
overcome it together.
Could I have a moment?
Yes?
Actually, I've got a favor to ask...
Old man...?
Is he pulling another–
Touma-kun!
It's about time.
"Aishiteru" "Aishiteru"
"I love you" "I love you"
Itsuka mirai de
In the future
Boku ga kimi ni chikau kara
I swear to you, someday
Everyone, are you ready?
Get you!!
Ikou!!
Let's go!!
Saa ikeru!!
Now let's go!!
Everything's just right, honey!
Donna kyou demo
No matter the "today"
Futari naraba koi wo hajimeyou
The two of us can start a new love
Um, are you guys 765 Pro?
Boy meets girl, start–
Huh?!
The accompaniment
data is acting up?
I'm sorry. I don't know
how it could have happened...
There isn't much time, so it's
looking like we'll just skip you.
Wait a minute!
No, see... we can't alter the
entire program at this point...
Then take this.
We brought the source data with us, so please use this to deal with it.
Okay.
I guess I can at
least give it a shot...
I'll go, too.
Ritsuko. Take care of things here.
Of course!
Then let's hurry.
Right...
But I'm not sure whether
or not we'll be in time...
I just hope the source data
proves to be of some use...
Little upstarts who never grow up need to be taught a lesson.
Step by step
Mune no naka de
In my heart
This might take some time...
Tomaranai owaranai
Can't stop it, can't end it
This is love
You're kidding!
Yorokobi mo kanashimi mo
Both happiness and sadness
Isn't there some way we can make it in time?
Easier said than done...
Go to love
Te wo tsunagi hibi tsunagi
Joining hands, joining our days
Today's show is
absolutely critical!
Get our love
Doko datte doko made mo
No matter where, no matter how distant
Well, we'll do our best...
"Aishitai" "Aishitai"
"I want to love you" "I want to love you"
We're laying our hope on you!
Kako mo mirai mo
Past and future
Yeah...
Boku ga kimi ni ieta toki
Once I've told you
No matter what,
I want to let her sing...!
Oide!!
Come here!!
Saa oide!!
Now come here!!
No matter what!
Donna kyou demo
No matter the "today"
Let's Start A New Love
Lyrics: Shirase Aya  Composition/Arrangement: Jesahm
Futari naraba koi wo hajimeyouyo
The two of us can start a new love
Let's think of a way to bridge the time
until we can get the accompaniment back.
Chihaya, you're opening,
so you'll be in the wings.
R–Right.
See you later.
Let's see... How about
everyone takes turns emcee'ing?
Or how about Makoto and
I fill the gap with a dance?
But you need music to dance to.
That's right!
If we need things we
can do without music...
How about our segments
from "Are We Live?!"?
That might be a good idea!
Then Mami and Ami will go
on first with "AmiMami-chan"
and make the audience
explode laughing!
That sounds like fun.
Then we can have Haruka-chan and Miki-chan
tie segments together with their intermissions...
Okay.
Then let's configure things according to the schedule from "Are We Live?!".
Okay!
Okay, let's see...
We can have AmiMami-chan
up first, right? Ami, Mami.
Chihaya-chan?
Okay, Ricchan!
Leave it to us!
Then next is...
What is it, Chihaya-chan?
Did you forget something?
Um... I...
You have an idea, don't you?
But... this might just
be a selfish request...
But that's what you
want to do, right?
Then that's fine!
I'd really like it if you told me
what you actually wanted to do.
I bet everyone else would, too.
Okay.
But there'd be
no music for that...
Um... everyone!
Chihaya!
Chihaya onee-chan!
What's wrong?
If you don't get–
Um...
I wanted to ask you all a favor.
Ever since this morning,
and even now,
everyone's been trying
so hard to let me sing...
At that last concert, too... I managed to sing because everyone was there supporting me.
I really, truly appreciated it.
But I can't depend on
everyone's kindness forever!
So, even if there's no accompaniment,
I think that this is the time for me to sing.
Hold on a second.
You know, Chihaya,
today's show is really
important for you.
Not everyone who came
today is going to be a fan.
Yes. I know.
It might be reckless to sing with
no music in circumstances like these.
It might be safer to wait
for the next opportunity.
But I want to sing right now!
I want to show everyone
today, right here,
that I'm okay now!
As long as I have this voice
that everyone gave back to me,
I know I can fly all on my own!
And I want all of you to see that!
Okay.
Go on already, Chihaya.
Sheesh. If that's how you felt, you should've said so earlier!
Chihaya. If anyone
can do it, you can.
Spread your wings and fly,
just as your heart tells you.
I totally can't wait
to hear you sing.
We'll all be watching from
the wings like you wanted.
If something goes
wrong, just signal us.
Now, now, Chihaya-chan.
Relax those shoulders.
Thank you. Everyone,
thank you so much!
Haruka...
Ain't that Kisaragi Chihaya?
Think she can sing?
She really came!
Kisaragi-kun...!
Zutto nemutte iraretara
If I could sleep forever
Kono kanashimi wo wasurerareru
I could forget this pain
Sleeping  Beauty
Lyrics: Mori Yuriko  Composition/Arrangement: Shiina Gou
Sou negai nemuri ni tsuita yoru mo aru
There are nights when these thoughts guide me to sleep
Futari sugoshita tooi hibi
The days we spent together so long ago
Kioku no naka no hikari to kage
Are the light and darkness in my memories
Ima mo mada kokoro no meiro samayou
Still wandering the labyrinth of my heart
Are wa hakanai yume
It was a fleeting dream
Sou anata to mita utakata no yume
The transient dream I saw together with you
Members
of Jupiter
Huh? She's a cappella?
During rehearsal, there was
an orchestra, wasn't there?
Tatoe hyakunen no nemuri de sae
Even if it be a sleep of a hundred years
What am I doing?
Itsuka monogatari nara owatteku
Every story will end someday
We're bringing the music
in at the next chorus.
Saigo no Page mekuttara
And if you should turn that final page
Yes, sir!
Thank you very much!
Nemuri hime mezameru watashi wa ima
Sleeping Beauty awakens, and I now
Damn! If that's
how they'll play it–
Dare no tasuke mo karizu
Seek help from no one.
Just stop it!
You  brats...!
That's enough, isn't it?
Shut up! Out of my way.
Tatta hitori demo
Even if I'm alone
Old man!
Shameless punks.
Asu he aruki dasu tame ni
So that I can keep walking 'til tomorrow
You're far too young to
give me  your opinion!
You're nothing more than pawns.
Asa no hikari ga mabushikute namida afuretemo
Even if the morning light is so blinding that tears fill my eyes
Pawns?
You're treating us
like pawns again?
We...!
We don't sing at
your beck and call!
Hitomi wo ageta mama de
I'll keep my eyes raised
Get your head out of the clouds.
Bastard–!
Touma! Don't get too worked up!
He's right! Socking Kuro-chan
won't solve anything!
I guess this is it.
Donna ibara no michi datte
No matter the thorny road
What?
Maybe you're right.
Anata to naraba heiki datta
I was fine if I was with you
Sorry, Kuro-chan, but you just don't know when to give up.
Kono te to te tsunaide zutto aruku nara
If we could clasp hands and just walk forever
To be honest, we
can't keep up with it.
Kizukeba soba ni ita hito wa
Before I knew it, the person beside me
Then do as you will.
I'm sure a day will come
Haruka na mori he to satteita
Had vanished into the distant forest
Te wo nobashi namae wo nando yondatte
Even if I outstretch my hands, no matter how many times I called his name
when you all see that I was right.
And when that day
comes, it'll be too late.
Warui yume nara ii–
Would that it were a bad dream–
–Mukou he to namida ha nugui sari
–wiped my tears and flew away
Ano sora miagete
Staring into the sky
Chihaya-chan, you're wonderful!
Welcome back!
Chihaya-chan, we
were waiting for you!
Chihaya-chan, thank goodness!
Chihaya-chan!
Thank you, everyone.
Chihaya-san! I was so touched!
I bet I'll never forget today's show!
Hey, who's next?!
Standy, standby!
Haruka.
Thank you!
Hey.
What do you want?
Maybe we didn't know,
but sorry about a lot of things.
Old man Kuroi caused you
guys a lot of grief, right?
If that's all, it's no big–
No way!
Even if we quit the place,
I'll settle things like a man!
You quit?!
A lot happened.
Today's our last day.
Then what are you
going to do now?
We'll start over from scratch.
This time, we'll do it somewhere
that trusts in our ability.
I see.
And now I've apologized, okay?
Yeah. Got it.
Boy, look how worked up
Touma-kun's getting!
Touma! I didn't know you were into–
O–Of course not!
Dear me, it must be
great to be young.
Where did that come from?
Well, I started remembering the past a little.
How about I take you all
to a nice little spot today?
Let Ritsuko-kun's car know, too.
Come, come.
What a beautiful restaurant!
It has such a mature atmosphere!
Look. There are big names
in the industry everywhere.
Isn't that Yoshizawa-san
and President Kuroi?!
Hey! Why's he here?!
He's ruining the mood!
I'll kick him out.
Wait! Wait, Iori!
But–!
I'll be fine.
Then I guess I don't mind...
Minase-san. Thank you.
Please enjoy.
Here to laugh at me?
Not really my intention, actually.
Listen up. I'll say this only once.
I don't consider this a loss to you.
This place is beautiful.
Yeah.
Huh? I wonder what's going on.
Hitotsu umareta tane
A single seed was born
Flower
Lyrics: yura  Composition: Fujisue Miki  Arrangement: Kageie Jun
Yowaku chiisai keredo
It was small and weak
Fukaku ne wo ayumase
But its roots ran deep
Tsuyoku ima wo ikiteiru
And lives strong moment to moment
Another.
And for me.
Certainly.
Yagate tsuchi wo oshiagete
Eventually it pushed up the soil
Honestly. You never change.
I don't want to hear
that coming from you.
Mabushiku utsuru ano hiroi sora
And into the brilliant, never-ending sky
Now, now.
Maybe you're right. I guess
I was the one who changed.
Sore wa utsumakanai de
Because it never looked down
When did you become
such a philanthropist?
I wouldn't call myself
a philanthropist.
Ue wo miru kara
And continued to look up
I just believe in those girls. In idols.
Itsuka sakou kitto
Let's bloom someday
Trust  in your idols? Ridiculous.
Akiramenai de
If we never give up
You think so? The three with you looked to be nice boys in their own way.
Ha wo hirogete unto
Spread our leaves with confidence
Kuki wo nobashite
And stretch our stems out
Takakutatte yukeru
We can go however high it takes
You should try to understand one another–
It's none of your business.
Massugu ni me wo
Let's face our sprouts
You understand nothing.
Kagirinai ashita he mukete yukou
Straight at our neverending tomorrows
Yes, that might be true.
But I think that it might be a good idea to
leave the young ones to do things their way.
There are things they can teach us.
I'll see myself out.
Aren't you going to let me finish?
Kaze ni yureru tsubomi
Flower buds swaying in the wind
He's not even a
bad guy behind all that.
What a troublemaker.
Mamoru sugata ni niteru
Look like they're protecting something
His feelings are so strong,
he has trouble expressing them.
He's just awkward that way.
Ikutsu kizutsuitemo
No matter how many times they're hurt
Gyutto dakishimeteita
They hold on tight
So? Were you surprised?
Haretara hizashi abite
When the Sun comes out, we'll bathe in the light
Yes!
Otonashi-san looks like
she's enjoying herself.
She is, isn't she?
Ame ga futtara megumi ni kaete
When it rains, we'll make it a blessing
Everyone finds a different way to
enjoy and revel in singing, after all.
Hitotsuzutsu wo–
And one by one we'll–
I was so surprised.
Yeah. I never knew Kotori-san
was such a good singer.
I wonder if Kotori just
never wanted to be an idol?
Now that you mention it...
I wonder why not?
Otonashi-san. I bet you wanted to be an idol once, didn't you?
Women have all sorts of pasts.
But I think I'm happy right now if
I can just sing every now and then.
Kotori looked so happy.
Yeah. The customers loved her, too.
Yes.
I wonder what an "idol" is?
The way I see it, it's someone who sparkles like a diamond, I guess.
And everyone why looks at them goes like, "so bright...!" and their hearts race.
Sparkles and racing hearts?
Maybe. It could be someone who can
bring happiness to the hearts of others.
Happiness...
I want to be able to
do that with my singing.
Oh...!
Of course, everyone
has their own dream.
But mine right now is for
everyone to become Top Idol.
If I can help them do that,
that'll be my happiness.
They're all truly blessed to
have you say that for them.
Cold!
It's freezing!
It's almost Christmas.
If we just sit around,
the year'll be over!
Let's race to the car!
Hey, wait! Miki!
Sora ni naritai jiyuu na sora he
I want to be the sky, the free sky
Tsubasa nakute toberu kara suteki ne
Even if I didn't have wings, I could still fly! Isn't that wonderful?
Sora ni naritai sukina sora he
I want to be the sky, the sky I love
Kumo de yume egakeru kara
Because I could paint my dreams with clouds
"Hajimari wa doko ni naru no?"
"Where does it begin?
"Oshimai wa doko ni naru no?"
"Where does it end?"
Ue wo mite anata ni kiite mitara
Looking up, I asked you, but you said,
"Hajimari to oshimai nante
"The beginning and end
"Tsunagatte meguru mono
"Just take turns
"Daiji na no wa yamenai koto to
"The important part is to never stop
"Akiramenai koto"
"And to never give up"
In spring, let's make lots of flowers bloom
In summer, let's make lots of light sparkle
It's not a miracle and it's not luck
You've just got to believe in yourself more
In fall, you have to overcome the nights with all your heart
In winter, you have to embrace the snow with all your heart
It's okay to laugh and it's okay to cry
Because the cycle turns and spring will come again
It's a rainbow that binds everything
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
Hiya! This is
Ganaha Hibiki–
Look out,
cuz here comes–
Hey, Hibiki! If we're going to
talk in unison, then say the same thing!
Same goes for you!
Then let's
match up for the end!
Okay! Ready, and–
On Christmas Eve
Look forward to it!
Bye-bye!