"Betsu ni" nante iwanaide
Don't say "Not really"
Lyrics: mft  Composition/Arrangement: Nakagawa Kouji
Miki's commercial...!
So it started today.
"Chigau" tte itte
Say "You're wrong"
Iiwake nanka kikitakunaiwa
I don't want to hear your excuses
Mune ga harisakesou de
My chest feels like it's about to burst apart
I've got to do my best, too!
Watashi no koto ga suki na–
If you love me–
Changin' my world!! Kawaru sekai kagayake
Changin' my world!! The changing world shines
Changin' my world!! Watashi no sekai
Changin' my world!! It's my world
Watashi no mono Change!!
It belongs to me! Change!!
Kirameku Stage
The shining stage
Event gurabia CM
Events, photo shoots, commercials,
Terebi de Show time
Showtime on TV
Hajimaru tsuzuku Story
A beginning, a continuing story!
Nando NG demo
No matter how many times we NG
Donna Rival datte
No matter the rival
Makenaide Try again!
Don't give up and try again!
Tachi agaru Street
It's a path you pave by standing up
Encore wa nai Life
Your life doesn't get an encore
Ichido no Live
It's a one-shot performance
Susume dokomade mo
Keep moving forward and never stop
Show must go on!
Three
Two
One!
Changin' my world!! Kawaranai yume egaite
Changin' my world!! It might be an unchanging dream we're drawing
Changin' ima wo!! Suki ni jiyuu ni kaeru Ready!!
Changin' right now!! But change it however you want! Ready!!
Changin' mae wo!! Atarashii mirai oikakenagara
Changin' what's in front of us!! While we chase a new future
Watashi rashii watashi de motto motto
I'll just be myself to keep on, keep on
Dreams come true
I love all
Meeting Room 3
A
Performer Meeting
–is how we'll be doing things,
so if the mic gets muddy we
can adjust it. Just let us know.
After Kisaragi-san records, we need
to change the set right away.
Points of difference include–
Episode 21
On Christmas Eve
Wh–Where'd it go?
Producer-san?
What are you doing?
This wallet has a hole in it,
so when I get change...
This one is Haruka's.
Thank you very much!
And this is Chihaya's.
Thank you very much.
You're our producer,
so you should at least
get a decent wallet.
You're right.
Dressing
Room
Members
of 765 Pro
Come look at this.
This is the New Year
Concert poster sample.
It came out very well.
Didn't it?
And about practice... it looks like I won't be able to show up much.
I'm sorry.
That's all right.
We all know you're busy.
We'll do the things
we can by ourselves.
I see.
Then you're in charge.
Of course!
However!
Don't go overboard.
Be mindful of your health.
You're going to be busy between recording year-end specials and Christmas events.
That's right! It's
Christmas! Christmas!
However long, however far!
We all had a Christmas
party together last year.
However long, however far!
You can join us
this year, Producer-san.
However long, however far!
Haruka... I don't think
it'll be possible this year.
Our schedules won't allow it.
Oh...
That's right.
It's a bit of a shame.
All right. Let's do it!
Work comes first, so it'll probably just be whoever can make it.
Producer-san!
–nakuno...?
–will you cry...?
Subete moeru ai ni nare
Everything should just become burning love
Lyrics: yura Dark  Composition: Fujisue Miki  Arrangement: Kusano Yoshihiro
Sekira ni ima kogashite
Char it in its stark nakedness
Watashi ga mamotte ageru
I'll protect you
Subete moete hai ni nare
Everything should just burn to ashes
Sore ga kono you no jiyuu ka
That must be freedom in this world
Anata ga hohoemu nara
As long as you smile
Chihaya-chan!
You were so good!
Thanks.
Where's Producer?
He went to his next location.
Producer's even busier
than we are, isn't he?
I wonder if he's okay?
He's in no position to be
worrying about us all the time.
"You were great, Chihaya!"
A message from Producer-san.
He just gets more
and more incredible.
And it's thanks to you
he says that to me.
I–I just...
No, it wasn't me. It's really
all thanks to Producer-san.
Look at the incredible sets
we stand on these days.
I agree.
Amami-san! On standby, please!
Okay–
Good luck, Haruka.
Thanks.
Chihaya-chan, do you think it was okay to contact everyone about the Christmas party thing?
Sure. It's our first break in a while,
so I think everyone will want to come.
It would be nice if we
could all get together.
Yeah. The more you have to look forward to, the harder you can work, right?
–suki nara
–love me
It's Miki's commercial!
Ano ko wo wasurete
Forget all about her
Dokoka tooku he tsurete itte
Take me far away somewhere
Meet her in her new album.
Doesn't she look awesome?
She gives off this "Top Idol" vibe.
Bell Aspiration.
Here's BooBoo S' Winter Festival
Cheer Squad Captain, Hoshii Miki-san.
After a rousing PR conference,
we got an act like this:
Who do you want to
spend Christmas with?
I guess I'd want to spend it with the person I love most, after all.
Meaning?!
Naturally, that's Honey!
Who's Honey?!
As much as you're
allowed to say!
Isn't Miki incredible?
She is. She keeps blazing
new ground ahead of us.
So how about you, Hibiki-chan?
Think you can make
it for Christmas?
Let's see...
I'm recording a New Year's
Special with Makoto on that day,
but I'll try my best
so I can make it.
I really, really want to go,
but I've got recording for
a variety show on that day...
Isn't this kinda late, Harurun?
I'm doing an event with
Yayoi-cchi on the Eve.
Year-End
Super
Get-
Together
Special!!!
That's right. We're going to put on Santa costumes and deliver presents to all sorts of houses.
Truly, a splendid proposition.
However, I've work singing a song of blessing from a place close to the heavens that day.
I know not whether
I will be able to come...
Of course...
We've got another important celebration
that day, so I want to go no matter what...
Waiting Room 5
A
765 Productions
Members of
Ryuuguu
Komachi
My!
Doesn't that sound nice?
I'll impose then, too.
And I said it depends on the
situation at the mini-concert.
Oh dear, did you?
Haruka, this year
is very important.
You're a proper idol now,
so rethink your priorities.
But...
Harurun, Onii-chan just called about the
same thing and got yelled at by Ricchan.
Hey! Ami!
Producer-san did?
"I really want us all to get together" and garbage like that... Sheesh. He's not a kid anymore.
I see...
Break a leg at your show!
Tell Iori for me, too.
And then Miki...
I should probably
text her instead.
She looked especially busy today.
We're idols, so I guess I should've expected that we'd all be busy on Christmas.
Right, right!
For idols, the smile
comes first and foremost!
Uchi-
yama
Acco-
unting
Office
Studio 3
Thanks for working late!
You did it, Haruka!
I'm gonna be the
lead in a musical?
Really?!
Miki's going to be in it, too.
But it sounds like who gets lead and who gets the sub-lead position will depend on how you do at practice.
Between Miki and me...?
That's right. Congratulations, Haruka!
Thank you very much!
Good morn–
Oh! We're always
very much in your debt.
Yes. We'll get back to you
on that very soon. Yes.
Then, if you'll excuse me...
Ah, Haruka-chan!
I was waiting for you.
Yes?
Spring Storm
Tah-dah! You got the lead role.
Stage Script
Spring Storm
Congratulations, Haruka-chan!
Thank you very much!
Producer-san wanted to
give it to you himself,
but he decided to get it
to you sooner instead.
Of course!
Both the lead and sub-lead are
pretty much onstage all show long.
When I think they're going to be Haruka-chan and Miki-chan, it's really amazing.
No. The person who got us those
auditions was Producer-san.
Monthly
Schedule
He's been pretty sharp recently.
Onstage with Miki, huh?
It'll be rough since you
have concerts booked too,
but I know you can do it!
I will!
Congratulations, Haruka.
Thanks.
You were offered a recording deal overseas too, weren't you?
That's incredible.
I was just hoping I could improve myself some by experiencing the authentic environment.
But the New Year's Concert
conflicts with your schedule...
I suppose.
But this is my home base.
I'll come to rehearsal as often as I can.
Okay.
When we talk about all sorts of things like this, it kind of gives me a shot of energy.
Haruka...?
To think not too long ago,
we saw each other every day.
These days we don't run into one another
except on Sundays, so it kind of feels weird.
Oh, but a couple of days ago, I was
talking with Hibiki-chan at the office.
She was like, "Long time no see!"
and laughed.
That's why I can't
wait for Christmas!
I bet everyone else can't, either!
Me too.
Kotoshi hajimete no yuki ga
The first snow of this year
Lyrics/Composition: Asu  Arrangement: Seki Junjirou
Ureshisou ni odotteru
Looks happy as it dances on down
Konya kitto Santa-san ga
Tonight, I bet Santa-san
Merry Christmas!
Sono yume wo motte kite kureru hazu
Will bring you all sorts of dreams
Theme Song:
Hagiwara Yukiho
Konya wa Christmas
Tonight is Christmas
Minna ga waratteiru
Everyone is smiling
Kotoshi mo mata kimi to
I want to spend this year with you again
Sore dake ga watashi no saigo no
That's my one and only, final,
My Wish
We need to change
tapes, so take five!
Sorry. Recording
is dragging a little.
Don't worry too much.
Nobody else is here yet.
Really?
Okay. See you.
I wonder if it was
too much to ask...?
Attakana yuki wa
Warm snow
Warm Snow
Lyrics: Shirase Aya  Composition: Koujiya Takuto  Arrangement: Maruyama Tetsuo
Hitori hitori no kimochi
Carries each person's feelings
Gotta hurry...!
On Sale Now
Christmas Cakes
Kokoro kara wa kokoro he to
From heart to heart
Christmas Cake
Strawberry Cheesecake
Watashi kara wa anata he
From me to you
If it's too big, it'll go to waste...
Okay!
Fuwa fuwa
Soft and light
Got the whole thing!
Furi dasu shiroi yuki
Snowflakes begins to fall
Ryoute wo utsuwa ni shite
Cupping my hands together
Hitotsu tsukanda
I caught one
Furetara
When I touched it
Tsumetai shiroi iki
A breath of cold and white
Haruka!
Chihaya-chan!
You're done with work?
Anata wa waratte
You laughed
Yes, luckily.
So you got a cake, too.
Te nigitte kureta
And held my hand
I did.
Yasashii nukumori
This kind warmth
Looks like a white Christmas.
Tebukuro mitai da ne
Is like a mitten, isn't it?
Sorry I'm late, Kotori-sa–
Yuki wa tokete kieta...
The snow melts and disappears...
You're late, Haruka.
Oh, Chihaya's with you?
Harurun! Chihaya
onee-chan! Merry merry!
Samui fuyu dakara
Because it's a cold winter
Merry Christmas!
You two are late!
Chiisai nukumori datte
Even a little warmth
Everyone! You made it!
Ran it pretty close, though.
Nagai fuyu dakara
Because it's a long winter
We made it because Producer
adjusted our schedules.
Mienai yasashisa datte
Even kindness behind the scenes
Producer-san did?
Kanjirareru shiawase
This happiness we feel
Yet that very Producer
himself has not arrived.
Umarete arigatou...
Thank you for giving it all to me
Actually, he called a bit ago to say he's
bringing Miki, so he might be a little late.
I see.
Come on now, you two.
We've got two things to
celebrate today, so help set up!
Yeah yeah! And look at all the cake!
We bought cake, too...
Both of you, too?!
S–Somehow
I made it...
Yukiho!
Merry Christmas!
M–Merry Christmas...
And
Happy birthday, Yukiho!
Thank you, everyone!
They're here! They're here!
Sorry we're late, Harurun!
My! You look like
you're having fun.
I'm so glad you
girls could make it!
We were in the middle of
the after-party with the staff,
but nobody enjoys a party
without the leading lady, right?
Oh? But Iorin, you didn't
go to the after-party
because you wanted to
buy a present for Yuki-pyon.
Iorin, you gotta be honest with us on the Holy Eve at the very least.
Would you shut up?!
Sheesh!
Are we last?
No, there are still...
Takagi Junjirou
Speaking of which, the Chief
is on the phone in his office.
Takagi Junjirou
Then the only ones
left are Miki-chan
and Producer.
Not that it matters,
but don't we have a
few too many cakes?
Sorry we're late!
Huh? Don't tell me we're last?
Miki! Producer-san!
Looks like we made it somehow.
Yeah.
Hey hey! I got us a cake!
You too...?
"Too"?
And with that,
we're all here.
It's so bright when
everyone's here.
Sorry about this. Asking everyone to come and then being late...
No worries.
So you're all here!
Chief! We made it, somehow.
I'm amazed everyone made
it with how busy we all are.
Yes.
But I think it was because someone here treasures the time we have together.
Producer-san!
Merry Chr–
Well then, let's do this right!
Merry Christmas!
Ramen Nijuurou
There–
Boom–
What are we going to
do with all of these...?
I was going to get a shortcake, but when I thought everyone would be here...
You too, Makoto?
Congratulations!
Yukiho
They went out!
Okay, I'm going to cut the cake!
Ami wants Santa-san!
Mami wants the
Merry Christmas sign!
If you could cut mine
on the large side–
We've got plenty more,
so don't worry.
I've got a very important
announcement for you all.
Hoshii-kun. Come forward.
Hoshii Miki-kun. This year's Shining Idol New Artist Category Award
went to you. Congratulations!
Did Miki get something?
Wh–When did that...
We just got the call a minute ago.
Congratulations, Miki-chan!
Thank you!
Um... Um...
Then, this award
will be my Christmas
present to Honey!
How is it, Honey?
Do you like it?
S–Sure.
Of course! Of course I do!
It's the best present
I could've gotten!
Yes! Yes!
I'll use this momentum to take the musical world by storm!
Way to go, Miki-Miki!
That's great, Miki-san!
Miki?
Y–Yes?
You know this isn't
the finish line, right?
It's the starting line.
I–I know that already.
Congratulations!
I'm so happy for you.
Thank you, Ritsuko!
Where's the -san?
...s–san!
Thank you for waiting, everyone!
Tah-dah!
How's this outfit? Am I cute?
O–Oh. Sure you are.
It feels like the miracles
are just piling up today.
I'll knock you out with sexy!
Well, it is Christmas.
Gosh, Honey!
But it turned out just
like you said, Haruka.
What you said back in
summer at the beach.
We were talking about how everyone
would be so busy that time next year, right?
And somehow or another,
we're all popular idols now.
I guess so.
I wonder if we won't be able
to get together next year?
It's good that we're getting busy.
Isn't it more natural for an idol
to spend Christmas with her fans?
It is, isn't it?!
Okay! Next year I'll make sure to
put on a concert in a frilly costume!
Would you figure out you don't look good in those already?
What was that?! That's not true!
Oh yes it is.
It's so lively when
everyone gets together.
Sure is.
But like Minase-san said, we should probably spend days like this with our fans.
Changing things little by little
might be what it means to advance.
But
there are things we
don't want to change, too.
Right!
I hope we can get together like this
next year, and the year after that, too.
Me too.
Huh? We're missing someone.
Harurun! Chihaya Onee-chan!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Harurun, hurry!
Coming!
Happy Christmas!
You're taking forever!
Sorry, sorry!
Subete ga marude Candle mitai ni
They all look almost like candles
Kirameku machi nami
These rows of houses and stores
Tame iki de kesanai you ni
As though not to put them out with their sighs
Shiawase sou ni aruku hito tachi
People walk along happily
Aitaku naru ima hayaku naru iru kotoba wo
Wanting to see one another, right now, and speak to one another
Holy Night
Minna de kazarou Christmas Tree
Let's decorate the Christmas tree together
Negai wo komete Forever
Imbue it with our wishes Forever
Tenshi no oshaberi ni michibikare
Led by the gossip of angels
Santa ya tonakai mo
Even Santa and his reindeer
Sanka shitaku naru
Will want to come join
Table kakomi
Surrounding the table
Kami yurashite
Shaking our heads
Egao ni nareru
And smiling
Mahou no Place
It's a magical place
Tokubetsu na kono hi wo
On this special day
Minna tsunagu omoide ni shiyou
Let's make memories to link us all together
Tanoshii toki mo
In fun times
Tsurai toki mo
And in hard times
Issho ni itai to
They're the friends
Omou nakama
You want to be with
Present koukan ai wo
We'll pack lots of love
Gyutto tsumekonde For you
Into the presents we exchange, all for you
Warai atte tanoshii
Smiling at one another, let's make this
Christmas ni shiyou
A fun Christmas
Kaeritakunai
I don't want to go home
Toki wo tomete
Just stop time
Zutto Happy Christmas
It'll be a Happy Christmas forever
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
This is
Otonashi Kotori.
How did
everyone's Christmas–
Ah! I only realized it
after I brought it up myself!
A–Anyway, please
continue to watch 765 Pro
even after the
new year arrives!
I