Hello!
Oh. Hello, Haruka-chan.
I see you're in your uniform today.
Yes.
I came straight from school.
But don't you still have some
time before your lesson?
W–Well, you see...
We have exams soon,
I was hoping you'd let me study
here until my lesson...
Oh dear.
Then that makes two of you.
Yayoi!
Haruka-san!
Don't tell me you're struggling, too?
I am!
When I'm at home, things get so busy...
Let's work hard, Yayoi!
Okay, Haruka-san!
Studying for tests, huh?
How nostalgic.
Huh?
Yes!
I understand.
I'll tell everyone.
Yes.
Really, thank you so much!
Producer-san?
Everyone, listen to me for a minute.
That call was from the Chief.
A live performance!
We're doing a live performance
for a 765 Pro Thank-You Event!
A live performance?!
Are you ready? I’m lady! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m a lady! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I know it! I can’t fail, I’m number one
Start hajimaru kyou no Suteeji
Start, today’s live is beginning
Check maiku meeku ishou It's showtime
Check my mic, makeup, outfit, then it’s showtime!
Try challenge!
I’ve got to challenge myself
Stardom hikari hikaru Spotlight
The light of stardom, the shining spotlight
Mabushii kagayaki massugu Debut
A brilliantly sparkling, straightforward debut
Yume wa kanau mono
A dream is something that needs to come true
Watashi shinjiteru
That’s what I believe
Saa ichi ni tsuite Let’s go
So get on your mark, let’s go
Yeah!
Are you ready? I’m lady! Uta wo utaou!
Are you ready? I’m a lady! Let’s sing a song!
Hitotsu hitotsu egao to namida wa
Every last smile and tear
Yume ni naru Entertainment
make up the entertainment that becomes a dream
Are you ready? I’m lady! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m a lady! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I know it! I can’t fail, I’m number one
Episode 11
Anticipation, Anxiety,
and Foreboding
I'm getting so nervous!
Finally, a live performance like we've always wanted...!
Well, the main event will be Ryuuguu Komachi.
Doesn't matter!
I'll just give it everything I've got and
stand out more than Ryuuguu Komachi!
Yeah, yeah!
Mami's gonna dance so good you won't even recognize her!
If I do well at the performance,
I can advertise myself to Ritsuko...san, too.
Okay, I'm going to announce your new song!
A new song?!
It's not the finished version yet, though.
Okay, everyone stop!
Are you all right?
Y–Yes!
Takatsuki-san, don't lag behind!
I'm sorry.
You too, Hagiwara-san.
Your lead-offs are always too slow.
I–I'm sorry!
We haven't been making
much progress for a while.
Ganaha-san, you're rushing!
Hoshii-san, Kikuchi-san, you too.
I'm still too fast?
I can still dance faster...
Don't worry.
Let's get everyone together first.
Okay. Once more from the top.
Okay!
Thanks for taking care of it!
I'm just glad the timing fit with
the schedule for the hall.
So, how are our idols looking?
Oh, they're managing.
They're doing their best, but...
Yukiho!
What do you want to do?
Even if it's just a portion,
shouldn't we lower the difficulty...?
I don't think we should.
Miki...
But at the rate we're going–
But if we do that, we wouldn't be
performing with everything we've got.
So I don't think we should lower the difficulty.
I don't really want to lower it, either.
But...
Yuki-pyon and Yayoi-cchi kind of look like they're struggling.
I'm so sorry...
That's all right!
We've barely even started!
That's exactly why we're practicing!
You're probably right.
Shouldn't we decide after
we've kept at it for a little longer?
I think so, too.
Yeah.
For sure.
Okay, got it.
Let's keep doing it this way for a while.
Is that all right?
Okay.
Then let's form up into teams
and help one another out!
Okay!
Yukiho will be with Takane and me.
Yes.
Y–Yes, please!
I'll go with Yayoi.
Mami, you'll help too, okay?
Aye aye, sir!
I'll do my best!
You can do it, you two!
Chihaya-san and I will teach Haruka.
Huh?
You fall out of sync now
and then in the second half.
You need to be careful.
Yup, yup.
Okay. Please do.
Okay everyone, one more time from the top!
Okay, once more.
O–Okay!
And...
If we could stand on the sparkling–
Stop, stop!
Amami-san.
Yes?
If we could stand on–
No, no...
H–Huh?
Mami-chan, that goes for you, too.
Huh?
Just singing confidently doesn't make it right.
Yikes.
Are we going to be all right like this?
Want one?
Thank you!
Thanks!
When you're tired, you
really need something sweet.
Come to think of it,
how are you all studying for exams?
I'm studying with Makoto-chan.
I'm just glad it isn't covering a lot.
I got Iori-chan to teach me at the office earlier, too.
You're the only one Iori is nice to, Yayoi.
That's not true.
Iori-chan is nice to everyone.
You really think so?
Oh my, are you all right?
Imagine her sneezing just now.
Ryuuguu Komachi,
They're still working, right?
you're on standby, please.
Yeah, probably.
Okay!
All right!
Let's do it!
Smile!
Lyrics: Inamura Sachiko
Composition: DY-T  Arrangement: Kusano Yoshihiro
Kurikaesu mainichi wa tomaru koto shiranai kara
After all, these endless days don't know how to stop
Nayandari naita jikan mo toori sugiteyuku
The time we spent worrying and crying passes by
Math
Tutor
Literature
Physics
Tanoshii koto dake jyanai kedo watashi ganbatteru kara ne
It's not always fun, but I'm still trying my best
Waratte! no meeru kujikesouna toki itsumo yomi kaesuyo
When I feel like I'm going to break, I reread the "Smile!" text you sent me
Ima wa tokidoki ne shuumatsu no houkoku
Sometimes, it feels like I look forward to hearing your voice
Soreyori mo koe ga kikitai
More than reaching the end of the week
Aitaiyo...
I want to see you...
Okay, stop there for a second.
Make sure not to let the detailed movements slip by you.
R–Right!
Okay, next we'll fit Team A in.
Okay!
Haruka.
Haruka!
S–Sorry!
One, two, three, four!
One...!
Ah...! Stop a second!
Yayoi! Are you all right?
Y–Yes...
I'm sorry, Chihaya-san...
Don't worry. I'm sorry, too.
What do you want to do?
Don't you think
some adjustment is–
I–
I'm not going to perform.
Y–Yukiho!
But...!
I can't hold the rest of you back any more!
Yukiho!
Hagiwara-san, you see...
But...
But...!
No matter how many times I–
Hagiwara Yukiho.
Shijou-san...
It would appear that you lack something
that should come before technique.
Do you know what that is?
It is determination.
You need to attain the determination to
crumble that wall which blocks your path.
B-But...!
I...!
I'm trying as hard as I know how to...!
Yukiho...
Don't feel like you have to rush.
Okay?
Makoto-chan...
M–Me too!
I'll try my hardest, too!
S–So...!
Shijou-san, I'm sorry.
I won't be negative any more!
Let us aim for the top together.
Yukiho!
Yes!
Huh?
Haruka, is your leg all right?
Is your leg all right?
Yeah,
it is.
Hey, Azusa-san's group is still practicing, right?
Karamaru suriru chaaji
–a shot of thrill
I think this was the one.
Yofukashi no neko madowasu
Misled by a cat up late
Come on, don't dance like it's just a routine!
You won't impress the audience like that!
Sayonara
Goodbye
Ototoi oide
And don't come back
And...
Like a bird that–
Azusa-san's and the girls were
amazing, weren't they?
Once more.
Yeah. They were perfectly together, but...
How should I put it...? Their
intensity was on another level.
Indeed.
That certainly must be
their sense of responsibility as an idol.
Do you think we'll be all right?
What do you think, Haruka?
Huh?
I want to be like that soon, too, you know?
Let's put everything into our rehearsals, too!
Then we can catch up to them!
Sheesh. Harurun is so laid back.
Huh?!
But I agree with Haruka.
I kinda get the feeling that I
want to practice more and more.
Yeah.
Me too. I don't want to give up.
Okay! Then, we'll all–!
We'll all get into Ryuuguu Komachi together!
Huh?
Don't you mean to make them our goal?
It's important right now that
you stay positive, after all.
Yes.
In a positive sense, Haruka-kun's easy-going attitude
might be what pushes them higher.
La– La–
Like a bird that flies in the open sky–
Flies in–
Flies in the–
Huh?
Chihaya-chan?
If we could stand on the sparkling stage
It would be the greatest–
Wait, Haruka.
Don't want to let it end.
I think it was fairly good like that.
Thank you so much, Chihaya-chan!
Hey!
Producer-san!
Hey, you two.
Don't you think it's about time to let them have the key back?
Of course!
...Huh?
Is it already that late?
What's wrong?
What do I do...?
I won't make it to my transfer stop...
I can't get home!
I'm sorry, Chihaya-chan.
I can't believe I'll be imposing on you.
That's all right.
I don't mind.
Producer-san said he'd pay for a taxi,
but it would be so expensive...
Haruka!
I had the office contact your family.
And here's your ticket.
Thank you...
Chihaya... Sorry, but take care of things, would you?
I will.
Thank you for all this.
Aren't you lonely living alone?
It's easier this way.
I don't have to be so considerate for a lot of things.
ALL ITEMS
HALF OFF
That's amazing.
I don't like being alone,
so I don't think I could take it.
What do you usually do about food?
Convenience stores, I guess.
Isn't that bad for your nutritional balance?
I make sure to take supplements.
Supplements...
But ever since that last TV show,
I've been cooking for myself from time to time.
Then let's make something together!
Come in.
Excuse me.
Haruka?
N–Nothing!
Haruka? What's wrong?
N–Nothing! It's nothing.
You really are good at this.
Really?
Recently, I haven't just been making sweets.
I've been trying to help Mom with the cooking.
I see...
Hey.
Don't you want to live with your Mom or Dad?
They just finished their divorce.
For now, I want to leave some distance between us.
Hey, Chihaya-chan.
Doesn't this remind you of Gero-Gero Kitchen?
I guess it does.
That frog costume was so hot!
Thank you for the meal.
It's good!
Right?
I can't wait for the performance.
Yes.
We've definitely got to make it a success!
Hey...
Haruka, why did you want...
How did you decide to become an idol?
Hmm?
Well, you've never told me before.
Is that right?
It was my dream.
Your dream?
Right!
Ever since I was little.
On a radiant stage, surrounded by thunderous cheering.
And then the whole hall comes
together and heats up with energy!
That's why I just can't wait for this performance!
When I just think about all of us
standing together on that stage...!
But we have exams before that...
I'm begging you, Chihaya-chan!
Tutor me!
What?
That's fine, but we're going
to do it right if we do it at all.
But we really need to do everything we can.
We've finally been given a chance.
I want to catch up
to the three of them. To Ryuuguu Komachi.
And then all of us can put on the
greatest show that's ever been together.
You're right.
Absolutely right.
I'm sorry.
It kinda feels like you got up because of me.
That's all right.
Then I'll see you later.
It would be great if the show goes well.
Don't worry.
I just know it'll go great.
ENTRANCE
One, two, three, four!
We did an entire run-through...!
You did it!
F–Finally...
Yukiho.
It would seem
the results of your practice are showing.
I could hardly recognize you.
If this is a dream, I hope we never wake
Yukiho, don't cry!
Like a bird that flies in the open sky
I want to spread my wings and soar
Let's go as far as it takes
To the world we dream of
I don't want this to end as just a dream
Okay!
All right!
It's coming together pretty well.
Yes.
Ryuuguu Komachi seems to
have been a good influence.
I certainly hope so.
Okay! Let's keep going like this and make it better and better!
Yeah, of course!
Oh, but maybe we should reinforce what we've already done.
I'm going out for a second.
Okay.
Ritsuko...san!
Oh, Miki.
Did you see me dancing?
I did. You did a great job.
We really can't afford to let up.
We'll renew our enthusiasm–
Then if you considered the current me,
you'd let me into Ryuuguu Komachi, right?
Huh...?
What do you mean?
Huh?
If I try really hard, I can get into Ryuuguu Komachi.
That's what Producer...
And then, after this part...
Hello!
Hello, Haruka-san!
Hello.
How were your exams?
Perfect!
How about you, Yayoi?
I managed somehow, too!
Nice going!
Yeah!
That's odd...
Has anyone seen Miki yet today?
Now that you mention it...
That really is strange.
She hasn't been late at all recently.
Hoshii Miki
Re:Re: Really?
TY Office
Enclosing promotional materials
BBS Itou-san
Re: Regarding broadcast time changes
Cosmetics Harada-san
Re: Next stage outfit planning meeting
Studio KYU
Regarding photo studio days off
ST Music
Practice has paid off
Looks like it's from Miki.
Hoshii Miki
Re:Re: Really?
TY Office
Enclosing promotional materials
BBS Itou-san
Re: Regarding broadcast time changes
Cosmetics Harada-san
Re: Next stage outfit planning meeting
Studio KYU
Regarding photo studio days off
ST Music
Practice has paid off
Hoshii Miki
Re:Re: Really?
TY Office
Enclosing promotional materials
BBS Itou-san
Re: Regarding broadcast time changes
Cosmetics Harada-san
Re: Next stage outfit planning meeting
Studio KYU
Regarding photo studio days off
ST Music
Practice has paid off
Hoshii Miki
Re:Re: Really?
TY Office
Enclosing promotional materials
BBS Itou-san
Re: Regarding broadcast time changes
Cosmetics Harada-san
Re: Next stage outfit planning meeting
Studio KYU
Regarding photo studio days off
ST Music
Practice has paid off
Hoshii Miki
Re:Re: Really?
Producer,
Hoshii Miki
Re:Re: Really?
Producer,
Hoshii Miki
Re:Re: Really?
Producer,
Hoshii Miki
Re:Re: Really?
Producer,
Hoshii Miki
Re:Re: Really?
...liar (><)
Rarara... Odekake
La la la... Going out
...tte koronjyatta...
...oops, I fell...
Dakedo saa okite GO!!
But let's get up and GO!!
Rururu... Utaouyo
Lu lu lu... Let's sing
Sukina uta demo
A song we like
Dakedo muzui OH MY GOD!!
But it's hard OH MY GOD!!
Ima yatte mitai no to
The things I want to do and
Ima yatte dekiru no wa
The things I can do
Nanka awanaiyo ne...
Don't seem to match
Demo akirametakunai
But I don't want to give up
Shippai shitemo heiki
I don't mind if I fail
Hop step jump
Hop, step, jump
Itte miyou!!
Let's go and see!!
START!! START!! START!!
Start!! Start!! Start!!
EVERYTHING OK
Everything's okay!
Sono ippo ga kono ima he ano mirai ni naru
That first step will lead the present into the future
Suki na mono dakara suki de itai
Because it's something I like, I want to keep liking it
START hajimete
Start! Let's get going
START yacchaouyo
Start! Let's do it
CHALLENGE!! LET'S START!!
Try something new!! Let's start!!
Ichi ni tsuite!!
On your marks!!
Yooi don!!
Ready! Bang!!
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
This is
Hagiwara Yukiho!
I can't believe I'm
giving the preview
after such an
important episode!
Everyone,
I know you're all
nervous about next time,
but let's all get
through it together!
Last Stop on a One-Way Road
Look forward to it!