What happened, Onee-sama?
I can't find it.
The diamond necklace...
Our memento of Mother is gone!
The maid... has been murdered.
Li...ly.
Lily?
When she was attacked, the vase those lilies were in fell.
There was lily pollen on that lawyer's sleeve.
Let's find the culprit.
We three sisters will solve this with our own hands.
The lawyer has...!
Which means there's another culprit.
Let's set a trap
in order to close the curtain on this case.
Impossible...!
I know I killed you!
I heard that.
So you were the culprit.
Little brats...
You're going with her!
Onee-sama...
What...
What have I done?
When I think back,
everything had been set in motion that night.
Onee-sama...
Onee-sama!
Let's start new lives.
Goodbye,
days of our memories...!
Okay!
That was a great last scene.
Good work!
That was the horrendous incident
that shook 765 Pro to its very core!
Sisters
Detective
Beautiful
Sisters
Detective
Ryuuguu Komachi
Sisters
Beautiful
Detective
Ryuuguu Komachi
Sisters
Beautiful
Detective
Ryuuguu Komachi
Sisters
Beautiful
Detective
Ryuuguu Komachi
Sisters
Beautiful
Detective
Ryuuguu Komachi
Sisters
Beautiful
Detective
Ryuuguu Komachi
Are you ready? I’m lady! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m a lady! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I know it! I can’t fail, I’m number one
Start hajimaru kyou no Suteeji
Start, today’s live is beginning
Check maiku meeku ishou It's showtime
Check my mic, makeup, outfit, then it’s showtime!
Try challenge!
I’ve got to challenge myself
Stardom hikari hikaru Spotlight
The light of stardom, the shining spotlight
Mabushii kagayaki massugu Debut
A brilliantly sparkling, straightforward debut
Yume wa kanau mono
A dream is something that needs to come true
Watashi shinjiteru
That’s what I believe
Saa ichi ni tsuite Let’s go
So get on your mark, let’s go
Yeah!
Are you ready? I’m lady! Uta wo utaou!
Are you ready? I’m a lady! Let’s sing a song!
Hitotsu hitotsu egao to namida wa
Every last smile and tear
Yume ni naru Entertainment
make up the entertainment that becomes a dream
Are you ready? I’m lady! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m a lady! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I know it! I can’t fail, I’m number one
Next is a guest appearance on Dokkyun Live Radio.
We'll go back to the office for a bit first,
but after a thirty minute break, we'll head back out.
What?!
Things We Can Do Because
We're Together
Episode 9
But I promised Mami that we were going to beat the last stage after this!
We can't get to the last boss in thirty minutes!
What do you want me to do about it?
Which is more important? Work or games?
There's no way I could choose between them!
Boy, it would be great if we could pass today's audition.
Nii-chan! Hurry, hurry!
I promised Ami we'd beat the last stage!
Hey now, Mami!
Which is more important? The audition or games?
There's no way I could choose between them!
Iorin? You're kinda looking all perky.
I guess.
To celebrate the end of filming for that drama,
I have a reward prepared for myself!
What's the reward?
The dessert that's the talk of the town!
Gorgeous Celeb Pudding!
Gorgeous Celeb Pudding?!
Isn't that the fifty-time consecutive
Number One Most Popular Dessert?!
The one that sells out in fifty minutes?!
U–Um...
Is that–
And naturally I have some for everyone else, too.
I put them in the office fridge.
All right!
Way to go, Iorin! So generous!
What?!
Gorgeous Celeb Pudding?!
Way to go, Iorin! So generous!
Finally, the long-awaited moment of destiny!
What's wrong, Iorin?
They're gone.
They're gone!
The ultimate dessert,
my Gorgeous Celeb Puddings have vanished!
What?!
Who was it?! Who ate them?!
This morning, you put the pudding you bought in the fridge,
and then left for filming. Right, Iori?
That's right.
Well, the three from Ryuuguu Komachi
and I were together at the filming up until now.
Chief had the whole day off.
Mami and I were out at an audition around that time.
Otonashi-san's cavities hurt, so she can't eat anything.
Which means...
In other words, the culprit is someone who isn't here.
Who came in to the office today?
Let's see... Yayoi-chan, Makoto-chan and
Yukiho-chan had a meeting for their event outfits.
Hibiki-chan and Takane-chan had a dance lesson together.
Haruka-chan, Chihaya-chan and Miki-chan
went to their vocal lesson a little while ago...
So everyone showed up.
I was really looking forward to them.
Leave it to us, Iorin!
Gray brain cells and a rainbow-colored sense of intuition!
Sexy Beautiful Detectives Ami and Mami!
In Grandpa's and Grandma's names,
In the name of the Moon,
we'll arrest the culprit!
I think you've got a little too much mixed in there.
They've turned this whole thing into a game...
Make way!
Hey there, missy.
We're the police.
Have you noticed anyone... suspicious around the fridge?
Um...
Now that you mention it,
I think Yayoi-chan was cleaning the kitchenette like always.
I'm back!
Huh? I didn't see any pudding.
You know,
it'd be a lot easier on you if you just talked.
Your mama out in the country is crying, you know.
But Mom's at home...
It's not your fault.
Poverty is the problem.
You must have really
wanted to eat some pudding.
I have  eaten pudding, you know.
Even yesterday, the entire family had some.
Would you just listen to her?
No way, right?
The third Wednesday of every month is sushi combo day!
If you put pudding and soy sauce on it instead of urchin, it's really yummy!
I see.
At Yayoi's place, pudding is the same as urchin.
Yup, yup.
On the contrary, it's almost a waste to eat it plain.
Congratulations.
The suspicions against you have been cleared.
Huh?
Back to square one of the investigation.
However,
a great detective doesn't give up!
Then let's psych up
and search for clues!
Sweet...
S–Sweet...
Bittersweet...
Sweet...?
Bittersweet?
Sweet?
Bittersweet.
Who'd have thought it would be Mako-chin?
Can't judge a book by its cover!
Wh–What do you mean?
Okay, Mako-chin!
We already know what you're hiding!
So give up
and hand it over!
Huh?
Pudding?
What are you talking about?
You ate the pudding in the fridge, didn't you?
"Sweet" and "bittersweet"... You were talking about the pudding!
No, that's not it.
They're song lyrics.
I came up with them.
Lyrics?
I thought I'd challenge myself by writing song lyrics.
Then why did you run?
I was embarrassed!
I couldn't think of any words except common themes
like "sweet whispers" or "bittersweet memories."
Oh, jeez.
Back to square one again.
Hold on.
The word "pudding" reminded me, but just a minute ago...
Yukiho, what's wrong?
Have you seen Iori-chan?
No... Didn't she go to pick some things up?
Really?
I wanted to tell her about the pudding...
She really,
really said "pudding"?
Sure did.
Maybe Yuki-pyon
knows who the culprit is!
That must be it!
That was–
Yuki-pyon's voice!
Yukiho! What's wrong?
Get ahold of yourself!
Hi... Hibi...
Hibi?
That must have been the culprit's name just now.
And by Hibi... she meant–
Hibikin!
What do you mean, "the investigation's off"?!
Is it political pressure, Big Boss?!
Who're you calling Big Boss?
I told you break time was thirty minutes, didn't I?
It's almost time for your radio talk show appearance.
But the case isn't happening at the radio studio,
it's happening on the scene, Ricchan!
We've got to capture the true mastermind,
or else Yuki-pyon won't be able to rest in peace!
Hey...
Yukiho's just fainted.
Not happening.
Come on. We're leaving, Ami.
Sheesh. And it was just getting interesting.
Not much you can do about it, right Ami?
You can just continue when you get back.
Sorry...
It looks like this is the end of the road for me.
Senpai... Don't worry!
I'll carry on your dream!
It's up to you, kid.
Senpai–!
We're leaving you behind, Ami!
Why do I have to...
Thanks for waiting!
Here. Snacks!
Th–Thanks.
Sweet bread and milk...
The basics for any stakeout, right?
Are you really planning on catching Hibiki?
Of course!
We can't let Yuki-pyon's death be in vain!
I'm telling you, she's alive.
Dokkyun Live Radio!
Today's guests are the three
up-and-coming girls of Ryuuguu Komachi!
Thanks for having us!
Yay!
Honk, honk!
Then let's get started!
First off, the opening!
Mami, you bummed out that you
have less time to spend with Ami?
'Course I am.
Isn't it obvious?
Recently, playing games, window
shopping, going to lessons, teasing you...
We've been doing all of those things separately.
I see.
I understand how you feel,
but right now Ami needs to–
I know that.
But if it sucks, it sucks!
So that's why Mami's gonna get super popular
and be able to do work with Ami!
So you better hold up your side of the deal, Nii-chan!
Roger that.
She's coming out!
Huh? Only Takane?
What happened to Hibiki?
Maybe from the back door...?
You can't be serious.
We're gonna bust in, Nii-chan!
R–Right!
My! If it isn't Mami-chan and
the gentleman from 765 Pro.
Is something the matter?
Where did Hibiki go?!
If you're looking for Hibiki-chan, she left over thirty minutes ago.
Huh? That long ago?
She's on the run!
She's escaping overseas!
Nii-chan! Go check around the station!
H–Hey, Mami!
So I hear you made your first appearances on a drama?
That's right.
It was just a thirty-minute mini-drama,
but it's going to air late-night next month.
We just finished filming the last scene this morning.
It's fresh 'n' steaming out the oven!
Okay Ami-chan, could you give us a simple run-down on the story?
Sure!
It's a story about the three of us as sisters,
and we become detectives to solve a crime!
So first, there's a precious treasure that vanishes...
and then the first victim appears...
but before she dies, she whispers the culprit's name.
Hi–Hibi...
Hibikin!
Isn't anyone here?
This case
is exactly like the story in that drama!
Which means...
Hibikin...?
Um, Ami-chan?
How about the rest?
You found out the culprit's name, right?
U–Um, that's what we thought,
but that person wasn't the culprit.
Oh, Ami's radio show!
And then, the true culprit
takes a knife, and–!
Run! Mami!
Huh?
Mami...!
What's wrong?!
Not one word out of you.
Ma–
Wh–What?!
Quiet.
Don't worry.
It'll be over in an instant.
I–Insecticide?
A co...?
A cockroach?
Did you get it?
Yuki-pyon!
So you fainted because you saw a cockroach?
And that hibi business was because it escaped into a crack in the wall?
Yes.
And so Takane heard about it from you and exterminated the bugger.
Indeed.
Didn't you say you wanted to talk with Iori about pudding?
Oh, that was...
When I got some drinks out of the fridge,
I almost dropped the box of pudding,
so I was worried that something might have spilled inside.
In short, it had nothing to do with the incident.
Wh–What is it?!
And now we've whittled down the suspects.
It looks like we've finally approached the climax.
Let's set a trap.
We'll close the curtain on this case.
Huh?
It's pitch black.
What's going on?
Wh–What?
Wh–What are these?
How dare you eat them!
I'll curse your bones!
Wh–What did we eat?!
Calm down, Haruka!
They're all Gorgeous Celeb Puddings!
E–Everyone?
Huh? Are we done already?
We haven't scared them yet...
I–Is this some kind of event?
Silence, please!
The culprit is amongst us!
No, I'm pretty sure everyone already knows.
There was only one person out of these three
who recognized these as Gorgeous Celeb Pudding.
And that person is the culprit!
In short!
Miki-Miki!
You ate the pudding in the fridge, didn't you?!
Yup. Sure did.
It was a horrible incident.
No doubt.
Surely it will be spoken of for all time
as the tragedy that befell 765 Pro.
But why did you eat them without asking?
But my jellies were gone,
and I found pudding there instead.
Jellies?
Someone ate the Go! Go! Fancy Jellies I put in there.
I was really looking forward to them, too.
Those jellies are super good too, right?
The best part is all the fruit stuffed inside!
You two sure seem to know a lot about them.
Well, sure. We ate some this morning.
They were in the fridge.
Wait... those couldn't have been Miki-Miki's jellies...?
In other words, you two were at the root of everything.
Come to think of it, things in the fridge have been disappearing pretty often.
So you two were behind it!
And thus, the mystery was solved!
Just leave the crime-solving to
Sexy Beautiful Detectives Ami and Mami!
Hold it!
Stop right there, Ami!
We have a meeting coming up!
You can let her go just for today, can't you?
Mune ni waki agaru kimochi Saikou? Kandou?
These feelings that rise up in my chest... Awesome? Inspiring!
Itsuka yakusoku shita kiseki Satellite
Some day, the traces of that promise. Satellite
Mai agatte ima tenkai mawari hajimeru
Soaring high, the plot develops
Jump ahead, go!
Saa! Koko kara hoshi he tsunagu yo koe wo
Look! We'll connect our voices with the stars from here
Doko mademo aoku hibiku yorokobi
This immature happiness resonates endlessly
Boku-tachi wa koko de kimi to deaeru
We can meet with you here
Michi afureru kitai
Overflowing expectations
Tourai reimei Swing-by! Starline's Day
Descend, daybreak, swing-by! Starline's Day!
Tobi kome! Koko made!
Dive in! Until you reach me!
Even so, I can't believe you ate so much pudding.
I only ate one.
What?
Day ten of my diet.
This is the toughest point.
Oh?
What are these?
Azusa-san!
We need to leave for the studio!
Okay!
Wh–What
What have I done...?
Goodbye...
Goodbye, days of my diet...!
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
It's a little sudden,
but here's a quiz!
Of the follow three people,
who's giving the preview right now?
Mami? Ami? Nami?
What?
"Who's Nami?" you ask?
Go check things
like that on the web!
Even Just a Little Bit Farther, Together
Look forward to it!