The Fall sky above us is so blue it feels like you could pass right through it.
Zebra grass is showing up in the riverbeds,
and when I push the pedals of my
bicycle, the wind feels a little cold.
You can really feel Fall coming.
Hello!
New Star
Huh?
Isn't anyone here?
Oh!
Hello, Haruka-chan!
Hello, Kotori-san.
Haruka-chan, you have a magazine interview this afternoon, right?
Yes!
Nobody comes into the office anymore,
so it's a little lonely for me.
No,
you shouldn't say that, Kotori!
You should just be happy for them!
Oh no!
It's time for the show to start!
Takatsuki Yayoi's
ABC's of
Cooking
Takatsuki Yayoi's
ABC's of
Cooking
Takatsuki Yayoi's
ABC's of
Cooking
It's Takatsuki Yayoi's
ABC's of Cooking!
Good girl! You spoke every word clearly.
Yayoi-chan, you're doing great!
It isn't just the season
that's moved up a notch.
Everyone at 765 Pro
Yayoi's Light-As-Air Omelette
Egg
Ham
Pizza Cheese
Salt / Pepper
Butter
and the environment that surrounds us
has changed greatly!
CHANGE! Ima wa kawaru sekai kagayake
Change! It's a changing world, shine!
CHANGE! Ima wa watashi no sekai
Change! It's my world
Watashi no mono CHANGE
It belongs to me! Change!
Kirameku Stage
The shining stage
Event gurabia CM
Events, photo shoots, commercials,
Terebi de Show time
Showtime on TV
Hajimaru tsuzuku Story
A beginning, a continuing story!
Nando eru chii demo
No matter how many times we attain this position
Donna Rival datte
No matter the rival
Makenaide Try again!
Don't give up and try again!
Tachi agaru Story
It's a story about standing up
Encore wa My life
My life is an encore
Ichido no Live
A once-upon-a-live
Susume dokomade mo
Keep moving forward and never stop
Show must go on!
The show must go on!
Three
Two
One!
CHANGE! Ima wa kawaranai yume egaite
Change! It's an unchanging dream we're drawing
CHANGE! Ima wo suki ni jiyuu ni
Change! It's a time to do what you want and be free!
Try lady!
Aim to be a lady!
CHANGE! Ima wo atarashii ni Live
Change! It's a time to start a new show
Oikakenagara
While we chase after
Watashi rashii watashi de
A me who's really me
Motto motto Your dream come true!
Keep trying, keep trying! Your dream will come true!
I love you all!
Episode 14
The World that Began to Change!
After our first show ended,
so much changed.
If I were to single out the biggest change,
it would have to be that we're
getting a stunning amount of work!
It's super  cute!
It's all squishy here. I love it!
Huh?
Where's my costume?
Haruka-san,
isn't that it?
Which?
Everyone is so busy, and we're
constantly working against the clock.
Hi, Makoto-kun.
Miki...
You could tell it's me?
Yup. Plain as day.
See? I told you.
Um...
Who are you?
Huh?
It's a burglar!
It's a pervert!
No!
Oh my.
So it was Hibiki-chan.
We had a really tough time when Makoto got recognized by a fan.
But I even disguised myself and everything.
No no no.
That outfit
is actually leveling up
your Mako-chin levels.
You think so?
Our fans recognize our faces.
Despite the troubles, we're
really happy in the end.
Cosette's
Lover
Yukiho.
Are your theater rehearsals going well?
Um...
It's a musical, so there's
singing, dancing and acting.
There are just too many things to do.
Yukiho,
you might say that, but
you look very composed.
I might be useless when it comes to stamina,
but recently I've started to
feel confident about acting.
This song sounds hard!
Maybe.
Getting that note to come out at the end might be difficult.
But it's a beautiful song worth arranging.
Little by little, we're becoming
capable of challenging ourselves
with the various realms
we've always wanted to try.
It really feels like we're
all climbing to new heights
and working as hard as we can!
You look good in that, too, Iori.
D–Do you really think so?
Isn't it a little too childish?
Not at all.
Hey, honey!
Does it look good on me, too?
Hey, Miki!
I  was talking to him just now!
Huh?
I didn't see you, Forehead!
Don't call me Forehead!
I really like this part here, see?
Sheesh!
You aren't even listening to me!
Isn't it cute?
I was talking to him first!
What do you think, honey?
And one more thing!
Oh. Sure, I guess.
Miki started calling Producer "honey"!
Is that it?
According to Miki,
Isn't there more?
"Producer is special, so he's honey!"
Come on, come on!
Then I'll show up for this one,
so can you go to that one, Ritsuko?
Got it.
Yoshizawa-san is propping us up again.
Complete analysis of their new album!
Yoshizawa-san, who wrote an
article about our first show,
turned out to be an famous reporter!
I had thought he was just the Chief's tea-time friend the whole while...
But the article he wrote
had an enormous effect!
Thanks to that article,
our presence really grew.
And now we even have a photo shoot for the cover of TV-chan.
We've got to thank Yoshizawa-san.
Yes.
But it only happened
because we had the talent!
And so, though there are
many things that changed,
Okay, everyone!
Give me your best smiles!
there are also things that haven't!
Okay–
Come out, spread your heart, you are my melody
It's the advance of 765 Pro onto the field!
Right now, we're riding the wave!
You Are Melody
Lyrics: Endou Fubito  Composition/Arrangement: Uchida Tetsuya
Ima afureru kimi wa Melody
You're a melody rushing out
Dare mo tomerarenai Melody
A melody that nobody can stop
Mado no soto no hidamari ni saku
It blooms outside the window in a patch of sunlight
Kaze ni soyogu taiyou no kaori
Like the scent of the sun, fluttering on the wind
Muri ni egao tsukuranaide yo
Don't force a smile
Japanese Macaque
Ari no mama wo uke iretara
Accept everything as it is
Japanese Macaque
Kyou mo suteki na asa ga hajimaruyo
Another beautiful morning starts today
Ima afureru kimi wa Melody
You're a melody rushing out
Kotoba yori tashika na mono wa
What's more certain than words
Kimi to tsumugu Memory
Are the memories that tie you and me together
Futari de egaita Story
The story we draw together
Kirakira hikaru kimi no me no naka ni wa
In your sparkling eyes
Tenshi ga kureta umaretate no namida
Are the newborn tears given to you by an angel
Today went great, didn't it, Haruka-san?
"The dialogue game got really heated up!"
is what the director was saying when he complimented us.
Yeah!
I'm so happy!
Members of
765 Productions
Let's keep it up next week, too!
Haruka-san,
high five!
Members of
765 Productions
Yay!
Members of
765 Productions
Hey! Watch where you're going!
Those are Jupiter's...
I'm sorry.
Save your ruckus for someplace else.
Members of
765 Productions
So you guys are 765 Pro.
Yes, that's right...
From the looks of things,
you guys don't know yet.
Man, sucks to be you guys.
Wh–What are you talking about?
You're just getting what you deserve.
Fan letters?
Look how many we got this week.
This is impressive!
There are more and more every week.
It's a lot of work just to organize them.
Isn't today the sale day for that magazine we took photos for a while ago?
I think you might be right!
Hey, hey, Nii-chan!
Has TV-chan arrived at the office yet?
Well, let's see...
Huh? Didn't they send us a review copy?
Something's telling me
it hasn't arrived yet...
Iorin said she'd stop by the
bookstore and pick up a copy,
so I guess we have to wait for that.
I wonder how it came out?
I bet everyone came out real cute!
While we were having the shoot done,
it kind of felt like I'd
actually become a grapefruit.
No, don't you think you've
already got your grapefruits?
No, no. Those have gotta be watermelons.
Ah! Iorin brought it!
Hurry and show us! Show us!
What's the meaning of this?!
Wha–
THETVchan
Jupiter
What the heck is this?!
Why is Jupiter...?
Maybe it wasn't this month's issue?
No, I'm pretty sure that's not the case.
Then what's going on?
Well...
They didn't contact you beforehand?
They didn't.
I didn't hear anything, either.
Is that really possible?
I wonder if we messed something up?
I knew it! It must be because my
expression was too gloomy or something...
I don't think that's what it was.
Right!
We all looked great.
Hello, this is TV-chan's Editorial Department.
Hello.
This is 765 Pro.
There's a matter I'd like to discuss regarding the cover page of this month's issue.
I'm terribly sorry!
N–No, that's not what I meant.
We just want to know what happened.
Your outrage is absolutely justified.
We're really and truly sorry.
You have our apologies.
But someone of my position
can't disclose those details.
I–If you'll excuse me!
Wait!
Hello?!
What happened?
Chief!
This.
Jupiter
THETVchan
This is...?
Jupiter
THETVchan
It couldn't be...!
Black!
Even if we're talking about 765 Pro,
I can't believe you'd go this far.
Seriously. Old man Kuroi,
you got no restraint.
This is nothing.
You guys know how dirty
765 Pro is, don't you?
Because you keep telling us.
Pesky ants need to be stepped on.
Eventually, we'll dye the entire industry in noir!
Ants are black too, right?
They're a million years too
young to get in my way!
I'll show you, Takagi Junjirou.
I'll show you how deep Hell is!
We'll crush a group like that
with just our pure talent.
THETVchan
Jupiter
You're kidding!
Why?
As far as I could learn,
it's undeniable that
President Kuroi from 961 Pro
used his connections to have the
cover swapped through the back door.
He's pressuring us.
Pressuring us?
Why us?
I suppose I hadn't told all of you yet.
What?
What are you talking about?
President Kuroi from 961 Pro
and I were friends long ago.
There was a time when
we even worked together.
I'm sure Yoshizawa-kun
knows all about it, too.
President Kuroi and I entered the
entertainment industry at the same time.
When we met, we were friendly rivals.
And then we worked together as friends.
But after a time, we began to argue over how to raise our idols.
I couldn't tolerate his ways.
I tried to convince him, but he
wouldn't accept my ideologies.
And then we finally parted ways.
President Kuroi uses any
means to sell his idols, after all.
But why would he go after us?
"The nail that sticks out gets
hammered in," I suppose.
It just means that you've grown quickly enough to catch President Kuroi's eye.
How cruel...
I can't believe he'd use such dirty methods.
In other words,
this is President Kuroi's declaration of war?
I suppose that's how we should take it.
However, he isn't the kind of opponent
we can face head-to-head at the moment.
So you mean things like
this will keep happening?
It's too scary to think such a
frightening person is after us!
That's terrible!
We've all worked so hard...
So in the end, the big offices
have all the power in this world.
It's kinda depressing.
Hey, hey...
I won't stand for it.
Iori?
If they're going to use cowardly tactics,
then I've got a plan of my own!
You need to face influence with influence!
I'll tell Shindou everything and have
the Minase Conglomerate get involved.
Wait a second, Iori!
What?!
You can't do something like that!
Then what should we do?!
That's right, Nii-chan!
They played dirty first!
Right, right!
Like they say, "An eye for an
eye, and ni hao  for a tooth!"
Mami, I think you may
mean "a tooth for a tooth."
Yeah, that.
Producer.
Does that mean you want
us to just surrender quietly?
No. We're not going to surrender.
We're going to file an official
complaint with the magazine publisher.
Then what about President Kuroi?
Are we just going to back down?
I don't want to!
We have to get back at him!
And I'm saying we can't!
If we get back at him or do
anything, it'd put us on their level!
I know that...
But...
We went to all that
trouble to take it together!
Producer.
We need to at least say something to him.
I mean, President Kuroi is the
one who did something wrong!
That's right!
When my animals play pranks,
I make sure to scold them!
Makoto and Hibiki's words have merit.
That's right, Nii-chan!
We can't just stay on the receiving end!
I don't want him to pick on us forever!
If it comes down to it, I'll just
bring him a super  spicy drink...
W–Wait!
Like thumb tacks in his shoes or something!
And whoopee cushions and stuff!
Everyone! Calm down!
There's no point in doing any of that!
Are you trying to back
down without a fight?
Iori...
Um...!
We haven't lost!
Miki...
I don't think we've lost.
Just look at this photo.
They don't look good at all.
We totally looked cuter than this.
Right, honey?
You bet.
What do Iori and the rest of the girls think?
Th–That much was obvious!
Yup, yup!
That photo came out really well, right?
It was also the first job in a while we could all get together for,
and your enthusiasm really came through.
I remember thinking, "This is going to
be a great front page!" while I was there.
So I do understand why
you're all so frustrated.
But you know, that doesn't mean we
need to imitate the offending party.
We didn't trail them in any
respect when it came to work.
If that's the case, we should just
face them fair and square as idols.
Yeah!
We'll just work hard together,
and make 765 Pro a powerhouse that 961 Pro can't afford to mess with.
Well, yeah, but...
But we can't do that right away...
I understand the concept too, but...
It just doesn't feel right.
It leaves me feeling all gloomy...
Yeah.
And that's how it should be.
I'm not asking you to accept
what I'm saying right away.
I'd like you to add that to the list of things you leave to the Chief, Ritsuko and myself.
You can direct all of
your dissatisfaction at me.
Okay! Enough of that for today!
Everyone, you've all got work tomorrow, right?
Nobody forget to confirm your schedules!
Okay.
And I was really looking forward to it, too!
We finally all had a job together.
I know, right?
I wanted to see it in print...
Kotori-san.
Let me help.
My, thank you.
This is cute!
Oh, you're right!
What is it?
It's so cute!
Do you think it's a bear?
Is it a cat?
I wonder?
What, what?!
'Sup!
I'm Kuma-cchi!
Oh, that's cute!
Right? Right?
I wonder what's going on?
My! Something looks exciting!
Iori-chan!
Tah-dah!
Iori-chan
Look! It's Iori-chan!
Th–This?!
Is this me?!
It looks just like you!
It totally feels like Forehead!
What feeling is that?!
There's one for Miki-chan, too!
Miki-chan
New Star
THETVchan
Jupiter
"I've learned a lesson from the hard work you all do every day,
"so I'm working hard and
not slacking!" it says!
"I want to become a cute
princess for Prince Makoto."
That's Makoto-chan for you!
"Prince Makoto," she says!
Come on, you two!
"Hibiki-san, you have so
many pets! I'm jealous.
"Doesn't pet food cost a lot?"
They're worried about you, Hibiki.
Hmph! No need to worry.
I'm working real hard for my family.
"We're always rooting for you."
"Please make sure you
become Top Idol!" it says.
"The things we can do right now"...?
They must mean putting all of our
effort into what we're doing right now.
That's right.
That's exactly what they mean.
The opponent we must
face is not President Kuroi,
but ourselves as we aim
for the pinnacle, isn't it?
I bet honey will get us even bigger jobs, too!
Right?
Sure!
But we aren't going to lose
to President Kuroi, either!
Sheesh!
A
Dear Chihaya-chan,
Hello, Chiha
I always
when you
love to wa
I wish I
My little br
to hear you
Please contin
We hope Chihaya-onee-chan
Okay! Let's do the usual, Harurun!
Okay!
Chihaya-chan!
Okay! Here we go!
Aim high! Go for Top Idol!
765 Pro! Let's go!
Yeah!
Okay, then let's go reconfirm our plans for work tomorrow!
I'm so glad everyone's smiles are back.
After all, they're 765 Pro's
number one selling point.
Dear me, how sturdy our idols have become!
Jiyuu na iro de egaite miyou
Let's draw with whatever color we want
I couldn't be happier!
Yes.
Kanarazu mieru atarashii sekai
We'll definitely see a new world
But whatever shall we do
about 961 Pro?
I'm not sure how far I can take it,
but I want to do something
for them as their Producer.
I see.
Yes!
Isshou ichidou no Chansu nogasanaiwa
It's a once in a lifetime chance. You can't let it get away
Zettai tenuki shinaide mono ni suruno
You can't go easy. You've got to make it yours
Shippai osoreteitara te ni hairanai
If you're scared of failing, you'll never have it
Koukai suru yori wa mashi Attack shiyou
It's better than regretting, so let's go for it
Shirazu dareka ni amae hito wo kizutsuke
Unaware, we take advantage of people, hurt people
Nige bashou tsukutteta
And find places to escape
Dakedo kyou korekara wa tomatterarenai
But starting today we can't stop
Ashita ni mou Dash
It's a mad dash to tomorrow
Speed agete jidai wo koeyou
Kick up the speed and overcome the era
Suteki na mirai kitto matteiru
There must be a beautiful future waiting
Kibou no koe ga kikoete kuruyo
I can hear the voice of hope
Goal wa chikai ato sukoshi hashirou
The goal is close, so let's run just a little more
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
It's Ami!
It's Mami!
Together, we're–
Ami! That's a surprise
for next week!
That's right!
Everyone, make sure
to pay special attention
to Ami-Mami-chan's
award-winning acting!
Everyone Together, It's a Live
Broadcast! A Live Broadcast!