"Idol"
They are to what girls will eternally aspire.
However, those who reach that apex are but a select few......
Into that brutal world,
13 girls take the first step.
Touch 1 second
Good morning!
Owww...
"A–Are you all right?"
I–I'm so sorry!
I panicked a little.
With the office so far from her home,
she commutes by train early in the morning.
The one essential for your commute—
Music
"About how long does it take you to get to the office?"
Let's see... It's about two hours.
"Isn't it tough to commute like that?"
It is, but if I listen to music or go over my audition materials on the train,
it's over in a flash.
It doesn't bother me at all.
Makoto! 'Morning!
'Morning, Haruka.
"What were you reading?"
This...
It doesn't really fit
my image, does it?
This is a secret, but I like
these kinds of things a lot!
That's 212 yen, please.
"Kikuchi-san, I've heard most of your fans are girls..."
That's right...
It's not like I'm unhappy with that,
I've received 212 yen. I'll put these in a bag, okay?
but I'd like boys to be interested in my work, too.
Talent productions   765 Productions
Out of order
We apologize for
the inconvenience.
I wonder when the elevator will be fixed.
Well, it makes for good
exercise, so who cares?
Talent productions
765 Productions
Well, this is our office.
One, two...
Welcome to 765 Productions!
Episode 1
This is where the girls start
Their everyday "routine"
Flight
Junjirou
Let's see...
We have the studio on the 19th.
Kotori-san, I'll go with
them for this one.
That's right, there's this one too...
We're obviously short on office workers, too.
Chief said he's going to be hiring people sometime soon.
Good morning!
I'm Akizuki Ritsuko.
I'm a producer for 765 Pro!
"How many idols are
working with this office?"
We have twelve!
Most of them debuted just half a year ago, so most everyone is just starting out.
"I've heard that you used to be an idol, too, Akizuki-san..."
"Are you no longer interested in performing as an idol?"
I did kinda want
to keep that a secret...
"I have high hopes for you."
By the way, who did
you hear that from?
"From Chief Takagi."
I knew it. He's such a gossip.
But right now I'm doing
my best as a rookie producer.
That's right, I finally got
my driver's license too!
Aki           zuki           Ritsu        ko
License
Conditions
Glasses
Driver's License
Shwach!
Sheesh...
What are you girls doing?
We're in the middle
of an interview here.
Go on, you two go introduce
yourselves properly.
Yes, sir!
Futami Ami!
Futami Mami!
Yo—!
Hey, hey, ask Ami something, too!
C'mon, let Mami film!
Hey!
Don't get in his way!
Nyaa~
What a disaster!
What now?
Hamuzou, where did you go?!
Come out already!
What's the heck's
all the noise about?
Hamuzou disappeared on me!
Hamuzou's lunch looked so good that I couldn't stop myself from eating it!
So then Hamuzou got mad at me...
Sheesh, you're hopeless.
Ah, Hamuzou!
Where?!
Thattaway!
Hibiki, we'll catch him for you!
M–Me too!
There he is!
Come on out!
I'm sorry already!
What's going on?
Is something back there?
Kyaa! It's a cockroach!
Wh–Where?! Where's the cockroach?!
No—!
Where, where?!
Makoto-ku—
A man!
No—!
There's— There's a cockroach!
Yukiho-san, what's wrong?!
Yukiho-san, please calm down!
Please, someone, hurry!
The cockroach—!
I'm sorry!
I can't take any more!
Yukiho-san, you can't dig
a hole in the boiler room!
Who cares about that, just hurry,
hurry and chase the cockroach out!
What are you talking about?!
Hamuzou is a hamster!
Huh? Hamuzou?
Nihihi! Hook, line and sinker, Makoto!
Iori, not again!
Only an idiot would fall for that!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Got a problem?!
Um, Makoto-san, Iori-chan...
...the camera's rolling.
A TV interview...
What? It's taping?
Tell me that sooner!
Um...!
I'm Minase Iori! I'm looking
forward to working with you!
It's a little late for that.
Would you shut up?!
Hamuzou! You're surrounded!
Come out with your hands up!
Please!
W–Wait, Hamuzou!
Hold it right there!
Ah! Sorry it's so rowdy.
It looks kind of exciting over there.
About how much does
one of these cost?
It kind of depends on the size.
It changes depending on how big it is?
How big?
I wonder if this is on the small side...
By 'size' I meant the memory, so—
It seems so complicated.
Don't worry about it!
Even I can use it.
It's out of my league.
Dear me, fortune-telling through
famous quotes, can you believe it?
Oh my, only one star for
luck with work this month.
But it says three stars for
luck with love! What a relief!
Truly a mysterious way
to tell one's fortune.
Is it truly accurate, I wonder?
"Do you believe in fortune-telling?"
Yes, if it's a good fortune I'd believe it.
Takane-chan, what was
your fortune? Any good?
Me?
I believe that life is about forging a path to one's own destiny.
Destiny is a path you forge yourself...
You might be right, Takane-chan.
Where are you, Hamuzou?!
He came this way!
Sit still so we can tie you up!
There he is!
He went right into Miki-Miki's... you know!
Hamuzou's a man, after all!
Hey! Hamuzou, you pervert!
Hamuzou!
I'm so glad you're safe!
I'm so sorry I ate your lunch, Hamuzou!
Miki-Miki, you're on camera! Say something already!
Afu.
Hoshii Miki. Ninth grade.
All done.
That's it?!
Too short!
Oh, and I have a big chest.
Jeez, Miki-Miki!
I wonder if this is what
"Children who sleep, grow" means.
We're rather short on hands
at the moment, you see...
I'm sorry, I couldn't quite pick that up...
Could you say that
once more, please?
Everyone, give it a rest already!
'Kay...
Occupation:
Idol
Confirm
stage
performance
location
Magazine interview  14:30
Exclusive Gravure
Idol Audition
(Shibutani Studio)
10:00   ~   19:00
(Shijou - Separate
location, Miura)
O
Vo
Da
Group
Lesson
O
Meeting
Recording
9:00
O
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
O
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
Ganaha
Shijou
Futami
Ami
Mami
Kikuchi
Minase
Takatsuki
Amami
Kisaragi
Miura
Hagiwara
☆
Fresh
Idol
Audition
set
greeting
rounds
13:00
Stage
outfit
coordination
at office
(All
members
participate
O
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
Futami
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
Futami
Dance
Lesson
15:00
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
Mami
Minase
Takatsuki
Dance
Lesson
15:00
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
Futami
Ami
Mami
Minase
Takatsuki
Dance
Lesson
15:00
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
Dance
Lesson
15:00
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
O
Dance
Lesson
15:00
O
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
Dance
Lesson
15:00
O
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
Ganaha
Dance
Lesson
15:00
O
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
O
Shijou
Vocal Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
Shibutani
Studio
Hisaki
Photo
Shoot
10:00
(at
the
office)
O
Kikuchi
Takatsuki
Amami
13:00
Stage
outfit
coordination
at office
(All
members
participate
Minase
Amami
Kisaragi
Hagiwara
13:00
Stage
outfit
coordination
at office
(All
members
participate
Mami
13:00
Stage
outfit
coordination
at office
(All
members
participate
Shijou
Futami
Ami
Mami
13:00
Stage
outfit
coordination
at office
(All
members
participate
Ganaha
Shijou
Kikuchi
Minase
Takatsuki
☆
Fresh
Idol
Audition
13:00
Stage
outfit
coordination
at office
(All
members
participate
O
Kikuchi
Minase
Takatsuki
Miura
Hagiwara
☆
Fresh
Idol
Audition
Amami
Kisaragi
Miura
Hagiwara
☆
Fresh
Idol
Audition
13:00
Stage
outfit
coordination
at office
(All
members
participate
☆
Fresh
Idol
Audition
13:00
Stage
outfit
coordination
at office
(All
members
participate
O
☆
Fresh
Idol
Audition
13:00
Stage
outfit
coordination
at office
(All
members
participate
O
Vocal
Lesson
14:30
(Hoshii -
Amami -
Kisaragi)
O
See, I don't really know
much about this job,
so I think I'll take it a bit
at a time, nice and slow.
See? I'm doing pretty well, right?
Magazine Interview
"Monthly Idol"
15:00
(Kikuchi
Hagiwara)
O
Anyway, I have confidence in my stamina!
So I especially want
to polish my dancing!
I want to look my best dancing on TV music shows or on a big stage!
You have a lot of female
fans after all, Kikuchi-kun.
Since you come off as boyish.
Wha—
This question... again.
It's all Dad's fault I ended up like this.
He always gets in my way when I try to make myself feminine!
Ma... Makoto—
One day, I need to break through the wall my dad has created!
Just you wait, Dad!
Well then, Hagiwara Yukiho-san.
U–Um! I...
I'm not very good at
talking with boys, so...
Then why did you decide to be an idol?
You see, I don't really have many things I can be proud about,
but I want to be an idol...
Do you think I'm reaching too far?
That's... not really something I can answer, right?
I wanted to cure my
introverted personality—
but even my audition form was turned in for me by a friend—
There really is no hope for
someone like me, is there?!
Um, I can't really hear
what you're saying...
Hey, Yukiho, come back already!
I can't!
Tour CD
sales
&
greetings
"The
Sun's
Jealousy"
(Amami)
Please have a look!
I'm Amami Haruka!
Please give me your support!
That's right. When Ritsuko-san can't make it to every event,
765PRO office worker
Otonashi Kotori
I help out like this.
Here you go.
"Are you kind of doubling as a producer?"
No no, not anything like that.
I'm just a helping hand at best.
Oh no!
I've got to get to the next location!
Cameraman-san, take care of
Haruka-chan for me, would you?
"Wha...?!"
" 'Take care of her, would you?' she says..."
I guess I'm in your care, then.
"R... Right"
Well then, let's both do our best!
Yeah—!
"Y...yeah—..."
CHEX Live Opening performance
Hall
15:00
ENTRY
(Kisaragi)
O
Aoi tori
Blue bird
Moshi shiawase
Even if happiness
Chika—
were to be close—
"What kind of feelings do you have regarding singing?"
No matter what kind of song it is,
I'd like to capture it as best I can.
If I didn't, I feel that it would be rude not only to
the song, but to the people who listen to me sing.
"You really love to sing, don't you?"
That's right. After all, I have
nothing else but singing.
That's why I have no time to waste.
Um, I'm sorry, but can we finish here?
I'd like to focus.
—and then I jumped out too
and was like, "Wait for me—!"
Audition
(Shibutani)
Shijou -
Ganaha,
separate location
Miura
Monsters'
Little
Sister
Audition
I come from 765 Pro.
My name is Shijou Takane.
Where are you from?
My birthplace?
It's terribly regrettable,
but that is a top secret.
As such, I can not tell you.
You're pretty funny.
"They seemed to like your joke at today's audition."
" 'My birthplace is a top secret'... did you plan that in advance?"
Plan... a joke?
What exactly could you mean?
I simply don't think well of asking for
one's background purely out of curiosity.
Anyone has a secret or a
hundred they wish to be kept.
Well then, introduce yourself, if you would.
Hiya!
I'm... wait, I mean,
my name is Ganaha Hibiki.
I'm super good at dance, and I love animals!
At my place, there's a hamster,
a snake, a chipmunk, a parrot, a rabbit,
a dog, a cat, a crocodile,
a pig, and a momonga!
"Isn't it a lot of work to have that many animals around?"
No problemo!
It's a lot more exciting
when you have a big family!
They're all my cute
little sisters and brothers!
…and then when Hamuzou escaped the
other day, it was an even bigger scene...
Okay, thanks for that. Next person, please.
R–Right!
I only told them about my pets!
"Your audition didn't work out?"
Yes. Today's audition was for a magazine's
exclusive gravure idol position,
but unfortunately... even though I had the signature pose Ritsuko-san thought up for me...
"So... what kind of pose was it?"
Well, I think it was something like this...
I wasted all of Ritsuko-san's help...
"What was the impetus for you to join 765 Pro?"
After graduating from junior college, I just applied on a whim.
I'd never sung or danced up until then.
I thought things would just work out if I worked at it for five or so years.
But it's only been a half a year,
so I'm just getting started, really.
Oh my...? More importantly, where are we?
I'm sorry, I seem to have gotten lost!
"First, Minase-san."
"Why did you decide to become an idol? I've heard
your family runs the famous Minase Conglomerate, but...?"
Though my father and elder brothers are involved in the business,
I wanted to make a name
for myself with my own hands.
That's why I applied for the audition at this office on my own and—
"Actually, I've heard you were entrusted to
the Chief from an acquaintance of his..."
Oh... was that how it happened...?
"And the rabbit? You carry it everywhere, right?"
Don't call him "rabbit"!
He has a name, after all.
"A name?"
Really?
What's the name of your stuffed rabbit?
Charles Donatello the 18th.
What a yummy name!
It sounds like a donut!
Wait, don't compare him to a donut!
"Okay then, a question for Takatsuki-san."
Right!
"What are you most proud of?"
Well, I'm the oldest out of six kids.
We're pretty poor, so keeping the family finances out of trouble can be tough.
So I'm proud of looking after
my little sisters and brothers
and going to the supermarket to buy items on sale during time-service—
"...Not like that, but your sales point
as an idol, please (sweatdrop)"
W–What is it, I wonder?
Um...
"...How about your positive attitude?"
I don't think I can think of any...
You think so?
Being positive is a sales point?
I think I like the sound of
the "sales" part, don't you?
It feels like I got a good deal!
Then I'll approach every day
with a "sales" attitude!
—and then you put this number here...
"Isn't it tough to manage both school and your life as an idol?"
It's a piece of cake! They're
both fun, after all. Right, Mami?
Yeah, yeah! You're better off with a whole bunch of fun things!
When we're together, the hard
things are only half as bad
and when everyone else is
around, it's nothing but fun.
But this homework isn't fun at all.
I know, right?
Later!
See ya!
See you later!
Looks like it might rain.
Do you think all the sakura will wilt?
"What do you think it takes to be an idol?"
Let's see...
Never giving up, don't you think?
Rather than chasing a dream
that won't come true,
continuing to have the will to make your dream come true...
...though it's a little ironic for me to say that.
But I'm really looking forward to watching them mature as idols!
"I'm looking forward to seeing you as an idol too, Ritsuko-san."
Hey now...
765Productions Chief
Takagi Junjirou
"Okay, last is Chief Takagi. A word in closing, please."
I suppose you're right.
I think Ritsuko-kun said everything for me.
"Thank you very much."
A question.
What is an "idol" to you?
If I had to say...
It's kind of fluffy, kind of tender...
I kind of hope that I can
be that way some day.
U-Um, I don't have confidence in myself...
That's why it would be nice
to become a different "me."
It sounds like a lot of fun, right?
Yeah, yeah! I want to be on
TV and stuff more real soon!
I think I want to make some money for
the family and be of help to my parents.
It's obvious!
It's to make everyone respect me!
If I keep working as hard
as I have been as an idol,
I'm sure someone will find me, right?
I've got to make enough for
everyone's pet food, you know?
That's a top secret, too.
I don't really like getting
all worn out and stuff like that.
So I guess it'd be nice if it's
reeeally easy being an idol.
To sing.
That's all there is.
It's a dream, I guess.
I've always wanted to be one,
ever since I was little!
I'd be lying if I said it was never hard,
but my dream has only just begun.
So right now I can't think of anything else.
Thank you so much for toda—!
These unchanging days that flow by
are beginning to change, little by little
carrying the dreams of these young women... ...
Look up at the sky and join your hands
The sky is sparkling
If everyone in the world holds hands
The world is all one !!
The
world
is
all
one !!
Sora miage te wo tsunagou
Unity mind
Un
ity
mind
Kono sora wa kagayaiteru
The world is all one !!
Unity mind
Yay!
Woo!
Hey, of all the people we encounter
Sekaijyuu no te wo tori
Hey, we have in this world
How many of those people are smiling?
Nee kono sekai de
Hey, crying is a lifetime
Hey, and so is smiling
Nee ikutsu no deai
Then why don’t we live smiling, together
Nee naku mo isshou
Lift your head, everyone’s smiling
Nee warau mo isshou
Pool our strengths and aim for the light
Don’t forget that
In this world we have friends,
I
ssho
Friends who will move forward with us!
Sekai ni wa tomodachi
There are things you can’t do alone
There are things you can't do alone
Doredake no hito ga waratteru no?
Kao wo agete minna egao
And things you can do when you're with friends
And things you can do when you’re with friends
Issho ni susumu tomodachi ga
Being able to overcome them is Unity is strength
stren
gth
Naraba waratte ikiyou yo issho ni
Look up at the sky and join your hands
Hitori de wa dekinai koto
Chikara awasete hikari mezashi
The sky is all connected
Nakama to nara dekiru koto
When everyone in the world holds hands
Iru koto wo wasurenai de!
The world is all one !! The world is all one !!
The
world
is
all
one !!
The
world
is
all
one !!
Sora miage te wo tsunagou
Kono sora wa tsunagatteru
Unity mind
Un
ity
mind
Unity mind
Yay!
Norikoerareru no wa Unity is strength
And there's one more person...
Sekaijyuu no te wo tori
Everyone, if you could listen for a moment...
Today, I have fantastic news for you all.
The world is all one !! The world is all one !!
Finally, a gifted producer has
arrived at our own 765 Pro.
He will surely become 765 Pro's savior.
Finally, we won't be short-handed any more.
Also, regarding the documentary cameraman who's been working with 765 Pro...
No need to hide it any longer!
He is 765 Pro's new rookie producer.
Surprised, right?
In order to learn about you
all as naturally as possible,
we had him film a documentary as a cameraman—
I was so surprised when it happened.
No kidding!
Why did you keep quiet about it?
Well, the Chief asked
me to keep it a secret...
It's just sneaky to fool us!
Sorry...
Okay, okay, everyone quiet down!
Well then, let's have our Producer
make his introductory announcement!
Uh, well...
It hasn't been very long
since I became a producer,
but in any case I intend to do my very best.
We all share the dream of Top Idol!
I look forward to working with all of you!
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on IDOLM@STER!
This is Miura Azusa.
Please make sure not to
miss us next week, either!
Link your fingers♪
Make a promise♪
Well then,
look forward...
The Girls start "Preparing"
to next week!