Things that make
you feel cooler.
White things.
Shaved ice.
Almond jelly.
Polar bear.
It's~ so~ ho~t!
The color white?
And what the car's
GPS showed them
was the other side
of a tall, tall cliff.
Then, right next to their ears,
"You should have fallen!"
Nihihi!
So? Feel colder?
That was too scary, Iori!
Wh–What do I do, Makoto?
I won't be able to
sleep alone tonight!
The Matterhorn in winter.
A blizzard in Siberia.
Um...
A blank white schedule.
In a way,
that's the coldest it gets, huh?
Extra Audition
Mt. Fuji
Out
of
order
Out
of
order
Broken air-conditioner!
Crappy air-conditioner!
Useless air-conditioner!
It'll be repaired the
day after tomorrow.
I don't wanna wait!
We'll melt like ice cream and
become monstrous ooze by then!
Clear your heart and soul of worldly
thoughts and even fire will become cool.
Hey, everyone!
I bought popsicles!
Out
of
order
Out
of
order
I'm coming back to life...
Ro! Sham! Bo!
One more time!
Where I used to live, it was only a little ways to the ocean.
Again!
I miss the beautiful sea!
The beach, huh?
Again!
Producer!
The beach! The beach!
Aki Live
Opening
Performance
Campaign
Girl
Audition
"—I Saw an Idol!!" Heroine Aud—
—tra Audition
Make it a company trip!
Aki Live
Opening
Performance
Campaign
Girl
Audition
"—I Saw an Idol!!" Heroine Aud—
—tra Audition
Mister, I wanna go
on a company trip!
D–Don't be ridiculous.
Oh, it's fine, isn't it?
Public welfare and promoting health is part of your job too, Producer.
Aki Live
Opening
Performance
Campaign
Girl
Audition
"—I Saw an Idol!!" Heroine Aud—
—tra Audition
Well then,
as long as it doesn't
affect the schedule.
All right!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I’m sure, I can’t fail, I’m number one
Start hajimaru kyou no Suteeji
Start, today’s live is beginning
Check maiku meeku ishou ni Showtime
Check my mic, makeup, outfit, then it’s showtime!
Try challenge!
I’ve got to challenge myself
Stardom hikari hikaru Spotlight
The light of stardom, the shining spotlight
Mabushii kagayaki massugu Debut
It sparkles brilliantly like the path before me
Yume wa kanau mono
A dream is something that needs to come true
Watashi shinjiteru
That’s what I believe
Saa ichi ni tsuite Let’s go
So get on your mark, let’s go
Yeah!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Uta wo utaou!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s sing a song!
Hitotsu hitotsu egao to namida wa
Every last smile and tear
Yume ni naru Entertainment
make up the entertainment that becomes a dream
Are you ready? I’m ready! Hajimeyou!
Are you ready? I’m ready! Let’s get started!
Yareba dekiru
If I try, I can do it
Kitto zettai watashi Number one
I’m sure, I can’t fail, I’m number one
Episode 5
Summer Break with Everyone
When I called around for anyone who didn't have work to do,
everyone came.
It's true business is slow at the moment, but it's not like we wanted it like that.
You too, Ritsuko?
I was, well...
I thought you would have
it tough alone, Producer...
Isn't it fun to go on
vacation with everyone?
Well, I guess you're right.
I'm a me~rmaid...
Here, Chihaya.
I baked some cookies.
Have some.
Thank you...
You look like you're
having fun, Haruka.
Sure. After all it's
the beach. The beach!
The glimmer of the
sun on the waves...!
Harurun! Trade me for this!
I pay two chocolates from my hand to summon four of Harurun's cookies!
Hey!
Watch your manners.
Thank you very much!
Here with all your friends?
Yes!
We're going to the beach.
That was close.
Takane...
You should really look
into getting glasses.
When they looked closer, there were
countless handprints on the car window.
I'm so scared...!
H–Hey, hold on...
Though they wiped the prints away, one just wouldn't come off...
After all, that one
and that one alone...
was made from the inside!
Be quiet!
It's the ocean!
Godly SUMMER!!
Lyrics: yura  Composition/Arrangement: Tanaka Yuunagi
I'm gonna be first!
No, I will!
Not gonna let that happen!
Thirty meters to destination point!
Charge!
Wait for me!
Haruka, are you all right?!
Don't forget your sunscreen!
They're just like children, getting all worked up over something as dull as the beach.
Sheesh, leaving everything
where they tossed it...
Were they really looking
forward to the beach that much?
Maybe not the beach,
but being together
is what makes it fun.
The radiance of the summer sun
frees our hearts to a
greater degree than usual.
Kumo ga sora kakushita
The clouds hid the sky
Terenaide dete oide yo
Don't be shy, come on out
Takatsuki
Junbi taisou wa ALL OK
We're ALL OK with our warm-ups
Habataku kamome-tachi
The gulls take off flapping
Issee no yooi doon!! Ano umi he
With a "Ready, set, go!!" towards the ocean
Kami-SUMMER!! Mina-sama!!
Godly Summer!! Everyone!!
Happy ni narou
Let's be happy
Motto motto motto sekai de ichiban atsuku nare
More and more and more, be the hottest in the world
Kami-SUMMER!! Ohi-sama!!
Godly Summer!! Sun!!
Happy ni shichao
I'll make you happy
Minna minna minna sekai de ichiban atsui natsu ga daisuki
Everyone, everyone, everyone loves the hottest summer in the world
But you know,
isn't it a little disturbing
that not one person has
made a fuss over us?
I mean, we are an idol agency.
Sure is.
That might be so, but only
because it's still "now".
Standby
Mister!
This way!
Chi–ha–ya~!
What is it?
Since we're at the beach,
let's swim together!
I'm...
not a very good swimmer...
It'll be fun if everyone's there with you!
Here, take off your t-shirt!
Come on, come on!
H–Hey, Haruka!
I get it already!
Sheesh!
Let's go!
Wait... Don't push, Haruka!
Everyone gets along
so well. It's so cute.
Yeah.
CHALLENGE!
Jumbo
Ramen
3 bowls!!
That was quite exquisite.
A princess!
A gluttonous silver princess!
A four, a four-leaf clover–
You! Hey, you! You're so cute!
Ugh... Pick-up artists.
Where're you from?
Not "you", it's Miki.
So cute! Don't you think you could be a celebrity or something?
I guess.
It's true I could probably be one.
Idiot!
Here. You can have that,
so come eat something with us!
Hey, instead of them, come with us!
You can have these, okay?
How about this?
I guess I'll have lunch with whoever swims to the other shore fastest.
Huh? All the way over there?
Here we go!
Ready... Go–!
Swim hard!
What a little demon...
Yes!
Huh?
Hibiki?
I got it, ribbit~!
The sun's so big!
Everyone! Make sure
you have all your things!
Okay–!
He~y! Aren't you
forgetting something?
Well, I pretty much expected
something like this.
Sorry. There was the budget and all.
I like how it kind of feels
like a training camp!
It is  a company vacation,
just to make that clear.
First up is the indispensable
"Can you peek into the girls' bath?!"
check!
Hey, don't run off on your own!
Thank you for coming such
a long distance, and welcome.
We'll be in your care.
Sign: Party from 765PRO
This will be your room.
It's so big!
It feels so good to
lie down on tatami!
It looks like there's plenty of room even if everyone sleeps here.
It's so calming...
There aren't very
many channels here.
Put your valuables in here, okay?
Let's see...
Hamuzou is a valuable, isn't he?
Azusa, don't!
An open-air bath!
Mixed bathing!
...or not. Tch!
Mister's room!
All alone by himself
in this tiny room.
I'm so lonely all by myself...
I'm the loneliest of all.
I hope they get back soon.
Oh?
Hello, this is 765 Pro.
Chief
Oh, Chief. Good evening.
Yes.
Yes...
Really, the project was?
Ryuug
It's–It's so good!
It's really, really good...
There's plenty more, too.
U–Um, it's delicious, isn't it?
Indeed. Eating outdoors has
a unique charm, doesn't it?
Takane, shall I get
something for you?
Some corn, if you would.
Mister, gimme meat!
Mami wants sausage, too!
Don't forget your vegetables!
Azusa, go ahead and eat.
My, thank you.
Producer.
Shall I take over?
Nah, that's okay.
I need to put some more
charcoal on, anyway.
In that case...
Here!
Oh, my!
A–A~h!
A–hm!
Yummy!
Hey, Miki!
My, my.
That was for Producer!
You can grill your own!
I'd rather focus on eating!
H–Hey!
Um... Producer?
Some drinks.
Then I'll have a beer.
Hello? Kotori?
Yes, thank you.
Huh, the project was?
The bath is so nice...
It feels so good!
They should rename the "Large Public Bath" to the "Small Public Bath".
Dragon Water Current!
Ocean Splash!
It stings!
Even though we put
on sunscreen, right?
You seem to be in
a good mood, Ritsuko.
I guess.
Huh? I forgot the conditioner.
Here, take this.
Miki...!
Huh? Where's everyone else?
Next door, next door!
Next door?
Eek...!
This is the way to go!
I know!
Smash!
It feels so good...
What do I do...
Something wrong?
I might have left my
cell phone on the beach...
Why did I need to come?
I'm so sorry...
Because you keep
telling scary stories!
Found it!
Thanks, you two.
Then let's get back, quick.
Yeah!
Right, right.
I haven't told you the end to that story about the beach at night, have I?
W–Wait, now's
not really the time...
Even though it was so late, there was a
woman swimming just past the breakwaters.
But rather than swimming, it was
more like she was just floating there.
When their eyes met,
the woman came ashore.
Her pale white skin...
her long white hair...
When they looked into her face...!
Hey, Takane...
Don't just stand there
watching the moon.
Hibiki, you lack elegance.
Look. This moon is not something one could see so easily in the city.
You're right. So pretty.
The wind feels nice, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Hey.
Chihaya, do you not like going
on trips with everyone like this?
I'm not sure.
But...
I think the reason singing jobs don't come my way is that I lack ability.
For now, lessons are more
important than having fun.
But
I like quietly listening to the
sound of the waves like this.
I see.
What's the matter?
Who knows?
Okay, cheers!
How many is that, now?
Who cares how many!
Here, you too, Ritsuko!
I'm a minor, actually...
My, what a shame.
Well then, all for me!
Please don't drink too much.
Next to sing, Miura Azusa!
Anyway, despite the events that led to us coming here,
we were able to deepen the
bonds between everyone.
Maybe it turned out for the best.
Maybe.
But I'm not going to stop here!
You just watch me!
Ritsuko, do your best!
Ghosts... scary...
The ingredients for rice balls are...
...strawberry bavarois...
They're talking to each other...!
Chihaya, are you awake?
Yes.
Today was fun, wasn't it?
It felt kind of like a field trip.
Wouldn't it be great if we
could come next year, too?
Yeah!
Hey, what do you think
we'll be like next year?
It'd probably be something like, more
and more work building up for us, right?
Yeah, yeah! I'd be so happy if we had our own weekly shows or something.
Doing more concerts,
putting out more CD's...
Maybe one of us would
even be Top Idol!
And then, wearing a stage costume with lots of lace and frills...
Well, aren't you all carefree.
Look at reality for a change.
Ignoring Ritsuko for the moment,
just look at that unreliable Producer.
Forget about relying on him,
I wonder if he can keep his job here?
You think so? It looks like he's
working really diligently to me.
That reminds me, didn't he show up at a meeting recently with bed hair?
Well, I suppose it's because
we have that kind of Producer
that the rest of us need
to look out for him.
Iori...
You're right.
And if we do, then I just know even the things Haruka was just talking about–
They might happen!
But if that really happened
I wonder if we wouldn't be able to go on trips like this together any more?
Don't be stupid.
Thing about those things
after you've achieved them.
I guess you're right.
Good night.
'Night.
We're back!
It's cold!
Welcome back, everyone!
The air conditioner is fixed!
The repairs just finished.
It's so cool!
Things are finally comfortable around here.
Now, with our batteries
charged, it's time to work!
Yeah. I'd like to get back to
lessons right now, if we could.
Right now?
Hibiki, you're so tan!
Hamuzou is, too!
Shijou, you didn't tan at all!
Everything comes
down to discipline.
Everyone! Let's go over our
schedule for after today.
You seem to have rested up some
while I was running around everywhere.
M–My apologies!
Chief, these are souvenirs from everyone.
Oh?! Well, thank you!
But before that...
Ritsuko.
Sir.
Your plan regarding the formation
of the new unit, Ryuuguu Komachi,
has been officially approved.
Congratulations!
Ryuuguu Komachi?
Ryuuguu Komachi
MOONY Good night
Manatsu ni hikaru
Shining down in midsummer
Otsuki-sama onegai yume wo
Oh Moon, please take my dream
MOONY Good night
Manatsu no taiyou
Midsummer sun
Mata aki made Sing again
Sing again until it's Fall once more
Memory taiyou umi mizugi
Memories, the Sun, the sea, swimsuits
Camp hanabi natsu yasumi
Camp, fireworks, summer break
Hizashi dassui heizen ni kaeru koro
When the merciless rays of the sun have calmed
Tanoshii omoi de ippai
We'll be full of fun memories
MOONY Good night
Manatsu ni hikaru
Shining down in midsummer
Otsuki-sama onegai yume wo
Oh Moon, please take my dream
MOONY Good night
Manatsu no taiyou
Midsummer sun
Mata aki made Sing again
Sing again until it's Fall once more
Next Episode Preview
Next week,
on iDOLM@STER!
Here's a surprise quiz!
Who's talking right now?
Is it Ami? Is it Mami?!
I bet you're totally on the edge
of your seat to know who
so check next week
for the correct answer!
The Decision to Move Forward
Look forward to it!