Where am I?
I don't have any memories
of the last two years.
And I also can't walk.
SUMI WASHIO-SAMA
MIMORI TOGO-SAMA
I was told it was
because I had an accident.
Just when I started
getting used to life in a wheelchair...
it was decided that we would move
because of my parent's job.
Living in a place
where I didn't know anyone, in this body...
Yuna-chan was the one who save me...
when I was being crushed
with anxiety.
Hello!
Are you the girl who is going to live here?
Yes.
Then you're my next-door neighbor.
Oh, I'm Yuna Yuki. Nice to meet you.
I'm Mimori Togo.
Togo-san!
Wow, that's a cool surname.
T...thanks.
MUNICIPAL
SANSHU MIDDLE SCHOOL
Every day was fun after entering
the Sanshu Middle School...
with Yuna-chan.
PREPARATION ROOM
HERO CLUB'S CLUB ROOM
I joined the Hero Club
after being encouraged by Fu-senpai.
We did things that would
benefit everyone in high glee.
The everyday life
I spent with everyone
at the Hero Club was my treasure.
But that everyday life
suddenly ended one day.
We became real heroes...
without knowing that
it was my second time.
YUKI YUNA IS A HERO
EPISODE 7
A SUNNY PLACE
-Huh?
-Yuna-chan.
Togo-san.
It can't be.
Surely not!
-Oh, sis!
-Itsuki!
I'm glad you were okay, sis.
Listen, everyone's acting strange,
and...
-Itsuki.
-Huh?
Itsuki, listen to me carefully.
We...were the one.
It's a phenomenon
called forestization.
-Is it an earthquake?
-Time stopped,
and the people who were
chosen as heroes
got sent to the sacred boundary
which Shinjyu-sama created.
Fu-senpai, who was sent
by the amnesty,
gathered girls
who had high aptitudes
and formed the Hero Club.
Humanity's enemy.
Heroes must fight
the mysterious life forms
called Vertex
in order to protect the world.
The world will be brought to ruin
if Vertex reaches Shinjyu-sama.
Before that happens,
we show our willingness to fight
and become heroes for Shinjyu-sama.
Even though the world might end...
Even though everyone is at risk...
I couldn't show my willingness.
Yuna-chan!
But Yuna-chan was...
I don't want...
someone to get hurt...
nor feel the pain.
If everyone has to go through
something like that...
I'd rather be the one
who gives it my best!
Yuna-chan!
Hero's punch!
The Hero Club's activity
is to do things that would
benefit everyone in high glee.
I'm Sanshu Middle School
Hero Club's Yuna Yuki.
I'm going to become a hero.
PREPARATION ROOM
HERO CLUB'S CLUB ROOM
I'm sorry for keeping it a secret.
Why didn't you tell us
about the real meaning
of the Hero Club earlier?
Both Yuna-chan and Itsuki-chan
might have died.
I'm sorry.
But we didn't know
which team would be chosen
by Shinjyu-sama
until the enemy came.
It's a big deal since humans might
become extinct.
You kept something this important
a secret this whole time?
Togo...
If I'm the only one
who can't transform at this rate,
I'll slow down the Hero Club.
I felt pathetic for giving in to fear...
and I said horrible things
to Fu-senpai.
But I was glad.
Because of our aptitude
I was able to meet people like
Fu-senpai and Itsuki-chan.
-Because of our aptitude?
-Yup.
We'll have fun from now on too.
We just have a mission
that's a little bit harder.
Oh... You're right.
I was happy that I was able to
meet everyone too.
It's our mission
to protect this world.
If I also have the power
to protect my important friends...
Stop...
Don't bully Yuna-chan!
Togo-san...?
According to Fu-senpai,
our job will end
once we defeat 12 Vertex.
And Karin-chan
who had special training,
and was send from the amnesty
joined us.
Karin-chan, who was dismissive about
the Hero Club at the beginning,
opened up to us little by little.
Each and every one of us have
important everyday lives and dreams.
We have to protect that.
Seven more to go.
Maybe all of them are here.
It's the worst attack pattern.
Down to the battlefield!
All right! Line of battle!
-Let's go!
-Yes!
Mankai, a hero's trump card
which releases the
accumulated power.
By repeating Mankai,
the hero amplifies her power.
That's how the amnesty explained it.
We went Mankai one after another
against the remaining seven Vertex.
Mankai!
Right there!
You all did great!
Let's celebrate the great victory
of the Hero Club. Cheers!
Cheers!
Juice definitely tastes better
after achieving a goal.
The members who went Mankai
in that battle
all had some unusual changes
to their bodies.
Yuna-chan lost her sense of taste.
Fu-senpai lost her left eye.
Itsuki-chan lost her voice.
I lost the hearing in my left ear.
Both the amnesty and the doctor
said it'll heal right away...
but there was no sign of recovery.
And I found out the truth
about the system of heroes.
I've been calling for you
the whole time, Wasshi.
-I missed you.
-Huh?
Her name was Sonoko Nogi.
She looked at me
with a very sad eye...
and called me Wasshi.
-You went Mankai, right, Yuna-chan?
-Huh?
The one where you open up in a breath
and get stronger in one go.
Oh... Yes, I did.
I did too.
What do you think would happen
to a flower in bloom?
You must have become
physically disabled in some way...
after going Mankai.
I think it was from kindness
that the people at the amnesty
kept this system a secret.
But...
I wish...
they told me about that properly.
If I knew that...
I could have played
with my friends a lot more.
So...
That ribbon looks great on you.
This ribbon
is really important to me.
I do remember that.
But...
I'm sorry...
I can't remember...
It can't be helped.
YUKI YUNA IS A HERO
What's wrong, Togo?
Why did you call us out suddenly?
Fu-senpai, Yuna-chan...
there's something
I want you guys to see.
T...Togo-san?
Heroes can never die.
In order to make sure
that the story of the late Hero...
Sonoko Nogi's story was true...
DEATH BY DROWNING
SELF POISONING
I tried to die
by using every possible method.
The spirit stopped it
no matter what method I tried.
The spirit wasn't there
to protect the hero.
It existed to bind the heroes
to their roles.
In other words,
what Sonoko Nogi was saying was true.
The aftereffects we had
was the price
for the power of Mankai.
It was an offering.
Then...
Itsuki's voice will never...
I didn't know...
I had no idea.
In order to protect humans,
we sacrifice our bodies and fight.
That's what heroes are.
Because I made Itsuki
join the Hero Club...
Hey, sis.
-I found something I want to do.
-What is it?
You have a dream for the future?
If so, you should tell me.
-It's a secret.
-What? Don't be mean.
THERE'S NO MEDICAL ISSUES
TO THE BODY, AND SHOULD HEAL SOON
I won't tell anyone.
I'll tell you one day.
Wait!
What are you planning to do?
I'm going to destroy the amnesty!
The amnesty deceived us!
The aftereffects of Mankai
is permanent!
Why do we have to go through this?
THINGS TO DO TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER
SLEEP A LOT
IF I GET MY VOICE BACK, I WANT TO...
SING!!
Why does Itsuki
have to lose her voice?
Why does she have to give up
on her dreams?
This is the price for saving the world?
-Yuna!
-Get out of my way!
No!
I don't want to see you hurt people,
Fu-senpai!
How could I forgive such a thing?!
But...even if they have told us
about the aftereffects,
we would have been
fighting the Vertex anyways!
-What?
-It was the only way to save the world.
No one had any choice!
Itsuki...
I'm sorry...everyone.
I WOULDN'T HAVE HAD THE DREAM
TO SING IF I DIDN'T MEET YOU GUYS
I'M REALLY GLAD THAT
I JOINED THE HERO CLUB
ITSUKI
Listen to me calmly.
I'll tell you the secret
of the world beyond the wall...
and the scheme of this world.
You see...
I think you should
see the truth with your own eyes.
Her story was true.
The world is in a sacred boundary
on a cosmic scale...
and Vertex regenerates
infinitely.
We repeat an endless battle
while sacrificing
the functions of our bodies.
And eventually...
Like a tree, you won't be
able to move your body...
and will be enshrined like this
in the end.
I made the decision
to destroy the wall
and defeat Shinjyu-sama.
I have to destroy Shinjyu-sama
to break free from being
the sacrifice as a hero.
I can't bear everyone getting hurt
more than they are now.
Itsuki...
Why go to such lengths...
Thanks.
I just felt like saying it
for no special reason.
Things like this house
and the Hero Club...
I've been making you do
all the hard things...
But, to tell you the truth...
I wanted to be able
to walk alongside you.
Never mind being alongside me...
you're standing in front of me
without realizing it.
Why? How come?
Why can't I transform?
I... I'm...
a failure as a friend.
Karin-chan...
Yuna.
I'm...
going to stop fighting
as a hero for the amnesty.
What?
From now on...
I'll fight as a member
of the Hero Club.
I won't let them
destroy our Hero Club.
I don't want to see
your crying face, Yuna.
Karin-chan!
What an idiot.
The impermanence of all things.
Come on.
It's showtime!
Ye who are afar, hear and tremble!
Ye who are near, behold and wonder!
Sanshu Middle School's
second year...
and a member of the Hero Club...
This is the power of Karin Miyoshi!
Take that!
The world where Fu-senpai
and Itsuki-chan
don't have to fight anymore...
Five articles of the Hero Club!
First!
You're likely to succeed...
if you try!
Karin-chan!
Please don't lose
any more than this, Karin-chan.
Please!
How cruel this world is.
And the amnesty is...
This is the only way
for us to be saved.
Hey, Yuna.
There's something
I wanted to tell you.
I wanted to say thanks.
What?
I've been trained as a hero
for a long time.
Fighting was the only meaning
of my existence.
But, thanks to you guys, I...
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
If it's you, Yuna,
you can change Togo's mind...
no doubt...
Stop!
-Mankai!
I fought as a hero at one time
and lost memory of it.
I can't be a hero
if I can't protect my best friends.
If we end everything,
our living hell will end.
If Yuna-chan and everyone
were to become victims...
if I were to forget the
feeling of caring again, I'd rather...
Togo-san!
You won't forget.
-You're lying.
-I'm not.
-I'm not!
-Really?
-Yup.
I'll always be with you.
By doing that, you won't forget.
Yuna-chan.
What is that?
The sun...
I've done something horrible.
It's not your fault, Togo-san.
-We'll stop him!
-Okay!
It won't stop...
I'll never give up...
Yuna-chan!
Not here...
My legs...
Itsuki-chan.
Sorry for what I did
at an important time like this!
Fu-senpai.
I...
Welcome back, Togo.
-There!
-Karin!
Don't underestimate the Hero Club!
All right!
-The Hero Club...is the best!
-Is the best!
Yuna!
-Yuna!
-Yuna-chan!
Take that!
FOR HEROES TOMORROW
Even though everyone in the Hero Club
were going through hard times themselves,
they stopped me
with all their might
for their friends.
Yuna-chan put forth
her whole energy against me...
and hugged me with all her might.
So, I'm not scared anymore.
And the functions of our bodies
started to come back to us...
after wiping out the enemy.
I was able to get
my important memories back.
I still don't know
why it came back to me...
but at least I know
that this isn't a dream.
It's because the life which was lost
didn't come back.
Going to school, studying,
playing, and going home together...
I didn't know everyday life
could be this precious.
I know that everything isn't over yet.
Vertex is still out there.
I don't know what will happen
in the future.
But we're enjoying this
precious sunny place for now.