Making one plus one plus one
equal ten instead of three.
I thought we could do it.
We had to.
The enemy's name is Vertex.
A dreadful being that was born from a virus.
In order to eliminate them...
But why did they name them Vertex?
A word which means "the top."
At this point,
I still didn't know that Vertex was blank by blank.
Time's up.
The power of heroes can only be used by
innocent girls who were chosen by Shinjyu-sama.
We have to depend on you girls.
And so, your next assignment is...
-to rest properly for a while.
-What?
You can't transform unless
you have a stable state of mind.
You won't last until the end if you're always tense.
Yes!
I'm good at resting.
Me too. Me too.
-Yay!
-What should we do?
-Ines?
I guess it's part of our job to rest
in preparation for the next battle.
Nevertheless, will I be able to relax?
My lady, Nogi-sama is here to see you.
This early in the morning?
Hey, Wasshi.
Let's enjoy life in Kagawa!
It's so plush, both your outfit and your car.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, let's go out, so that we can enjoy our time off.
Sure.
Her high energy makes me worried.
Hey, hey, hey. Oh, yes.
Oh, nice, nice, yeah. Yeah, everybody.
SONOCCHI AND I ARE ON OUR WAY
SO EARLY!
DAAAAANG
I'LL BE WAITING!
-Yay, Kagawa!
-Gin is excited too.
You should get into the spirit too, Wasshi.
-Hey, hey, yay! Yes, yes, yes!
-Just listening to music won't get me excited.
-Are you enjoying yourself?
-Hooray!
Now let the fun time off begin!
-Enjoy!
-Hooray!
I'll take you and start running
To a place where no one can catch up
Now is the time to fulfill it
The promise from that day
Yuki Yuna is a Hero
A bud of happiness in the corner
It had a silver glow
I'll show it to you when it blossoms
In the album that I looked back on
It was like that back then, and it still is now
We're laughing together
The season which gets colored from the south
Please, say "I'm back"
I'll definitely come to welcome you straightaway
I'll take you and start running
To a place where no one can catch up
Now is the time to fulfill it
The promise from that day
I was waiting for you patiently for so long
Welcome back
Please, don't ever leave me again
EPISODE 3 EVERYDAY LIFE
This outfit...
I really don't think it suits me.
That's not true. Right, Wasshi?
Wow, I've never seen anyone bleed like that before.
You look really good in it, Gin.
But what is this feeling that's welling up within me?
This Wasshi seems...
like a pro. So cool.
Photos express love. Oh, Gin,
you have to try on all the beautiful clothes today.
Amazing, Gin.
-Your name means silver, but this is gold.
-I'm so confused.
The score is high for this one.
This is also nice.
-This one is out of the question.
-No, it's not, not, not...
-That was good.
-What was?
It's your turn, Wasshi.
I think you'll look good in an outfit like this.
No, I can't wear such unpatriotic clothes.
I think you would look great in it.
What? Seriously?
Here, I'm just going to make you wear it.
Come on, come on.
Oh, nice. You look good in it too, Sumi.
You could even become an idol.
I'll be your first fan.
Really?
I shouldn't wear such unpatriotic clothes.
A Japanese woman like me, doing such a thing.
Wasuyu.
SONOKO'S DREAM
Sonoko's dream.
Sonocchi, I...
am prepared to become an idol.
You guys, too, Sonocchi and Gin.
-Me too?
-That rocks!
Let's go.
The concert is going to start.
This is a hero-like liveliness!
Rock!
That's the dream I had.
Were there a lot of audiences?
How rock 'n' roll of you to worry about that.
Wasuyu.
What did you draw, Sumi?
It's the second destroyer of the
Shokaku aircraft carrier, Zuikaku.
It's so realistic.
Right?
It's a carrier vessel which participated as
a major force in a number of battles
in the Showa period during the former century.
It became the decoy,
and did its best until the very end.
You're so knowledgeable about those things, Sumi.
My dream is to become a historian.
Just as expected, you're a serious person.
-It does sound like a dream Wasshi would have.
-Do you have a dream, Sonocchi?
Maybe a novel writer would be nice.
I've been posting my work online sometimes.
Oh, I kind of get it.
You do have a unique imagination.
I want you guys to be in the novel as characters too.
Mino-san who is kind and reliable,
and Wasshi who is earnest and sometimes funny.
Sometimes funny?
It's better than being boring.
I know, but...
I want to be relied on too.
I like your expression when
you're kind of feeling sorry for yourself.
What? That's not a compliment.
Wow, the atmosphere
between you two is great right now.
It's really nice.
It's great.
What about your dream, Gin?
When I was in kindergarten, I wanted to be
a pretty guardian to protect my family and everyone.
I get it. The superhero who protects the country.
That's every girl's aspiration.
What about now?
Why did you blush?
Well, families are nice,
so I thought it would be nice
to get married and settle down.
But that would make my dream for the future...
a bride.
If it's you, Mino-san,
that dream will come true right away.
-I'm looking forward to seeing you dressed in white.
-Come on, stop poking me.
I'll use it as a story in my novel.
You can't. It's embarrassing.
-Shall we practice...
-A novel, huh?
-...the goodbye kiss?
-No.
This must be it.
Sonocchi's novel.
"SPACE SANCHO"
RIVERS OF TEARS... A MASTERPIECE!
She has great reviews.
She has the highest number of readers as well.
Just as you would expect of Sonocchi.
Oh, I got it.
I'll influence everyone to have national defense ideology
through my historical novel.
Now let's see what kind of reviews I got.
THE SENTENCES ARE LONG,
AND IT'S PAINFUL TO READ
THIS AUTHOR SHOULD JUST WRITE COLUMNS
I hate that my writing skills can't fully
convey the excellence of my country.
-Wasuyu.
-Sonoko's dream number two.
SONOKO'S DREAM
Hey, Wasshi.
Look over here.
No, I'm not Wasshi.
My real identity is...
the hero of wealth and military strength.
Attention.
I am the National Defense Mask.
Rock!
How cool.
That's the dream I had.
You were a knight in shining armor
who looked like this.
Oh, that's a fashionable outfit.
-Rock!
-Wasuyu.
23 CENTIMETERS
GRATITUDE
Orientation with the first-grade students
is coming up soon.
Be aware that you are in sixth grade,
and make sure to look after them properly.
GRADE 6
CLASS 2
What do you do in an orientation?
You do fun things with the first-graders.
Innocent first-year students.
As heroes, our role is to protect this country.
-In other words...
-In other words?
It's part of our mission to look ahead
and educate them on patriotism.
Is it?
That sounds like fun.
Let's make a plan, then. What is this?
TO NOGI SONOKO
I got a letter.
-Is it a letter of challenge?
-Be careful.
It might be a chain letter.
Well...
"Whenever I notice, I'm always looking at you."
-Just as I expected. It's a duel. Where will it be?
-It's a curse. We might need salt to purify.
"I would like to get to know you better."
That is more terrifying than
just placing a curse on you.
"Your job must be hard,
but that's precisely why I want to be your support."
That's what it says here.
Sumi, this could be...
The thing that starts with the letter L.
-A statue of Rakan?
-No, a love letter.
Oh, I see.
Dot, dot, dot...
Love, love, love...
Wow, I got a love letter.
I'm so happy.
Why are you so calm?
You got a love letter.
I knew it as soon as I saw
the handwriting and the envelope.
The person who gave me this is a girl.
Oh, it's just a girl.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Sumi-sama, this is for you.
TO SUMI WASHIO
Could this be?
I got...
a love letter too?
YOU'RE AN HONORS STUDENT, BUT
YOU SOUND NAGGY WHEN YOU GIVE ADVICE.
PLEASE, BE AWARE OF IT.
ANONYMOUS SENDER
How could I get excited about a mere piece of paper?
What a mistake.
Wasuyu.
Come on, let's go, Sonoko.
All right, I'm going to push you.
-We're going to aim for the Ryugu castle.
-So fast.
Two, two, three, four...
-One, two, three, four...
-Hey, Sumi.
How long are you going to be warming up?
Accidents at the pool are scary.
If you don't do a warm-up properly,
your body won't be ready.
We have this whole place to ourselves,
so let's enjoy ourselves freely.
Hey, if the enemy comes right now,
does that mean we have to go
on a mission in our swim suits?
I hope we don't have to do that.
Something that irregular probably
doesn't happen that often, but...
The first one did come early.
We shouldn't let our guards down too much.
Sumi really does have big boobs.
Maybe she's actually in high school.
I think she's older. Maybe she's in college.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, Gin. Do you want to race me?
Sounds like fun. I'll accept your challenge.
We have things to do for the orientation
after this, so don't overdo it--
Ready, go.
They're not listening.
Sigh...
Sigh... Sigh...
You overdid it at the pool.
Not at all. One final push.
I'm looking forward to the actual day.
Thanks.
Thanks to you guys, it'll be an awesome orientation.
The evil monster is coming
to attack our country from beyond the sea.
We're in trouble.
Thump, thump...
"What a beautiful place.
Give me this land."
This shameless monster is saying things like that.
What would you do?
I'll run away.
If you do that, the monster would take over this place.
-I don't know what to do.
-I'll fight.
That's right. We have Shinjyu-sama on our side.
Let's gather our courage and fight.
Alongside the National Defense Mask.
-That paper is blank.
-It's blank.
You're right.
Then let's call them all together.
Say it after me.
All together now.
National Defense Mask.
People are calling us to protect the country.
They're screaming for us to protect love.
-Attention.
-A patriotic warrior.
-National Defense Mask arrives.
RICH COUNTRY, STRONG ARMY
Today we'll learn how
to defend our nation while exercising.
Now stand up, everyone.
The weather is clear today.
We'll now begin the national defense.
Be careful not to bump into each other.
Let's begin.
NATIONAL DEFENSE EXERCISE
SONG BY SUMI WASHIO
A round, full, bright, red sun
To the right, to the right
Round and round
Look up to the sky
Say hello
Look down and say hello
Clench your fists
Up, up, and up
To the front, to the back
Both feet firmly on the ground
Through and through
With all your might
Jump, jump, jump
Take a deep breath
Push, push, push
Hide your presence
Slowly, slowly
Today is another peaceful day
Thank you very much
Rich country, strong army!
You overdid it.
I'm sorry.
Wasuyu.
SONOKO'S DREAM
Sonoko's dream number three.
As punishment for brainwashing
the students in the lower grade,
I forbid you from eating udon for a week.
No way.
You're kidding, right?
-I can't eat udon anymore!
-Oh, no. We should go to the hospital right away.
-It's over!
-Calm down, you guys.
Wasuyu.
Your tea is ready.
Thank you. But, Sumi...
Don't take too much of the housekeeper's work.
I feel calmer when I'm doing something.
Since it's Sunday, why don't you go
and play with Nogi-san and the others?
Gin has plans, so we're on our own today.
Then you should go and do what you like, Sumi.
I was thinking Gin might get in touch
to ask me to hang out with her after her plan.
And Sonocchi might suddenly
come to the house like before.
It seems like you made good friends.
GIN: I'M SHOPPING WITH MY
FAMILY NEAR THE STATION
SONOKO: I'M WALKING AROUND THAT AREA
SUMI: SONOCCHI, SHOUT YOUR NAME
REPEATEDLY IF YOU GET LOST
SONOKO: SONOKO NOGI
She's already lost?
In the end, we all got together again.
Heroes naturally get drawn towards each other.
Jeez, I'm glad Gin found you.
Is it okay that we haven't
said hi to your family, Mino-san?
It's fine. You already know
my dad and my mom, right?
I mean, I'm not good at those kinds of things.
It's nice that you go out...
-...to shop with your family on your day off.
-Yeah.
Well, it's embarrassing when
you bump into someone you know.
I'm done with my errands,
so I'll hang out with you guys.
Oh, but give me a minute.
Hey, little bro.
Don't be sad because your sister is popular.
There, there.
Come on, smile.
Sigh...
Our time off is almost coming to an end.
We have to be on alert again.
We should brace ourselves.
The orientation ended up like that, but it was fun.
Yup.
It went by so fast.
Oops, you guys are going
in a different direction than me.
See you, guys.
Sumi?
Wasshi.
I'm sorry.
No, I understand how you feel.
Our time off is going to end soon.
That's what you thought, right?
I know I said that I was confident
about being able to rest, but...
because of our job, I wasn't sure
if I could actually relax.
But?
Yeah. It was an unnecessary worry
with the three of us together.
Me too.
I had a great time.
You too, right, Wasshi?
Yeah. Her face says yes.
If Vertex destroys Shinjyu-sama,
this fun everyday life will disappear.
-We'll never let that happen, right?
-Yup.
Of course, I feel the same way.
Let's do our best.
Yeah.
We can't go home if we stay like this.
-Disperse.
-I have an idea.
Let's just have a sleepover.
-That sounds great. Let's do it at Gin's house.
-My place? I have two younger brothers.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
-Heroes possess courage and determination.
-What? Two of them?
-What is this?
-He shot an arrow.
It was so much fun.
-Just as you'd expect of Sonocchi.
-Get out of here!
NEXT EPISODE
SOUL