SANSHU MIDDLE SCHOOL
PREPARATION ROOM
HERO CLUB'S CLUB ROOM
"Sanshu Middle School's Hero Club
is a club that does things
which would benefit the world
with honor.
We do our best not to give up.
You're likely to succeed if you try.
We keep things like this in mind
and do our best.
The Hero Club will be
making our way today as well!"
Sounds like an essay
by a grade-schooler.
-It's by a middle-school student!
-I know that.
Yuna. The town magazine is
going to introduce
the Hero Club's activities,
so come up with a good slogan, okay?
-Okay!
-Sis,
we got a lot of thank-you e-mails
from the kindergarten.
This is amazing!
It was a great hit the other day.
The parents were
laughing wryly, though.
-That's not true!
-Sorry! Sorry!
Have you guys started already?
I fell asleep during cleaning duty.
Sonoko.
You're probably the only one
who can sleep at a time like that.
Wow, I got complimented.
Good for you. Karin-chan doesn't
compliment people that often.
That wasn't a compliment!
Nibosshi!
That has nothing to do with this.
All right. We're all here, right?
Then, let's start our
December quarter session.
Okay!
First, I've laid out all the requests
that have been sent on the map.
A lot of things happened till fall,
but now Sanshu Middle School's Hero Club
is full of energy like this.
EPISODE 1
SPECTACULAR DAYS
Zero is nothing.
The Indian people who came up
with that concept are amazing.
Well, rather than something like that,
can we do things that'll prepare me
for high-school entrance exams?
Why is Sonoko-san in
second year teaching my sister?
Odango!
Nogi is smarter
than most home tutors around here.
I know she doesn't seem like it.
Really? Then I want her
to teach me too!
Oh, that's a good idea!
I'm a bit worried about you, Itsuki.
I didn't study during the summer
because there was so much going on.
Your grades were good
up till your second year, right?
They were extremely good!
But now, they're extremely bad!
House!
Sis.
It can't be helped.
Too many things happened
since I started third year.
We can be here now
because you worked hard,
Fumin-senpai.
PREPARATION ROOM
HERO CLUB'S CLUB ROOM
I'm Sonoko Nogi, a prospective member
of the Hero Club!
What? Sonoko Nogi? That Sonoko Nogi?
I was a hero over at the Long-Bridge
two years ago.
Allow me to again
thank you in advance.
Why is the legendary hero here?
Because I don't have anything to do
at home.
Just for a reason like that?
I dropped out of grade school.
How could she say
such a serious thing so calmly?
Since she was freed from her role,
she asked the amnesty
to let her go back
to having a regular life.
I never thought I could go back
Yes, indeed.
She's a weird legendary predecessor.
We would love to welcome
the previous great hero, Nogi-san.
You can just call me Nogi
or Sonoko, Fumin-senpai.
-Fu?
-Thanks in advance, Nibosshi.
Who told her that?
You'll be Ittsun, Itsuki-chan.
What? Ittsun?
Yuna-chan, I think you'll be Yu-yu.
Wow, sounds wonderful.
Then I'll call you Sono-chan.
-Oh, that would be great.
-Okay!
Oh, this is Sancho.
He's glad to see you guys.
Nice to see you all.
Nice to meet you.
She's an intriguing person.
I see.
FIVE ARTICLES OF THE HERO CLUB
This is how you guys have been
enjoying your youth.
Sono-chan.
Welcome to the Hero Club.
Yup! I'm also going to enjoy my youth
from now on.
Let's do this! Yeah!
I've been watching
from my bed the whole time.
I was thinking that the Hero Club seemed like fun,
that it must be fun.
I didn't think I could come back
to school again.
I'm so happy.
All right! Let's study then!
Let's start
with my favorite complex matrix.
-I don't understand it at all.
-A complex number is...
Karin-chan.
Thanks for coming out
even though it's a Sunday.
Well,
I just happened to be free today.
It was just by chance.
Yeah.
But you were so cool, Karin-chan.
You can do it!
You weren't bad yourself.
Strike!
Thanks!
The Hero Club is such a weird club.
That's why it's fun.
Something different happens
every day.
That's true.
The sun will go down,
and it'll be tomorrow again.
It'll be Monday already.
Time goes by so fast on our days off.
We'll have to do homework
when we get home.
I already did mine.
What? Even though you had
a game this morning?
I did it on Saturday.
That's to be expected.
You're so good, Karin-chan.
-What's wrong?
-Oh, no. It's nothing.
Ta-da!
A cake! How did you sneak that in?
I had my home economics class today.
I didn't think of that.
-Did you make that, Itsuki-chan?
-Yes.
I brought it
because I made too much.
You did well, my sister.
What a unique taste.
You should say that
she's expressive.
Come on, let's eat.
How is it?
-Setting aside what it looks like...
-It tastes good!
Lady, you're a professional.
Itsuki finally made something edible.
Sis, that's actually more hurtful.
Ittsun, Ittsun, let's open a shop.
We can make it a franchise
in the future.
Sonoko-san, your dreams are so big
that I can't tell if it's a joke or not.
But I appreciate it!
I can keep on eating this!
Go ahead then, Karin-chan.
No, thanks.
Itsuki should have it.
Oh, I already had some during class.
Sonoko-san, please go ahead.
You're the one who should have it,
club president.
If I ate two of them, I'd have to be
concerned about my femininity.
Fu, why did you cut it
into five pieces in the first place?
I don't know. It was from habit!
A habit?
Oh, well
it was for no special reason.
It's cut into five pieces.
How did you do it?
I just used math.
Wow! Impressive!
Botamochi.
What is it?
I was just thinking maybe we ate
botamochi in the club room before.
Oh, you made it
in home economics class before right, Yuna-san?
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Come on. Snack time is over.
Let's practice for Sunday.
Okay!
YUKI YUNA IS A HERO
OFF-LIMITS
Mino-san.
I finally was able to come.
Long time no see. How have you been?
Oh, I guess
that wasn't the right question.
GIN MINOWA
Speaking of not seeing
for a long time,
the shop in Ines that had
the Shoyu-mame flavor was gone.
It's too bad.
The flow of time is always cruel.
Listen, Mino-san.
I joined the Hero Club.
That's right. The one
in Sanshu Middle School.
Everyone is really interesting.
They're neck and neck
with our team.
Today is a Saturday,
but all of us are going to put on
a play at a kindergarten.
I'm going to do
an excellent job as a tree.
Don't miss it.
Oh, that's right.
I made this at home.
I remembered
how you used to make it
and made it myself.
This is for you, Mino-san.
Make sure to compliment it
if it's good.
And this one is for myself.
And...
Mino-san, why do you think
I made three of them?
MONUMENT TO THE WAR DEAD
Nogi isn't here yet?
It's almost time.
She hasn't read the messages.
I wonder if she's still asleep.
Sonoko-san was
so excited about today.
Even though she's only a tree.
We have no choice.
I guess we'll have to do this
without the tree today.
Yuna.
Yuna?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, what's wrong, Yuna?
It's time for our performance.
Are you not feeling well?
I feel all right.
Um...
Yeah?
I kind of feel restless.
Do you guys feel like that too?
Yuna-san?
Shall we cancel today?
Everyone in the Hero Club.
Thank you for doing this today.
Oh, actually...
The kids have been
looking forward to today.
They've been waiting anxiously.
It's all right.
Let's do it. Everyone is waiting.
Hey there!
I'm the nefarious Satan.
I'm here today to get the kids
who don't listen to their teachers.
Let's run wild and do as we please!
There's no need to control yourself.
Wait, Satan!
Don't give the kids any bad ideas!
You're so stuck-up!
No matter how much
the hero got hurt,
she never gave up.
It's because if everyone gave up,
this world would be stuck
in the darkness.
Everyone was bowing down
to Satan one after another
and the hero found herself
all alone.
No one knew the hero was all alone.
Even if I become all alone...
A hero is still...
Yuna?
Still,
a hero is...
It's because as long as
we don't give up,
there will still be hope.
Even if I lose everything...
Nevertheless...
I don't want to lose my
most important friend!
-What's wrong?
-She's crying.
Yuna-san?
Nogi?
I...
I promised that
I'll always be with her.
But yet...
Yuna-san.
You too, Sonoko.
PREPARATION ROOM
HERO CLUB'S CLUB ROOM
Both of you, what's going on?
-Listen carefully.
-Yup.
The memory we have now isn't real.
Something horrible is happening,
and I don't know what that is,
but we're pretending that
it didn't happen.
What are you talking about?
-Hey, Yuna--
-I
remember now. Wait.
The Hero Club had
another really important friend.
There's no way we could forget.
There's no way we should have forgotten.
But I...
Why did I...?
Yuna, calm down.
Guys, try to remember!
Togo-san!
There used to be a girl called
Mimori Togo here!
Oh, come to think of it,
where is Togo now?
Togo.
Mimori Togo.
Ta-da!
It's Sonoko from the Nogi family.
Are you surprised?
What? You're that Sonoko Nogi?
We're in the same class from today.
Thanks in advance.
Sonocchi.
Hey, Wasshi.
It's me, Sonoko.
Sonocchi.
You're surprised.
-My surprise was a big success!
-Sonocchi!
Hey, Wasshi.
PREPARATION ROOM
HERO CLUB'S CLUB ROOM
I'm Sonoko Nogi,
a prospective member of the Hero Club!
Sonoko Nogi!
I was a hero over
at the Long-Bridge two years ago.
Allow me to again thank you in advance.
I never thought I could study
with you again, Sonocchi.
Scold me if I fall asleep
during class, okay?
You should be careful
not to fall asleep.
It's as if Togo is her mom.
The circle of fate.
Oh, sounds cool!
What does it mean?
It means a fateful encounter.
I'm the girl of fate!
-Fortune!
-Wealth and happiness.
It also means
an unavoidable situation.
What's with the serious face,
Itsuki?
National Defense Mask.
The mysterious hero
who's a sensation right now.
-There's someone like that?
-Yup.
People are calling us
to protect their country.
They're screaming
for us to protect love.
A patriotic warrior!
National Defense Mask is here!
Someone!
Stop!
People are calling us
to protect their country.
They're screaming
for us to protect love.
A patriotic warrior!
National Defense Mask is here!
-I got you!
-What?
I'm the National Defense Mask.
I'll show up as much as I can
when people are being exposed to evil threats.
As much as you can?
Hey!
I found you, Togo.
I don't even know where to start.
The National Defense Mask is here?
Yuna-san.
Thank you for saving me
the other day
when I was in danger!
-Would you shake my hand?
-What happened?
She lost her wallet at night
and the National Defense Mask
looked for it with her.
For some reason, I'm really comfortable
talking to you, National Defense Mask!
I wonder why.
That's not surprising.
Hey, how come you're here
at the Hero Club today?
It's because...
Because...
Yuna-chan, I'm the National Defense Mask!
We knew that.
It can't be.
I had no idea that Togo-san was
the National Defense Mask!
You're serious, aren't you?
So, what do you mean you're sorry?
Ever since I recovered,
I've been in agony.
How come?
The fact that
I destroyed part of the wall.
Even though it was
an impulse of the moment,
it's a fact that I put the world
in danger.
That's something unforgivable.
I didn't know how I could make amends for it.
So I thought about ways to atone
for my sins.
That's how you came up
with the National Defense Mask.
Wasshi, you're really extreme now.
I understand how you feel,
but you're rushing it too much.
I'm sorry.
The National Defense Mask is
so cool! I want to become one too!
What?
To tell you the truth,
despite my appearance, I'm
the second National Defense Mask!
Then, I'll be the third one!
Don't create more of them!
Sheesh.
What are we supposed to do
if people like Karin mimic you
and become the Dried Sardine Mask?
I won't mimic them!
Togo-san.
We feel the same way about wanting
to do your best for everyone.
She's right, Wasshi.
You can rely on us
if there's something going on.
Yuna-chan, Sonocchi.
Yeah, they're right.
Togo-san.
You guys.
Thanks.
What? What's going on?
What is this?
Why don't any of us have
any memory of Togo?
It's as if she never existed
in this world!
Sis.
Even though I'm the club president,
yet again...
But I remember now.
Why?
What's going on?
Wasshi,
where are you,
and what are you doing now?
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
What's going on?
We'll go there without stopping!
This is just plain dangerous!
What a cool ship!
-Make sure to come back, Yuna.
-Togo-san!
I'll save her
over and over again!
EPISODE 2
IMPORTANT MEMORIES