I found out about "blank" after "blank."
And that what made "blank" suffer in the past
wasn't "blank," but it was "blank."
Also that the cause of it was "blank" in the first place.
I thought it was a little similar
to the story of the "blank" of "blank."
New equipment?
Yes, you will need to hand in
your smart phones temporarily,
so that you can get them.
Shinjyu-sama gives power to the heroes,
so that they can fight with the foreign enemies.
But not everyone can receive that power.
It's a very limited thing.
A person who can identify with Shinjyu-sama
at an extremely high level,
so it can only be used
by a very small amount of selected people.
This is the new gear?
Yes.
They're spirits that make the hero's armor
a lot stronger.
Nice to meet you.
If this came on time...
No, it's nothing.
This is encouraging.
Yup.
EPISODE 6
PROMISE
What a lavish breakfast.
Did you cook this, Sumi?
Yes. I specially made it with a lot of vegetables today.
How come? It's all right to have
a lot of meat in the morning.
No.
You have to be careful with your health, Mother.
Now let's eat.
Sumi.
You don't have to work yourself so hard
when you have your studies and your job to do.
Well, there's nothing much I can do other than this.
Sumi.
You're already an important daughter to us.
I know. Thank you, Mother and Father.
Besides, I like to cook.
More than you do, Mother.
Well, I'll be going now.
Okay, be safe and see you later.
For people like us who couldn't have our own kids,
she's more than we deserve.
She's really a good girl.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
-Good mornin--
-Morning, Sancho.
OUR HEROES, HANG IN THERE
We made this secretly behind the teachers backs.
We're sorry about the other day.
You're not supposed to do this kind of thing.
But, we couldn't think of anything else.
Since we bombarded you with questions,
without thinking about you guys, nor Gin-chan.
It must have been so hard for both of you.
We all thought about it together,
and we really wanted to apologize.
We definitely should keep this
a secret from the teachers.
But thank you. Really.
Hey, your job will be over someday, right?
Then we can hang out normally, right?
-Sure.
-Great!
I've wanted to become better friends
with you, Washio-san.
Sancho's cute.
Look at the pumpkins. It's a festival from overseas.
It shows how broad-minded our country is.
We get to enjoy all kinds of festivals.
Yes.
-Yeah!
-Whoa, what?
Wear this hat.
See, Wasshi? You look great in it.
You--? You think so?
You should learn
how to pull a pigeon out of that hat.
Hey, don't come out, Sebastian.
-Seba--
-Sebastiantengu Crow.
I gave it a middle name.
I-- I see.
You shouldn't come out without permission.
So these are the spirits that Shinjyu-sama sent.
Unlike their looks,
their powers are probably truly terrifying.
I hope so.
Mom, that pumpkin is flying.
Oh, you're right.
It's floating with alpha wave.
What? That's amazing.
Wasshi, you're amazing.
Hurry up and put it away.
There's no choice, if that's also part of their role.
Sonoko was born to the Nogi family,
and it's her mission.
But Sonoko isn't responsible for any of this.
Her soul will always be able to be with Shinjyu-sama.
It's a very honorable thing.
I know, but...
If it was possible, I wish I could take her place.
Can we not tell them about that new system?
There's no way we can tell them such a cruel thing.
My thoughts are with you.
The Shoyu-mame flavor
doesn't hit the spot for me after all.
You'll get yelled at by Mino-san.
Give me some of your vanilla flavor, Sonocchi.
Wasshi stole my ice cream!
You look like you're going to go for it again!
Please, be sure not to get upset.
For the sake of the girls
who exist together with Shinjyu-sama.
But...
It's as if they're sacrifices!
They are politely carried off as heroes,
but they will continue to get chosen for eternity,
WASHIO FAMILY
NOGI FAMILY
and will be the sacrifice to be lost.
Our fathers, mothers,
and friends are all rooting for us.
We're fortunate to have our roles.
They even gave us a banner.
Is it coming?
Yup, it's coming.
We're starting to know when it's coming.
This battle is probably going to be a tough one.
Shinjyu-sama was also trying to tell me that.
WARNING
WORLD OF TREES
Brace yourself.
Yup, we'll need to concentrate.
Oh, that reminds me...
Wasshi, hold on to this.
Okay.
I wouldn't mind it if you put it on your hair.
I'll put it on once the battle is over.
-Compliment me if I look good with it, okay, Sonocchi?
-Yup.
I'll protect you, Sonocchi.
I'm going to protect you too,
Wasshi. That's a promise.
Yup, it's a promise.
We'll definitely go home together.
Yuki Yuna is a Hero
There are three of them.
I see.
All right, let's do this.
-Roger that.
-Cool.
Thanks in advance. Your name will be Shirogane.
Oh, that's a good name.
I'll back you up, so count on me.
I'll be the forward, then.
Yeah!
This should...
I felt an electric shock.
Thanks, Sebastian.
What is this? I can't see anything.
Gas. It can't be.
This is the hero's new power?
Here we go.
Ready?
-All out!
Your attacks won't reach me anymore.
What is that?
Wow, it came to crush me.
Two down, and one more to go.
Oh, Wasshi.
My legs.
What? My eye.
It already came this far.
Wow, there are so many of them!
There are too many of them!
We have no choice but to do it.
-Sonocchi!
-Yup!
-All out!
-Oh, my--
-Wasshi!
Sonocchi!
The Long-Bridge.
My arm is numb.
No.
Sonocchi.
You're okay.
Hey, Wasshi. Something is weird.
Is this how we should be fighting?
I don't know.
But for now, if we don't protect Shinjyu-sama,
our world will disappear.
You're right.
The same attack as before.
I won't let happen.
I won't let anyone else...
Wasshi!
I'll leave the rest up to you, Sonocchi.
Please, stop him.
Yup.
You can count on me, Wasshi.
All out!
Get out of the way!
Get out of here!
What is that?
Wait.
I thought my heart stopped beating for a second.
I won't let it escape.
What is this?
My heart isn't beating.
I get it now.
What happened to the city?
Wasshi!
Oh, my God!
It's terrible. Outside of the wall is...
Who are you?
What is going on?
That's right. What about Gin?
Where's Gin?
Wasshi!
It's all right.
I'll do something about the rest.
I'm Sonoko Nogi.
You're Sumi Washio.
That girl is Gin Minowa.
Three of us are friends.
We're BFFs.
I won't die.
We'll be able to see each other again later.
So, I'll be back soon.
All out!
I don't care how many times I die.
Because I can never die.
We are kept alive.
Where am I?
Who am I?
Four people are missing
from the accident at the Long-Bridge.
UNPRECEDENTED CATASTROPHE
AT THE LONG-BRIDGE
Many were injured. They are still conducting a search.
According to the amnesty's announcement,
-there is no further damage.
-It was announced
that the fire at the coastal factory area
was due to chemicals catching fire.
The fire at the mountain last night
was extinguished before dawn,
and did not affect the surrounding area.
MS. SUMI WASHIO
Wow, it's so big.
Was my family this rich?
My new life is going to begin here.
Hello!
Are you the girl who is going to live here?
Yes.
Then you're my next-door neighbor.
Oh, I'm Yuna Yuki. Nice to meet you.
I'm Mimori Togo.
SUMI WASHIO'S CHAPTER
Continuing to fight while
"blank"-ing your body for Shinjyu-sama.
Apparently, that is supposed
to be a very wonderful thing,
and I heard my parents were crying.
Wasshi...
I guess you are now "blank"-san.
I'm glad it affected you less than it did me.