When I heard I was chosen by Shinjyu-sama,
I knew it was something remarkable.
I just didn't realize
what the significance of it was.
But hearing that this enemy
would destroy the world,
I felt that I had to fight.
In the beginning,
I was just fighting feverishly.
So little did I know
that I would end up fighting like this.
Your daughter made the miso soup today.
I hope you like it.
It looks delicious.
Let's eat.
GRADE 6
CLASS 2
PEACEFUL MORNING,
RICH COUNTRY, STRONG ARMY
-Good morning.
-Good morning, Washio-san.
Good morning.
I'm sorry, Mom.
This isn't home.
Nogi-san.
This is the classroom,
and it's before the morning homeroom.
Good morning, Washio-san.
Good morning.
Good morning, everyone.
Morning!
I made it.
-Gin Minowa, you're late.
-Ouch, miss, that hurt!
Hurry up and take your seat.
Mino-san, late as always.
Hey, Gin-chan, why were you late today?
There's a lot that goes on
when you're in 6th grade.
Oops!
I forgot my textbooks.
Class helper of the day, go ahead.
Yes.
All rise.
Bow.
We are here today because of Shinjyu-sama.
Let us bow to the shrine.
Take your seats.
Is this...?
It's time.
It's time for us to fulfill our roles.
Here it comes!
I've never seen anything like this before.
Is this...?
Shinjyu-sama's sacred boundaries.
EPISODE 1
SUMI WASHIO
This is the world of sacred boundary
that Shinjyu-sama created?
A world of trees.
It's just like they taught us.
This is amazing. It's all trees.
Oh, I wonder if that's the Long-Bridge.
Yeah, I think so.
The bridge that connects this side
to beyond the wall.
That's where the enemy comes from.
The fact that we're the heroes
makes me so excited.
Minowa-san, this isn't a game.
I know.
Oh, look at that.
It's here.
So that's the enemy, huh?
When it crosses the bridge
and finds its way to Shinjyu-sama,
the world will end.
Yeah, I know.
We have to stop it.
-Let's fulfill our roles.
-Yup.
Things that come from heaven and earth shall not leave.
As a god, declare your arrival and presence.
Souls rise up
to call down the power of the gods.
The gods called down by the souls
are summoned now.
Wow, our first actual fight.
We haven't done a joint training yet.
The enemy appeared earlier than predicted.
Well, it'll be all right.
Let's deal with this carefully.
All right, I'm gonna knock it down.
Mino-san, wait for me.
Both of you, wait.
This place is huge.
It's so different from our training.
Isn't it so strange that this place
was originally a city, Washio-san?
It's huge.
-This must be...
-The thing that came from the other side.
Vertex.
-Oh, look.
-A corrosion.
The longer it takes to beat it,
it'll have a more harmful effect
on the original city.
In that case...
-Wait.
-Hey.
A swift attack.
What is this?
Mino-san!
You two.
Yes.
Take that.
Jeez.
-Nogi-san.
-Crap.
I forgot this turns into a shield.
Hurry.
It's like a huge typhoon.
Do something about this.
I will.
No way.
Washio-san.
What should I do?
YUKI YUNA IS A HERO
My arrows can't damage it enough.
Minowa-san is strong, but she can't get near it.
I don't know how to manage Nogi-san.
What should I do?
Watch out!
-It's dangerous. You have to keep moving.
-Minowa-san.
Mino-san.
This thing is resilient.
Mino-san, are you okay?
She drank the whole thing.
For a hero with the power of God,
it's easy to drink up all the water.
I feel sick...
You're amazing, Mino-san.
What did it taste like?
It tasted like cider at the beginning,
then it changed into oolong tea midway.
That sounds disgusting.
More importantly, the Vertex.
That thing is dangerous.
It has so many wakemitama.
The exit must be close.
We have to go after it.
But it didn't have any effect.
If we don't hurry,
it'll leave the Long-Bridge.
We won't be able to fight it off if it leaves.
-Let's go again with sheer determination.
-Oh!
I've got an idea.
It noticed us.
It's looking over here.
We have to hurry.
It's coming.
Expand.
This spear can turn into a shield.
-That's handy, Sonoko.
-Keep on marching forward.
Nogi-san, are you okay?
Heroes should have guts.
Push it back!
Heave.
Come on, you too, Washio-san.
Heave. Heave. Heave.
-Now!
-Charge!
Washio-san!
It's difficult to aim.
Mino-san, I'm going to swing you around.
Go for it.
Here I go!
Minowa-san!
I'm not gonna let you go!
Mino-san!
Take that!
What is this?
The ceremony of chinka.
Mino-san, are you all right?
Yeah, I weakened it with all my might.
Thanks to you, it has started.
How pretty.
It's gone.
It calmed down.
-Did we...?
-Beat it?
-We did it!
-Yay, yay, yay!
-Alrighty!
Yes!
I see, we're not back to the school.
Oh, crap, I'm in my indoor shoes.
You're right.
I took a photo of the world of trees.
Wait, what?
It's not the world of trees.
I guess it can't be photographed.
Hey, Washio-san.
Sumi-san?
Sumisuke?
It was a narrow victory.
I couldn't have won against it on my own.
HOW TO MAKE FRIENDS
As I told you all yesterday,
these three have important roles
to fulfill for Shinjyu-sama.
So there will be times when they will
suddenly disappear from the classroom.
But don't panic or make a fuss about it,
and calmly support the three of them in spirit.
You all have the duty to study hard every day.
GRADE 6
CLASS 2
Hey, is your role hard to do? Does it hurt?
Well, I'm not supposed to talk about it.
-What? You're such a meanie.
-Seriously?
-Come on, tell us.
-Yeah.
Hey, Nogi-san, Minowa-san.
If you're available,
how about a triumphal celebration after this?
Oh, that sounds great.
Yeah, let's go.
Well...
I am very pleased that we were able
to welcome today without any accidents.
Thank you all for coming today.
Era of the Gods, year 298.
Since this is the triumphal celebration
for the heroes' first battle,
I wish for all your continued prosperity,
health, and bright future.
You're way too formal. Cheers.
Thanks, Sumisuke.
I've been thinking about asking you out,
but I had trouble bringing it up,
so I'm really happy you asked us out.
Yeah, isn't this the first time
that you asked us out, Washio-san?
Yeah, it actually is.
Even though we haven't had
any joint training,
I think we did pretty well in our first battle.
Yeah. I got so excited,
I've been wanting to talk about it.
To tell you the truth, I also wanted to talk about it.
That's why I asked you two out.
I...
don't think I really trusted you guys.
It's not because I hated you guys or anything.
I'm not good at relying on other people.
Sumisuke.
But that's not good.
If I were on my own...
If I were on my own,
I probably couldn't have done anything.
Because you guys were there...
So...
Will you be friends with me from now on?
We're already good friends.
I'm glad.
I wanted to become good friends
with you too, Sumisuke.
You see, I'm not good at making friends either.
Nogi-san...
Sumisuke, you were feeling the same way too, huh?
-I'm glad, Sumisuke.
-Um...
Nogi-san...
Yup?
What's with that name "Sumisuke"?
You started calling me that out of nowhere.
Oh, I was calling you
by a nickname without realizing it.
You didn't realize it?
I'm flattered, but...
I don't really like that name.
Then how about Wasshina?
Doesn't it sound like an idol's name?
I hate it even more.
Seriously?
You wouldn't want to be called
Sonokorin either, would you?
Wow, that's a nice name.
I'm sorry. Forget I said that.
Oh, I've got an idea.
Then how about Wasshi?
I guess that'll be all right.
Let's stay good friends, Wasshi.
Yeah.
Good. Then call me Gin.
Minowa-san is too formal.
You're right.
Well, whatever.
All right, then.
Let's celebrate today by eating
the amazing gelato from this place.
I'm so happy.
These roasted green tea and Calpis flavors
are spot-on.
How about yours, Mino-san?
I got Shoyu-Mame gelato.
What is that? It looks good, though.
This is delicious.
The balance of this bittersweet green tea flavor
is perfect.
What is it?
I want a bite of it, if it's that good.
I've never done anything like this before.
It's delicious.
This is our first collaborative work.
That's not the right way to use that word.
I've always wanted to do something like this
with a friend.
How about you, Wasshi?
Oh, yeah. Me too. Oh, I mean...
-I'm glad.
-Yeah.
I'll take you and start running
To a place where no one can catch up
Now is the time to fulfill it
The promise from that day
YUKI YUNA IS A HERO
A bud of happiness in the corner
It had a silver glow
I'll show it to you when it blossoms
In the album that I looked back on
It was like that back then, and it still is now
We're laughing together
The season which gets colored from the south
Please say "I'm back."
I'll definitely come to welcome you straight away
I'll take you and start running
To a place where no one can catch up
Now is the time to fulfill it
The promise from that day
I was waiting for you patiently for so long
Welcome back
Please don't ever leave me again
Era of the Gods, year 298.
This is a story of three heroes.
A fairy tale of three girls
who were chosen by God.
It's always an innocent girl who gets chosen by God.
And in many cases,
the end result is...
ON NEXT EPISODE
-It's kind of like Battleship Nagato...
-What is this!?
-This is weird...!
-Charge!
-Let's share who we have a crush on!
-I can help too.
-Training doesn't end until we are home!
-Goal!
NEXT EPISODE
FRIENDS