According to the materials from
the blank calendar times,
which was blank of years ago...
when you wanted to be friends forever,
apparently people used to say, "BFF."
I liked it because it was kind of an interesting word.
Three of us are friends forever.
Even now,
I feel like they're close by.
Thanks for helping me
with the blackboard monitor job.
No problem.
I usually have it easy as
the health care staff of the classroom.
Sumi makes people get in line relentlessly, though.
We'll head to the morning assembly,
but anyone who talks would be
punished with moxibustion.
You rarely ever hear the word,
moxibustion, right?
We should always do our job with everything we got.
Speaking of jobs,
the fourth Vertex hasn't come yet.
We do have the class trip coming up soon.
I hope it doesn't come at the same time.
About that class trip...
I wonder if it's okay that we're leaving town?
Once we turn into heroes, we can get
to the Long-Bridge right away, so it'll be fine.
I don't want it to come though.
We won't be able to do anything
if we overthink about everything.
You have a good point.
Well, even if something happens,
this hero would take care of it.
Wow! You're so cool, Mino-san.
You guys are right.
It'll be ok if it's the three of us.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'll take you and start running
To a place where no one can catch up
Now is the time to fulfill it
The promise from that day
Yuki Yuna is A Hero
A bud of happiness in the corner
It had a silver glow
I'll show it to you when it blossoms
In the album that I looked back on
It was like that back then, and it still is now
We're laughing together
The season which gets colored from the south
Please say, "I'm back."
I'll definitely come to welcome you straight away
I'll take you and start running
To a place where no one can catch up
Now is the time to fulfill it
The promise from that day
I was waiting for you patiently for so long
Welcome back
Please don't ever leave me again
EPISODE 4 SOUL
The blisters on my hands stings and hurts.
Today's training would be tough.
Maybe you should change how you hold your spear.
The teacher said it won't get better even if I change it.
There, there.
Pain, pain, go away!
TRAVEL GUIDEBOOK
These are for you two.
Su-- Sumi-san, what is this?
As you can see, it's a guidebook for the class trip.
I sent the data version of it to your handsets as well.
Wow! You took the trouble to make these?
I got enthusiastic, and stayed up till late,
so it got a lot thicker than I planned.
Wasshi, you're a perfectionist,
and you're the type who gets devoted to this.
Your future husband would be a happy man,
but also might have a hard time in a lot of ways.
Why would it lead to that?
If only there was a guy like me.
You guys would be great together.
At any rate,
let's use this travel guide, and finish
our preparation for the class trip.
I'll perform moxibustion on you if you're late.
Where do you even buy that?
-Ines.
-Ines. Nice! Yay!
-Y-- Yay?
-Yeah!
I'm ready now.
Whoosh. Bang!
Roar!
Ahh, run!
I should let Sumi know.
I FINISHED GETTING READY FOR THE CLASS TRIP
SONOKO : OH, MADAM, ME TOO.
SUMI : YOU'LL NEED A PLASTIC BAG TOO
Oh, I guess to put dirty things in.
Plastic bags.
-He's cute no matter how many times you look at him.
-Your guard's down!
Come here, you!
You can't beat a hero with an attack like that!
Hey, sis, can you bring back some souvenirs?
You're just so spoiled, aren't you?
-All right.
-Woo-hoo!
-But in return, look after Kintaro properly, okay?
-Yup!
I wonder if he'll start crawling soon.
Yeah. I'm looking forward to it.
Follow me!
As a hero, we have to play at the athletic course.
This sort of thing is also fun.
Both of you are fast. Wait for me.
Oh, it swings!
-Nogi-san, you don't need to be that scared.
-It swings. Aah! It's swings.
When I think it's a bottomless pit when I fall,
it's actually pretty thrilling.
You-- You have great imagination.
You must never step on the fifth tire.
-What?!
-It's the end if you touch it.
The ghost of a fleeing soldier would
stand by your pillow every night
and tell you to give him back his rice field.
What's the point in scaring her?
She wanted some thrill,
so I thought I would give that to her.
You're almost here.
Heroes possess courage and determination.
Gotcha.
There, there. Great job.
Now that I got used to it,
I can do it more smoothly next time.
What are you doing, Sumi?
I wanted to get in because you guys were having fun.
You're like a puppy.
Wasshi probably wanted to get her
head patted by you, Mino-san.
You are good at it, Mino-san.
You just want to be spoiled, don't you?
There, there.
Gin-chan, catch us too.
All right, come on then!
Gin's popular.
She's always been popular.
-Hey, Gin-chan.
-What's up?
The thing is, my sister asked me to get your autograph.
What?
I think she looks up to you, because
she heard about your important job.
Oh, I see!
I guess I'm now the person who writes autographs!
It'll be lunch time after we climb this.
All right!
Here we go.
Heave ho!
Well, this is too easy.
I can climb with one arm.
Hey, Gin. Stop fooling around.
It's totally fine.
My blisters. Watch out!
Are you okay, Mino-san?
Yeah, that scared me.
Gin, I know you're having fun, but
you're probably being too frivolous.
You should think about the importance of our roles.
I'll repay my debts.
And I'll reflect on myself.
I'll speak less.
That's great. You're good at this, Minowa-san.
I help out at home sometimes.
Nevertheless, it smells so good!
This would definitely be delicious!
After all, I did make it.
Gin, weren't you saying that
you were going to speak less?
You're such a tomboy.
I think you're pretty much a tomboy too, Sonocchi.
I forgot you didn't like bugs, Wasshi.
It's all right. I'm sure you'll come to like them.
You-- You think so?
It just looks like cockroaches to me!
It's delicious! It tastes like beetles.
We didn't cook it!
It tastes good.
Aren't you used to eating
better meat than this, Sonoko?
This meat tastes better.
-It's probably because we're eating it together.
-Oh.
Sonoko, you have some around your mouth.
Thanks.
Your energy level changes a lot.
Both of you guys can cook, but I can't,
so I suddenly felt ashamed of myself.
I'm sure you can make things like yakisoba, Sonoko.
Then, can you and Wasshi teach me next Sunday?
-Sure.
Oh! Jinx.
By the way,
teacher, you're leaving the peppers, aren't you?
I don't really like them, but I am going to eat them!
-I wonder if something happened in her previous life.
-At times like this, it'll be fun if you
imagine that the pepper fairy would
come to see you in the middle of the night if you eat it.
Th-- That's unique. Thanks.
I should be able to eat it smoothly.
You got complimented by the teacher.
As a reward, you should ring the bell, Sonoko.
The bell?
We cleared the entire athletic course!
We did it.
Oh, Sumi. Is our town over there?
Yes, you're right.
Just as I thought, you can't see
the Long-Bridge, nor Ines.
You really like Ines, don't you, Mino-san?
Ines is great. After all,
there's a community center in there.
Correct!
I knew that too.
You guys can read my mind already, huh?
Can you read my mind?
In your case, I can't.
We'll probably never be able to do that.
That's kind of sad.
Don't worry. I could guess that you would react like that.
Really? Yes! Woohoo!
How hyper she was going to get
was unpredictable, though.
-Just as you'd expect from Sonocchi.
-By the way,
I have enough knowledge about you
that I can even write an instruction manual.
Oh, I wonder what it would say on the first page.
It's a pretty difficult product, so please be careful.
It-- It's as if I'm someone annoying.
But I fully understand why.
I think it's good to be complicated.
Mine would probably be as thin
as a flyer in the newspaper.
That's not true.
You're easy to read,
but there's a lot to write about you.
You-- You think so?
I want to keep on uncovering
all different sides of you from now on too.
Uh, don't be too hard on me please.
To tell you the truth, I thought we
wouldn't get along at first, Mino-san.
What is it all of the sudden?
-I felt the same way.
-What?
Well, you were cheery, and good at sports,
so I felt like we were from different lines.
But I knew you were really nice once I talked to you.
-Wasshi's character is a good one too.
-I'm a character?
I see. It's true that you can't
tell these things till you talk.
I'm glad you liked me.
I'll be counting on you from now on too, friend.
-Likewise.
-Yup!
Yuki Yuna is A Hero
It was so much fun.
You're going to trip, Sonocchi.
I wish everyday was a class trip.
I agree with that.
This must be....
It's the enemy!
Geez, we just had a fun class trip.
It's not nice that this would happen right at the end.
It's not the worst since
it came after the class trip.
It's the class trip till you get home, Gin.
You sound like a teacher!
Let's finish this quickly,
so I can take the souvenirs home!
I'm getting used to seeing this scenery.
Be careful, Gin. Times like that--
Could be the most dangerous, right?
It'll be all right.
My clothes are strongly made for close combat.
That doesn't mean you should let your guard down.
You did almost get injured at the athletic course.
Mino-san, it's as if you're
saying things on purpose recently
so that you would get told off by Wasshi.
I got into the habit of getting told off by Sumi.
Give me a break.
It's here.
What? Two of them?
I didn't see that coming.
Even if there are two of them,
it'll be okay if we work together!
True!
Mino-san and I'll deal with one of them each,
so back us up with a raid!
You can count on me, Sonocchi!
Let's go!
I'll fight with the gross looking one!
They both look gross.
Oops! Take that!
You're easy to read! That's perfect for me!
Nice!
Looks like it'll hurt if I get hit by it.
There!
We have the upper hand.
We'll keep fighting though like this.
-Crap!
-Uh-oh!
You two! Over here!
What is this?
Sumi! Sonoko!
Are you okay? Sonoko! Sumi!
He shot an arrow.
Gin...?
I'm the only one who can move.
It's crunch time, even if it is scary.
Leave it up to me, and you guys rest.
See you!
Gin.
Gi--
Those bastards!
You got a lot closer.
But I won't let you go...
any further than this!
I know how you're going to attack!
I knew you would do that!
I saw it before!
Don't look down on me!
N-- Now you've done it!
That hurt!
Try taking it yourselves!
You guys should...
get out of here!
If they kill Shinjyu-sama....
I won't let them do that.
Never!
I won't let them.
I'm going home!
I'm going to protect it!
Monsters like you won't understand this power!
This is the human's...
courage!
Determination...
and soul!
Where's the enemy?
Wasshi! Over there!
Gin.
We'll be there right away.
Gin!
Mino-san!
You chased them back, didn't you, Mino-san!
That's amazing, Gin!
Seriously.
G-- Gin.
The world of trees would unravel soon.
Let's go to the hospital after that, okay?
S-- She's right!
You have to give the souvenirs to your little brother.
I...
was supposed to learn how to cook from you.
Yeah.
Three of us were going to do that next Sunday.
Hey, Gin.
Gin.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
-We need to get stronger.
-Let's fight for Mino-san.
-This is Gin-trained determination!
-Mino-san would...
-Gin would!
-Please don't forget about Mino-san.
Not just two of us, all three of us are heroes.
NEXT EPISODE
GOOD BYE