When I met Gin Minowa for the first time,
I felt like she was a difficult
person to deal with.
I got overwhelmed by her loud voice
and her aggressiveness.
But when I got to know her,
she was actually a really nice person.
So, who would have thought
she would blank and blank?
Half a month after finishing our first job
as heroes protecting humanity,
the second enemy appeared.
I can't move!
That spinning thing...
It might be weak against an attack from above.
There's nothing we can do. This is unfair.
This is bad. I have to do something.
Sumi?
Namuhachiman...
Bodhisattva.
No way.
Oh, watch out!
Mino-san!
Minowa-san!
There's a limit to bulldozing your way through.
Yes, ma'am.
No matter how many lives
you all have, it won't be enough.
You did a good job by
keeping the damage to the
real world to a minimum, but...
That's thanks to Minowa-san and Nogi-san.
Your weak point is not having
enough practice working together.
First let's decide on a leader
within the three of you to take charge.
The leader? That's me.
Nogi-san.
Can I ask you to be the leader?
Me?
I'm not the leader type.
So as long as it's not me, I don't mind.
I see.
The Nogi family have great power over the amnesty.
She's from a lineage that should be
chosen as the leader in a situation like this.
I also agree that you should be the leader, Nogi-san.
Wasshi...
But I'm the one who will
actually have to unite them.
Yup, I'm going to do my best.
So that's decided, then.
According to the oracle,
we have some time before the next attack.
We'll do a training camp
to strengthen your coordination skills.
A training camp?
I'll take you and start running
To a place where no one can catch up
Now is the time to fulfill it
The promise from that day
Yuki Yuna is a Hero
A bud of happiness in the corner
It had a silver glow
I'll show it to you when it blossoms
In the album that I looked back on
It was like that back then, and it still is now
We're laughing together
The season which gets colored from the south
Please, say "I'm back"
I'll definitely come to welcome you straight away
I'll take you and start running
To a place where no one can catch up
Now is the time to fulfill it
The promise from that day
I was waiting for you patiently for so long
Welcome back
Please, don't ever leave me again
EPISODE 2
FRIENDS
RESERVED FOR SHINJYU HALL
She's late.
Minowa-san is late.
Oh, sorry that I'm late.
You're late.
You're ten minutes late, even though
you were so eager. What's going on?
It's complicated.
I mean, I'm the one who's at fault, but...
Anyway, I'm sorry, Sumi.
Let me give you an advice on this occasion.
I think your lifestyle is too sloppy.
You should have an awareness
that you were chosen as a hero.
Mom, where are we?
I guess I have to be the reliable one after all.
So we can protect this beautiful country.
SANSHU
SUN BEACH
Since your role has officially started,
the amnesty will fully back you all up.
Don't worry about your family
or school, and do your best.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you ready? The rules for this training are simple.
You must safely get Minowa-san to that bus.
Don't forget each other's roles.
Ready?
Defend me properly, okay?
Am I not allowed to move from here?
Yes, you're not.
Okay, start.
Let's go!
Can we not jump from here?
We shouldn't cheat.
It's an easy win.
-Out.
-I'm sorry, Minowa-san.
Don't worry, Wasshi.
What you call me is too formal.
You can just call me Gin.
And call me Sonocchi.
Okay, try calling us that now.
All right, try again.
We're going to do this till you can reach the goal.
You must do everything together
during this training camp.
You're going to make one plus one plus one
a ten instead of a three.
Wasshi, are those all your things? It's not a lot.
You think so?
Mino-san, you're buying souvenirs way too early.
What about your luggage, Sonoko?
I don't even know where to begin...
I'm going to make udon with that stone mill.
Out. Start again.
Therefore Shinjyu-sama made the wall
so it will protect the humans from the viruses.
I thought we wouldn't have
to study during the training camp.
However, something happened.
Nogi-san, can you answer what happened?
Yes, ma'am. Vertex was born
and started attacking our home, Shikoku.
That's correct.
She was actually listening.
Booyah, this should do it!
Out.
Thanks.
Yeah!
Goal!
We did it!
All right!
Eating balanced meals, getting disciplined intensely,
and getting proper sleep every day.
It's more like a training camp
for a sports club, instead of heroes.
Won't there be an event where
we can learn a super killer move?
Don't you agree, Sumi?
We don't have a choice. We're doing this
to strengthen our coordination skills.
I think I gained more muscle.
It's all right to get stronger,
but it's a difficult menu
for pre-adolescent girls to complete.
Mino-san, does your wound
from being caught in the tornado hurt?
I'm fine. How about you, Sonoko?
This stings more than anywhere else.
Yeah, holding that thing will definitely do that to you.
Sumi Washio, show us your body.
Why?
I want to admire the biggest breasts in our class.
It's as if this is a fruit shop.
Give me those peaches, old man.
Hey, stop it.
I only said the truth.
If anything, you're expecting too much
by being self-conscious about having big breasts.
I wish Sancho could be part of this too.
Minowa-san and Washio-san...
Don't be too loud in the hot spring.
Wow, the body of an adult is impressive.
You can't really tell when they're wearing clothes.
You're right. It's kind of like Battleship Nagato.
What's that?
It's a battleship our country
proudly had in the former century.
I'll tell you about it in detail.
Oh, okay.
You guys think you can sleep that easily
on the last day of training camp?
I brought my own pillow, so I can sleep easier.
What was its name? Tacos?
It's Sancho. There, there...
So, Sonoko-san, what's with your clothes?
It's a chicken. I like charbroiled chicken.
-Yeah, it is tasty.
-At any rate, we shouldn't stay up this late.
-You're at your own pace, aren't you, Sumi?
-If you don't listen to me,
they'll come and get you in the middle of the night.
They'll come and get us?
Stop saying horrifying things,
and let's share who we have a crush on.
As in someone we like?
What about you, Minowa-san?
If I had to choose, it would be my little brother.
Family members don't count.
I don't have anyone either, so it's even.
What about you, Nogi-san?
I have someone.
Wow, is it time for girl talk?
Who is it? Is it someone from our class?
Yup. It's Wasshi and Mino-san.
Just what I expected.
Are we okay like this?
We're fine. We have sacred roles to fulfill.
Let's all work hard tomorrow too.
Training doesn't end until we are home.
-Fine.
-Lights off.
What is this?
It's a planetarium.
Why do you have it here?
I brought it with me because it's pretty.
Turn it off.
She's late.
Sorry, I had some business to take care of.
Some business?
Something is fishy.
SET MEAL WITH GRILLED MEAT
SOLIDITY
That was a close one.
You didn't make it.
I'm sorry.
Minowa-san is late way too often.
But she never says why.
Maybe she has her reasons.
No, you can't.
A cat? Why? It's so suspicious.
Yuki Yuna is a Hero
We're almost at Minowa-san's house. Nogi-san...
Where is she?
It's an ant. Hey, hey, how are you doing?
Don't go wandering off.
MINOWA
This must be Minowa-san's house.
Let's see what's going on.
-Are we going to ding dong ditch?
-You shouldn't do such a terrible thing.
Let's use this. I brought this thinking
that it might come in handy.
Wow, you're like a pro.
Hey, don't cry.
You're my little brother, aren't you?
Don't cry.
The only time you can cry is
when you realize that
you won't get back your New Year's money
you entrusted to your mom.
Oh, he's getting cranky.
You probably don't want milk,
or your diaper changed.
Here, here, here.
Oh, you stopped crying.
What a good boy, little bro.
You're such a spoiled little brother.
I'll make you my underling and
push you around once you're grown up.
Oh, did you get used to our house?
Sis, what about the errands?
All right, give me a second.
Wow, Mino-san is wonderful.
She's babysitting and helping with housework.
I didn't know she had such young brothers.
I wonder if she's having
a hard time looking after them.
Oh, Wasshi, look at that.
I wonder if he asked her for directions.
Again?
Mino-san is so kind.
She's putting the bicycle back up.
They keep on coming.
I guess Mino-san has a tendency
to get involved in incidents.
I wonder if this is because she's a hero.
It's a lost child this time.
She's mediating a fight.
Instead of being caught up in it,
it's more like she can't leave them alone.
I can't watch this anymore. Minowa-san.
Oh, Sumi?
I'm here too.
-We'll help you.
-What?
What's going on, you guys?
So, you guys have been watching me
from the front of my house?
Seriously?
I feel kind of embarrassed.
You shouldn't feel embarrassed. It's admirable.
So this is why you're always late.
You should have told us.
If I do that, it's as if I'm blaming it on other people.
In any case, it is my fault for being late.
Have you always had that tendency?
I'm unlucky most of the time.
I've never won anything in a bingo either.
See? Our Sunday is ruined.
This time for sure.
It's here.
It looks like a visual kei.
I'll survey the situation first.
What's this?
Is it because of that enemy?
This time for sure.
This time for sure. This time for sure.
Relax, Sumi.
Minowa-san.
Let's defeat it together.
Nogi-san.
Let's use what we learned at training camp.
You guys.
All right, let's get close to the enemy.
-Roger that.
-Okay.
It's taken command of the air.
Hey, get down here!
It's going to launch something at us.
Willpower!
-Mino-san!
-I can hold it off for at least a minute!
Go get the enemy up there!
But Minowa-san will be in danger if we do that.
What should I do? There's going to be
damage to the real world.
And Minowa-san...
What should we do?
The two of us will strike the enemy!
-Wasshi, get up there.
-What? Okay.
-Mino-san!
-Take that!
Get out of here!
Charge!
Mino-san!
Shatter it!
Get ready for a triple payback.
Keep the change!
It started.
The ceremony of chinka.
It's over.
Oh, it hurts.
Mino-san, are you okay?
I'm tired.
This battle was hard on my back.
We were able to attack it
because you were taking its attack like that.
Thanks, Mino-san.
You did great too.
Well, you said you could
hold it off for one minute.
So I knew it would work out okay
if we had that much time.
It would have been dangerous
if we had dragged it out.
Our teacher saw through it.
Nogi-san's inspiration at a critical moment.
I just kept on debating what to do.
And yet...
I assumed Nogi-san got chosen
because of her family lineage.
I'm a huge idiot.
I was thinking I had to be the reliable one.
But I was just dragging them down.
I'm hungry.
You were in the middle of eating udon, weren't you?
-What?
-What's wrong, Sumi? Are you hurt?
No, I...
I'm sorry.
Next time, I'll go along
with you guys from the beginning.
I'll work hard.
Yeah, let's do our best.
Here you go, Wasshi.
Thanks...
Sonocchi.
Say that again, Wasshi.
What about me?
Gin...
Gin.
That makes me happy.
I feel like we're finally friends.
Gin.
This is a story of three heroes.
A fairy tale of three girls who were chosen by God.
It's always an innocent girl who gets chosen.
And in many cases,
the end result is...
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
-What is this feeling?
-I'm so confused.
-Let's enjoy.
-What would you do?
-I got a love letter too?
-It's really nice.
-Hooray!
-Let the fun time off begin!
NEXT EPISODE
EVERYDAY LIFE