Shinjyu-sama is God itself.
That's why I prayed...
I don't want to part with my friends.
In a way, that became a reality.
In exchange for our friend's sacrifice...
we obtained blank's blank.
Gin Minowa died while serving Shinjyu-sama.
It's sad to say goodbye to a friend.
But let's send her off with a sense of pride.
The funeral will be held tomorrow.
Classes will be canceled, and we'll all go together.
I'll take you and start running
To a place where no one can catch up
Now is the time to fulfill it
The promise from that day
Yuki Yuna is a Hero
A bud of happiness in the corner
It had a silver glow
I'll show it to you when it blossoms
In the album that I looked back on
It was like that back then, and it still is now
We're laughing together
The season which gets colored from the south
Please say "I'm back."
I'll definitely come to welcome you straight away
I'll take you and start running
To a place where no one can catch up
Now is the time to fulfill it
The promise from that day
I was waiting for you patiently for so long
Welcome back
Please don't ever leave me again
EPISODE 5
GOODBYE
I would like to offer my condolences today.
We are about to say goodbye to our hero
with great sadness.
Gin Minowa used her natural abilities...
unflinching fortitude...
and...
her humane personality...
to serve her important role for Shinjyu-sama.
That bright accomplishment
will remain as our guideline forever.
We pray that you rest peacefully with Shinjyu-sama...
and watch over our future for years to come.
THE MINOWA FAMILY
Thank you for coming today.
It's a shame. She was still very young.
I didn't know Gin-chan was doing religious services.
It's beyond our imagination for people like us in the
municipal government, it must have been tough.
It's a very honorable thing
to die while serving Shinjyu-sama.
Even so...
If it were my own child...
Gin-chan did really well.
Gin-chan became a spirit of the war.
I envy her.
The Minowa family can receive
fantastic benefits from now on.
It's more likely Gin is feeling a sense of pride
from being able to do her daughterly duty.
Ladies...
Well, although it was for a job...
losing a child's precious life...
causes unbearable grief for the friends and families.
The family must be going through such heartache.
Gin Minowa's...
floral tribute.
Mino-san...
If there is a God, why didn't it protect her?
-My sister's worked hard this whole time!
-Tetsuo, stop that. Tetsuo!
-But why did it have to be my sister?
-Tetsuo.
-Don't take away my sister!
-Come over here, Tetsuo.
That's not something a god would do!
Sis!
Tetsuo.
At a time like this...?
Wasshi...?
Then... let's fight for Mino-san.
Mino-san would say we should beat the enemy.
Mino-san would...
Gin would be able to break through this!
This is Gin-trained determination!
-Sonocchi!
-I'm going to give it my all!
We did it, Mino-san.
I wonder if Gin was watching this.
She was.
I bet...
Ms...
Both of you...
Thank you for your service during this hard time.
No.
If we couldn't do anything right now...
Mino-san would surely yell at us.
Well...
No.
Even though you've experienced
many frightening things...
and had sad things happen to you...
the two of you are giving your full attention
to your difficult jobs.
You two are definitely heroes.
I don't think you've ever complimented us like this, Ms.
But, Ms...
Mino-san is the one who is the greatest.
She chased back three of them all by herself.
So...
please don't forget about Mino-san.
She was strong...
and amazing.
Not just the two of us...
all three of us are heroes!
Yes.
I'm sorry. I'll make a correction.
All three of you are heroes.
Yuki Yuna is a Hero
What a creepy dream.
A great enemy is coming.
The dream was probably a sign of that.
The battle will get fiercer.
I need to get stronger.
-Morning.
-Good morning.
GRADE 6
CLASS 2
Good morning!
Morning.
Nogi-san.
I've been wanting to ask you this.
Okay.
But we were told not to ask about your
role in Shinjyu-sama.
Nogi-san, you had to do your job
during the funeral yesterday too, right?
You disappeared.
-Hey--
-Was it okay? Weren't you scared?
What? Well, no.
Nogi-san, what kind of things
do you have to do for your job?
Hey, you're not supposed to ask them.
The Amnesty will make you disappear!
-They'll make you disappear, since you said that.
-Seriously? They're going to make me disappear!
-Crap!
-Gin-chan is going to be in the text book.
My mom told me. Isn't it amazing?
-Yeah.
-Keep up the good work, Nogi-san and Washio-san.
The people chosen by Shinjyu-sama are so incredible.
You guys are the heroes of Shinjyu Hall.
I'm rooting for you!
Well...
It's not like I wanted to be like that.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning, Washio-san.
Hey...
I don't know the circumstances...
but did Minowa die for all of us...?
She was a strong girl, who could do that...
That's why she was chosen by Shinjyu-sama.
Minowa...
If you care about Minowa-san...
please leave us be.
Here!
Sonocchi.
Oh, sorry.
I should have been one beat faster, right?
Hey.
Heroes need a change of pace too.
It's such a rare thing for you
to invite me to hang out, Wasshi.
I'm glad our teacher gave us permission.
Let's forget about our roles and relax today.
You're all fired up, Wasshi.
My parents made me wear this.
You sure do look good in it.
You look like a doll.
Spin around slowly.
That's embarrassing.
Just do it.
-Like this?
-Wow, you're in high spirits!
Oh, this is a photo opportunity.
Hey, no photographs.
Seriously? I was going to make it my home screen.
That's embarrassing, don't do that.
-I have you on my home screen right now too.
-What?
See? It's from when you were eating udon.
Hey, take that off. It's really embarrassing.
It's my phone. I can do whatever I want.
I'll put you on my home screen then.
Oh, you'll put me on your home screen?
You're not embarrassed by that?
-I want that one.
-Thanks for waiting.
Will you buy me that?
Hey, this isn't a place to cry.
It's a fun place, so smile.
Candy apples and chocolate bananas...
they're such classics,
there's nothing new about them.
Considering all that,
you seem to be fully enjoying yourself.
Even though it's a classic,
it tastes good when you have it at a festival.
I guess so.
Something smells good!
Welcome!
Can I have two of these please?
Oh, I won't be able to eat that much.
What, really? I'll eat both then.
You have an enormous appetite.
Wow, this tastes good! What is this?
I want to buy the whole shop!
What?
-Call me on this number!
-Hey, that's enough.
You! You're so cheeky.
-Holy cow!
-You don't have any allowance left.
Is that the one you want?
Yeah. That first prize bird.
Wasshi, what are you doing?
Calm down.
Adjust your breathing.
Oh, okay.
I've been watching the rifle's tendency.
Leave the adjustment up to me.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Concentrate on the target.
Concentrate...
Stay relaxed...
and squeeze your finger.
Now.
-It's all about the willpower after that.
-Willpower!
-What?
-Yes!
-What the heck!
-I got the bird!
-There's no way this could fall down with a cork ball.
What do you mean by that?
Oh, I...
Here. It's yours, miss.
Wasshi, we did it.
It is my area of specialty.
But you're the one who pulled the trigger.
That's yours.
Wow, I did it!
Can you swap this for those three?
This should be the best place to see the fireworks.
It's a great spot.
You've done your homework.
I identified it from past blog posts.
You're really good at things like that.
It's so big.
Thanks...
for this.
Yup.
One is for Mino-san.
Thank you too, Wasshi.
I'm glad you and Mino-san were chosen as heroes.
I'm weird, right?
I couldn't really make friends...
You're not weird, Sonocchi.
You're wonderful.
If I wasn't with you guys...
maybe I wouldn't have worked this hard.
Gin is very aggressive...
and I lacked flexibility.
If you weren't the leader,
we wouldn't have come together.
We were able to work hard because it was us.
Yeah.
Since we started sixth grade...
I've had fun during our training and sleepovers.
I'm glad I was able to become friends with you two.
Me too.
The three of us...
are friends forever, no matter what happens.
Yup.
Yes. I've received the data.
I'm confirming it right now.
The girls?
Yes. I decided to give them a break.
The mental trauma they suffered
when they lost their friend
seems to be quite severe.
Yes.
Goodbye then.
"The new system to prevent further loss of heroes..."
What is this?
If something like this is implemented...
You can strengthen weapons
and techniques in many ways.
But there's a limit to the strength of mind.
Those girls...
We shouldn't make them...
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
-New equipment?
-Don't come out, Sebastian.
Floating with alpha waves!
I'm going to protect you too, Wasshi.
I'll protect you, Sonocchi.
-Let's go!
-Sonocchi!
It's a promise. We'll definitely go home together.
NEXT EPISODE
PROMISE