Lazy Lily is starting!
Lazy Lily
SUMMER VACA~CHUU~N! +
Lazy Lily. I’m a carefree lady,
yuru yuru I'm a nonki na lady
my spirits are higher than ever now, baby.
kyoumo kibun ha joujousa baby
After all’s said and done we’re fourteen,
nandakanda ittatte otoshigoro fourteen
so we are junior high school students!
so we are junior high school students
Lazy Lily. You are a girly angel,
yuri yuri You are girly na tenshi
hair aflutter, you are a cutie!
hair ga chotto nabiite cutie
It’s a grand old sunny bright day!
sansan kyoumo ii tenki da nihonbare
Everyone now: Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
minnade wasshoi saa wasshoi
Rush! Rush! Rush!
rashurashurashu
Coming home from a long day of play,
asobitsukarete kaettanara
a hot bath sounds like just the thing.
ofuro ga iiyu da na
You only get to live once,
ichidokirino jinseidakara
so don’t hesitate, don’t fret.
tamerawazuni hora chuucho ha yamete
No time to think, just fly!
imasugu tobidase
Life is happy, so don’t be idle,
jinsei ha happy taidani baibee
just be happy-go-lucky - why not?
sunawachi happy go lucky de iijan
If we come to a roadblock we can sit a moment and have tea,
ikitomattara hitomazu ocha demo nonde
Rush! Rush! Rush! OK!
rashurashurashushushu de OK
Get on your marks, and take a bold dive,
isseinose de goukaini diving
our every single day is an adventure!
sunawachi nichijou koso daibouken
The days go by like sweet ice cream melting.
amai aisu no youni toroketeku mainichi
Rush! Rush! Rush! OK!
rashurashurashushushude OK sa
Even when we grow up we won’t forget this,
otonaninattemo wasurenai
Lily shu-ra-shu-ra-shu-shu-shu!
yurishurashurashushushu
I’m going out!
Take care.
Okay!
Huh?
Akari, you’re late!
What? Weren’t we meeting at 3?
Doesn’t Akari Time entail arriving 30 minutes early?
What kind of logic is that?
We thought we’d surprise you by matching your time.
Oh! I get it.
Kyouko, I did as you asked and wore clothes I don’t mind getting wet.
But what’s going on?
I brought a change of clothes too!
When I say “summer,” what is the logical response?
Shaved ice and watermelons?
Not quite.
Gaming till you drop?
That sounds fun! Let’s do that sometime.
Swimming pools, then?
Almost!
Is it homework?
Akari, you like homework, huh?
On such a hot day? What else?
Oh! Water balloons!
I used to play with those! It’s been a while.
Truly it is the activity of the season.
Water fights, though? How childish.
Excuse me?
Oh, Yui prefers adult play.
Do you play with women?
What are you saying?!
So we play catch, like that.
Looks fun!
It seems a bit difficult though.
If you drop it, it’ll go BOBOUH!
What kind of sound is that?
Think fast, Chinatsu!
Okay, next is Akari.
Remember: don’t let it burst!
Here I go then.
You’re doing good!
Here, Yui!
Kyouko!
Hey!
Oh sorry. My chest just kind of slipped.
That doesn’t make sense.
Again!
Geez, Kyouko.
What are you trying to do?!
Whatever happened to “let’s play catch”?
My heart is as the seasons.
It is ever-changing.
That’s some fast changing.
You’re wide open!
Now you’ve done it!
Looks like it’s just gonna be us getting each other soaked.
They seem to be having fun.
Akari, think fast!
You surprised me!
Doesn’t it feel good?
Yeah, it feels nice and cool.
Yui, why don’t you join us?
Well...
Here goes!
W-Wait!
Why’s it three on one?!
Akari has sustained a direct hit!
Akari went BOBOUH!
Whoops, sorry!
I’m completely drenched.
Same here.
Chinatsu looks kind of different.
Yui, you didn’t get very wet at all.
Really?
It’s a hot day. You ought to be wetter!
Let’s go for another round.
What?
Here goes!
Right back at you!
You’ve done it!
So cool!
Amazing, Yui!
So sorry. Your bullets have no—
How’s this?!
That’s not allowed!
Take that!
That’s not allowed either!
If you’re going to play that way!
Not fair!
Look who’s talking!
You leave me no choice.
Transform!
I am Anti-bully Ranger: Leaf Mask!
You’re making fun of me!
How dare you do that to the hero of justice?!
Eat this!
I won’t lose to you!
Come on, you two!
Calm down!
So… who won?
Everyone lost.
So the trial continues.
We’ll just say I lost.
It’s getting dark.
If we go home like this we might catch the cold.
Of course! Let’s change together in the shade of that tree!
You’ll be reported.
We can use the bath back home.
Bathing with Yui?
Thank you, Yui!
I wonder what we’ll do tomorrow?
Tomorrow’s a school day.
Oh that’s right!
Akari, you forgot, didn’t you?
I’m telling you, I saw them!
Oh, Sakurako.
Just look at me!
Do I look like I’m lying to you?!
Good morning!
That face! You don’t believe me, do you?!
Of course I believe you.
What’s the matter?
Akari!
Listen to this!
You see, last night, on the way home from the grocery shop, I saw ghosts!
The ghosts of four young girls,
drenched in water and staggering down the street!
What? Ghosts? That’s freaky.
Chinatsu, have you ever seen a ghost before?
You’d have cried for sure!
Not true.
No, I’m sure you would!
It’s true!
Where’d you see them?
It was near the park at Icchome.
It’s dangerous, you better not get close!
What should we do…
Disarming that situation was too much work.
Sakurako was really excited.
So that’s what happened.
The Oomuro house must be near that park.
Speaking of that,
we’ve never been there before, have we?
Why don’t we go visit sometime?
Good idea.
Okay, gather ’round.
Look what I have brought you today.
I was thinking we have to leave a record of our shining day to day activities.
Here we go then!
Say cheese!
I want to make that picture my wallpaper!
I didn’t know you had a computer, Chinatsu.
No, I mean for my room.
Wallpaper for your room?!
Over here, Akari.
Say cheese!
Why’re you doing rapid shots?!
Kyouko!
You didn’t move enough.
We’re retaking it.
Then you should have told me!
How about you try some sort of action?
M-Maybe like this?
I don’t know... Maybe it should be a bigger action.
How about headbanging?
Headbanging?!
Yeah! I bet we can get some cool shots that way!
Is this good, Kyouko?!
Great! Put your back into it!
Like this?!
That’s incredible, Akari!
Can’t she just do a jump?
Don’t you wanna see something unusual?
Oh… That’s the idea, huh?
Can I stop yet?!
Alright, here we go.
Only one shot?!
Oh... I forgot!
Kyouko...
Whoops! Sorry!
Kyouko, how about we shoot you?
Yeah, I’ve been taking all the pictures.
Take a picture of me with a backdrop of the great wild!
Okay…
Say cheese.
I think you blinked.
Really?
Yeah, you did.
One more time.
Oh well...
You’re fine with that pose?
Isn’t it cool?
Sure, whatever.
Here we go.
You blinked again.
I’m bad with flash photography.
Oh I know! If I roll my eyes back I won’t be blinded!
That’s freaky! What are we shooting here?!
Fine, we’ll go without the flash.
There’s enough natural light, I suppose.
Akari.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I’m okay.
Let’s take a picture together!
Yeah! Yui, will you take it?
Okay.
You’re a little too far apart.
How’s this?
Come on, get closer!
Closer, closer.
There!
This won’t do!
Like this, Akari!
Yeah, that’s a cute picture.
Yay! Thank you.
I want to take one with Yui next.
Yeah, let’s.
If we’re taking pair shots, let’s switch it up a bit.
I guess you’re right.
Akari, Akari.
Okay!
Ch-Ch-Ch-Chinatsu! They’ll come off!
I’m sorry! My jealousy got the better of me!
In that case, you too.
I think that’s gonna be a great picture!
Make sure you make prints of that! Giant size!
Now it’s my turn.
No need to restrain yourself.
Oh Yui. Always so shy.
I could not restrain myself.
I am a little bit jealous.
Now let’s take some facial expressions we don’t usually get to see.
Like Yui smiling wide.
I also would like to see you with a big smile!
Me too!
Come on.
Yui!
It was really cute!
It was beautiful! So don’t lock yourself in here!
Aren’t you all forgetting something?
Does this camera ring any bells?
Isn’t that the same camera we took on the camping trip?
In other words…
Camping pictures?
Camping pictures!
There’s so many!
Kyouko, can I pick them up?
These are well photographed.
Yui looks wonderful here!
I-It’s...
It’s the miracle shot!
Akari, you have a miracle shot too.
Come on, Kyouko!
What part of that is a “miracle”?!
Geez.
Don’t you make that face when you’re sleeping too?
Oh, come on. I can’t have you picking on me too.
Yeah, I’ve seen it too.
One time I turned over at night and saw you with half closed eyes. That was a surprise.
Really?!
I didn’t know…
Forget that. Look at this!
Forget it?!
Wow, we took this photo?
It’s kind of embarrassing.
But I like this picture.
Me too.
This is that picture that was taken without my consent.
How embarrassing!
You took this yourself!
For crying out loud.
Hey, look at this picture.
When was this?
Oh, that.
Oh I remember!
Thanks by the way.
I mean… back then.
Alrighty!
Let’s go show these to the student council.
Yeah!
We took a lot of pictures!
It’s because everybody helped take lots of pictures.
I snapped a lot of pictures too!
And a fine job you did, Private Sakurako.
Why did Toshinou Kyouko bring her flute again?
I don’t think she needed a reason.
Be silent!
Didn’t you enjoy my wonderful live flute performance?
You mean the “hee hee hoo” sound we heard?
I put all of my feelings at the time into that performance.
Yeah, I was so full I thought I might give birth!
My sincerest congratulations.
That curry I made was just too delicious. There was no helping it!
Yes, of course.
Sakurako!
Hey, you don’t know that it was me!
You’re right. I don’t.
But it was, right?
See!
For goodness’ sake! You never change.
I had to babysit you the whole trip.
What did you say?
I could say the same! I had to…
You look like you’re enjoying that.
Chinatsu made that.
It was a simple meal,
with mackerel and lots of other ingredients.
How embarrassing!
That really wasn’t my best cooking at all!
But it was really tasty.
I wanted to have some.
Yoshikawa, you must be good at cooking.
In that case...
Next time I’ll make something that’ll really shock and surprise you!
I’ll do my very best!
No… You must be very busy after all.
You don’t have to put quite so much effort into it.
No way! I know that if I put my all into it,
my bond with Yui will deepen,
and a beautiful new story will bloom!
Isn’t that nice?
No, I’m not…
I like it too!
Hey, everyone. Just write your names on the back of any pics you want.
I can get them printed.
Hooray!
Is that OK?
Thank you.
I want this picture…
But will Toshinou Kyouko think I’m weird?
I found a picture of Ikeda and me!
Oh, I want that one too.
Ikeda.
When I’m mature enough,
please explain what it was you were talking about that time!
I’d just like to say something:
I’m going to write my name on this photo,
but it’s not because I want a picture with you in it.
I’d say the same thing. Make no mistake.
You’re really busy, aren’t you?
Chinatsu! I found another one.
Thank you. Put it there!
Akari, why do you seem so used to this?!
Sugiura Ayano
You seem very happy.
Yeah, kind of.
I kind of want all of the pictures.
I get what you mean.
We had a lot of fun.
I want to do it again.
Yeah.
It was so fun, the time just flew by.
We should go camping together again.
I agree!
I can hardly wait.
We’ve still got half the summer vacation ahead of us.
Oh? Don’t you mean vaca-chuu-n?
Kyouko! Forget about that!
President!
We have a picture of you too.
Hey! Who would do this?!
Who took a picture of me sleeping?
Asleep?!
And here’s one of me.
Whoa.
Yikes! Me too.
Oh my.
You’re right...
Wait, is there one of Kyouko?
So that means...
I will have them framed nicely.
Don’t frame them!
Toshinou Kyouko!
I’ll confiscate those pictures!
Oh, Yui, please give me yours too.
Um, Chinatsu?
It’s kind of pointless though.
I’ve already seen Himawari’s sleeping face.
What did you say?
I’m tired of seeing you asleep too, believe me!
I really do sleep with half closed eyes…
We make the Earth our bed and take a nap,
Chikyuu wo ofuton ni shite ohirune shite
then the bright sun becomes our blanket.
soshitara taiyou sanzan kakebuton
I’m a bit sad when we have to wake up,
okitara nandaka choppiri samishikute
I’m hungry, too, so let’s go home together.
onaka mo suitashi isshyoni kaerou
I wonder what will happen tomorrow?
ashita ha donna koto ga okoru kana
So laid back, ah, this wonderful world!
yurukute aa subarashiki kono sekai
I know I’ll take a nap with you here again.
ashita mo kimi to kokode ohirune wo
Staring into the universe behind closed eyes.
mitsumeru mabutonoura universe
Even though the moon is so high in the starry sky,
hoshizora annani tsukiga takainoni
I wonder if it’s because of you that I can’t sleep?
kimi no sei kana nazeka nemurenai
...I can’t sleep.
nemurenai