Puri Puri Pudding
When you’re done with that,
you’re doing the rest of your homework.
What? Can’t I just copy your answers?
You already know the answer is no.
Himawari!
I want to express my genuine gratitude to our seniors!
Are you really Sakurako?!
How rude!
Because, they’re always so nice to me.
They always finish up the work I didn’t do because I was goofing off,
they even wipe up the crumbs I leave after eating!
Maybe instead of showing gratitude you should beg for forgiveness.
Especially Sugiura!
Y’know how she shares her pudding with me?
Oh.... um... you can have it then...
Hooray! Thank you!
She lets me have it even though it’s her favorite!
Isn’t that amazing?
I’ll invite them over and prepare a royal reception!
Exactly what is pudding worth in your world?
In that case, how about cooking a banquet?
Wow! For you that’s a pretty good idea, Himawari!
What should I make though?
Well...
How about a favorite dish of yours?
You mean delivery pizza?
Try again.
Lazy Lily is starting!
Lazy Lily
SUMMER VACA~CHUU~N! +
Lazy Lily. I’m a carefree lady,
yuru yuru I'm a nonki na lady
my spirits are higher than ever now, baby.
kyoumo kibun ha joujousa baby
After all’s said and done we’re fourteen,
nandakanda ittatte otoshigoro fourteen
so we are junior high school students!
so we are junior high school students
Lazy Lily. You are a girly angel,
yuri yuri You are girly na tenshi
hair aflutter, you are a cutie!
hair ga chotto nabiite cutie
It’s a grand old sunny bright day!
sansan kyoumo ii tenki da nihonbare
Everyone now: Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
minnade wasshoi saa wasshoi
Rush! Rush! Rush!
rashurashurashu
Coming home from a long day of play,
asobitsukarete kaettanara
a hot bath sounds like just the thing.
ofuro ga iiyu da na
You only get to live once,
ichidokirino jinseidakara
so don’t hesitate, don’t fret.
tamerawazuni hora chuucho ha yamete
No time to think, just fly!
imasugu tobidase
Life is happy, so don’t be idle,
jinsei ha happy taidani baibee
just be happy-go-lucky - why not?
sunawachi happy go lucky de iijan
If we come to a roadblock we can sit a moment and have tea,
ikitomattara hitomazu ocha demo nonde
Rush! Rush! Rush! OK!
rashurashurashushushu de OK
Get on your marks, and take a bold dive,
isseinose de goukaini diving
our every single day is an adventure!
sunawachi nichijou koso daibouken
The days go by like sweet ice cream melting.
amai aisu no youni toroketeku mainichi
Rush! Rush! Rush! OK!
rashurashurashushushude OK sa
Even when we grow up we won’t forget this,
otonaninattemo wasurenai
Lily shu-ra-shu-ra-shu-shu-shu!
yurishurashurashushushu
What happened to the “pon”?!
Yo.
Akari and Chinatsu aren’t here yet?
You’re here too early.
There’s still about 20-30 minutes.
In that case, we should play Namo Bros.
while we’re waiting!
Summer vacation’s over soon.
Shouldn’t you be starting your homework around now?
Yeah, but I can do that whenever.
Same goes for games.
Oh, I think I get it. You’re scared of losing.
Yeah, right.
I’ve been training extra hard just to beat you up.
I’ve got to see these skills you have for myself.
Now loading...
One hit kill?!
I’ll get you this time!
Oh, a hammer!
Very odd. Somehow I didn’t win.
Rematch!
I won! I beat Yui!
Finally! Victory at last!
Come on. You’re getting a little too excited.
Yes, yes! I finally beat Yui!
Next round, let’s go.
I lost again...
Gotcha.
Hold on, did I see a fist pump?
Were you slightly bothered when I won the other round?
You were, weren’t you?
Shut up.
Oh, I knew it.
Welcome.
Excuse us!
Just now, I had a little taste of Yui’s humiliation.
What... is that?!
Don’t say it in such a weird way.
I just lost in a game is all.
Oh, don’t scare me like that.
Well, I’m using the bathroom.
What is it?
Why don’t we take a picture of Kyouko asleep?
Asleep?
I mean, when we went camping she took pictures of all of us,
but nobody got a picture of her.
I get it!
We’ll want a full collection for the album!
Then, we’ll play with her lots after dinner to tire her out, and then...
All right!
Were you... talking about me?
Hello.
Welcome!
Please, right this way.
Excuse us.
Sorry... for...  the wait...
You poured too much!
I just wanted to make sure...
that you guys would have...
enough to drink...
And here’s yours, Himawari.
So little!
Well I poured so much...
I don’t have any left for myself.
I perhaps should have taught you about moderation.
This vaguely menacing rice omelet...
Is this because of earlier?
Look, I’m sorry it came out so badly! The ketchup exploded, okay?
You don’t want any drawing on your omelet?
I prefer my omelets without ketchup actually.
Look, mine came out really nicely!
Nice one, Akari.
Mine is just perfect!
Thanks for the meal!
I really ate.
Can you wrap up the salad?
Hey YO! My belly so full yo!
I said “wrap.”
I’d like to thank my folks!
No thanks for the omelet?
This one!
Ugh, the old maid.
Not again.
It’s too bad.
Oh, look at the time.
Should we have dinner?
Yes, please.
Roger Dodger!
Here we go! I call it “Sakurako Curry!”
It looks good.
Thanks for the food!
Delicious!
I wonder what the secret ingredient is?
I wonder.
The meat is so tender!
Su—
Sugiura, this is for you!
You don’t want it?
I don’t.
It doesn’t seem like it.
Well, I have a lo—
Please accept!
In that case...
Do you like it?
Then please, take this!
And this. And this.
This goes here.
And this. And this. One more!
Wai— Slow down!
My stomach is pumping like a pompadour.
She did feed you all that.
We’ve got dessert too!
Um, maybe not now...
Why don’t we take a break?
Good idea!
In that case let’s do some gaming!
Crossing Animal: Wild City Leaf!
Oh, but I didn’t bring my portable.
I am prepared for this contingency.
I borrowed my sister’s!
That’s pretty prescient, for you.
Now that we’re done eating, it’s time for games!
Wait, what about the summer homework?
That’s right: games it will be.
You’re not even listening.
Crossing Animal: Wild City Leaf!
Akari Town is getting lively, lots of shops are opening!
Not Akkarin Town?
I don’t like that name!
What’s this then?
Welcome!
What is that?
A present for you!
Also, I planted some flowers in Yui’s Kilimanjaro Town.
Could you plant in moderation?!
I’m not sure if you should thank that villager or kick her out...
It’s pretty though.
Right?
The interior of my house is lovey-dovey in preparation for Yui’s visit!
I-Is that so...?
Please come see!
Sure.
This is my—
Oh yeah, I dug that hole.
Cut it out!
I fell too!
Oh, that’s good.
Yui made it, after all.
Hey, how about we play a mini game?
I’m game!
How about we go online?
OK!
Isn’t it kind of exciting to play against someone you don’t know?
Barley Tea
I’ll help you with that.
I’m... all... right.
We’re home.
Welcome home.
I hope you’ll excuse me being here.
Hey, Himako.
We’ve got curry today.
It’s my special Sakurako Curry.
Curry?
Must be ready-made.
Sakurako went the extra mile and cooked it from scratch.
What?
Sorry for the wait!
Thanks.
No problem.
Now then, did you make any progress?
Yes, a little.
Excuse me.
Wow, this clothes shop is cute!
Welcome!
I see you have no patience in-game either.
Let’s fight a team of players online!
Good idea!
The Bug Catchers' Championship
Waiting for opponents to connect
The other team looks pretty cute.
I agree.
We win by catching more, right?
I’ll catch lots.
Teamwork is the way—Zimbab-way!
Slowly...
I did it! I got the cross animal butterfly!
Wow, that’s a rare catch!
This is an assured win.
It’s only got to do with the catch count.
And we’re neck and neck.
A pitfall?
I fell too.
Sakurako, you...
I thought I could sabotage the enemy...
That won’t work if you dig them around your teammates!
Fill them in.
I don’t really remember where I dug them.
What do you think you’re doing?
You can’t just laugh it off!
They’re fighting?
No, it must be some sort of ruse.
They don’t seem to understand the importance of teamwork.
You’re saying that?
What are you doing down there, Akari?
Kyouko! Why are you holding that shovel?
You better cut that out.
Sorry.
The bath’s open.
Oh, Sakurako.
She must have been tired.
She looks comfortable.
She woke up earlier than usual because she wanted to prepare for your visit.
I see.
The food was delicious.
I had a bit too much though.
Sorry about that.
She said something about paying you back for the pudding.
Pudding?
You always share with her,
so she wanted to treat you her favorite food.
She was all pumped up saying she’d cook the curry she learned on the camp.
I see.
It’s so nice to have such considerate friends.
Thank you too, Furutani.
Not at all.
Okay, I’ll take a bath next.
I’ll show you the way.
Thank you.
Let’s have pudding together some time.
That was refreshing!
Wow, it’s late.
Are you tired?!
Um... not particularly.
She always sleeps late.
We’ll have to resort to drastic measures.
What’s your plan?
Leave it to me.
Kyouko.
I will sumo wrestle you.
Why?!
Yes.
She’s on board?!
Hakkeyoi!
Nokotta!
I think she’s trying to tire her out?
That must be it.
Go, Chinatsu!
Dosukoi!
Is this how sumo wrestling works?
Winner!
C-Congratulations...
Man, all this exercise...
I feel really awake!
Whoops.
And I tried so hard...
Oh yeah. Let’s do homework!
Why?!
We’ll forget otherwise.
I knew it.
Nicely done, Yui.
Should we take it now?
She’s sleeping too lightly still.
Kyouko, if you sleep here you’ll catch a cold.
Let’s get you to the futon.
It’s too early to go to sleep...
You can just wake earlier to make up the playing time.
Go to sleep.
We’ll play again tomorrow...
Three fluffy sheep...
It seems to be working.
I think she’s completely asleep...
Akari, wake up!
This is our shutter chance!
She does usually sleep around now...
We can’t photograph her like this!
One moment.
Rum raisin?
Isn’t that only sold in the winter?
Kyouko stashes them for the summer here.
Exactly how much does she like rum raisin?
Rum raisin!
There we go.
I think we can go with that.
The rum raisin was surprisingly effective.
And now she is ready to be photographed.
Wum waisin...
I don’t believe it!
Okay, now she’s back.
Akari, you did a good job!
Thanks a lot.
Okay, now let’s take that photo.
Me too.
Say cheese.
Mission accomplished.
Good job, team.
You especially, Yui!
Now we can complete the sleeping photo collection.
Jeez, I can’t believe she took all these.
Nobody even noticed.
This one never gets old.
Come on, Chinatsu.
But I guess I don’t mind.
It’s a bit embarrassing but at least it’s a good memory.
I’m so happy to be... with...
Akari’s out of batteries!
I think she’s been struggling to stay awake.
Maybe we should go to sleep too.
I guess you’re right.
What?!
You were taking pictures?
It’s what you get for taking those pictures before.
We turned you face up with some rum raisin.
Wow, thanks a lot, Yui.
It’s not fair. You should have let me in on the action.
If we did that we couldn’t have taken the photo.
Well whatever. Oh yeah, I got some pics too.
Pacifier... Kelp...!
Dammit, Akari. Stop eating my twintails...
When did you—
It’s ‘cause you put me to bed so early!
Delete those!
No way! These are precious camping memories!
What does it have to do with camping?!
Sleeping in again, huh?
They’re already up.
Is that so...
Setting aside your laziness...
I’m not sure I like the way you’re talking...
I wanna do this again!
I wonder what we’ll eat next time...
Pizza maybe?
You’re really bent on pizza.
Good morning.
Morning.
Thank you for yesterday.
That was some good curry.
I’m glad.
Here you go, Oomuro.
I bought this earlier.
We can share.
Really?!
Yes!
I love it!
You really seem to be enjoying it.
That’s because it’s so good!
doseino wakkani gorogoro nekoronde
We roll around lazily in Saturn's rings
manmaru takoyaki kaseiwo hoobatte
then gorge ourselves on plump, round Mars takoyaki.
konomama minnade yurayura tabiwo shite
Forget everything and take a carefree trip together.
gingano hatedemo isshyoni waraou
Smiling all the way to the edge of the Milky Way.
akubide mata hajimaru daibouken
A grand adventure that begins with a yawn.
pokapoka gokurakuheno pasupo-to
A nice warm passport to our own paradise.
kirakira sugiru hibiha nagareboshi
These brilliant sparkling days are shooting stars.
choppiri koigokorowo dakimakura
As we embrace our affection like a big fluffy pillow.
hoshizora annani tsukiga takainoni
Even though the moon is so high in the starry sky.
kimino seikana? nazeka nemurenai
I wonder if it's your fault that I can't sleep.
nemurenai
...I can't sleep.