Shoot first, ask questions later
Sumanai
Osokunatta
Nanimonodaa!?
Mate mate
Odorokasete warukatta
Saa, sono bussouna mono wo orosunda
Gomennasai AKARI
Kyuuni haittekurukara, tsui
OK! Mondai nai!
Kimi wa un ga ii
Mou sukoshi de hachi no su ni natteita tokoro sa
Yoseyo, joudan kitsui ze
Sate, korede zenin shuugou shitane
Shinsaku na wake da ga
nani wo suru ka ka-do de kimeyou to omou
Junbi wa iikai?
Erabunda AKARI
Sore ga wareware no unmei to naruwakeda
Tanonda wa yo, AKARI
Oi oi
Kyanpu nante joudan kitsui ze
Oh! megami wa anata ni mikata shinakattayoune
Shiroi akuma ga azawarau jiki ni arienaiyo. Nansensu
Somosomo, konna nonki na koto wo yatteiru hima wa naidarou?
Tashika ni AKARI no iu toori da
Chotto ohuzake ga sugite shimatta ka na
Akkarin! Akkarin!
Kita ka!
Minna, deban da!
Sekai no tame ni!
Ikuzo!
OK! Rettsu go!
Ready, go!
Yuru yurin rin rin rin rin!
Yuri yuran ran ran ran ran!
Gimme a high-five, high-five.
It’s another wonderful day.
Okay!
It’s time for lift off!
Lazy Lily
Summer Vaca-chuu-n!
Where are we going?
We’re all going on a fun camping trip!
What?!
Camping! Camping!
Wait for me!
My alarm clock goes ring ring ring ring ring
mezamashi tokei ga rin ririn ririn
I’m really running late, gotta run run run run run
chikoku shisou de ran raran raran
Take the usual route, don’t be so hasty.
itsumo no michi isogabamaware
That thing you lost is probably on top of the shoe rack.
wasure mono wa tabun getabako no ue
The Girl with the Silly Face
.................................................................................................
1st Place
The school bell goes king kong kang kong kang
shyugyou no beru ga kin kokan kakan
Until the lesson ends it’s kukku kukku kuu (snoring)
houkago made wa kukku kukku ku
Our days never change, we live in constant bliss.
itsumo onnaji sore ga shiawase
What you’re looking for is probably here.
sagashi mono wa tabun kokoni aru kara
Forever and ever, I want to follow you on your path.
zutto zutto isshyoni aruite ikitai
Brimming with cheer, your smile’s the best.
genki mantan egao sansan
Yeah yeah yeah yeah it’s all right.
yay yay yay yay ittsu orai
If we can always laugh together.
donna toki demo warai aetara
The weather’s bright, preparations all right.
tenki kankan junbi bantan
Yay yay yay yay it’s OK.
yay yay yay yay ittsu okke
Onward, to the boundless future,
hateshinai mirai e
hand in hand in hand in hand we go together.
te to te to te to te o tsunaide kou
It’s another hot day...
Oh, I know!
Why does it have to be so hot...
For goodness’ sake.
Strange... nobody’s here.
Didn’t Akari head here before me?
Ugh... so hot...
I really wonder where she went.
Well, I might as well make some barley tea.
I can’t believe I forgot we were out of tea.
I was looking forward to drinking some ice cold tea...
Well, I shouldn’t limit myself to cold drinks just because it’s hot.
That had me scared for a sec.
Great, now my skirt’s all wet.
What a drag.
I wonder if it’ll dry on its own...
Oh, Chinatsu!
It’s another hot day, huh?
Yui!
I guess your class ended ear...
No! It’s not what it looks like!
No, it’s alright, Chinatsu.
It just kinda caught me off guard...
No, really! It’s not what you think!
Y-Yeah.
This is tea! Barley tea! I just spilled it is all!
Oh, is that it?
Yes, it is!
Look, just try smelling it!
You’ll just get the scent of tea!
No, I think I’m alright. It’s alright.
Hey! What’s wrong?
I thought maybe you’ll hate me!
Don’t cry, Chinatsu.
It’s alright.
Even if you had  wet yourself, I could never hate you for it.
Yui! I couldn’t be happier!
I love you!
Thank you.
In any case, let’s wipe it up.
Whoa, did you get burned at all?
Yes.
What? Where?! We gotta put ice on that!
Right on my heart!
Oh, that’s good. You’re OK then.
If we just put it here, it’ll be dry in no time.
How about we hang up your uniform to dry too?
Oh, but I don’t have anything to change into...
If you don’t mind my gym clothes, I can lend you those.
Your gym clothes?
I’ll wear it! I want to wear it!
Here, I’ll hold your skirt so it doesn’t get anything wet.
Yahoo! Make way for Kyouko!
W-What perverted activity is this?!
I want in!
You’re the only pervert here. Get a grip.
Oh, so it was just a tea spill?
But are you sure  it was just tea?
What if you’re just using that as a cover-up?
It’s the truth!
Quit that. Stop teasing her.
It’s really hot today, huh?
Oh. Akari, you’re later than usual today.
I was wondering why your bag was here when you weren’t.
I thought we could enjoy some ice-cream, so I went to get some.
Ice cream?!
How nice of you, Akari!
But I couldn’t find any rum raisin.
Hah! Rum raisin has rum in it.
Alcohol has a low melting point, which means rum melts faster.
Therefore during the high temperature of summer,
storing rum raisin is more difficult, which is why it is winter only!
Wow, I didn’t know!
Impressive.
It’s nothing!
Only when it comes to things you like, that is.
What do you mean “only”?!
Well instead, I got vanilla, and lemon sherbet, and...
Look, see that?
What should I do?!
That’s exactly how it happened!
Oh? Really?
You’re lucky you didn’t get burned.
Huh? What are you all talking about?
Oh no! The ice cream’s gonna melt! But then my skirt too!
Someone get some tissues!
We used them all up earlier.
Toshinou
It’s hot though.
That didn’t cool me down at all.
And I didn’t even win.
I wonder if we’ve got a fan or something.
Maybe it’s in one of these boxes?
If we found a severed head we’d all be in cold shock.
That would be quite an incident.
Show-off
It doesn’t look like there’s anything useful in here.
What’s this?
That’s a cooking kit.
Summer is here
It’s a pillow.
That’s a cooking kit.
Summer is here
It’s a bag.
Cooking kit.
Summer is here
It’s a hat.
It’s a cooking kit!
Summer is here
I know! It was a joke, okay?
Oh really? Knowing you, I just assumed you were serious.
Duh! Obviously not.
What a shame. It’s empty.
Is there supposed to be something inside?
You’re usually supposed to find the last bit of hope inside.
What, is that supposed to be Pandora’s box?
OK, put something in!
Hot!
I’d like to cook some rice.
You’re hungry?
What, you’ve never been camping?
Of course I have!
That’s when you set fire to things and watch ’em burn, right?
What kind of camping trip was that ?
We make a ring around the towering flames,
ceaselessly chanting even as our throats grow hoarse,
dancing until our bodies are depleted and our souls subsumed.
What is this, some kind of occult ritual?
Hey.
What might this be?
IT’S A CORPSE!
Enough with the murder plots!
But it’s so hot...
Don’t scare me like that! Jeez!
Oh, it’s a tent.
It looks like an antique.
Tents get you pretty excited, don’t you think?
I’ve got it! Let’s go camping!
What?
We’ve got a tent and a cooking set. That means we have to camp!
What, we’re going to do a tribal dance around a towering flame?
What is this, some kind of occult ritual? You’re scary.
You said it!
Let me explain to you what I mean by “camping”!
And that is?
To be in nature and to meet nature.
At times, facing nature.
At times, savoring nature.
And enjoying nature through it all!
To be in nature,
and to meet nature…
At times, facing nature!
At times, savoring nature.
And enjoying nature through it all.
Well…
TOSHINOU KYOUKO!
Excuse us.
Oh, Ayano.
Before you start your summer vacation, you need to turn in your paper!
Oh, sorry, I completely forgot!
I was so busy with camping preparations.
Camping preparations?
Um, we are going camping, right?
Wh-What are you talking about?
You’re all going together?
Approved! I approve this motion!
Huh? When?
Hold on, you mean camping as in… you’re going to stay overnight?
Yup!
What? All of you, staying outside for the night?
Oh, it sounds like fun!
My sediments  are a Cambrian mountain range away!
So you two will be coming with us then, right?
Um… it’s not… I mean…
N-No way in Niagara would I want to go with you!
That was two in a row… That’s really quite something.
Just sand  your message right away and be dune  with it.
Why won’t you laugh when I make a pun?!
There’s no need to restrain yourself, Yui!
Mommy!
Hurry! Quickly!
The Mirakurun movie’s gonna start!
Don’t get too excited, Mari. You’ll trip.
Being at a café on my own... it’s like I’m an adult.
I was looking forward to it, a little.
How wonderful.
I wanna be able to sip from my drink as elegantly as that someday.
Today, I just have banana juice though.
W-What are you doing, Sakurako?!
Well, I was walking with Himawari and I saw you!
May we sit with you?
Of course!
Are we ready to order?
Hey! This “Wiener Melange” coffee sounds like a good deal!
It doesn’t come with a wiener.
What? It doesn’t?!
Fine, I’ll just have cocoa.
Yes, and I’ll have it hot!
And a hot lemon tea for me, if you please.
Yes, certainly.
You seemed a little fidgety about something. What is it?
I was thinking, I wanna be like an adult who can look elegant enjoying a cup of tea.
You’ve got practice, Sakurako?
Of course I do!
Let me show you!
Really?
Alright, watch closely.
Hot!
She gave up…
Who is it?
It’s Chinatsu.
She says she’ll be a bit late.
Today, the two of us are going to study up on camping.
Camping?
The amusement club’s going camping!
What? Really?! That sounds like fun!
So we’re going to read up on the subject.
Give it here!
This? Sure.
So that’s why you’re studying.
Yeah, that’s right!
OK! I replied that you’ll be waiting for her.
Thank you!
A reply? That was quick.
That’s quite bold of you,
Akari…
I’m a little surprised （＾　＾；）
I’ll hurry so wait a
little longer!
Chinatsu
D
That’s quite bold of you, Akari…
I’m a little surprised.
I’ll hurry so wait a little longer!
The cocoa’s a little cooler now.
What kind of reply did Sakurako give?
Akari
I’ll be waiting~!
It’s pretty hot today so I
just wore a swimsuit and
sandals♪（＞ワ＜🌼）
Gotta embrace the summer✩
I’ll be waiting!
It’s pretty hot today so I just wore a swimsuit and sandals.
Gotta embrace the summer!
That’s not embracing, that’s embarrassing!
Come on, Sakurako! You’re making me look weird!
So sorry, it was just on an impulse.
Jeez!
Sakurako, there you go causing trouble again.
Alright, give it to me again then.
Be serious this time, ’kay?
OK. OK.
The swimsuit was hot too so
I took it off!
Chinatsu
The swimsuit was hot too so I took it off!
This is not OK!
Jeez.
It’s just a joke.
You were definitely going to send it!
Yeah, she was.
Sorry for the wait!
Wait, where’s the swimsuit?
You believed it?!
Sakurako was playing a prank.
Oh, I see. I was thinking you were already in camp mode.
No matter how excited I might be, a swimsuit is just not happening.
All this excitement is enough to make Himawari want to suddenly change into a swimsuit.
Not in the slightest.
Now that’s improper!
What is the matter with you?!
Himawari sure is unladylike.
...and that concludes the semester.
Enjoy your break!
THE PRINTS!
Oh… it was a dream…
What’s wrong?
It’s just… like, it’s like that other room...
Did you see a dream about camping?
That’s right! Camping!
Let’s go camping with Akari and the rest!
How did you know about that?
We talked about it with them a few days ago.
Yeah but… I mean, together…?
SUGIURA AYANO!
Toshinou Kyouko?
I’m gonna borrow your AC.
We are in the middle of a student council meeting!
Yeah but it’s hot.
Oh man, this is nice.
It’s not fair that only you guys get this.
Well, there’s not much I can do about that…
Oh well, I’ll make do with some pudding.
Hold it, what do you think you’re doing?
I’ll take you camping, so just call it even.
I don’t recall asking if I could go.
Oh, camping sounds nice…
Yeah, why not? Let’s go!
It certainly does seem like fun.
Getting bit by mosquitoes,
getting rained on, burning the rice…
It really sounds nice.
Those are nice  things?!
To share the burden of pain and suffering…
It’s a recipe for romance!
Don’t worry about me… just go on.
No way! We’re going home together!
We’re going back to Nanamori!
Thank you...
...so much...
...for the fun…
AYANO!
Oh, the counter intuitiveness of it… so nice…
You see? Everybody agrees it’ll be great!
Let’s enjoy!
Enjoy what?
Oh! Me too! I want to enjoy!
Look, Himawari will enjoy it too!
Can you not make decisions for me?
Not that I don’t agree.
Let’s take a vote then.
I cast my vote yes!
You’re not part of the student council!
Come on, let’s go.
Ayano, you really don’t want to go?
Um, to say that I don’t want to go is…
Well, that’s not quite it…
How about we say I’ll do it if I have no choice!
In that case, if you value the life of this little pudding, you’ll come!
Kidnapping?!
No, this is pudding-napping.
We’ll await you at the camping ground!
Hey, hold on!
Looks like we have to go!
That poor pudding’s life is in our hands!
Camping and pudding. It’s a dream come true!
Yeah! That’s like… something in a dream!
She just said that…
Alright, I get it.
I’d be worried if it was just you guys out there, so we’ll join you.
Yeah! Camping confirmed!
Yay! Campudding!
Cool it, Sakurako!
Can you please not hug me out of nowhere?!
Camping sounds nice…
I’ll be sure to bring home lots of stories.
Kaede, once you get bigger, let’s go together.
Okay!
Yeah, so that’s what happened.
I would’ve been fine with you staying there a bit longer though.
Like for the rest of your life.
What? My whole life?!
You’re all going camping?
It sounds like fun.
It sure is!
I’m so excited, I don’t know if I can go to sleep.
Akari is going too, right?
Yes! And Yui too!
In that case, Akari’s sister will be at the house on her own, won’t she?
I suppose.
It must be lonely.
I wonder if she’ll be alright. I’m worried.
There we go.
Koujo Park exit
(North exit)
Yui!
You’re early, Chinatsu.
You too, Yui!
It’s exciting, isn’t it?
Yeah.
It’s really exciting, isn’t it?!
You’re really enthusiastic about this, aren’t you?
Yes! I’ve been so enthusiastic, in fact, that I made this!
Wh-What is that...?
It’s a charm to protect us from bears!
And look! They match.
T-Thanks…
Now we’re all prepared in case we meet any bears!
Made in Chiina, huh?
Yes!
Hello!
What’s with the outfit?!
What do you mean? I like this outfit.
I hope you get stung. A lot.
Just kidding!
I am aware of the issue.
So I brought something proper to wear too.
This minimalist masterpiece!
Get stung till you’re all bumps.
All bumps?!
Akari sure is late.
That’s not typical of her, being late.
Overslept, maybe?
If we’re talking about Akari, I don’t think so.
Yeah.
Alright.
Having left home early enough to get here 30 minutes early,
she came across an old lady carrying heavy stuff at a crossing.
When she went to help, the old lady said she was going to visit her granddaughter, but got lost.
So she helped her find the place using her hazy memory of the area, and thus ended up late.
That’s way too cliché.
Guys!
I’m sorry!
I left my house early enough so that I could—
The old lady!
What? How did you know?
Alright, let’s go.
It feels like it’s gonna get hot today too.
If we’d done this earlier in the morning it would have been cooler.
Kyouko was the one who decided on the schedule, right?
It’s here!
Hey.
That is…
Here it is! The special Mirakurun train is here!
Wow! That’s cute!
Chinatsu!
Here!
Line up there!
Jeez. Just for a little while.
Hey! It’s Mirakurun and Mirakurun!
So that’s why you chose this time.
Okay, now get on. Wave at me from the window.
Like this?
Mirakurun on za mirakurun!
But, could you try to have more of a kyarurun  feeling?
Kyarurun?
Yui and Akari are saying they want to see it too!
Chinatsu is cute.
I understand.
Um, I didn’t—
Kyarurun!
There it is! This is great!
Anyway, let’s get on.
Yeah!
Thank you for riding with us.
This is our initial stop.
By the way, around this area—
Oh, wow. Even the announcements are Mirakurun.
They’ve really got it.
It seems to be really popular.
There’s a Mirakurun movie out right now.
Then I wonder if this is all promotion for that?
K-K-K-K-K-K-K-K-Ky—
I thought I’d die there…
Yui, you sure make a big deal out of things.
Whose fault do you think that is?
In any case, it’s good that we didn’t miss the train.
We didn’t forget anything, did we?
I don’t think so. I made sure to pack everything.
Who is bringing the tent, again?
TENT?!
Not an issue!
I arranged to have it express delivered.
Delivered?!
That is going to reach us, right?
At the very worst, we can just sleep outside.
No way!
We humans are surprisingly durable, you know?
As long as we have a little money, and big dreams, we can make do!
You’re not going to distract from the issue with pretty words.
Speaking of that, I’m hungry.
What were you just saying?
Speaking of that, that old lady gave me this as thanks.
Speaking of that, we’re in the height of summer.
Speaking of that, I made some sandwiches!
The bear trinkets took up all my time, so I couldn’t make anything too great.
Don’t expect too much…
No… it’s nothing…
It looks… tasty?
Go ahead, help yourselves.
Here we go…
This is…!
It’s good!
Yeah.
It’s delicious! It’s a miracle! It’s a Mirakurun sandwich!
This isn’t tuna, is it?
Oh, that’s mackerel.
Mackerel?!
I wanted to put more effort into it, really…
No, I think this is a miraculous sandwich, honestly.
Is it really that good?
Yeah. It’s really good.
You’re amazing, Chinatsu!
Mmph! Mmph!
We have no idea what you’re saying.
I’m glad I made them!
I wonder what the camping spot is like? How exciting.
Tonami Bus Stop
It’s probably a place by a beautiful, snow-coated mountain range,
its image reflected in a clear blue lake.
Nearby there is a field where the flowers bloom wild.
And in the distance, you can see a family of horses grazing. It’s gotta be like that!
You really have high expectations.
What kind of place are you hoping for, Yui?
Well, I just wanna have nice weather,
with nobody getting hurt, and for us to be safe.
Yeah, and I’d like the tent to arrive in one piece.
I can’t eat any more!
Yeah, you’re obviously not trying to change the subject.
I just thought I might not get another chance to say something like that.
Yeah, sure.
I have a once-in-a-lifetime line I’d like to say too.
What is it?
Indeed, let’s hear it.
Keep all interaction with bears to a minimum.
BEWARE
Love is something you will never regret!
Wow! What sagely words!
BEWARE
That’s really like you, Chinatsu.
I have something to say too.
What? You’re going to get married after this?
No!
I just want to say I’m so glad to be with you guys.
Akari sure is plain.
Plainly cute.
What?
Come on, Akari. Plain is best.
Alright! Break’s over, let’s go.
Right!
We have arrived!
Wow!
It looks wonderful.
This is a nice place.
More compliments! Keep ‘em coming!
Yeah, good job.
You’re late!
Sorry!
Well, I brought it for you. You’d better be thankful.
This is the express delivery service you mentioned?
It must have been a long ride for you. Did you take the bus?
Yes! And you came by car?
Yeah! We did stuff like play Sevens on the way, it was fun!
You played Sevens?
Yeah, we played some Karuta.
Wow…
Yeah.
Alright, we’ll come get you tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
Ms. Nishigaki! Explode in moderation!
I wonder if that’s the kind of thing you can do in moderation.
There we go…
Stop playing.
You seem like you’re having fun.
Because I get to work with you!
This is a lot of work.
I’m getting bored of this.
Sakurako, could you hold that for me?
You can say that once you’re done.
Sure!
Haha! It’s me, Pinocchio!
There we go!
Already?
It’s done.
This is pretty spacious.
We’ve got some time. How about we take a walk around?
Sounds good!
The air is clean and refreshing.
It makes my soul shine.
So that means your soul was all dirty?
It’s just a metaphor to say that it’s refreshing.
There’s a see-saw!
It’s decided! Yui, we’re getting on.
What? I’d rather not. There’s probably a spider or something.
In that case, it will have to be me and Himawari in your stead.
Who are you trying to imitate?
It’s exactly like you, isn’t it?
The see-saw is kind of embarrassing, anyway.
You’re wrong, my dear Hima.
That’s a gittan bakkon.
I haven’t heard someone call it that in forever.
What? Isn’t it called a gikkon battan ?
I’m pretty sure it’s gikkon batton.
“Batton” ?
I say gittan bakko.
There’s no ‘n’ at the end?
Nope.
Wait up a bit. I’m not following you guys.
Gitton ? Gitta ?
It’s true. It’s getting hard to remember.
Let’s just call it a see-saw.
You’re the one who started this.
It must have been quite an ordeal to get here from the bus station.
Yeah, it was kind of far so we took a break on the way.
Kyouko was energetic the whole way, though.
Yeah, that’s pretty much expected of Toshinou Kyouko.
Toshinou! I want to snap, snap too!
Sure.
Yay! Thank you!
Camera, camera!
Funami, I’ll be going on ahead!
Yui!
W-What is it?!
Oh, a spider.
I saved you from a spidery fate.
I get it, I get it! Just let go of me!
Oh, this is camera gold. Get closer!
Yui! Did something happen?
This is really cute!
Nothing happened!
Sakurako, can you get the curry ingredients that I asked for?
Yes, ma’am!
Sharing a meal with everyone is going to be fun.
I’m hungry already.
We did a lot of walking. I’m getting pretty hungry too.
Then let’s make it quickly!
I will give it my all!
...remember: moderation.
Here we are, Himawari.
“Curry”...
This is a limited edition, fairly hard-to-find brand!
You were in charge of the meat too… right?
Nothing gets past the ol’ master Sakurako.
BONUS BEEF
After an extensive survey,
we’ve become aware of a crucial oversight in our food supply.
As such, the following people will form our shopping team:
Ms. Toshinou Kyouko.
Here...
Ms. Oomuro Sakurako.
Roger Dodger!
Ms. Yoshikawa Chinatsu.
Here!
Chinatsu! Our dinner is depending on you!
Yes!
I want this! Let’s buy it!
They have toasting mochi too!
Which one do you want, Chinatsu?
Which one is it?
Rejected and rejected.
We’re going to quickly get the meat and the curry mix that we came for, and be on our way.
What is it?
Yui sure would love these potato chips.
Funami probably wants some baked mochi right about now.
Yeah, no.
Cheapskate.
Cheapy, cheapy skate.
Skaty cheap, cheap.
Skating cheaper!
There’s the curry mix.
There’s a lot of varieties…
We have to get mild!
Spicy for sure!
If it’s spicy, you can’t even tell how it tastes!
What kind of curry lacks spice? Heresy, I say!
Chinatsu, you want it mild too, right?
Despite how she looks, Mirakurun sometimes has a drop of spice in her!
Mirakurun has nothing to do with this.
Fine, let’s get the potato chips then.
That has even less to do with this.
A post-meal snack is important!
This girl gets it!
Where would we be without potato flavored chips?
Where indeed!
And the two of you were disagreeing just then…
Everything goes well with miso flavor!
Miso? You must mean mentaiko!
Mentaiko? No way!
Miso flavor is heresy!
Mentaiko! Mentaiko! Mentaiko!
Could you please stop fighting?!
We’ll cook the rice al dente.
I think that’s good.
How are you doing there?
I’ve just finished the preparations.
Nice job. You’re good at this.
Thank you.
Funami?
I just thought to myself,
things are almost going... too  smoothly.
Ah, I think I understand.
Were we using eggs for something?
Would you like some help?
Oh! No. It’s okay now. Thanks.
Don’t put in too much.
Watch: the flow of air is important.
Wow, amazing! The flames are swelling!
It’s like you know everything.
No, I wouldn’t say that.
But I do like to think about all kinds of things.
All kinds of things?
Come to think of it, she seems to get nosebleeds pretty often. I wonder why?
Um, why is it that you often get nosebleeds?
It happens when my fantasies are running loose.
Fantasies?
Well, you know…
For example, if this was a campfire…
Are you cold?
I’m fine thanks to you.
Are you afraid?
I’m not afraid because you’re here with me.
Let’s live on together, even if it’s only the two of us.
This may be a little too early for you, Akari.
Come on! I’m a middle schooler now!
That’s true. Well, imagine if two people did this with their hands.
And then… uh…
If I try to put this in words… it’s actually really embarrassing!
I had never thought of it,
but am I always thinking these crazy things?!
Ikeda?
I-I’m sorry. I can’t say this after all. Just forget it.
What?!
Yeah, I may be childish, but...
I want to become more of an adult!
I want to know about more things!
I may still be a child, but I want to hear what you have to say!
Huh? No, that’s not—
I want to become more of an adult, like you.
Well, you see...
Chitose!
Can I put this on the flame for a bit?
Oh, yeah! Of course.
We just finished growing the fire.
Akari, unless you’re busy could you lend us a hand over here?
Okay!
When I grow a little older, I want to hear all about it, okay?
Well, here I go.
What were you two talking about?
N-Nothing at all…
What  were they talking about?!
Hey, everyone!
‘Twas a bountiful catch!
I think the flame is still a little too weak.
I think Chitose had the fan. Let’s go get it.
Leave this to your top idol Kyouko!
Who’s an idol now?
A recorder?
Using this, I will deliver air to the flame!
Classic Kyouko! Gosh, she’s so smart.
Here goes.
One, two...!
Try blowing.
If you don’t plug all the holes, no way in Niagara will it work.
Oh, oil! Let’s pour oil into the flame!
Stop! That’s dangerous, you know?
Is that Nishigaki?
Are those two… okay?
Wow! This looks delicious!
Curry a la Kyouko!
You only bought the curry mix.
Not just that. I picked out that curry mix.
Yes, but half of it is Sakurako’s mild mix.
Did everybody get some?
Yes!
In that case:
Let’s eat!
Oh, this is good.
Yeah, it is.
Do you like it? Is it good? My curry?
This isn’t your curry.
It is good.
Really?!
Yeah. Thanks for going to the store.
Then, you can have this carrot.
Is it good?
Yes. In return, you may have these bell peppers.
Isn’t it good?
After all, I’m not a child like you, Himawari.
I don’t want to hear that from you when you can’t eat carrots.
Well, carrots are for adults!
They ought to give it only to people over 15.
Then I’ll be sure to give you tons of carrots on your 15th birthday.
No! I don’t want it!
My sister Himawari has gone camping.
Apparently they’re going to have curry together.
I am worried that Sakurako might have eaten too much.
I can’t eat any more…
I was finally able to say it.
Good for you. You’ve accomplished your dream.
My stomach is full to bursting.
Congratulations.
What are you doing?
I thought maybe it’d help.
You really ate a lot.
We’re not out of the woods yet! There’s still dessert.
What is it?
Looks like she has something.
Chitose…
The Kyouko is open to anything and everything!
I suppose I have no choice.
A cooking set?
Pudding!
Pudding?!
Oh, so that’s what those eggs were for.
It’s big! Amazing!
That looks delicious.
I wanted to eat some and I just happened to make a little too much, is all.
Ayano, thank you!
Sugiura, I love you!
Me too!
Quit it, you two...!
Sheesh.
Someone get tissues!
Wow! Look at that!
The stars are so clear!
You’re right! They’re beautiful.
Camping, and a clear night sky.
When it comes to this, there’s only one thing to do.
One thing? You mean…
I’m too young!
Probably not that.
Homework…?
Nope.
Bathing? Brushing teeth?
Hmm, no.
We put on masks, grab chainsaws, and chase couples!
What is this, a horror movie?
And why would we be the ones doing the chasing?
Summer is all about horror. It keeps you cool.
A test of courage!
Test of courage?
Oomuro has the answer.
Come on, Chitose…
Why do you have to bring up weird ideas?
Doesn’t it sound like fun?
No way I’m going to miss this…
Paired up
Show-off
Four
Oh, it’s Laika!
Looks like I’m with you, Akari.
Let’s go together!
Yeah!
It looks like you’re my partner, Ayano.
Let’s do our best!
If that’s the result of the draw,
then I suppose there’s no other choice.
Glad to work with you.
Same here.
You again?
That’s my line.
What did you say?
What’s your problem?
Careful, the frisky couple is always the first to die.
We are not a frisky couple!
That’s the part you’re concerned with?
Kyouko solicited you to come camping with us out of nowhere, didn’t she?
Was it bothersome?
Not at all! It’s been a lot of fun.
What about Chizuru, by the way?
She prefers to stay home, apparently.
Is that so?
Next time, though, it’d be nice if she could come.
Really? She’s very shy, but I’m sure she’d love it.
Alright. We made it.
That was pretty quick.
Let’s go back, then.
It was this way, right?
Yeah.
What should I do… I’m not good with the dark…
Afraid of the dark? You’re such a baby!
What did you say?
To be honest, when she’s like this I feel like I can rely on her.
I’m not scared! I’m not scared! I’m not scared!
S-Sakurako…?
Oh, come on…
What’s the matter?
It’s so quiet, I can’t concentrate.
That was so freaky!
I was fine with the dark, but then,
something horrible emerged from the shadows!
Chinatsu, would you rather be in front or behind?
When you’re waiting to get your shots,
are you the type to go first, or wait till last?
F-First! Definitely first!
Kyouko, Sugiura… Can we go first?
Sure, but...
But… what?
Didn’t you know?
Those who go second last are most likely to die!
Quit it.
Yeah… this is actually pretty scary.
Akari… don’t suddenly disappear on me or anything, okay?
I’m not going to disappear.
Are you really sure?
Akari.
If you do disappear,
please at least leave behind your dotted outline.
What do you mean dotted outline?!
Akane? It’s Yoshikawa.
Yes, I heard from Chinatsu that you’re alone in the house.
Do you have anybody to keep you company?
If… If it’s alright, could I possibly—!
Thank you.
...Sister
...x
Sister
But… I’m just fine!
Sakurako!
Do you understand what you just put me through?
Hey! Listen when people are talking to you!
Alright then. I guess it’s our turn now.
Here we go!
It’s like a child leaving to run an errand.
Yeah. I wonder what they will talk about?
Excuse me, I’m going to wash my hands.
Yui!
It was really, really scary!
I didn’t know if I should just take off running or not,
I returned here thinking of you!
Could you say something?
Alright then. There was once a place where an old man and his wife lived...
Is this a folk tale?
One night, they heard a knocking on their attic door.
When the old lady opened the door, nobody was there.
Hold on…
Once again, there is knocking.
This time, the old man came.
The attic was completely soaked in water! And then…
Stop! I’ve had enough!
What? I was weaving an epic story for you there.
Toshinou Kyouko, you’re not afraid? It’s dark here.
Yeah! I love zombies and Dracula and all that good stuff.
You’re a weird person.
How about you, Ayano? What do you like?
What? What do I like? Well, lots of things.
Like Frankenstein?
Stop fixating on horror.
Me, I just like people.
Really? Who?!
Is it everybody’s favorite top idol Toshinou Kyouko?
Who’s an idol now?
I mean like Chitose, the vice president and others like that.
Chitose, huh? I see.
That’s right! She’s serious about work,
and a considerate person on top of that.
I see. That’s like me, almost.
Anyway! She’s always such a helpful person, and I’m always indebted to her.
And… you too, Toshinou Kyouko…
Huh? What did you say?
It’s nothing!
What about me?
You heard what I said!
No, I didn’t hear!
Liar!
That’s why I’m asking!
Kyouko?
What happened?
Did you see a ghost?
A severed head! All bloody!
I thought my heart would stop!
It was a real scare.
So sorry.
We really shed a lot of sweat.
It’s a good thing there was a bath house nearby.
I anticipated this! That’s why I chose this place.
Yeah, great.
This is spacious.
Yay, bath time! I love bath time!
There’s a lot of baths.
I wonder which I’ll get in first.
Oh wow! A jacuzzi!
The open air bath is also a contender.
And what’s over there?!
Kyouko! It’s dangerous to run!
What do you think you’re doing?!
It sure is lively.
Really.
You don’t mind being in the open air bath with me?
Of course not. I feel calm with you around.
Don’t say that, I’ll blubblubllb...
Even my mother told me,
I’m really lucky to have a friend like you.
Chitose?!
I’m also glad that you’re my friend.
Geronimo!
Toshinou Kyouko!
Make room, make room!
The Kyouko has decided to join the party.
There’s no helping it.
Kyouko, show a little restraint, won’t you?
It’s no problem. Would you like to get in too?
Is there space?
It’s fine.
Well, I might as well then.
It sure feels nice.
Yeah, it does.
And it’s all thanks to me!
Yeah, yeah.
What’s all this? Looks like fun!
Fun?
I get it! You’re trying to fit as many people as possible!
Akari! Chinatsu!
Sakurako?
What’s going on?
We can still... still fit… more!
That hit the spot!
Now then, everybody. Let us now return to our castle!
Akari, is your head OK?
Yeah… well actually it still hurts a bit.
And to think that I specifically chose this bath house because I heard it heals bruises.
I don’t think that would help...
It’s starting to get cold.
Did you bring something warm to wear?
I only brought a hoodie in case it rains.
Same here.
Kyouko to the rescue!
These are pretty cute!
These suit all of you pretty well.
It’s a bit embarrassing though…
Yeah. After all, you’re not cute enough to be a rabbit.
Well, yours suits you just fine.
Oh? Well!
Yes, in that you have a memory span of three steps.
Huh? Did you say something?
Oh, nothing.
You went to all the trouble of bringing these?
Thanks so much, Toshinou!
There’s no need to thank me.
Who are you?
Oops, wrong outfit.
That’s more like it.
That’s way too forced.
No, the proper thing to say in that situation was “Kyouko is so cute!”
Or something like that.
Yeah, alright. “Kyouko is so cute.”
Hey. Ayano is cute too!
C-C—
I’m wearing it only because I had to!
That’s too bad. It’s really cute.
But if it’s such a bother, you don’t have to.
Huh? Well...
I guess it’s fine since I don’t have anything else as warm.
I sheepose  I’ll take you up on your offer.
Thanks.
Really? I’m glad.
Akari? Are you feeling sleepy?
I’m fine.
I want to talk with you guys more…
But you look really sleepy.
Don’t worry. I’m widely awake.
Today was… really…
You’re falling asleep! Akari!
Well then, good night.
Good night!
There was supposed to be a hill with a great view around here. I forgot!
I guess we’ll do that tomorrow.
I’m looking forward to it.
Darn.
Morning, Akaza.
Sugiura! Good morning.
Here you go.
Thank you!
You’re up early.
I just woke up for some reason.
Me too.
It’s still early, but why don’t we start making breakfast?
Yes. I’ll help.
A sheep and a dog.
Is this a farm?
Good morning!
Morning.
A little longer…
The fish is in the tiger’s jaws…
Oh, she’s always bad with waking up.
All the blood is being redirected to her boobs and all.
Kiss...
Wow! Look!
Amazing!
Beautiful.
I’m so happy to be with everybody.
This is such a wonderful summer vaca—chuu !
Come on, Akari. You messed it up.
There’s a saying: “Take nothing but photographs, and leave nothing but footsteps.”
Get to work.
You’re alright?
Yeah. We decided we’re all going back together.
In that case, we’ll take all your luggage back to the school.
Thank you very much.
Yay! Nothing to carry!
Take care!
Especially the explosions!
Okay, now let’s go home.
Yeah.
The bus is this way, right?
That’s right.
Sakurako actually knew the right direction?
Oomuro, are you good with maps?
Not at all! My sense of direction is all it takes!
Akari! What’s the matter?
No, it’s nothing!
One day, we’ll come back together!
Well I’ll be.
We could’ve just skipped the train and took a bus straight here.
Somebody really wanted to ride that Mirakurun train.
Hey, who cares! It was fun.
Yeah, it was!
You’re really a handful, Kyouko.
That’s really like Kyouko.
Oh, the bus is here.
I wonder when we’ll be able to come back.
Soon, I bet!
Definitely.
Yeah!
Like tomorrow, or something.
What do you think you’re saying, Toshinou Kyouko?
That’s a bit too early.
Now that we’ve been to the mountains,
naturally the sea is next our destination!
Sakurako, you’d better finish up your homework first.
Oh, isn’t there going to be a festival too?
Oh! I want to go to the amusement park!
Oh jeez! I’m looking forward to so many things!
You’re stuck somewhere between serious and playful,
kyou wa tsukkomi, ashita wa boke de
somehow it just doesn’t feel right.
nanda ka hen na kanji
It’s hard to get used to, and sometimes it’s a bother,
narenai koto de bimyou na kanji
it just really tires you out.
tsukarecchau kedo
But if you change something, you just might see,
tokidoki kawaru koto de atarashii hakken
that each day can be fresh, and full of adventure.
mainichi ga totemo shinsen, wakuwaku tomaranai
I wanna see your smile
egao ga mitai yo
or at least your silly face.
hengao mo ii ne
Seeing your smiles always brings me joy.
minna no kao ga itsudemo daisuki yo
Give me a cute smile.
kawaiku waratte
everyone, let’s PEACE.
minna de piisu yo
I wanna hold onto this moment,
kono shunkan wo nokoshitai kara
so let’s relive it again, a hundred times over.
watashitachi no memorii hyakubai fuyashitai yo
One, two, three, four, let’s go!
Just look up at this rainbow stretching into the sky,
sora ni kakaru kono niji wo miagetara
and a wonderful breeze will touch your heart.
mune no oku e to kimochi ii kaze tsukinukeru yo
You can always find someone
kagayaku kono sekai de itsumo hanashite kureru
who’ll remind you what matters in this one world.
taisetsu na mono wakaru you ni
These times won’t end, as long as we keep looking up
itsumademo tsudzuku yo, minna shiawase da mon
I love you all! Slow & Love!
daisuki na SLOW & LOVE
The End