Glancing up towards the sky,
Whenever I turn my back
Against this perfect world
I mumble out
"Where should I go?"
With you, someone who shares the same thoughts I do.
In the shadows of an alley, the hands on a clock
Restart the time that stood still
The arms extended out to you
And the unfinished puzzle
Have been left behind
Until we met
And realized something was missing.
So the last piece
Must be found
In order to move forward.
What's the matter?
Nothing...
Nothing at all.
I see.
It's nothing, really.
In that case, let's get started. It's cold out here.
I shall commence the lecture.
Today's topic is about the last words of famous people.
Huh?
"Light, more light!"
Whose words were these?
Is this a quiz?
Don't you know?
It's a famous person.
I-It's him... that person...
Come on... a very famous person...
The answer is Goethe.
He was a famous novelist.
Yeah, Goethe. I was just about to say that.
Next question.
"I want to eat something."
Huh?
Someone uttered those words right before their death?
Here's a hint. This person was a novelist as well.
Then it's... you know, that foreign novelist
who wrote that book, whatever the title was...
The answer is Natsume Souseki-san.
He must have been a gluttonous person.
Next question.
"Ibuse-san is an evil person."
How about... Dazai Osamu.
Yes, you got it!
Huh?
What a will he left, criticizing someone to the very end.
I wonder what that Ibuse person did to him.
The novelist series is done. The athlete series is next.
The first quote is "The mikka tororo tasted good."
Note: Tororo is grated yam.
That's from the suicide note of Tsuburaya, the marathon runner.
Right! You're absolutely correct!
All right!
I'm surprised you knew the answer, Satou-kun.
It's a famous suicide note, after all.
In addition to that, he also wrote that
sushi, wine, and cuttlefish all tasted good.
Right, right. You know it well.
It seems Tsuburaya-san returned to his homeland
and ate tororo with his parents just before his death.
I suppose people want to go back to their birthplace before they die.
Speaking of which, are you from this town, Misaki-chan?
No, I'm not.
Since that's Cassiopeia, the North Star should be around there...
So it's around there, a small town along the Sea of Japan.
There's a pretty cape down there, but ever since a famous
person committed suicide during the Meiji Period...
It became known as a landmark suicide spot.
I didn't know about it as a child, so I frequently played at the cape.
Even now, I occasionally see it in my dreams.
It might have all been a dream from the beginning, though.
I wonder if mikka tororo tastes good.
Who knows...
Don't be surprised, but there will be an exam tomorrow.
Is it the end of the term exam that was postponed from last year?
No, it's a graduation exam.
Huh?
It looks like I have to go away to a distant place.
I see.
Aren't you going to ask me where I'm going?
Where are you going?
To a distant town no one knows about.
I see.
I'll meet you in front of the station at noon tomorrow, even if it rains.
Yeah.
Night.
Even if it snows, okay?
I will now announce the results of the test.
You passed with flying colors!
Congratulations, Satou-kun!
This concludes the project.
I commend you for your hard work over this period of time.
Misaki-chan...
Huh?
Why... was it me?
Why did I become the subject of your project?
You already know I can see this park and
your apartment from my room, Satou-kun.
As I was looking outside my window,
I found... a person worse than I was.
It happened to be you, Satou-kun.
As I thought.
Sign this.
Huh?
This agreement is made by and between Satou
Tatsuhiro, hereby referred to as "Subject A",
and Nakahara Misaki, hereby referred to as "Subject B", which states...
One: Subject A shall not dislike Subject B.
Two: Consequently, Subject A will gradually come to like Subject B.
Three: Those feelings will remain perpetual.
Four: Those feelings will never change at any time.
Five: In times of loneliness, both parties will stay by each other's side.
Six: However, this is always the case for Subject B.
Therefore, Subject A will always remain at the side of Subject B.
Seven: As a result, the lives of both
subjects will probably change for the better.
Eight: Therefore, both subjects' struggles are likely to dissipate.
Nine: In the case of a breach of the preceding
articles, a fine of ten million yen will be assessed.
It's simple...
Be kind to me...
In return, I'll be kind to you, Satou-kun.
I dedicated a lot of effort in order to rescue you, Satou-kun.
Satou-kun, aren't you head over heels for me?
This is... no good.
Why? Satou-kun, I'm the only one left in your life.
If you don't sign this, you'll be alone forever!
I can't!
This is... so futile.
Sign it! If you don't, I'll become useless!
It's okay!
You'll be okay.
Misaki-chan, you could toughen yourself mentally and
physically by rubbing your body with a dry cloth.
You won't think of stupid
things if you occupy yourself by training.
A cute girl like you will surely be able to attain a wonderful life.
Lift your head up and walk!
Say, aren't you lonely!
I'm not lonely.
I'm... I'm...
Lonely!
I'm not... lonely!
Liar!
Say, Satou-kun...
Aren't you lonely, purin?
I'm not lonely.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm lonely!
Why didn't you sign the contract, purin?
Is it because she called you a failure of a human?
I'm not qualified to save Misaki-chan.
Is that really it?
Satou-san, it's natural for a person to
deny he's a failure as a human being.
That's why he searches for somebody
who is more miserable than himself.
That's why so much animosity exists on the Internet.
Those who aren't able to find a more miserable person turn to the
Internet and call other people losers, even though they've never met...
Just to make themselves feel superior.
Isn't that pathetic?
There's a sense of security that comes
from speaking badly of someone else.
But... that isn't true salvation.
Wouldn't you feel more relieved simply
admitting you're a failure of a human?
Huh?
A mere NEET... A failure who's receiving
the pity of a girl younger than you.
Yes. Admit it, Satou-san.
Admit it, Satou-kun.
Admit it.
You guys... Who are you?
Here, Satou-kun. Say "Ah".
Huh?
Ah!
Hey, wait... Let me eat that!
Wait... wait up!
Let me eat it... Wait... Let me eat!
I stopped receiving money from my parents
for living expenses one day in January.
I'm sorry, Tatsuhiro. Your father is going to be
hospitalized, so your allowance is no longer...
My last hope, which was assistance from Yamazaki, also...
About sending you cheese and stuff the other day...
Well, there were a lot of problems, so the plan fell through.
Don't laugh it off, bastard!
How many days has it been since I ate a decent meal?
I need some calories...
Anything is fine... I just want something to eat.
Ramen, curry rice, hamburger, katsudon, tuna and rice...
DHA is a substance present in tuna
that causes the brain to become active.
By eating tuna, it will definitely have a
positive influence on your creative activities.
Question: Why would someone want to continue living as a hikikomori?
Stop it!
Wait!
Answer: Because his clothing, food, and housing are guaranteed.
Since he always finds a way to get by, he
can afford to continue living as hikikomori.
In hindsight, living as a hikikomori was a luxury in itself.
Without clothing, food, and housing, you don't have any
other choice but to work unless you're prepared to die.
Congratulations, Satou-kun.
You finally managed to escape from your hikikomori lifestyle.
Misaki-chan, get a hold of yourself! Misaki-chan!
What in the world happened to her?
Well, there are a lot of things going on in the Chiba household.
They say she collapsed in the bath.
My, the poor girl.
You must be...
Satou-kun from Mita House, correct?
Huh?
I didn't know Misaki-chan's uncle was the landlord of Mita House.
I met you when you signed the lease.
Of course.
No wonder Misaki-chan knew about my
birthplace and the university I attended.
Um, how is Misaki-chan?
}She got dizzy and collapsed in the bathroom,
and that's when she got injured.
Oh.
That girl was my younger sister's only daughter.
She was a victim of unfortunate circumstances.
Soon after she was born, her father passed away.
My sister remarried after some time, but...
Her new husband was a horrible person.
Stop! Stop!
He rarely went to work, he would constantly get
drunk and inflict violence upon his family...
Stop!
Eventually, her mother...
Whether it was suicide or an accident, the truth was never known.
That girl, left with only her stepfather,
apparently suffered through her share of hardships.
P-Please...
Stop...
As a result, she became someone who
found difficulty in dealing with people.
After I took her in and had her enroll in a school here,
she couldn't adapt and dropped out soon after.
She probably feels like she's indebted to me and my wife.
At an age when girls want to dress up and have
fun, she doesn't indulge herself at all.
Instead, she accompanies my wife and works at the manga cafe I own.
However, she became rather cheerful after she met you, Satou-kun.
She looked so happy whenever she talked about you, Satou-kun.
Although it might sound strange coming from me...
Please continue to be good friends with her.
Misaki-chan!
Kazuko isn't here, either!
If they're together, I wouldn't have any worries, but...
Kazuko! Kazuko!
Nationwide Compact
Railway Timetable
The mikka tororo was good. Therefore... farewell, everyone.
She was in a really deep sleep!
I told you not to take your eyes off of her in her present state!
Misaki-chan!
Satou-kun's gone, too!
Welcome.
I suppose people want to go back to their birthplace before they die.
You know I'm poor, Misaki-chan!
Therefore... Farewell, everyone.
Nihon Hikikomori Kyokai.
Nihon Hiyowa Kyokai.
Note: Hiyowa translates to "weakling",
hikan translates to "pessimist".
Nihon Hysteric Kyokai.
Nihon Hikan Kyokai.
Welcome to the N.H.K!