Glancing up towards the sky,
Whenever I turn my back
Against this perfect world
I mumble out
"Where should I go?"
With you, someone who shares the same thoughts I do.
In the shadows of an alley, the hands on a clock
Restart the time that stood still
The arms extended out to you
And the unfinished puzzle
Have been left behind
Until we met
And realized something was missing.
So the last piece
Must be found
In order to move forward.
Satou-kun...
Where have you gone?
Satou-kun!
Kobayashi?
Don't you remember?
I was one of the class representatives.
Ah, class president?
I know it's kind of sudden, but I have something to tell
you. I was wondering if we could meet, Satou-kun.
Yes, I'm living around here now.
Come on... Can't you?
I'll meet you at the time and place of your choice, Satou-kun.
How about right now?
Huh?
To be honest, I just didn't want to be in that room.
I wanted to forget about the online game.
I wanted to go to a place where there weren't any computers.
Any excuse would have been sufficient.
Welcome.
She isn't here yet.
Satou-kun?
As I thought... it's Satou-kun!
Huh?
C-Class president?
My brother was already living in Tokyo, so...
I enrolled in an university out here as well.
What I'm doing now is... Let's see...
Something like volunteer work.
Volunteer work...
So you're still doing work befitting of a class president...
What's that supposed to mean?
What cynical remarks...
Satou-kun has been like that since the old days...
Always wearing that cold stare and degrading demeanor.
At first, I thought you acted like that around everyone, but...
After a while, I realized...
It was a reaction directed only at me.
Satou-kun, you hated me, didn't you?
No... it wasn't that.
lt's just that... the way you talked
did sort of rub me the wrong way.
You were too uptight, Pres.
You said the same thing in the past.
Huh?
During our senior year at the culture festival...
Satou-kun, stop wasting time!
The culture festival is tomorrow, you know! Do you understand?
Get serious...
Damn!
Pres, don't you get tired from being so uptight?
Huh?
"Serious, serious" might be okay with you, but...
If you can't be considerate of other people's paces,
wouldn't that simply make you an egoist?
Did I say those things?
You certainly did. Actually, those words really hit me later on...
After I graduated from high school and experienced many things.
Speaking of which, Satou-kun... What are you doing now?
When I asked your parents, they didn't give me a clear answer.
Did you have to repeat grades?
Or have you graduated from college only to remain unemployed?
I-I'd be better off if that was the case.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Satou-kun went somewhere...
There's no need to worry.
He has nowhere to go.
When he's hungry, he'll be back.
But...
What if he falls from a cliff?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Nothing...
Hikikomori? You, Satou-kun?
I'm not attending school or working...
In other words, I'm a NEET.
Go ahead and laugh.
There's no telling what makes someone become a hikikomori.
It's not a laughing matter.
Huh?
Oh, in that case, why don't you meet my senpai?
Senpai?
He's part of a wonderful group!
Even I was able to change upon meeting senpai.
Instead of being misguided by the words of those surrounding you...
You can have words you can call your very own!
Because every person has great potential!
Even Satou-kun's hikikomori ways can be cured!
Your life could change!
Talk about great timing... I'm about to meet senpai now.
Let's go together, Satou-kun.
Right now?
You have plenty of time, don't you?
Since you can afford to be a hikikomori...
What kind of person is this senpai we're going to meet?
Well, in short, someone who realized his dream.
Dream?
His name is Sagawa-san, a living legend who was
able to purchase a super car in less than a year!
Super car?
What kind of occupation does he hold?
I'll explain the details when we arrive, but...
It's a job that contributes to society!
Satou-kun, do you play online games?
Huh?
Why do you ask?
Well, they say hikikomori often indulge in those kinds of activities.
I'll never play an online game again.
Only the lowest kinds of people become
obsessed with such a fabricated world.
Satou-kun, since you're able to ride in a train, your
hikikomori condition must not be that serious.
That's not true.
Going out at night to shop was the best I could do until six months ago.
Does that mean your condition is improving?
How?
Even if you ask me how...
A lot of things have occurred recently, so it's probably because of that.
Yeah, it's not because of her...
Definitely!
We're going pretty far, aren't we?
We're almost there.
I followed her without giving it much
thought, but where the hell are we going?
Let's go.
Huh?
Sagawa-san's house is thirty minutes by foot from here.
Thirty minutes?
By foot?
I can't see anything besides silver grass...
Wait a second!
This is a legendary person, right?
I'm not lying.
See? There it is... a super car!
It certainly is... but...
S-Something isn't right.
Come on. Don't just stand there, let's go in.
Excuse me, it's Kobayashi!
M-Mouse Road?
A company that makes excellent products that
are used by celebrities all over the world...
We are the proud members of Mouse Road.
C-Could this be...
Ah, Kobayashi-san.
The preparations are complete.
Was that the Sagawa guy?
No, that's Kurokawa, a lower tier member like myself.
Sagawa-san will make an appearance and a
closing speech after the product presentation.
Please come in.
Huh?
Yay!
Ah, delicious!
A good, natural taste!
P-Pres...
Yes, we here at Mouse Road advocate safety!
It is our duty to provide safe products for people
with allergic reactions, from the young to the old!
In order to prove the products we sell
are superior to those sold at retailers...
We will conduct a demonstration.
The item we will demonstrate this time is
one hundred percent natural detergent.
This is a synthetic detergent, "Brand X".
We will pour both products separately into containers filled with water.
Look, Kurokawa-san!
Compared to the translucency of Mouse Road, "Brand X" is less clear.
You're right. "Brand X" contains an excess
of substances that make it opaque.
If we shake the two, the difference should be noticeable.
Oh, I can't hear any sounds from "Brand X"!
Exactly! "Brand X" creates too much foam,
which is why there isn't any sound!
But washing clothes utilizes dynamics like the force of impact
with water, as well as the friction created by fabrics rubbing together.
Right, which makes it obvious that Mouse Road products are superior!
Wow, I get it!
Fantastic!
Whoa, I see!
Awesome!
Bravo!
That... class president...
Who would have thought she'd be doing this?
Now that you understand the advantages of Mouse Road products...
Let me introduce you to the long-awaited
appearance of our super supplier, Sagawa-san!
Sagawa! Sagawa!
Sagawa! Sagawa! Sagawa!
Ladies and gentlemen, born into this world as human
beings, have you not wished to ride in a super car?
I realized my dreams through Mouse Road!
You can do it, too!
Those of you who wish to make your dreams come true, I
recommend you take part in the lecture following this presentation.
Mouse Road! Mouse Road! Mouse Road!
Even though I put my lots in so my chances
were up to more than 50%...
You weren't able to draw a bonus?
I pulled out a lot of "draw again" tabs, but...
Satou-kun!
Aren't you going to attend the lecture?
You're going to take my money, right?
Well... you'll have to purchase the
products, so it won't be for free, but...
It's not a large amount.
If all goes well, you'll be able to see returns in a month...
More importantly, it's a job with social significance.
In other words, you want me to aggressively sell products, which
I have to purchase here, to people and reap huge profits, right?
Yes, yes... You understand well.
And recruit new members, upon which I'll receive promotions.
It's that kind of system, right?
Right, right.
This kind of thing...
Huh?
It's called multi-level marketing, isn't it?
You see, I'm a hikikomori, so I watch a lot of television.
That's why I'm aware of the many controversies regarding this issue.
So what? It's not an illegal practice.
Damn it!
Satou-kun!
Treating me like easy prey!
Shit! Shit, shit!
Everyone around me treats me like shit!
Satou-kun!
Satou-kun... listen to me...
Go away!
I'm not as gullible as the others back there!
Wrong, it's not like that...
What was I wrong about?
Pres, you're just like that old man Sagawa...
Envisioning a nice car and receiving flattery from everyone!
So you called me, your old high school classmate...
with the intention of using me for your personal needs!
Isn't that the truth?
Yeah, you're right!
I was going to deceive Satou-kun into purchasing
enough detergent to last you more than ten years!
Not only detergent, either.
Organic food, pots, and kettles as well!
But is there anything wrong with that?
Senpai persuaded me into buying a mountain of products, too.
That's your fault! Don't involve me!
Right, right! All of this is my fault!
But... I'm...
I'm sick of being on the losing end!
What?
Pres?
My father collapsed soon after I came to Tokyo...
I had no other choice but to pay for
tuition and living expenses on my own...
In order to earn money, I wasn't in a position to be selective with jobs.
D-Don't tell me... Pres...
I engaged in cosplay and sold jewelry.
It was commission-based, and I climbed
all the way up to the number one position.
However, I didn't receive any decent pay.
In the end, the owner took the money and ran off.
I had no choice but to live with my predicament.
It was during that time... I was invited to Mouse Road.
But, as a result, I was burdened with a large debt.
What about you?
Are you going to live the rest of your life at
the bottom of the rat race as a hikikomori?
Being a smart person, I'm sure you
noticed it a long time ago, Satou-kun...
The condescending stares of the people around you.
Pathetic filth. Human failure.
A hikikomori failure.
You're a hikikomori, aren't you, Satou-kun?
Listen, Satou-kun...
You're being exploited by everyone.
The reason why an unemployed
hikikomori exists is because society desires it.
People need someone they can openly look down on...
Don't you understand?
The world is but a dog-eat-dog, look down or be
looked down upon, zero-sum game, you know!
If that's the case, why not be on the side that exploits?
Look down upon the people around you!
Right... If human relationships are going to deteriorate,
you might as well deteriorate them for the money.
Let's climb the ladder through Mouse Road!
By doing so, my debt will be cleared,
and Satou-kun's dream can come true!
My dream?
Yes, there is no dream that can't be realized!
Your success story awaits you, Satou-kun!
In order to earn it, you have to do whatever it takes!
The dream and conspiracy of...
That's right... You must take advantage of whatever you can.
Satou-ku...
Are you still here?
Don't you think it's time for you to go home?
I'm a super supplier!
Satou-san?
I'm a great success drea.... huh? Yamazaki, what are you doing?
That's what I should be asking.
What in the world were you doing until now?
Satou-kun, what are those?
Oh, I wanted to sell you some fabulous products, so I purchased them.
Products?
Purchased? Where did you get the money?
I had an acquaintance introduce me to a credit loan.
Loan?
Oh, don't worry!
As soon as I sell everything, I'll be able to repay it.
My success story has now begun!
Can I have a word with you, Satou-san?
Huh? What is it?
Could it be...
A typical, corrupt multi-level marketing scheme?
Don't be absurd! Do you think I'd fall for that kind of...
For that kind of...
I fell for it!
The cause is a deficiency of hormones in the brain.
T-This is good detergent.
Next Episode, Welcome to No Future!