Glancing up towards the sky,
Whenever I turn my back
Against this perfect world
I mumble out
"Where should I go?"
With you, someone who shares the same thoughts I do.
In the shadows of an alley, the hands on a clock
Restart the time that stood still
The arms extended out to you
And the unfinished puzzle
Have been left behind
Until we met
And realized something was missing.
So the last piece
Must be found
In order to move forward.
Sa-Satou-kun...
Let's go, Mia.
But your acquaintance is there, right?
Don't you have to log off?
Ignore it, ignore it. Forget about it, and eventually...
It'll leave on its own.
Let's enjoy the adventure, Mia.
How... did you become like this?
Until now... you were plagued with problems, but...
Basically... you were headed in the right direction.
To think you're even worse than before...
Sa-Satou-kun...
Let's go outside. It'll be better for you if you do...
See? It's a beautiful day outside. So, please...
Satou-kun...
SA10-kun?
Huh?
It's nothing. The person from the real world...
ls really annoying...
Could the person who's visiting you
right now be your girlfriend, SA10-kun?
No way!
Didn't I tell you she was just someone I knew.
I'm so relieved!
That Mia...
D-Don't tell me...
Satou-kun's infatuated with a girl in the world of that game?
Not good... This is definitely not good!
I have to do something...
Satou-kun, I'll bring you back to the
real world, even if I have to use force.
Dragon-slaying?
Us?
SA10-kun, you want to perform RMT... real money trading, right?
Yeah.
In that case, slaying dragons is an unavoidable path.
Rare items are usually in the possession of dragons.
But... won't it be difficult to defeat dragons at our current level?
If we had a dragoon, it would be a different story, but...
Should we ask a dragoon to join our party?
Huh?
Although I'd prefer if it was just the two of us...
It's not that he'll remain a party member forever.
We'll only ask for his assistance when we slay dragons.
Besides, I want to obtain rare items and see SA10-kun's happy face.
Mia...
Then I'll ask some friends, so stay here for a while.
My happy face, huh?
Satou-kun!
Huh?
What?
Please, Satou-kun. Come to your senses!
I'll dress up like this again, so...
Come to our counseling sessions.
Please!
Nya!
In any case, it's you...
I don't understand a word you're saying!
First of all, it's you...
What the hell are you up to, dressed like that?
It seems it's you...
You really make me crumble.
I-It's because you looked like you were obsessed with
a girl who looked like this in the game, Satou-kun!
Don't make fun of Mia!
The relationship between Mia and me isn't a superficial one!
If you want to make fun of us, I won't
hold back, even if it's you, Misaki-chan!
If you want to cosplay, go to a cospa!
What's the commotion? How noisy.
Shoot! No, no.
Mia? Mia, where are you?
SA10-kun, here! Here!
I've brought them here.
I heard from Mia-san.
So this is the first time you're going on a dragon hunt?
We'll lend you a hand.
Let's fight together.
You guys...
With these members, we'll definitely defeat it!
Thanks, Mia!
Huh?
So you want to RMT?
It's really difficult, you know.
That's what they all say, but I'll be fine.
I have all the time in the world...
To tell you the truth, I'm a hikikomori.
Hm... Is that so?
Come on, let's go, SA10-kun!
Yeah!
It's coming!
It's the dragon.
It's humongous...
Don't worry. It's not as strong as it looks.
No problem.
Let these white wings protect my party!
Regeneration!
Here we go!
What could have gone wrong?
Where did I make a mistake?
I see...
There are different kinds of moe, huh?
We're almost there.
SA10-kun!
Okay.
Let the black winds possess my blade!
Hurricane Blade!
I-I did it...
It's the Mythril Armor.
You sure received a nice item.
This will sell for a lot!
Aren't you glad, SA10-kun?
Hey, look!
This sensation is something that can only be felt here.
This is wonderful...
It's a truly wonderful world.
I have to go to my part-time job in the real world, so I'll see you later.
Right. I have work, too.
If there's another event like this again, make sure you give us a call.
Thanks, guys! Thanks!
I hope you can successfully RMT, Satou-kun.
That is... if you're capable of doing so.
What a naive guy.
Does he think he can make money that easily?
Onii-chan, I'll leave your meal outside, okay!
First of all, what's with that character's name of his?
SA10, it's the same as his actual name...
Huh, Satou?
That reminds me of someone named Satou from my high school class.
I wonder what he's doing now?
That's him.
Satou Tatsuhiro.
Weren't we lucky there was a shack nearby?
I didn't expect it to rain so suddenly.
Huh?
It looks like there's a bathtub in the back.
Say, SA10-kun... do you want to join me?
Huh?
I was just kidding.
Er... yeah...
This kind of situation isn't bad.
Let's go, Mia.
I'm ready, SA10-kun.
Let the blue flames burn every enemy in sight!
Spread Flame!
SA10-kun, our combo attack was successful!
I-I see...
It worked!
All right!
Mia, you're the best partner!
It's nothing...
I finally realized it...
The thing I was longing for all these years was this world.
Nothing in the real world is as valuable as
the experience I've obtained from this game!
The people in the real world talk about love and friendship, but...
It's a tainted world full of lies and avarice.
However, a truly unpredictable adventure exists in this world!
There are genuine companions!
Mia, I feel like I can do anything with you.
Stay with me for the rest of the adventure!
But I...
If you're worried about money, I'll earn it through RMT.
So I beg you...
Yes, okay.
Mia...
Mia!
Wait...
Huh?
There's one condition.
Condition?
I want to meet SA10-kun in the real world.
Huh?
Can I come visit you in the real world, SA10-kun?
The real world is slightly...
Aw... I can't?
It's not that I'm saying... no...
Really? I'm so glad!
To tell you the truth, I'm already in front of your apartment, SA10-kun.
Huh?
I'm going up the stairs now.
W-What are you talking about?
Oh, I can see SA10-kun's room!
Huh?
It can't be... No way...
I've arrived in front of your room, SA10-kun.
I'm going to knock on your door.
Your door isn't locked.
I'm going to open the door.
Huh?
Hi, my name is Mia.
Y-Yamazaki...
How was it, Satou-san?
Your adventurous journey with
the beautiful cat-eared girl?
I wanted to teach you the truth about online games.
So I created the character "Mia" and played with you.
Yamazaki...
You were Mia's secret identity?
Satou-san, don't tell me you thought the
person playing as Mia was a beautiful girl, too.
Over the Internet, name, age, gender,
and appearance can be changed at will.
Genuine companionship is but a figment of your imagination.
I-Imagination...
I-I knew that from the start.
The reason I stated playing online
games was to earn money from RMT.
RMT, huh?
In order to make money from RMT, you need to form
a team and dedicate yourself to severe practices.
Those who are able to do so are a select few.
It's impossible for someone who's gullible and
lacks programming knowledge like you, Satou-san.
But I have all the time...
Then how long do you plan on doing this?
Ten years? Twenty years? Thirty years?
Are you going to go on like that?
Imagine yourself thirty years from now!
T-Thirty years from now...
Your RMT dreams crushed, forced to return to your family
home... A fifty year old who's leeching off his parents.
Tatsuhiro, your meal is ready.
Come down to eat for once.
Shut up, old woman! Leave me alone!
But you must eat your vegetables...
Leave him be. He's already fifty.
He's at an age where he doesn't have
to listen to what others have to say.
But that boy... he's still unemployed, and...
It's too late for him to do anything.
Geez, saying whatever you want...
I may look like this, but I'm SA10, the
level thirteen thousand Magic Knight.
The hero of Vina Teelo!
Although I haven't been able to make money from RMT yet.
You people can...
Eat my confusion spell and...
My back...
I've gained weight recently, so...
Shit...
The ultimate NEET.
If your parents pass away, you'll lose your means of survival, you know.
Do you still want to engage in RMT?
I'm letting you know your free trial period ended
a long time ago, and you're currently in debt.
It's not that... I didn't care about RMT when I was playing the game.
The truth is... The truth is...
Romantic feelings are nothing but chemical reactions.
If the conditions are right, they come
into fruition no matter who the person is.
Yes, even if that person is me.
Satou-san, trying to obtain something from a game is futile.
Those who are making money are the people making the games.
Therefore, let's resume our game
production... and head toward the Fuyucomi!
Get out...
Huh?
Get out of my room!
Satou-san, games are meant to be created, not played!
The treatment might have been a little too potent.
What am I going to do from now on?
Hello...
Um... Sa-Satou-kun?
Yes...
I'm Kobayashi, a classmate of yours during high school.
Kobayashi?
Don't you remember?
I was one of the class representatives.
Class representative...
Ah, class president?
Right, right! Do you finally remember?
What's the occasion, calling all of a sudden?
Is there going to be a reunion?
Better news than that of a reunion, I think.
Huh?
My junior high school uniform, an apron, and homemade cooking...
With this, I can definitely bring Satou-kun back to this world.
I'm sure it'll be all right.
Satou-kun?
Satou-kun!
I'm coming in, okay?
Satou-kun?
I'll never play an online game again.
When he's hungry, he'll be back.
There is no dream that can't be realized!
Next Episode, Welcome to Happiness!