Glancing up towards the sky,
Whenever I turn my back
Against this perfect world
I mumble out
"Where should I go?"
With you, someone who shares the same thoughts I do.
In the shadows of an alley, the hands on a clock
Restart the time that stood still
The arms extended out to you
And the unfinished puzzle
Have been left behind
Until we met
And realized something was missing.
So the last piece
Must be found
In order to move forward.
For some mysterious reason
Aren't satisfied
With only text messages.
Inside my answering machine
With that voice of yours
Cold, cold, cold, cold.
Satou-san...
I want to feel a throb
Huh?
Here.
This scene from the scenario, Satou-san...
I think there should be more of a shy factor.
I'm plrin, purupuru rin
Huh? Do you think so?
pururin puru pururin
At the moment, I can't help but feel as if the protagonist is a jock-type.
rinrin purupuru pururin
It doesn't fit the character I created.
pururu
The magical powers
Shy, huh?
Are right there
All right, I'll think about it.
Bringing me joy
Please do.
To make dreams into hope
And hopes into dreams
Satou-san...
Of the magical girl
Huh?
In any case, we've finally made it this far.
Actually, it may be you
Since we're clear on what tasks need to be completed,
we'll probably be able to finish before the Fuyucomi.
Really? Will we be able to make it?
Yes, unless something serious occurs.
I-I see.
Great! Here goes my last spurt.
T-Telephone?
Fluffy like a marshmallow
Hello?
I'm teary-eyed
The dreams and hope
Although I understand your feelings, for those reasons...
Come back home to see your father.
Of the magical girl
Okay... I will.
That's me!
Bye.
Is something wrong, Yamazaki?
That "something serious" has taken place.
Huh?
So Yamazaki-kun went back home?
It seems his father was hospitalized.
He said he's going to check things out.
Is he coming back?
Huh? Of course he is!
The game hasn't been completed yet...
Besides, he still has school.
I see.
Of course.
Then I'll see you tonight at the park.
Shy, huh?
Shy...
Oh! I see someone in trouble, purin!
Suitorareeru the Third to the rescue, on the double, purin!
Plrin-chan! Don't be so reckless!
Purupuru pururin
Pururin
Purupuru puru...
It's so quiet.
That's right... Usually, from Yamazaki's room...
Shy appeal, huh?
Satou-kun, I brought your meal.
I'll see you later tonight.
Okay, I've finished setting it up.
Do you want to take a look, senpai?
Which star is it?
Um, er... What was it...
Who cares about the name?
It's about the romance, you know, romance.
The light from that star was from a hundred thousand years ago and...
Say...
Huh?
What meanings do our lives hold?
A human life will disappear in ten thousandths
of the time it takes for that light to reach us.
She was right.
By the time the light emitted from that star reaches Earth...
No one will know about the scenario
I wrote... much less about me at all.
A person's life is like trash.
Think about the meaning of life.
Huh?
A mountain?
Things that take shape will fall apart one day.
In other words, just like this.
These moments of our lives are more worthless than trash.
We are living in times more worthless than trash.
Yamazaki!
These are local specialties from my mother.
Add them to your food supply.
You didn't have to, but it'll help.
In any case, it's good to know your
father's illness wasn't anything serious.
It's not good at all.
Huh?
Satou-kun...
Satou-san, you're not interested in the affairs of other people, are you?
No, that's not true.
In that case, have you ever thought about why I'm a
first year student in a vocational school at my age?
W-Well, I thought it would be rude of me to dig into it.
At first, I was enrolled in the school of animal husbandry
at a local university, since my parents run a farm.
It was the natural course for a son
who'd take over the business.
Whether I liked it or not, the choice wasn't mine to begin with.
I never even thought about the possibility of different opportunities.
However, toward the end of my freshman year, my
relatives gathered at my house and were drinking...
There was an aunt of mine in the group
who was an insurance salesperson.
I'm home.
Insurance on Kaoru? Isn't it too early for that?
The sooner the better for things like this.
He's going to inherit the farm anyway.
I made an estimate, so take a look at it.
My life was completely planned out.
Age twenty-two: Graduate from the
university, work on my family's farm.
Age twenty-five: Marriage.
Age twenty-seven: Birth of my first child.
Age twenty-nine: Birth of my second child.
Age thirty-four: First child's first day of grade school.
Age forty-three: First child's high school entrance exams.
Age forty-six: First child's college entrance exams.
Age fifty: First child graduates from college.
Age sixty-five: Retirement.
And finally...
Age eighty: Death.
Even the amount of insurance money my
widow-to-be was to receive was written on the estimate.
It sent chills down my spine. I wasn't even twenty at the time.
Those people had the nerve to decide someone's life!
"Are you pretending to be God? Don't screw around with me!"
I yelled at them like that and decided to move to Tokyo.
My parents were opposed to the decision, of course.
That's why I saved money from various
part-time jobs and came out here.
So that's what it was.
Then... What about your allowance?
I'm not receiving any, of course.
Didn't you know I was working part-time jobs?
However, this life is to come to an end.
Huh?
My father was able to leave the hospital,
but he can't continue to work on the farm.
He wasn't very healthy to begin with.
In that case, you...
It's come to a point where I have to tread
on the tracks someone else laid down.
I've been granted reprieve until the Fuyucomi.
If our game receives acclaim, I can continue to create more.
This is our last chance!
Yeah!
Until me Fuyucomi, I'm going to keep watch
over you twenty-four hours a day, Satou-san.
Huh?
Eating meals, taking naps... everything will be done in my room.
Do you hear me?
Huh?
Y-Yes.
Wrong, wrong!
That's not right!
That isn't shy at all!
Even if you say so...
Imagine how you would actually ask a girl out!
It has to be more shy!
I don't get it!
I can't think of anything else, so it can't be helped!
We need to take a break.
Thank you very much!
Whoa! How luxurious!
Good food and booze are essential tools for creativity.
So drink as much as you want!
All right! I'm going to drink!
I'm telling you... the important thing is...
The shy aspect, you know! Shy!
I know, I know!
I know that already...
I have to take a piss.
Wrong, Satou-san!
You don't know anything!
As living proof...
Satou-san?
That way leads to the entrance!
Huh?
Yamazaki!
Snow! It's snowing!
Huh?
Oh, you're right!
We can't just sit here, Satou-san!
Huh?
When you mention snow...
You have to drink sake under the snow!
Whoa, I see!
Elegant, isn't it?
Really elegant.
It's getting a little cold, though.
Maybe I'm sobering up.
Did you say cold?
That reminds me... Wait here for a while.
Huh?
See? It's warm now.
Yamazaki, these are...
Yeah, they're my school textbooks.
I don't need them anymore.
Textbooks really burn well, just like trash!
That's right, Satou-san. I'll show you something even more interesting.
Something interesting?
I'm going to invite Nanako over to my galge-infested room.
Wow! You're a brave man, Yamazaki!
We're in for some great entertainment, seeing her
reaction toward the disastrous state of my room.
It's me... I have something important I'd
like to discuss, so can you come over?
Right, at my place.
My address is... Oh, you already know?
Yeah, Mita House.
Then I'll be waiting for you.
I called her over.
Bravo!
Huh?
Just now, you weren't shy at all.
Then the scenario has just been approved.
All right!
Mita House...
Listen, Satou-san.
Don't miss a moment of her reaction.
We might be able to use it in our game.
Y-Yeah!
She's here! Hide!
I've been waiting for you, Nanako-san.
Please come in.
Have a seat over here.
Um, Yamazaki-kun...
About your father's illness... is he all right?
How did you know about that?
Since I didn't see you at school in the past two or three days...
I was worried and asked my friends and teachers.
I see.
Well, my father is fine.
There's no need to worry.
Really? I'm glad for you.
Since you mentioned you had something important
to talk about over the phone, I first thought...
That aside, I have something much more important to tell you.
Huh?
More important?
Correct.
Nanako-san, you've probably heard rumors...
To tell you the truth, I'm a...
Galge... -
Figurines...
Doujinshi...
...super otaku who has to collect everything related to bishoujos!
He said it, that guy...
That's not all, Nanako-san.
I'm currently creating an erotic game using you as the character model.
You revealed that to her as well, Yamazaki?
What kind of reaction is she going to show?
Idiot.
Huh?
I mean... Stuff like ecchi games are gross, to be honest...
But the way you approach such things
so seriously is, how to put it...
How should I say it...
I think it's manly...
I mean... How do I say it... In other words...
That attribute of Yamazaki-kun is what I really like.
D-Don't tell me this mood...
Yamazaki-kun, do as you please.
Leads to adult entertainment...
Nanako-san...
Yamazaki-kun...
Are you out of your mind?
Huh?
Or are you some kind of in the closet galge enthusiast?
Ah, I got it.
Perhaps you have a fetish for monster
tentacle play, just like this illustration.
I hope you die, you icky otaku bastard!
People like you should vanish from this world!
Hey! Are you okay, Yamazaki?
I'm fine.
More importantly, did you record everything?
I told you it would be really entertaining.
A young girl punching a guy with a clenched
fist is a sight you don't see very often.
Is it okay? That girl... She was serious about you.
Even if she was... so what?
In a month, I'll be working on my family's farm.
There's nothing I can do at this point.
If we eventually have to break up, it's better to do so early.
Even so, there are proper ways to break up.
Wasn't this the best way to break up?
A dramatic break-up that can't be surpassed.
There was one thing I forgot about.
When you're hit during the winter, the bruise kind of smarts.
I'll get you some ointment.
Oh, I was wondering about tonight's
counseling since I forgot to ask you at noon.
Why don't you take it... The counseling session, that is.
I have to clean the room or we won't be able to continue with our work.
Don't act so reserved and go.
I see.
Satou-san!
Huh?
Our game... Let's definitely complete it.
Of course.
Good-bye, Nanako-san.
What are you saying? It's to be permanently stored.
It's hatsumoude.
Do you think God exists?
Next episode, Welcome to the Reset!