Will I be able to catch up to her?
Even if I can, what am I going to say to her?
I'm... lonely!
Do I have any right to stop Misaki-chan?
Liar!
Sir, are you sightseeing at this hour?
It's pitch-dark, so you won't be able to see anything.
Um... that is... I'm meeting up with a friend of mine.
At that cape?
Don't tell me you're...
Well, the construction has been completed,
so I guess there's no need to worry.
Huh?
("Misaki" = "Promontory" in Japanese)
3 lshihama Misaki Forest
Don't waste the only life you have.
Did I pass her somewhere along the way?
Or... don't tell me... she already...
Calm down...
I know which train Misaki-chan took
from the timetable left at the hospital.
I paid extra for the express train and chased her.
There's no way I shouldn't be able to catch her.
Why...
What?
Was my outlook too optimistic?
No, it wasn't.
But... Misaki-chan's...
Me? I'm right here.
Huh?
Satou-kun and I only arrived five minutes apart of each other.
Satou-kun, you could become a detective...
You found out even though I kept it a secret from you.
What am I going to do now?
Come on, let's go back. It's cold out here.
I refuse.
What?
You can't die. You have to live.
Don't screw around! I wasted the earnings
from my part-time job because of you!
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I should have died properly last night.
It's exactly as my stepfather told me...
Everyone becomes unhappy if I'm around.
I'm to blame for my mother's death.
My biological father's death was probably my fault, too.
Although my stepfather was determined to get
rid of me, he failed, and predictably, his luck went bad.
Ever since I helped my aunt with her solicitation work, she began
to struggle and started arguing with my uncle on a frequent basis.
It's all my fault.
I'm a pathetic human failure who only brings unhappiness.
I'm someone who isn't wanted in this world.
But... I didn't want to admit it.
That's why the project was conceived.
As long as there was one person who needed me...
the words of my stepfather would have been lies.
It would have given me a reason to live.
However, the project ended in failure.
Not even Satou-kun needed me.
There's no purpose in my life.
That's the reason for the mikka tororo?
Don't play games with me! That note
had "come after me" written all over it!
I didn't expect you to find it, Satou-kun.
That's why I thought my heart was
going to stop when I saw you here, Satou-kun.
It wouldn't have mattered if it did, though.
Besides, a suicide note is important.
Without a note, people wouldn't be able to discern whether it
was a suicide or not, further inconveniencing those left behind...
Like in the case of my mother...
Stop it...
Please...
Good things will come from living!
Your uncle and aunt will be sad!
I... er, need Misaki-chan!
I like you! I love you!
I beg you, don't die!
You say the strangest things, Satou-kun.
However, no.
I'm going to die.
As I thought, it's no use.
I don't have any words to stop Misaki-chan with.
Besides, what's so bad about dying?
The only difference is whether it happens sooner or later.
It's exactly as Misaki-chan said before.
Even if you continue to live...
It'll be a struggle full of hardships.
There's no meaning to it.
There's no meaning in life.
It's better to be dead.
But...
But... you definitely can't.
Don't say you're going to die!
Farewell, Satou-kun.
Unlike the others, I can't believe in God,
since I have a poor imagination.
If an extravagant miracle would occur
before my eyes, like in the Bible...
I could blame all the bad things on God.
It's not your fault, Misaki-chan.
Misaki-chan, you're not to blame at all.
Someone else is responsible for this.
There's someone who's causing Misaki-chan misery.
Yeah... Why would there be any reason for Misaki-chan to suffer?
It'd be ridiculous to say Misaki-chan was meant to be lonely and in pain.
That's why the source must exist somewhere out there.
There's an evil entity inflicting pain upon Misaki-chan.
Did you know conspiracies do exist in this world?
However, ninety-nine percent of all conspiracy
theories are simply delusions... or blatant lies.
Then... does that make the remaining one percent legitimate?
That's right, Misaki-chan.
Somebody has, against extreme odds,
become aware of a genuine conspiracy.
Huh?
Who is it?
Me.
Satou Tatsuhiro.
Then what's the name of the enemy?
I've known the name... for a longtime.
The evil organization that has been torturing us...
Yes, the name is...
N.H.K.
NHK?
That's right. The name is N.H.K.
An evil, secret society encompassing the entire world.
The unfortunate incidents occurring around
you are the work of the N.H.K., Misaki-chan.
Satou-kun, what are you sayi...
Satou-kun?
It's a mind attack by the N.H.K.!
They've come to finish me off since I told you
the secret of their organization, Misaki-chan!
What? What does N.H.K. stand for?
Nihon Hikikomori Kyokai.
The evil, secret society that transformed me into a hikikomori.
Note: Hiyowa translates to "weakling",
Hikan translates to "pessimist".
Or maybe it's the Nihon Hiyowa Kyokai.
Taking advantage of senpai's weak mind and
making her participate in an offline suicide meeting...
Misaki-chan, the N.H.K.'s sinister clutches are even after you.
In your case, the Nihon Hikan Kyokai!
They're the ones responsible for forcing Misaki-chan
into thinking pessimistically about everything.
Every single bad thing that occurs in this
world is due to the N.H.K.'s conspiracy.
It's not your fault, Misaki-chan!
You can call it whatever you like if you don't like the sound of "N.H.K.".
For example, God.
God...
Oh, so they've come to deliver the final blow.
Can't you see it, Misaki-chan?
It's right there!
I can't see anything.
You can see it! Carefully fix your eyes on what lies ahead of you.
I can't! I can't see it!
Yes you can! You can definitely see it!
That's the source of all evil... the last boss.
It's too late for me. I'm not going to die in vain, though.
I'm going to take it down with me!
Look, Misaki-chan!
This is the only thing that can defeat it, the revolution bomb!
That's right. In order to defeat it, I have to use this.
I have to carry out a suicide attack!
I'll protect your life!
Satou-kun?
Farewell, Misaki-chan!
Thanks for everything!
Live a healthy life from now on!
Live a happy life, too!
Those are my last wishes!
So Misaki-chan...
Live on.
I'm stupid, aren't I?
A genuine idiot.
In order to save the life of a girl I like...
This is the only thing I can think of.
I'm stupid... Really stupid.
Stupid...
Huh?
A girl I like?
I see. My feelings for Misaki-chan... were those of love.
A dramatic death isn't befitting of us.
Speak for yourself, Yamazaki. I'm going
to die for my beloved Misaki-chan!
What could be more dramatic than this?
The construction has been completed, so...
Construction?
Satou-kun? Satou-kun!
What the hell is this?
The construction has been completed,
so I guess there's no need to worry.
You're not going to let me die a dramatic death at any cost, huh?
That's unfair!
Don't look at me!
What are you crying about?
I'm the one who feels like crying!
You mustn't die.
Don't die!
Since it almost took an hour by taxi...
It'll be morning by the time we reach the station by foot.
Outside
Signal
Range
We'll freeze to death regardless of what we do.
There's an abandoned house nearby.
Abandoned house?
My house.
I heard it was built by my biological father.
He's the one who gave me my name.
It was because there was a cape nearby.
Half-baked of him, wasn't it?
This was my room.
I used it through middle school.
You're the first person, other than my
family, to enter this room, Satou-kun.
My stepfather would get angry if I brought friends over.
It's warmer this way.
Tell me something about yourself, Satou-kun.
Huh?
Anything is okay.
I'll listen to whatever you have to say, no matter how boring it is.
Then how about the dream I had this morning?
Okay.
A black serpent appeared out of the sea.
It fired rounds from its shiny, black gun.
Its broad and long sword...
Hey, sexual harassment warrants a fine of a million yen!
I got it, I got it.
Then how about a story about my childhood?
Okay.
When I was a kid, I used to play
baseball at a park near my hometown.
Well, it was something like baseball, since I
was using a rubber ball and a plastic bat...
Satou-san, I might get married in the near future.
My folks were nagging me to do some arranged marriage meetings,
ever since I came back.
I had one just for the sake of having one, but...
It was an instant bingo!
It seemed like she was interested in me, too.
We're in love!
Satou-kun, how is your hikikomori life going?
I gave birth to a healthy baby.
This luxurious house is my new home.
Everything is going well in my life.
Geez, what's with everyone?
I'm sick of this.
What a hassle.
It's no good, no good, no good!
Well, do your best, guys.
I'm going to take it easy... and make gradual progress.
Thank you!
You're late!
How many times do I have to tell you to
come as soon as you've finished eating dinner!
I just finished eating now.
Besides, you're not in a position to order me around.
Well, my uncle and aunt say they feel relieved
whenever I meet with you here, Satou-kun.
So did you do your homework?
Yes.
Okay.
For some reason, it's kind of humiliating to be taught by Satou-kun.
Misaki-chan is a high school dropout, while I'm a college dropout.
It's obvious who has the upper hand.
Is that so?
I'm definitely going to pass the University Entrance Qualification
Exam and enroll in a better college than you, Satou-kun.
Ah, that's right. I almost forgot about it.
I also thought about my NHK meaning.
Huh?
Due to Satou-kun's heroics, the evil God has been destroyed.
However, there's no telling when evil will return.
That being the case...
" N.H.K. Entry... Rules of the
Hostage Exchange Association 1. The Members' own lives...
Note: "Nihon Hitojichi Koukan-kai" translates to "Japan Hostage Exchange Association".
The "Japan Hostage Exchange Association?!
Each member offers their life
as a hostage to the other.
In short, it says "lf you die,
I'll die too, you scoundrel!"
If we do that, just like the faceoff between
nuclear powers during the Cold War,
even if one wants to die, they won't be able to.
Huh?
Members will always get along...
Members will gather every night at Mita Park on 4th Street
Come immediately after eating.
I think things will probably head in a good direction...
It will surely be all right, I believe.
The penalty for breaking this agreement is ¥10,000,000,000.
N.H.K. Chair Misaki Nakahara
Member No.1 ( )
Members will always get along...
Members will gather every night at Mita Park on 4th Street
Come immediately after eating.
I think things will probably head in a good direction...
It will surely be all right, I believe.
The penalty for breaking this agreement is ¥10,000,000,000.
N.H.K. Chair Misaki Nakahara
Member No.1 ( )
In the end, not a single one of our problems has been solved.
From here on, too, we'll probably be whispering
"l can't, I can't" every day while we go on living.
But still... Yeah!
I don't know how long it will hold up,
but I'll give it a try as best I can.
Member No.1 (Tatsuhiro Sato )
N.H.K. Chair Misaki Nakahara
Member No.1 ( Tatsuhiro Sato )
With this, I'm sure both you and I will be okay, Sato.
Welcome to the N. H. K.
Final Episode
Welcome to the N.H.K.!
Even if this world were going to end tomorrow
Since it's you
Would you take the curt attitude of
If so, that's okay with me?
There's no need to strain yourself
Just sometimes would be fine
So lift up your face and look this way
Look at me
Though it's a tiny world
For some reason it's too big for these two hands
Though it's an endless world
For some reason it's too small for these two hands
Hey, I want to laugh with you
In the irritating morning light