Sukoshi miageta sora
Dekisugita nichijou
Se wo mukeru tabi ni tsubuyaku dake
Doko ni ikeba iino sonna kao shiteru kimi to
Rojiura no kage
Tokei no hari ga tomatta jikan wo nurikaete
Sashinobeta ryoute kamiawanai pazuru
Okizari ni shiteta futari deau made
Nakushiteta nani ka
Saigo no kakera wo torimodoshite
Aruki dasou
What do I do?
Can I make it home alone?
Sato?
Senpai...
This is absolutely no good.
There's nobody for Sato but me now!
Thanks for waiting.
You know, Sato...
I guess I have a thing for you.
S..S..Senp.. p.. pai...
Come on, Sato.
Please, Sato.
Sato...
Sato?
Huh?
What's wrong? You're all glassy-eyed.
What?
This is a coincidence, huh, Senpai?
Really! What a surprise!
Running into you on a day like this,
in a place like this...
Damn, things are always too sudden with her.
Please, Sato.
Sato...
Huh?
It's a nosebleed.
Sato! Come over here.
Sure...
How is it? It is better now?
Y..Yes...
Looks like it stopped now.
I'll bet it was because of the crowds.
You're hikikomori after all.
Oh, or are you cured now?
If you're out in a place like this...
Well, it's gotten a little better.
A lot's happened, you know.
That's true, a lot.
Huh?
Sato, are you alone?
What?
Pardon me...
Senpai, what are you doing here alone?
Well, when I left the house I was with him.
Did you lose each other or something?
If only that were all...
A fight?
Wrong.
He got called away by an important client
over some sudden trouble.
Even on New Year's Eve?
There are a lot of places open even
on New Year's Eve, right?
That's true.
In a busy downtown on New Year's Eve,
normally there'd be no way a cell
phone call would get through.
Oh, you're right.
But somehow it's always those kinds
of calls that get through.
It only makes sense to me as a conspiracy.
What should I do?
Sato, you and I have a connection, don't we?
We do?
Yeah...
I mean, it's not often that you just bump into
somebody you know when you're out like this, is it?
In spite of that, this is the second time I've seen you.
Normally, that'd be unthinkable.
Don't you think it's a conspiracy,
by some group somewhere?
Is this a conspiracy too?
These conspiracies that are crowding
all around us as always...
Even that ceremony called a wedding, for instance.
It may actually be a conspiracy by some
huge organization somewhere.
Welcome.
Yes, one moment please.
Oh, hey, have you ever heard
of the "marriage blues?"
No.
As a wedding gets closer, see, you get uneasy.
Yes, ma'am!
Like, "ls this really the right person?"
or "Aren't there other things I should do
besides getting married?"
But as I see it, Mr. Jogasaki is
the perfect boyfriend.
Right, he's wonderful.
Looking at it objectively,
there shouldn't be any problem at all.
If I marry him, I've passed life's test.
I get on the best track, and beyond
that it's all a straight shot.
Isn't that great though?
Your order, please.
One hot sake. Two cups.
Gladly.
Right, table seven needs one hot sake, two cups.
But isn't it too good a story?
Yes, gladly.
Isn't it a conspiracy?
By some group somewhere...
You're happy, right?
I'm happy, and that's why I'm uneasy.
I haven't drunk this much since the "Off" meeting!
I'm sure it's because I'm with you, Sato.
There you go again.
When I'm with him, I take up a certain pose,
and I can't get this drunk.
You think it's the new year yet?
Must be pretty close, I guess.
Mapan-do
I've greeted the new year with Sato!
Is it that funny?
Sato, isn't it painful to be alive?
For me it's painful, somehow.
Do you want to have, like, an affair?
We do
kimono
fittings.
We do
kimono
fittings.
Which one should we get?
I'll leave it up to you.
Is this really okay, Senpai?
Yeah...
I've known since a long time ago.
The person I truly need is...
Senpai...
Sato...
Happy New Year!
Sounds like the new year's begun.
Jump! Jump!
Jump! Jump! Jump!
Sounds like it, huh?
Senpai, you're actually happy, aren't you?
Yeah...
If so, let's go home.
If we do it here, we'll be playing right into
the evil organization's hands.
I see. That's true, isn't it?
We were dangerously close to getting
caught in a conspiracy.
That's right. We were careless.
Can I do this until we get to the station?
Senpai?
Pretending we got caught in the conspiracy.
It's to deceive the eyes of the
huge evil organization.
I get it.
Shall we have a reunion for the Literature Club?
Eh?
Yamazaki, was it? Invite him too.
Not right away,
but about ten years from now,
once everybody's lives have gotten stable
and we're living happily day to day.
Sure, right.
So, this is goodbye until that time.
It'll be fine.
Huh?
By that time, I'm sure the huge organization's
conspiracies won't have anything on us anymore.
I hope they won't.
See you.
Sato...
I'm going to be a mother!
Congratulations!
Goodbye, Senpai.
Misaki...
You're still here.
I thought you'd already gone home,
Misaki, so I snagged myself a drink.
Even though you've got no money?
Someone bought me a drink; I hung out
with this nice middle-aged guy and...
But more importantly, did you take
care of your shrine visit?
If not, want to go together?
I'm not going.
Why not? Let's ask God to make this year
of all years a good one.
That's impossible.
Huh?
I mean, even if there is a God,
it's for certain he's a villain.
Huh?
What does she mean by, "God is a villain?"
Mita House
You got lost during today's exam, so it's invalid.
We will have another exam at a later date.
"At a later date?" Wasn't this a test
to wrap up the year?
Goodnight.
Well, her being unfathomable isn't
something that just started now, huh?
I'm not an unnecessary human being.
Sato needs me; he absolutely does.
Manga Cafe
That guy's an unbelievable loser.
Macky Shirota Keiko Uchiyamada
You know, I have a thing against these
NewYear's gifts to kids.
Macky Shirota Keiko Uchiyamada
You know, I have a thing against these
NewYear's gifts to kids.
Oh, is that so?
When I was a kid, I received rice cakes.
Rice cakes?
Yes, rice cakes, from my mother.
Hello?
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
Sato? This is Kaoru Yamazaki.
No, no there wasn't. My house...
Yamazaki? Have you been drinking?
I'm sorry!
I have been drinking.
All morning, relatives and work-related people have
been coming over nonstop, making me drink.
Things finally settled down a few minutes ago.
Wow, becoming the heir to a ranch
makes things a lot different, huh?
Did you know that out in the boonies,
interpersonal relationships all work out
as long as you're drinking?
If you're drinking and getting on each other's
wavelength, everything's okay.
Since that's the case, I wish I'd conditioned
myself better while I was in Tokyo.
You do, huh?
Sato, you need to train yourself to drink too!
Sake is important. Life's all about sake!
I get it, I get it. Don't you drink too much now.
Oh! "Drink" reminds me of the original
thing I called you about.
Huh?
That's right.
Sato is a worthless human being
who can't even feed himself.
My presence nearby has to be necessary
and indispensable to him.
Thank you, Yamazaki! Talk to you later.
Were you on the phone with Yamazaki?
Yeah, about that: right now, there's a
nationwide glut of milk and stuff,
so Yamazaki said they've got a lot of extra dairy
products and stuff that they made at his place.
He said it costs money to dispose of them,
so he's gonna send some to me!
It's milk! It's dairy!
After all, babies grow on nothing
but mother's milk.
If I've got milk, I won't be hurting for food!
Are you saying you don't need me anymore?
What? No, that's not really what I intended to...
It's just that if there's a god of throwing things away,
there's a god of scooping things up.
There aren't any such gods.
Huh?
Because gods are definitely villains.
H..Hey!
At the very least, leave the food.
I never heard that!
Oh, I'm not doin' that!
HAPPY NEW YEAR
We pray from the
bottom of our hearts
that this will be
another wonderful year
for all ofyou.
Juuhachibei Soba Shop
Oh, I'm not doin' that!
HAPPY NEW YEAR
We pray from the
bottom of our hearts
that this will be
another wonderful year
for all ofyou.
Juuhachibei Soba Shop
Then I'll do it!
I'll do it!
I'll do it too!
You go ahead.
Just a minute, you!
Huh?
I didn't think you'd come today.
If I skip of my own accord, it's a million yen penalty.
Oh, I see. So if you break the contract,
you have to pay too?
Uh, Misaki?
Cat
Today I'd like to lecture about God.
What?
Look at this, please.
Pie Graph ofLife
Enjoyable
Painful
Look at this, please.
Pie Graph ofLife
Enjoyable
Painful
Pie Graph ofLife
Enjoyable
Painful
I've attempted to graph the proportion of
enjoyable things to painful things in life.
As looking at this makes clear,
individual happy times, where you think things like
"this is fun," or "I'm glad to be alive,"
do not amount to even one-tenth of our lives.
People who believe in God say that
God created this world.
Thus, they are saying that the one who
made this world rife with suffering
is God.
There is no way a God who made this horrible
world can be a good person.
God is a bad guy. That's for certain.
Do you have any rebuttals?
God is a villain, so he does mean things.
I'm sure it's also God who turned you
into a hikikomori, Sato.
And it was also God's malice
that showed you and that Senpai
coming out of that hotel to me.
What? Hey, that was...
So, in truth, I know what I ought to do.
I ought to throw down God.
What?
God made the world...
But why do painful things...
What?
God made the world...
But why do painful things...
If that cruel God were gone,
God made the world...
But why do painful things...
this world certainly ought to become
something wonderful!
The problem is that I don't know where God is
or how I could overthrow him.
My imagination is poor,
so I can't make myself believe in God
as well as other people do.
"Other people?"
The people who show up at the
gatherings with my aunt,
or people who go to shrines for New Year's.
Oh...
All he would have to do is cause
a really flashy miracle,
Iike in the Bible or something,
right before my eyes.
If only he would do that,
I could believe even in God.
And if only I could believe,
I could blame all the bad things on God!
And then I could be assured
that things aren't my fault.
90% of the things that happen in life
are hard and painful, huh?
HAPPY NEW YEAR
We pray from the
bottom of our hearts
thatthis will be
another wonderful year
for all ofyou.
Juuhachibei Soba Shop
There's no way this new year could be a good year.
Yamazaki's gone.
And Senpai too.
Everything's rolling in a bad direction.
What am I supposed to do from now on?
I'm sure it's fine. It's perfect.
After all, I've spent this long a time
advancing my project.
...LONELY HUMAN BEINGS MUTUAL...
Tatsuhiro Sato, (hereafter PARTY A),
and Misaki Nakahara...
Party A will not grow to dislike...
After all, I've spent this long a time
advancing my project.
Sato...
Sato is already
Episode 22
Welcome to God!
Sato is already
Episode 22
Welcome to God!
my captive, isn't he?
Episode 22
Welcome to God!
Moshimo ashita kono sekai ga owaru to shite mo
Kimi no koto dakara
"Sore nara sore de mo ii ka"
Sokkenai taido toru no kana?
Muri suru koto wa nai kedo
Tama ni de mo ii kara
Kao wo agete kocchi wo mite yo
Watashi wo mite
Chippoke na sekai na no ni
Naze darou kono ryoute ni wa ookisugiru
Hateshinai sekai na no ni
Naze darou kono ryoute ni wa chiisasugiru
Nee modokashii asa no hikari no naka de
Kimi to waraitai
You've done good work over this long period.
That's really the only reason?
Do dry-cloth friction rubs or something
to toughen your body and spirit!
Next Episode
Welcome to Misaki!
Do dry-cloth friction rubs or something
to toughen your body and spirit!
Next Episode
Welcome to Misaki!
Next episode,
"Welcome to Misaki!"
Next Episode
Welcome to Misaki!