Sukoshi miageta sora
Dekisugita nichijou
Se wo mukeru tabi ni tsubuyaku dake
Doko ni ikeba iino sonna kao shiteru kimi to
Rojiura no kage
Tokei no hari ga tomatta jikan wo nurikaete
Sashinobeta ryoute kamiawanai pazuru
Okizari ni shiteta futari deau made
Nakushiteta nani ka
Saigo no kakera wo torimodoshite
Aruki dasou
Because of you guys, we didn't have
time to eat anything, you see.
Mm, this goes down pretty smooth, huh?
The Island Nearest to Paradise
August 11, 2006, 11:00 am
And I was thinking there was
no other possible way.
So was I.
When a person gets caught up in one notion,
he becomes unable to think of anything else,
even though, in fact, another way of resolving
things is often right before his eyes.
If we hadn't had that damned campfire,
we might have dragged ourselves
right up there and done it.
Yeah...
We have to be grateful to him.
Umm...
It's good you didn't die, huh?
You...
Don't!
Please...
Please stop...
I was more scared than that!
Why is it that at times like this
I'm not plagued by lethargy?
I'd like to just sleep,
without thinking about anything.
Huh?
What's that all about?
He looks like he's from an inn.
Would you be the group from the
"Island Nearest to Paradise" Off Meeting?
How does he know about us?
I put a call in.
We're all tired, aren't we?
We can take a hot spring bath and
relax a bit before we go.
Jogasaki...
Well, now, right this way please!
Shall we take him up on this offer?
I guess so.
Well, come along, Miss.
What? No, I'm not going.
Really? You're not with them?
Jogasaki...
I'll be there as soon as I return the boat.
Welcome!
Your names and addresses, please.
Right...
Guest Register
That was an unbelievable day, huh?
Yes...
At this time yesterday, we'd all given up hope
about everything in this world,
and now we're here soaking in a hot spring, huh?
Are you the ones?
The fools who were going to cast away your lives?
"Fools," you say?
Yes, fools.
Selfishly throwing away the life his parents
gave him is something a fool does.
If you actually were dead now,
you'd be beyond all salvation.
Hey!
Things are a little better anyway,
since you came back alive.
If you guys hadn't come back safely,
what do you think would've happened?
The marina staff would all have been
sent out as search crews.
In the worst case, the people from the fisheries
cooperative might have gotten dragged in too.
The inns hereabouts would've fallen behind
in their work with all the inquiries and whatnot.
If your bodies had washed up,
that would've been big news too.
Worst case, if they'd drifted up near the inns, it'd have
an impact on the lodge businesses here too.
It'd be huge trouble all around.
Well? Now do you see the idiocy of fools who would
throw away their lives and cause trouble to others
just because of their own situations?
If you do understand, then don't ever
think up anything so stupid again.
This is a warning from somebody who
was a fool himself long ago.
Hana-Hana's running late, huh?
Women's baths take a long time, you know.
There's nothing for it. Shall we start without her?
Huh? I'm sure that's...
That's my car.
I had that young man Jogasaki go get it for me.
What? Senpai?
You were out for a drive?
Just a bit, it's such a nice car. I couldn't help it.
Women really are tougher than men.
Mr. Nomura, Mr. Kusano,
members of your family are here.
Heart
Hidehito!
You don't have to worry about the clinic!
Just leave it to your father!
All this because you can't become a doctor...
Mother...
I was wrong.
Yuu!
How could you do something so stupid?!
The fault is all mine.
There's no excuse for what I did.
And you! Dragging our son into this...
Stop it, Dad!
I'm to blame.
It's because I'm such a wimp.
To have my mother cry at me like that is too much.
I got worn out and escaped.
Coming from me, it doesn't mean much,
but it is wrong to want to die.
After all this, I talked to my mother for the first time
in a long time, and I finally understood.
As long as there's someone who'll grieve,
it's wrong to want to die.
Uh, excuse me...
Sato, this is for you, if you're interested.
What's this?
It's a free pass to "Ultimate Fantasy,"
an online game.
If you type in this number,
you can play for the first month for free.
You're hikikomori, right, Sato?
A person I met online is also hikikomori,
and he's making a ton of money off of this game.
What? Off of a game?
How?
He does R.M.T.: "Real Money Trading."
He trades items and gold he acquires
in the game for real money.
Amazing, huh?
Wow...
With this, even if you're shut inside your house,
you can earn money.
It's perfect for you, Sato.
'"Vina Teelo"...
Thank you, I'll give it a try.
See you in Vina Teelo.
Well, I'm off.
Now you can't die at least
until you meet him inside the game.
Hidehito! Hidehito!
I'm going to head out too.
We probably won't meet again, but take care.
You too.
Hidehito, where are you?
I'm over here. Don't yell like that!
You're back, huh?
Let's get going soon.
Uh, right.
Uh, are...
Huh?
Yamazaki and the...
Yamazaki said he had something important to do;
he left a little while ago.
Something important to do?
Sample!
What's that?
Why do you charge 3,000 yen for a trial version?
Is he crazy or what?
So, he's saying the Comic Stall
is more important than I am?
And about that girl...
Huh?
She just vanished at some point;
I think she probably went home.
I wasn't really concerned about her.
Thank you.
Won't you ride back in my car?
What?
No, I'm in the mood to go home by myself.
I see.
Well, once things settle down, let's get together
in Tokyo to eat or something.
Sure.
Let's go, Hitomi.
Sato...
I'm truly sorry I got you caught up
in this kind of thing.
It's all right. Don't worry about it.
I wish you happiness, Senpai.
I'll give you a ride to the station.
Thanks.
Umi no soko ni orite iku machi de
In a town that descends toward the ocean floor
Makoto!
Kimi no egao wa midori no kage e kieru
Your smiling face disappears into a green shadow
Dad...
What are you doing here?
Mom told me to come meet you here.
Koukai dake ga hanashikakete kuru
Only my regrets speak to me
She said let's all give it another try.
Osero no you ni hikari o tsubushinagara
While I "put out the light" like Othello
Knock, knock, knock mugen no shoushin ni afure
Knock, knock, knock filled with fantastical grief
Kuchi mo mimi mo me mo kouzui
My mouth, ears and eyes are flooded
Kirinai media-nou ni suikonde wa
Drawn inside a never-stopping media-brain
Knock, knock, knock nakushita juuryoku no sei de
Knock knock knock because gravity is lost to me
Ukabidashita dekunobou
A good-for-nothing floats up and surfaces
Youkoso... Hitoribocchi
Welcome... loneliness
Misaki Nakahara
Hitoribocchi
Loneliness
You're hikikomori, more pathetic than a stray dog!
Hitoribocchi
Loneliness
...so much more of a throwaway
hunk of refuse than me!
So... You can't die! Absolutely not!
Hitoribocchi
Loneliness
I don't get her at all.
Sato!
Are you alive, Sato?
Damn it, I didn't think the Comic Stall
customers would all be jerks!
Learn to read things' auras!
Don't they even realize that once it's completed
it's going to be a big-name item?
What hurt us is that we didn't get
to go on the first day.
Games weren't the main items today.
It's your fault, Sato.
I don't care how much you despaired
about your hikikomori life;
there was no reason to stir up so much crap
on the day of Comic Stall!
The idiots in my class are giving me
cold glares too; I've had enough!
I'll be waiting
at the usual place,
at the usual time.
I'll be waiting at the usual place, at the usual time.
I'll be waiting
Sato...
Are you listening to me?
Yeah...
Won't you come with me to see the fireworks?
I think positive things would come out of it.
If we're together, I'm sure you'll be fine.
Damn! If it were at least finished,
those idiots would understand at least a little
how wonderful our game is!
Sato, where are you going?
I'm here.
This is a copy of the contract.
These past few days, you skipped
counseling without permission.
That's a complete violation of this contract.
"I'll be collecting that fine of one million yen."
Hey! You were...
Is what I could say.
But I was also keeping my house a secret from you.
I feel a little guilty about that. I'm sorry.
As a result, I'll dispense with the fine this time.
Starting tomorrow, we'll do counseling
as we did previously,
but you absolutely must come.
Who are you to decide things for me?
I'm glad you came back for me, Sato.
Welcome home.
Glad to be home.
Mita House
Huh? Who's that?
Hello?
Hello? Tatsuhiro?
Yeah. Mom, what's the matter?
I wanted to talk to you a little bit.
That's sure a gloomy voice.
I wonder if she heard something
about the "Off" meeting?
What's with the gloomy voice?
That's not like you, Mom.
I'm feeling really well on my end.
Is that right?
What's this? So, it's not about the "Off" meeting?
Tatsuhiro? Stay calm and listen, okay?
Sure.
The truth is, I'm sorry, but...
Huh? I can't hear you very well.
What?
That's... It can't be!
Episode 14
Welcome to Reality!
You're joking, right, Mom?
Moshimo ashita kono sekai ga owaru to shite mo
Kimi no koto dakara
"Sore nara sore de mo ii ka"
Sokkenai taido toru no kana?
Muri suru koto wa nai kedo
Tama ni de mo ii kara
Kao wo agete kocchi wo mite yo
Watashi wo mite
Chippoke na sekai na no ni
Naze darou kono ryoute ni wa ookisugiru
Hateshinai sekai na no ni
Naze darou kono ryoute ni wa chiisasugiru
Nee modokashii asa no hikari no naka de
Kimi to waraitai
You gather companions and adventure together.
You work too!
I owe this to you too.
Next Episode
Welcome to the Fantasy!
Next episode,
"Welcome to the Fantasy!"