Take action!
Raise your hands!
Release the shutter on this scene like it's the moment of a lifetime
"One scene" shattaa kiru you ni setsuna wo utsushite
Turn it into a story that can speak for itself
tsukuriageru na mo naki hitotsu no story
Every single one of us can become a hero
watashitachi wa dare datte hiiro ni nareru
The possibility hides within us, don't you think?
kanousei wo himeta sonzai, sou deshou?
Your first steps forward can be small to start
fumidashita ippo ga hajime wa chiisaku tatte
Keep it up, and we can create a brand-new future
kitto atarashii mirai wo egaki daserunda
I'll always believe no matter what
donna toki mo shinjiteiru yo
In this world and in my dreams
kono sekai wo, jibun no yume wo
This uncontrollable urge is compelling me to begin
osaekirenai shoudou wa hajimari no aizu datte sa
Telling me to go out and find the me I haven't become yet
mada watashi ga shiranai watashi ni deau tame
So off I go!
kimeta yo
Don't be afraid to try again
osorenaide try again
Keep getting up and fly away
nando datte fly away
It's showtime!
Oh I don't want to miss a thing
Starting from here
kono basho kara
Little Witch Academia
I swear I will stop you.
Oh? I wonder about that.
Now, let your emotions show.
Will they be red-hot anger? Deep-blue sadness?
Or perhaps pitch-black despair.
Sturcadasse.
It's futile to try and steal my magic.
As long as I keep my emotions under control,
you can't absorb them with your Fuel Spirit.
I'm not surprised.
Your talent for magic is the real thing.
I always admired your magic.
But you no longer believe in it.
Oh, but I do!
And I will make it stronger
through the power of science!
That is the true future of magic.
Do you really think things will work out as you plan?
It seems we must make it clear which of us is right, once and for all.
As I thought, you did get hit by the pollen.
You have no chance of victory if you can't fly!
You think your little tricks will work on me?!
Bye bye, Prof.
Professor Croix, would you care to explain what this is?
We are not giving you a choice.
Headmistress!
What... is this incredible energy?
What's going on?
We need to call in the military
to get them under control!
What's happening?
Looks like they're heading towards the leyline.
This is strange.
Let's return to Luna Nova.
Okay.
I never even imagined that I would collect
so much energy. The folly of man knows no limits.
I did not even have to activate it—
the Noir Rod has started itself!
What did you say?!
What?
Cease and desist!
My magic...
Ouch!
Hey!
Ow...
Why?!
Unfortunately for you, magic is now unavailable
to anyone without a router in this location.
Croix!
Don't!
What now?!
The leyline!
It's disappearing?
It can't be...
Now, to Arcturus Forest!
I've finally made it here.
The Nine Olde Witches' seal...
You're pretty stubborn, following me all the way here.
You're right. This is where the Grand Triskelion is sealed.
And it won't be much longer before I release it.
Just watch me as I finish the job
you were unable to complete.
Ouch...
Isn't this...
Arcturus Forest?!
This place is?
Man, this place is giving me the creeps.
Let's get the hell outta dodge.
Tia Freyre!
Huh?
It appears that our magic power has been drained.
The leyline was messed up too.
Something's definitely wrong.
Look, there!
What is that?
I suspect it's related to these occurrings.
Let's go!
And now to break the seal.
It's this?
Attention, all citizens involved in the riot!
You are to disperse immediately!
Failure to comply will result in—
A coup d'état?!
At this point, it's only a rumor.
However, going by the videos of the riots that have been put online, a coup d'état is a real possibility.
Unbelievable. Do the people in that country have no sense at all?
Gather more detailed intelligence.
A coup d'état, huh...
We may be able to use this.
"Use" how so?
Our moderates are far too soft on that nation.
But faced with a coup d'état, those pacifists
will have no choice but to open their eyes.
Deploying the military might be imperative.
You intend to exploit another country's crisis?!
Andrew!
Go and gather more intelligence.
Change the world!
Little Witch Academia
No!
This is all wrong!
This can't be true!
There's no way this is the world reconstruction magic!
It's wrong!
There's no way... this is the Grand Triskelion...
This banal...
Croix...
Professor Woodward!
Where is the Grand Triskelion?
Where is it?!
You already hold it in your hands.
That's a lie!
It is the truth.
Then why isn't anything happening?!
What part of this do you call world reconstruction magic?!
Why do you always look right past me?
Why won't you guide me?
If you'll never choose me...
Then stop showing me your face!
Go away!
Croix!
Emotional Pattern:
Red. Red. Red. Red.
R-R-R-RRRRR—
Stop!
Stop...
Stop it!
Turn off the machine!
I can't... it's not stopping!
Even you betray me in the end?!
Wh-What was that?
Wh-What...
Stop!
Croix!
Chariot!
Why?!
It's after me.
Just leave me and go!
No!
I'll never abandon you!
We'll both be—
I won't let you get Croix!
Chariot...
Run, Chariot...
You've done enough!
No, I haven't!
I stole your dream!
I stole Akko's power!
That's why I won't let anything more be stolen!
Chariot...
Chariot!
Murowa!
Professor!
Akko!
You're kidding...
This one looks pretty dangerous.
What now? We're all still in danger.
I see. Its energy link is starting to break.
That means...
This is it!
Croix!
Professor!
The Words!
Cast the spell!
Noctu Orfei!
Noctu... Orfei!
Aude!
Fraetor!
Shiny Arc!
You got it... you did it, Akko!
Akko...
Chariot...
We finally meet!
Take it.
But...
This isn't mine.
I made up my mind to return it
to Chariot once I found her.
Please accept it!
I saw one of your Chariot shows when I was a child.
It was so pretty and fun and cool,
and it felt like I was in a dream!
I can't even describe how moved I was!
That was when I decided to become a witch.
I believed that if I became a witch,
I'd be able to see Chariot again.
That was my dream!
And now I've met you.
My dream... came true.
Akko...
But this only happened thanks to everyone.
We met at school, got to know each other, and became friends.
I caused them lots of trouble and was always getting helped, and that's what brought me here.
Without them, I never would've made it.
It's thanks to them, and... and also...
Thanks to you.
Professor, it still doesn't feel real
that you're actually Chariot.
Because to me, you're my teacher.
And so...
Would you please keep being my Professor Ursula?
Akko...
I was the one who took your—
Professor!
I understand now.
I'll never be Chariot.
I wanted to be like Chariot, gracefully soaring through the sky and using beautiful transformation magic.
But Chariot is Chariot, and I'm me.
I can only be myself.
Even if I can't fly and always mess up.
Akko...
Professor, I'll keep working even harder!
I'll work hard to become a witch
who can make everyone smile.
Because to me, magic is the most wonderful thing in the entire world!
So please keep on teaching me how to use magic, just like you always have!
Are you sure you're fine with me?
I wouldn't want anybody else.
Thank you, Professor.
I love you.
Akko.
You made my dream come true.
That's...
Akko.
Put your feelings into words.
They will surely be the final Word.
Change the world.
Connect with other people, and your dreams will grow.
Phasansheer Shearylla!
What's that?
Isn't it just a stick?
This is the world reconstruction magic? Diana...
Huh? Well, I'm afraid I'm not sure...
Try it out and see what happens.
Okay!
Phasansheer Shearylla!
This... is the world reconstruction magic?
Even though I just learned another spell
oboetate no jumon ja
The things I want to do are still out of reach
kanawanai koto bakari dakedo
My skills are no match for my fantasies
imeeji suru no wa ima yori takaku
Yet my heart leaps out to meet them
tobitachi odoridasu kokoro
Breaking my tiny shell one layer at a time
chiisana kara nandomo nugisutete
I won't let my reckless abandon go to waste
gamushara dake de owarasenai
I'll leave who I was yesterday behind
kinou no watashi wo koeru you ni
Unfurling my transparent wings to the sky
toumei na tsubasa habatakasetara
I feel I can get closer to the tomorrow of my ideals
akogareteta ashita e kitto chikadzukeru ki ga shiterunda
Putting together the shards of a starry sky that I found
mitsuketa hoshizora no kakera musunde
I'll keep on chasing my dream to learn even more
motto shiritai yume wo ou yo