This is the Wild Hunt?
Yes, and those guys are the wild hunters.
They're aces who are specially trained to catch all of the ghosts within twelve days.
You've got to catch all of this year's ghosts before the year ends.
Does that mean they're coming to Blytonbury too?
On the final day, the twelfth night.
Then we get to see them here in person?
Yes, even the other teachers are in high spirits.
So thrilling and exciting!
Professor, is something the matter?
Huh? Oh, nothing at all.
Huh? That's Constanze's...
Wait up!
Hold on! You dropped this!
Ouch...
Whoops...
Take action!
Raise your hands!
Release the shutter on this scene like it's the moment of a lifetime
"One scene" shattaa kiru you ni setsuna wo utsushite
Turn it into a story that can speak for itself
tsukuriageru na mo naki hitotsu no story
Every single one of us can become a hero
watashitachi wa dare datte hiiro ni nareru
The possibility hides within us, don't you think?
kanousei wo himeta sonzai, sou deshou?
Your first steps forward can be small to start
fumidashita ippo ga hajime wa chiisaku tatte
Keep it up, and we can create a brand-new future
kitto atarashii mirai wo egaki daserunda
I'll always believe no matter what
donna toki mo shinjiteiru yo
In this world and in my dreams
kono sekai wo, jibun no yume wo
This uncontrollable urge is compelling me to begin
osaekirenai shoudou wa hajimari no aizu datte sa
Telling me to go out and find the me I haven't become yet
mada watashi ga shiranai watashi ni deau tame
So off I go!
kimeta yo
Don't be afraid to try again
osorenaide try again
Keep getting up and fly away
nando datte fly away
It's showtime!
Oh I don't want to miss a thing
Starting from here
kono basho kara
Little Witch Academia
Is Constanze here?
Oh, Akko. Cons is out right now.
Oh...
You need her for something?
Actually...
I broke her Stanbot.
She's gonna be pissed.
Thing is, she dragged us into helping her
build a weapon for the Wild Hunt.
Why's she working on that?
Cause she's gonna be in the Wild Hunt.
Seriously?! For real?
Professor Croix gave her special permission to enter.
Wow, that's awesome.
Ah, that...
Ow...
Whoa, what is all this?
Constanze!
U-Um...
Sorry!
I broke your Stanbot!
I'm really sorry! But it was an accident!
Forgive me, okay? Please!
I'll help you out with anything you want in exchange!
Wait, wait! Just calm down!
We can talk this out!
Are you okay?
That does sound rough.
But we all know that Akko's "help" is anything but.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Yo.
What're you doing?
Running some errands in Stanbot's place.
Though it's really just taking stuff to our room.
Gimme that! I'll do it.
She leaves me no choice but to force my help down her throat!
Constanze!
I brought it!
Wow, that looks amazing!
Sorry!
Here you go!
I cooked for you!
Constanze!
Let me out! I can't help you like this!
What do you mean? You want to do it all yourself?
Fine! Try and hold me back, cage!
Metamorphie Faciesse!
Whoa!
This is what she's using for the Wild Hunt?
Hey, I was just thinking...
Aren't we kind of similar?
Ever since we were little,
we were obsessed with just one thing!
It didn't matter what anyone else said about it!
We just go straight down the path we've chosen!
Don't you agree?
Come on, there are some things you can't do alone...
Akko! Bother!
Constanze wants to be alone!
Stanbot?! He's multiplying...
Go away!
H-Hey—
Hold on!
Go away!
Hey, that was fast.
You don't need to force yourself to help her.
It's not like Constanze has asked you, either.
Even I know that, but still...
You just want to bother Constanze then?
No way! Of course not!
Then just let her do what she wants.
I think she just honestly prefers being alone.
Little Witch Academia
Hey, Akko.
You finally give up on Cons yet?
I want this.
Not happening. That's an important cooking utensil.
It's not a toy.
Plus, you're getting in the way of my work.
Shoo, shoo.
Hey.
Have you heard of the Wild Hunt?
Here! The orichalcum whisk!
You need it to build your boat, right?
When I explained why we needed it,
he let us borrow it until the Wild Hunt ends.
After I said you'd be participating...
That's incredible!
He got all excited.
The Planta Tartarica Barometz grows on sacred land that is forbidden to trod on.
I cannot simply tell you its location.
Listen: this is not an issue of money.
It is most certainly not an issue of money!
Barometz?!
I know what that is! It's the plant
that grows into a golden sheep!
Shiny Volley
A stream of light running
across the sea of stars
Barometz
There is no plant as efficient as Barometz
Soft fleece surrounds its supple meat
Fountain of Polaris
The magic fountain that reveals the
path of light located at Luna Nova.
It bestows the great magic power of the
stars unto the witch with hidden radiance.
It's on one of the Chariot cards!
I know where to find it too!
Leave this to me!
Hey!
You're taking that without paying as much as a penny?!
But you said it wasn't an issue of money!
Metamorphie Faciesse!
Here! A Planta Tartarica Barometz!
I'm not really skilled or clever like you are, but I'm confident in my stamina and ability to take action.
If you let me handle the things you aren't good at, don't you think we'll be able to make something truly amazing?
It's fine to do some things alone,
but together we'll be able to do the impossible!
Are these... materials for the ship?
So then...
You want me to collect them, right?
Okay!
I'll do it!
Let's work hard together, Constanze!
Akko, what are you doing?
I thought up an idea of my own,
so I drew a picture of it.
Show it! Show it!
Impossible. Cannot be done.
A childish delusion.
Oh, stuff it!
You can't expect me to be as good as Constanze.
Are you an idiot?
Amateurs are scary.
Beginning to doubt sanity.
You don't need to go that far!
Go away!
Sorry, did I wake you?
Man, watching you kinda made me
think that anything really is possible.
So I tried coming up with something
like an "ultimate magic mecha".
But yeah, I guess there's no way this would work... right?
Constanze?
"Ghost hunt".
How could I possibly let such an entertaining chance slip by?
It's today!
The final day of the Wild Hunt!
The rumors were about this place, right?
I think I felt a presence just now!
If you buy some of these goods, you'll get spared some of the bad ghost mojo, probably.
What's going on?
It seems that talk of a ghost sighting in the plains around Blytonbury went viral online last night.
I think that's what drew all these occult fans here.
It's not like normal people can even see the ghost hunt.
Who the hell let it leak?
Things are gonna get messy.
It couldn't be...
Look!
They're here!
I wonder when it'll start.
When are they supposed to appear?
It must've been fake.
Just a bit longer!
You think?
Is the wind picking up?
Did you... just feel a chill?
All right! Captain!
Let's raise the anchors!
Bon voyage!
They're here!
It's Constanze and Akko!
Constanze!
Damn awesome!
That's the stuff!
Go.
Isn't it getting kinda noisy?
Hey, what the hell're those?!
Those are...
Captain, there's trouble!
What in the world is this thing?!
Got it!
Constanze! Let's do that!
Let's Metamor-formation!
Burning souls turned into magic power!
The seven shining stars of justice!
A believing heart is our magic!
Magic Suit Grand Charion!
On stage!
What is that?
Those guys are such morons.
So cool!
We nailed it!
My idea was a perfect success!
You're a real genius, Constanze!
Why aren't we moving?
We're out of magic power!
You mean we used it all up for the transformation?!
But we had so much of it!
That's it!
Attention, hunters!
If this goes on, the Wild Hunt will be ruined!
Please, lend them your strength!
Magic at one hundred and twenty percent!
Now, Constanze!
Grand Charion Big Wheel!
Miracle Magical Shining Tornado Punch!
Wild Hunt rocks!
We did it!
I guessed correctly.
What it is that you did.
An experiment. You caused a panic among the people
to gauge their rise in emotional energy—fuel spirit.
Am I wrong?
Just what are you plotting?!
You'll find out soon enough.
That no matter what my goals are...
There's not a single thing you can do to stop me.
For me?
It's thanks for helping her out.
Really, you didn't need to do this.
So cool!
And slow.
But I'm flying on a broom!
You call that flying?
Thanks, Constanze!
Even though I just learned another spell
oboetate no jumon ja
The things I want to do are still out of reach
kanawanai koto bakari dakedo
My skills are no match for my fantasies
imeeji suru no wa ima yori takaku
Yet my heart leaps out to meet them
tobitachi odoridasu kokoro
Breaking my tiny shell one layer at a time
chiisana kara nandomo nugisutete
I won't let my reckless abandon go to waste
gamushara dake de owarasenai
I'll leave who I was yesterday behind
kinou no watashi wo koeru you ni
Unfurling my transparent wings to the sky
toumei na tsubasa habatakasetara
I feel I can get closer to the tomorrow of my ideals
akogareteta ashita e kitto chikadzukeru ki ga shiterunda
Putting together the shards of a starry sky that I found
mitsuketa hoshizora no kakera musunde
I'll keep on chasing my dream to learn even more
motto shiritai yume wo ou yo