The fallin...
...lovelove bee?
I ordered a venomous bee, but they sent this one by mistake.
Anyone who gets stung by this bee
will fall in love with the first person they see.
The first person?
Will you return it?
Since we've got it, why not try it out on someone first?
Like who?
Maybe Akko.
The fallin lovelove bee, huh.
Well, if it isn't Akko.
What's with those outfits?
We've received an invitation to the Earl of Hanbridge's manor.
His son, Lord Andrew, just earned unparalleled honors at his prestigious school.
A party is being held to celebrate the occasion.
For Andrew?
Andrew Hanbridge.
Run away!
I didn't expect that thing to be inside!
Honestly, you've got a fantastic school here!
How lovely!
You're going too, Diana?
Why wouldn't she be?
The Hanbridge and Cavendish families share a long and illustrious noble bloodline.
Their families have been linked for over five hundred years.
I cannot embrace this.
I would much rather be studying than wasting time at a party.
Hannah, Barbara, let us plan to leave early.
Are you jealous?
Don't you want to go to the party?
Never ever, ever, ever!
Only nobility and the affluent are invited to the Earl's manor!
Little Miss Dunce can just stay here and wash away the ice cream on her cheeks with tears of frustration.
Damn them!
Doesn't that piss you off, Sucy? Lotte?
Not really. Couldn't care less.
Let's go, Akko.
I will! To the party!
Huh?
Just taking that on the chin would put the good name of witches to shame!
I'm going, and that's final!
Here where our long journey has finally led us
kakedashita hibi ni yukitsuita kono basho
We can push open the door
fureta tobira hiraite
In the footsteps of our dreams far beyond the stars
hoshizora no kanata yume no ashiato
Pick up the pieces with a song
hiroiatsume utau yo
Keep the destination of your dreams nestled in your heart
yume ga kaketeku basho ima mo kokoro ni himete
And envelop the night
yoru wo tsutsumikomu
Cast a magic spell
mahou kakete
And start to dance
odoridasu
The landscape looks like it's burning brilliantly
yaketsuita you ni irodzuita fuukei wa
But you can't see it fallen on the ground
koronda kurai ja tokenai kara
The world will keep on turning
sekai wa tsudzuku yo
Embrace the moment as if it'll never come again
hakanai mama no ima wo dakishimete
Let's keep walking as we are with the light in our sights
kawaranai mama jikan to hikari mitsumete aruiteku
The first thing we need are dresses.
Magic dresses that'll make us the life of the party!
Little Witch Academia
"Us"?
Yes, we're going! And that includes you two.
R-Right...
So you want magic dresses...
Everything I've got is way out of reach for you.
Could you change that?
Well, then...
How's this?
What about this?
Then this one.
Fine, then how about this?
A Cinderella set?
This was our bestseller a century ago.
"With a wave of your wand and the magic words,
you, too, can become Cinderella."
Buy now and I'll throw in a Snow White set,
and even knock the whole shebang down to half price!
All right, you've got a deal!
Okay, let's do this!
Bubide!
B-Bubbi-babbi?
Boo.
This is supposed to be our carriage?
It says here the magic will run out in two hours.
I get it. No wonder he was sitting on that shelfwarmer.
The Lord and Lady Rodester. We have
been eagerly awaiting your arrival.
Look, that's it! Earl Hanbridge's manor!
There's no way we'll be able to get in there...
Leave it to me!
Metamorphie Faciesse!
Now's our chance!
It's like a dream!
We've stepped into a world straight out of a girl's fantasies.
Thank you for being present as we honor my son, Andrew.
Andrew...
Such a magnificent feat, Lord Andrew. Not just anybody can be the top student at Appleton Academy.
That makes three consecutive years.
You have proved to be an admirable heir.
Earl Hanbridge's expectations for you were well placed.
One day, you will surely follow his footsteps
and become a formidable statesman.
I wish for nothing more.
Pardon me.
You don't look like you're having
the most pleasant day, Andrew.
There's no point in wasting time with formalities.
Diana!
Do you remember me? I'm Frank.
Andrew's schoolmate, I believe.
You become more beautiful each time I see you.
Your studies appear to be progressing well.
I feel privileged that you would take precious time out
of your so-called magic education to visit me, Diana.
Diana and Andrew are so picturesque together.
They're both nobles. We live in different worlds.
Th-That's right! They go perfectly together with their nasty personalities.
Akko?!
Wh-What a surprise to see you here!
What is possibly going through your mind?
You're the worst!
Why are you here?
I don't recall inviting you.
Y-Yeah, because you didn't!
Why would I even be considered?
But the fact is that I'm already here!
That makes me a full-fledged guest of yours!
Just the sort of twisted logic I would expect from a witch.
What was that?!
Regrettably, I must ask that you leave.
You want to throw me out?!
Witches, outdated and phony as they are, have no place here.
You can't even welcome a single cute and charming witch into your home?
S-Sucy?
Andrew, can you really call yourself a noble
with that intolerant attitude of yours?
Let it be, Andrew. What could be a more pleasant surprise than a visit from these witches?
Unfortunately, I hate surprises.
Andrew?
What's the matter?
There must have been something wrong with me. Why would I ever send you home?
Huh?
My thoughts have been in disarray.
Ever since the moment I first laid eyes on you...
You have been occupying a place in my heart.
Please let me be with you!
Forevermore.
N-No way...
It can't be...
This is...
D-Don't tell me!
You used the lovelove bee?!
Well, you're the one who said we should try it on someone.
W-Wait up!
Andrew's fallen head over heels.
This is a first.
C-Come back!
Come back!
Sweetest young lady!
What is your name?
How may we refer to you?
Um, I'm Lotte Jansson.
Lotte Jansson!
Lotte!
Tell me about yourself!
I-I don't think I'm a particularly interesting person.
Your hobbies are?
Are you betrothed?
Give me your hand!
I love you, Lotte!
There it is!
Diana, I'm coming too!
May I have this dance, Akko?
Y-You must be joking.
Profess your love, with lips so fine.
You've lit my fire, you must be mine.
Get away from me!
Sucy, do something about this!
There's nothing in the world better than toying with you, Akko.
You idiot!
Please wait, Akko!
Akko!
Little Witch Academia
I must find relief from this pounding in my chest.
What do we do?
Why not enjoy it?
This is the first time you've ever been desired.
Oh yeah, it is the first time!
And it's likely the last as well.
True, I'll probably never—
Hey, that's not the issue here!
We've only got another hour until the Cinderella set's magic wears off!
If you squish the lovelove bee with this,
you can probably break its spell.
So I've just gotta squish it with this!
There's no mistake.
That was a lovelove bee.
Where'd it go?
Diana!
Have you seen a bee? A weird-looking one.
Diana.
Akko...
How could I have ever been so cold to you up until now?
I... love you.
No, look what you've made me say!
Andrew.
It seems you opened our gates
to witches of Luna Nova.
Yes.
Are you aware of my antipathy towards witches?
Witches and magic are the evil relics of a bygone era.
We statesmen must be the ones to consolidate power for our nation.
Witches are without use.
You're saying we must abandon their dying breed?
That's politics. You have a bad habit of getting engrossed in useless things.
I recall you wishing to play the piano as a child.
I... haven't touched a piano in ten years, as you instructed.
Yes, as a matter of course. You are to become a leader of this country.
You have no need for effeminate music-making.
Remove the witches. Are we clear?
Wanna remove this witch here?
Just like you threw piano out from your life.
I had no idea you were so spineless. You're nothing but your father's puppet.
I highly respect my father.
He is an outstanding Minister of State
as well as head of our family.
I have a duty to succeed my father as a statesman.
Really, a duty? Don't you have any dreams?
A dream you found on your own.
You couldn't possibly understand.
There are those chosen by fate who must
bear the duty of a proud lineage.
I'm no noble, and I'm not rich either!
But I have a dream!
I want to be a brilliant witch!
I'll be the next Shiny Chariot!
I may just be a little witch right now, but I have fun every day chasing my dream!
Just imagining Chariot's smile is enough
to fill my whole world with rainbows!
Not like a certain someone would understand.
What's with the smirk? Are you looking down on me?
You are truly bewitching.
Th-That's not how you really feel. It's just because you were stung by that magic bee.
Bee?
There it is!
Help me out! If I can squash that bee,
you'll come back to your senses!
Hey, get back here!
Why you!
What is she doing?
What is the meaning of this?
She appears to be a witch of Luna Nova.
What?!
That's enough, Luna Nova witch.
I demand you leave the premises immediately.
Everyone, an incident has occurred.
At the moment, Miss Kagari is attempting to eliminate a dangerous bee.
A bee?
How horrid.
A-Andrew?
Play along.
Please enjoy this as she eliminates the bee.
Flight of the Bumblebee.
Where have you gone, Akko?
Who are you?
What is this ruckus?
Stop it! Sto—
Hold still, Earl!
Got it!
I finally got it!
That was a piece of cake!
My Lord!
Not bad, Andrew! I didn't expect you to be a pro at piano.
Of course I am. I'm perfect.
Unlike someone as slovenly as yourself.
Guess the spell wore off.
What was I thinking?
Seriously.
Let's get out of here. There are
no good girls around anyway.
I-I should've known. Of course this would happen.
Lotte.
Um... I think those clothes suit you a lot better.
I'm Frank. When's the next time you have off?
Do you want to visit the library?
Or is there anywhere else you'd like to go?
Um, you mean together?
I have the feeling we'd get along well.
How is it possible to be so beautiful?
Well, let's return home.
Lotte Jansson.
She's homely at first glance.
But then I saw her sad smile, and I realized...
She's the sort of kindhearted girl
you rarely find nowadays.
What about you and Atsuko Kagari?
Don't be foolish.
At the very least, you didn't kick her out.
You ignored an order from your witch-hating father.
My father is a brilliant statesman.
However, that does not mean our opinions will always align.
So basically...
That girl has caught your interest.
What?!
Wait, Lotte! Frank asked you out, but you refused?!
Yeah. I'm happy he did, but I felt it'd be rude to go on a date with him before I developed any feelings.
I told him we should start as friends.
Lotte, I bet you think you don't need a
boyfriend as long as you have night fall.
That's not true. So Akko, how about you?
Huh?
Did it make you happy to have a prince put the moves on you?
That was only because the bee stung him!
I know it put you on cloud nine.
"Profess your love, with lips so fine.
You've lit my fire, you must be mine."
There might come a day when Andrew says "I love you" for real.
No, no, no! That selfish, conceited guy would never say that!
Then you'd tell him?
No, no, no, no, no! Never, ever!
Seriously never! Even if I died!
Yeah, yeah.
It'll never happen!
I lost sight of everything else
muchuu ni natte oikaketeta
Chasing after a shooting star
nagareboshi tadotta saki ni
Longing to know more about this world
hirogaru sekai wo shiritakute
Just wishing won't make it come true
kanaetai to negau dake ja nai
But if you only push open the door
tobira wo akereba hora
You'll be one step closer
chikadzuite yukeru yo
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
The scenery may be ever-changing
keshiki wa kawatteiku kedo
But under this shining sky
kagayaku sora to
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
Thank you for staying by my side
soba ni itekurete arigatou
See you tomorrow
mata ashita ne