I can't let Croix go unchecked any longer.
She must be stopped...
Before it's too late.
Never did I imagine this could happen...
I need to tell Akko everything as well.
Take action!
Raise your hands!
Release the shutter on this scene like it's the moment of a lifetime
"One scene" shattaa kiru you ni setsuna wo utsushite
Turn it into a story that can speak for itself
tsukuriageru na mo naki hitotsu no story
Every single one of us can become a hero
watashitachi wa dare datte hiiro ni nareru
The possibility hides within us, don't you think?
kanousei wo himeta sonzai, sou deshou?
Your first steps forward can be small to start
fumidashita ippo ga hajime wa chiisaku tatte
Keep it up, and we can create a brand-new future
kitto atarashii mirai wo egaki daserunda
I'll always believe no matter what
donna toki mo shinjiteiru yo
In this world and in my dreams
kono sekai wo, jibun no yume wo
This uncontrollable urge is compelling me to begin
osaekirenai shoudou wa hajimari no aizu datte sa
Telling me to go out and find the me I haven't become yet
mada watashi ga shiranai watashi ni deau tame
So off I go!
kimeta yo
Don't be afraid to try again
osorenaide try again
Keep getting up and fly away
nando datte fly away
It's showtime!
Oh I don't want to miss a thing
Starting from here
kono basho kara
Little Witch Academia
New facts have surfaced in the goal controversy.
At the same time, protests are continuing to escalate.
The opposing faction has ended their silence
and launched counter-protests in turn.
Some supporters have started
resorting to extreme measures.
The two countries have been at war
three times since the middle ages,
and some are saying this uproar
may be the start of a fourth—
Our appeasement policy is reaching the end of its life.
They are taking us as weak-willed. This is not just a matter of winning or losing a match anymore.
Their whole nation thinks they can take advantage of us.
The time for compromise is over. We must demonstrate our firm resolve!
Is that really so?
Much time and effort was spent mending our relations.
Should we truly be willing to let that go to waste?
What, you think you can mouth off to me again?
Andrew.
This is one issue you cannot stick your nose in.
You should listen to your father's orders.
I overlooked the incident with the witch
at Appleton in deference to your father,
but cause any more problems,
and I will be forced to act.
I will not allow any defiance.
So long as I must keep cleaning up your messes, you are still a child.
It is your duty and responsibility, as the Hanbridge heir, to become a great statesman.
Bear that in mind henceforth.
I couldn't even give one word in response.
If she had been watching, I'd be getting called a coward about now.
There's Diana's messenger.
Now I'll be able to contact Miss Kagari.
Coming.
Diana?
Good day. Is Akko available?
Diana's looking for Akko? She must be plotting something.
Come on, Sucy!
Akko just left to go see Professor Ursula.
Professor Ursula?
Thank goodness, you really do seem fine now.
Didn't I tell you that there was no need to worry?
I was almost fully healed back then.
But it was my fault you even
got hurt in the first place.
Akko, didn't you promise not to say that anymore?
Yeah.
But I'm glad you came.
There's something I needed to talk to you about.
What's that?
I will tell you the seventh and final Word.
Phasansheer Shearylla.
Phasansheer Shearylla?
Not even I know its meaning.
You don't?
Just remember that the final Word
lies within your heart.
Within my heart...
The seventh star will shine in response to the feelings in your heart.
When the seventh star shines, say the final Word.
Okay.
There's one more thing I need to tell you.
Huh? There is?
I've been trying to find
the right time to tell you for so long.
Listen, the truth is—
Is Akko here?
Lotte?
Huh?! Diana too?
I have a message from Andrew.
He'll be waiting for you at High Street today.
Huh, Andrew said that? Today?
He's got something to give you.
Really? But, today...
What time today?
At three o—
Three?!
That's cutting it close.
Professor!
Go ahead. We can continue our conversation after you get back.
Thanks, Professor! I'll be right back!
Sorry, Lotte, but could you give me a ride?
Sure, let's hurry.
Excuse us!
I-It's unusual for you to come here.
There is something I would like to ask you.
You have a question for me?
H-Hopefully I'll be able to answer it for you...
Are you aware of the recent concentration of magic energy,
surpassing even the output of the Sorcerer's Stone?
After looking into it, events relating to that matter began after Professor Croix installed her SSS in Luna Nova.
I believe you were old friends with Professor Croix, so I had hoped you might know something about this.
I'm sorry, but something just came up.
Professor?
We'll finish this later!
Professor!
Don't tell me...
Was she affected by Wagandea's pollen?
Geez, out of everyone it could've been,
I never excepted you to call for me.
Forgive me, but I wanted to return this.
Oh, right. I forgot it in your car back then.
I intended to alert you immediately, but who'd
expect all calls and emails to be barred?
You're telling me.
All we've got is one-way messaging through magic.
I guess that explains why you contacted Diana.
Thanks to our families.
Seriously though, that was way too little notice. I barely made it in time.
Don't you know I can't ride a broom?
Why do you sound so proud about that?
Anyway, I apologize for rushing you.
I was on the way to Parliament with my father.
I figured this timing would work for us both.
Parliament? Wow, that sounds kinda fancy.
It isn't, really. I'm just accompanying my father.
No goal! No goal! No goal! No goal!
Wh-What's that?
That's actually part of the reason
we're heading to Parliament.
What's going on?
The enmity from a soccer match escalated and ended up
exacerbating the hatred between our nation and their's.
There seem to be similar demonstrations within their borders too.
Our two countries have been at ends since the Middle Ages.
Only recently were things finally starting to improve.
Yet look how little it took
to set us back on edge again.
It's such a shame.
No matter what their reasons are, I just can't understand how they can keep being so angry.
And... it kind of scares me too.
I'm with you.
This is exactly the kind of situation we need Chariot for.
Everyone should go and see Chariot's show.
They'd be thrilled and laugh and get emotional—
Then all their anger and negativity will be blown away.
They'd laugh?
And get emotional!
And then, all the world will be at peace!
That's quite the quixotic idealism.
Huh?
You're not laughing? Usually, you'd be
snorting at me or something.
I won't laugh.
It would be wonderful if that could turn into reality.
Far better than what's happening right now.
You've come to accept magic just a little bit more than before.
Perhaps my opinion of you has improved slightly over time.
But there's one thing I must say.
You want people to be moved and happiness brought upon them.
But what's the point if you just rely on Chariot and don't do it yourself?
Y-You mean I should do it?
Do you disagree?
No, you've got it right.
Fine, I'll do it!
Oh?
What's with that look? You can bet I'll do it!
Just watch me, Andrew!
That thing!
I saw it before!
Sorry, Andrew! I've gotta go!
See you later!
Sure—
What's the point if you don't do it yourself?
That's right...
Little Witch Academia
I wonder if things are going well with Akko and Andrew.
Come back!
Wait!
Guess not.
Akko?
You should really try to limit your foolishness to the school grounds.
Look!
That looks like the things that were flying around during the strike.
I remember seeing them at the Wild Hunt too.
Bad stuff happens whenever these things are around.
There too...
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Hey!
Look at that!
Those bastards!
They'll pay for this!
This is war!
It's only getting worse.
Huh? Where's Akko?
Professor Croix?
Professor Croix!
This is bad, Professor Croix!
Why are you here?
Sorry, there's a very complicated reason for that...
I see. So it was only coincidence
that brought you to the city.
You don't even have Claimh Solais on you.
Claimh Solais? What's that?
Wait, that's not important right now!
I saw all these weird, square-y things all over town!
They're definitely doing something bad!
Like that!
It's that thing!
Good work.
I developed these in order to convert emotions into energy.
You made those people...?
Not quite.
The emotion of anger comes from within them.
All I did was enhance it slightly and absorb it.
Absorb it? But why?
Noir Fuel Spirit.
You can convert strong human emotions
into powerful magic energy.
That is why I am probing the hearts of people around the world—
Anger, hatred, sadness, jealousy, fear, anxiety—
I want to completely absorb all of those emotions.
Absorb... emotions?
You should be aware as well.
Magic is in decline all around the world.
If nothing is done, magic will one day disappear entirely.
We need a method to generate it
from some sort of energy.
Don't you see how fantastic it would be if we could harvest human emotions as a new energy source?
Manipulation is easiest with crowd psychology.
I've been gathering emotions through this app...
And the results far exceed my expectations!
There's more than enough for my world reconstruction plan to come to fruition!
They'll all see magic in a new light!
Professor Croix, you're acting weird!
Stop doing something like that!
Why? Are you saying you wouldn't mind
if magic was lost forever?
Magic won't go away! I won't let it!
How?
Feelings by themselves can't change the world—you must take action.
Still... this is wrong!
Magic...
Magic should be used to make people happy!
You say the same things as Chariot.
That is exactly why she failed.
I can't comprehend incompetent witches who do nothing but chase after unachievable dreams.
This was a waste of time.
Our private lesson ends here.
You stay right there and keep your mouth shut.
Diphulaniado!
Chariot...
Professor... Ursula?
You've never learned how to keep your head down.
Do you still intend to interfere, Chariot du Nord?
Chariot?
You're... Shiny Chariot?
So you finally realized? Didn't I say you'd meet her soon?
The person you've so admired has always been
right next to you, pulling the wool over your eyes.
I'm sorry I kept this a secret from you.
I wanted to tell you properly.
That's enough, Croix!
Your methods are mistaken!
Do you intend to stop me?
You? Stop me? I'm surprised you can
say that with a straight face.
Don't you remember what you did ten years ago?
Why don't you be the one to tell her what happened the day Chariot descended from the stage forever?
What exactly it was that you did to the moon.
Dream Fuel Spirit.
Magic to convert the power of dreaming
into strong magical energy.
What exactly gives you the right to stop me after using that yourself?
That power—
Convert the power of dreaming into magic?
Oh, I see how it is now.
So that's the true reason you care so much about her.
Akko.
You saw Chariot's show in the past, didn't you?
Huh?
Dream Fuel Spirit gathers the dreaming energy of everyone in the area and turns it into magic.
And those whose dreams are absorbed...
Lose their magic.
Isn't that right, Chariot?
You tell her yourself.
When I learned that you once saw a Chariot show, I hoped it wasn't true.
I didn't want to believe it.
But after all the time we spent together,
I couldn't deny it anymore.
In all likelihood, I was the one who absorbed your magic.
The reason you can't fly...
Is all my fault.
That's a lie...
Come on, Professor Ursula...
Say... it's a lie...
It must be a lie...
It's a lie...
Never forget.
A believing heart is your magic.
That's a lie!
I doubt she'll be looking for the Words any longer.
Yet again, you couldn't reach it.
The seventh Word.
Even though I just learned another spell
oboetate no jumon ja
The things I want to do are still out of reach
kanawanai koto bakari dakedo
My skills are no match for my fantasies
imeeji suru no wa ima yori takaku
Yet my heart leaps out to meet them
tobitachi odoridasu kokoro
Breaking my tiny shell one layer at a time
chiisana kara nandomo nugisutete
I won't let my reckless abandon go to waste
gamushara dake de owarasenai
I'll leave who I was yesterday behind
kinou no watashi wo koeru you ni
Unfurling my transparent wings to the sky
toumei na tsubasa habatakasetara
I feel I can get closer to the tomorrow of my ideals
akogareteta ashita e kitto chikadzukeru ki ga shiterunda
Putting together the shards of a starry sky that I found
mitsuketa hoshizora no kakera musunde
I'll keep on chasing my dream to learn even more
motto shiritai yume wo ou yo