If I reach out, it's sure to begin!
My very own story!
Noctu... Orfei!
Aude Fraetor!
Shiny Arc!
Oh, that's right!
The Shiny Rod!
It wasn't just a dream!
I finally made it to the witch academy, Luna Nova!
Oh yeah!
Yay!
Morning, Lotte!
Check it out!
The Shiny Rod, right?
You got it!
You only told us about it
a hundred times last night.
It's Shiny Chariot's magic staff!
I have no idea why it was in that forest, but I'll
keep it safe until the day I can give it back to Chariot.
As long as I've got this staff,
I bet I can cast any magic I want.
O bed, take flight!
Move, Alcor!
Move, move!
I said move! Start moving!
Why you... move, move!
What are you doing, Sucy?
Move, move, move, move, move, move, move, move!
I'm extracting the petrification poison from this cockatrice feather.
Right, you came to Luna Nova for your collection of deadly poisons.
Why won't it move?
I originally planned to go back after getting myself a cockatrice feather...
Okay... I can do this. I know I can do it!
But then I heard there might be samples of an extinct poisonous mushroom here.
You can do it. You can do it, Akko!
There! Take that!
So I figured I might as well stay a bit longer.
How's that? Or this?!
Here! Once more!
Blow, o wind!
Tear my cheeks up!
That's strange...
It was definitely working yesterday.
Put that down and get ready.
We can't be late for class.
Class?!
Yay! Transformation complete!
Let's move out!
We wear that one for school functions and practical lessons. This is for regular classes.
Aw, really?
First period is magic linguistics.
Then, fundamentals of magic pharmaceutics
followed by magic numerology.
Today is the day I take my first step as a witch!
Akko, hurry up!
I'm coming!
Here where our long journey has finally led us
kakedashita hibi ni yukitsuita kono basho
We can push open the door
fureta tobira hiraite
In the footsteps of our dreams far beyond the stars
hoshizora no kanata yume no ashiato
Pick up the pieces with a song
hiroiatsume utau yo
Keep the destination of your dreams nestled in your heart
yume ga kaketeku basho ima mo kokoro ni himete
And envelop the night
yoru wo tsutsumikomu
Cast a magic spell
mahou kakete
And start to dance
odoridasu
The landscape looks like it's burning brilliantly
yaketsuita you ni irodzuita fuukei wa
But you can't see it fallen on the ground
koronda kurai ja tokenai kara
The world will keep on turning
sekai wa tsudzuku yo
Embrace the moment as if it'll never come again
hakanai mama no ima wo dakishimete
Let's keep walking as we are with the light in our sights
kawaranai mama jikan to hikari mitsumete aruiteku
Little Witch Academia
Today, we commence lessons for Luna Nova's
one thousand five hundred ninety-eighth term.
Let us honor the great Nine Olde Witches as we—
Professor Ursula...
M-My apologies.
Please straighten yourself out, Professor Ursula.
How are you to guide your students
with a demeanor such as yours?
R-Right.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Now then, please explain yourself, Professor Ursula.
What compelled you to mentor that new student, Atsuko Kagari?
I simply want to tutor her about fundamental magic during my spare time
and help her make herself at home here.
She must feel quite lost as a Japanese student coming from a non-magic lineage.
And yet it is your lack of dignity as a teacher that makes me feel lost about how to handle you.
Oh, look!
It's Kagari.
Professor Finneran, excuse me to go say hello—
Oh my!
Oh, oh, oh!
This is kinda lame.
Well, whatever.
I can't wait to see what magic lessons are like!
It's so thrilling and exciting!
In summary, the luna alphabet is a traditional writing system that was used by ancient witches.
It constitutes a form of phonemic orthography.
Is anybody able to read what I have written on the board?
Miss Cavendish.
Fortune to she who lets the stone rest.
A curse upon she who does not.
That was splendid, Diana Cavendish.
For as long as I have been a teacher here,
you are the first person able to read this.
I knew Diana could do it.
The more you stir, the further the color changes.
Then add a lively frog into the cauldron.
The frog must be taken straight from water to avoid its secretions.
Entrail of newt, crushed bat nails.
Carefully, carefully add them to the pot...
How's that? Doesn't it have a wondrous odor?
A-As I have explained, it is believed that Pythagoras laid the foundations of sorcery and divination.
Now, please turn to line 102 on page 923 of your textbooks.
From a numerology perspective, the numbers one through five can be used to represent the universe—
Professor Badcock.
I believe it reads one through four,
not one through five.
What?
Wh-What a blunder. You are absolutely correct.
Talk about losing face.
What's going on here?!
How are lessons about magic this boring?!
Isn't magic supposed to be flashy and all about dreams and miracles?
Lotte, could you pass that?
S-Sure.
This is nothing like I imagined.
I can hardly believe this is the same school
Shiny Chariot learned magic at.
You'd be hard pressed to find anyone
who respects Shiny Chariot's magic.
Certainly not at this academy.
Your name is Kagari, correct?
You are the new student.
Chusht khul mih Akcho.
Just call me Akko. Uh, you were the one standing out...
Diana Cavendish.
You don't know who Diana is?
She's like a celebrity in the magic world.
Everyone says she's the greatest witch to ever grace Luna Nova since its founding!
I do not mind referring to you
as Akko, as you suggested.
In any case, you will not find anyone in the magic world who holds Chariot's magic in high regard.
It's in your best interest to remember that.
That can't be true!
Chariot's magic show was world-renowned and beloved by all!
I must admit...
She did enjoy a period of popularity in the past.
However, those gaudy yet insubstantial
spectacles of hers had no lasting power.
Almost ten years have passed since Chariot left the stage and disappeared.
There is nobody who cares enough to even attempt to find out where she is now.
Chariot is...
She gave me a dream!
That much is true.
I even found her Shiny Rod.
Shiny Rod?
This must be a common replica.
It is not!
Are you truly proud of that toy?
It's perfect for a commoner.
I'll show you one of Chariot's miracles!
Peel your eyes!
Don't do it, Akko.
I know I'll succeed if I believe!
Please, Shiny Rod.
Show me another miracle, like you did yesterday!
Move, o statue!
S-Statue, move! Move for me!
Come on, start moving! Please!
I said to move!
Akko...
Why? It worked yesterday...
Ansolew Airo!
Wow...
That's incredible.
High class magic to breathe life into a statue!
You're the miracle witch, Diana!
Akko, are you all right?
Magic is cultivated through the accumulation of lasting traditions and assiduous research.
It is not something that those prone to temporary diversions can learn.
Diana is a daughter of the 1500-year-old Cavendish family.
She's on a completely different level than that performance witch Chariot!
Wait up!
Diana!
Professor Ursula.
Y-Yes?!
Have you looked into the matter I requested of you?
I-I was about to!
Little Witch Academia
A believing heart is your magic.
Ten years since she disappeared...
I wonder what Chariot is doing now...
Nobody anywhere has any idea.
Hey, it must've been pretty hard to collect all these.
Yeah. I remember everyone was big on collecting her cards during the Chariot craze when I was a kid.
Shiny Chariot
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
Seven stars, the magic of light.
The sea of light, the seven forms.
A Believing Heart Is Your Magic
"A believing heart is your magic"...
There was just one premium card I was never able to get.
I wanted it so badly, too.
"The mushroom of recalling lost love."
It's a unicorn.
"The immortal holy beast that protects maidens' happiness."
You have it memorized?
Of course, I remember all of them.
Though I always had trouble with the spell pronunciations.
Oh, I know this one. It's the magic butterfly.
Papilliodya.
Papilliodya
The butterfly that travels the five continents.
They emerge only once every hundred-twenty years,
and legend says they bring hope to the hearts of all who behold them.
It's quite weakened.
Professor Ursula. Has your research revealed
anything about the origin of its affliction?
Y-Yes, I believe that its current state of weakness is only temporary.
Once the cause of it leaves...
The cause of it? Have you unearthed some information?
I would like to dig a bit deeper first...
Please determine the full truth.
Headmistress.
The Jennifer Memorial Tree has been reduced to such a sorry state...
It is so, Diana. This Memorial Tree is already rather advanced in years.
Perhaps it is finally reaching
the end of its lifespan.
The Jennifer Memorial Tree...
Luna Nova's tree of life left behind to inherit the will of the great witch Jennifer.
I've finished this side.
I'll attempt to use revitalization magic on the magic tree.
Provided strong enough nourishment, large plants can be brought to life again.
This is a secret art passed down through generations of the Cavendish family.
Louperial Ral!
The flow of nutrients should now be restored.
You've done it, Diana!
Let's go inform the teachers!
I knew it!
My hunch was correct.
How could I not have realized?
Then this means...
A miracle is approaching.
Four damage to Sucy's life.
That means I win!
Yay, nine straight wins!
Why can you use effects that aren't even written on the card? I don't get it.
One more round.
What is this thing?!
Over there, Akko!
What is the meaning of this?
Stand back!
Diana?
What's going on here?
Look!
What are these things?
Looks like chrysalises to me.
Chrysalises?!
And not normal ones at that.
The roots had parasites.
They must be the cause of the Tree's decline.
My magic must have passed through the Tree and nourished the pests!
I have to eliminate them.
Murowa!
Aren't these...
Murowa—
Hold on, Diana!
These might not be pests after all!
You're interfering. Get out of the way!
I won't!
Murowa!
Akko!
Hang in there!
What has she done?
She's churning with magic.
This might be bad.
Papilliodya...
They're papilliodya chrysalises...
From this?
I'm sure of it.
Papilliodya that only emerge once every hundred-twenty years!
Magic butterflies that bring hope to the hearts of all who behold them!
Wait, Akko! Try casting this spell.
The papilliodya spell.
Um, Papillio Fillia...
Papillio Fillio Nymphodya.
Is that the proper pronunciation?
Thanks!
Papilliodya that travel the five continents.
Take flight, magic butterflies, towards hope!
Papillio Fillio Nymphodya!
Papilliodya spend 120 years as larvae in the dark underground before becoming butterflies.
As butterflies, the delight of their first flight—
Hey, look outside!
The delight of their first flight brings hope
to the hearts of those who behold them.
Goodness, the Memorial Tree!
How splendid!
It's all thanks to Diana's magic!
Thank you, Diana.
P-Please wait! This was not my doing...
Who else besides you could have done it?
I...
Please excuse me.
Diana truly is the pride of Luna Nova.
I lost sight of everything else
muchuu ni natte oikaketeta
Chasing after a shooting star
nagareboshi tadotta saki ni
Longing to know
more about this world
hirogaru sekai wo shiritakute
Longing to know
more about this world
hirogaru sekai wo shiritakute
Longing to know
more about this world
hirogaru sekai wo shiritakute
Just wishing won't
make it come true
kanaetai to negau dake ja nai
Just wishing won't
make it come true
kanaetai to negau dake ja nai
Just wishing won't
make it come true
kanaetai to negau dake ja nai
But if you only push open the door
tobira wo akereba hora
You'll be one step closer
chikadzuite yukeru yo
Let's go on a journey to find the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari no tsudzuki wo sagasou
You're not the only one who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no wa hitori ja nai kara
The scenery may be ever-changing
keshiki wa kawatteiku kedo
But under this shining sky
kagayaku sora to
I'll never let go of the treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono itsumademo hanasanai yo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
Thank you for staying by my side
soba ni itekurete arigatou
See you tomorrow
mata ashita ne