Vajarois wakes at the close of the Festival,
when the midnight bell tolls.
Unable to forget the agony of losing her friends, she demands sacrifices to...
Chomp.
Will that happen to us too? Just the thought...
Sends a shiver down my spine!
All right!
Let's make Vajarois burst into laughter during the ritual sacrifice!
Huh?
Chariot was chosen as the Moonlit Witch of the
Samhain Festival because of her metamorphosis magic,
but that wasn't why she performed it.
As far as I could tell, she just wanted
to give everyone a thrilling time!
That's why I want us to put on a fun metamorphosis magic show and make Vajarois the Wailing
double over with laughter!
For what reason?
Huh? Well, don't you think it's awful to have this whole ritual where people stare at Vajarois cry and eat sacrifices?
Magic should be more exciting and thrilling!
It's supposed to make everyone happy!
Like Chariot did...
Listen, what's the point in going that far?
It's not like anyone asked us to.
I think following tradition is good enough.
But then Vajarois will keep crying forever!
Let's blow away her tears with
metamorphosis magic, and...
The ritual's always been done the same way.
Besides, you can't even do regular
metamorphosis magic right yet.
But that's—true, I guess...
Akko...
I understand your feelings...
But we can't always keep up with you.
But I want everyone to see how fun magic is!
I'll work as hard as I can
so you two can understand too.
Just watch me!
Here where our long journey has finally led us
kakedashita hibi ni yukitsuita kono basho
We can push open the door
fureta tobira hiraite
In the footsteps of our dreams far beyond the stars
hoshizora no kanata yume no ashiato
Pick up the pieces with a song
hiroiatsume utau yo
Keep the destination of your dreams nestled in your heart
yume ga kaketeku basho ima mo kokoro ni himete
And envelop the night
yoru wo tsutsumikomu
Cast a magic spell
mahou kakete
And start to dance
odoridasu
The landscape looks like it's burning brilliantly
yaketsuita you ni irodzuita fuukei wa
But you can't see it fallen on the ground
koronda kurai ja tokenai kara
The world will keep on turning
sekai wa tsudzuku yo
Embrace the moment as if it'll never come again
hakanai mama no ima wo dakishimete
Let's keep walking as we are with the light in our sights
kawaranai mama jikan to hikari mitsumete aruiteku
Little Witch Academia
I see.
I don't want to give up.
Lotte and Sucy keep telling me we should
stick to how it's always been done.
I just think that if we use the metamorphosis magic Chariot did at her Samhain Festival,
we could make this really exciting for everyone...
The magic Chariot used at the Festival...
Arae Aryrha. The third Word.
Do your best, Akko.
I'll do some research on Vajarois the Wailing.
You keep practicing on your own.
Okay.
Thank you very much. I'll come
back if I need your help again.
Sure, I'll always make time for you.
The reason Vajarois is drowning in sorrow...
If I prove to Lotte and Sucy that I can do it, they'll definitely be on my side.
A word, Akko.
You certainly pulled a fast one on us the other day.
I-I apologize for that.
You think that's enough to earn our forgiveness?
It is not! Just how much humiliation
do you think we've had to face?
Still...
You know...
Considering that you have to be the pitiful sacrifices, we'll let it slide.
Oh, I can hardly wait to see you become laughingstocks!
I can't imagine better sacrifices!
Akko the Buffoon and Creepy Sucy.
Plus the girl with a presence as thin as air, Invisible Lotte!
A real merry band of leftover losers!
What's with that face? Got something to say?
Would you please not get mad when all we've done is said the truth?
Metamorphie Faciesse!
Metamorphie Facie—
The first successful greenhouse cultivation of purple mandrake was conducted by Doctor Weather thirty years ago...
Metamorphie Facie...
Invisible Lotte with a presence as thin as air, huh...
Look sharp! The Samhain Festival is almost upon us!
Yes!
Let's see... there it is!
"Princess Vajarois of the Book Kingdom.
Records state that a certain curse caused her to remain in existence as a ghost after her passing."
That's it?!
I guess I really will need to dig into older materials...
"Vajarois's Vestige"?
"Can be found in Luna Nova's reference archives."
It's been three weeks... Akko's working hard.
Three weeks and three days. Though she hasn't improved a bit.
Hey, Sucy... why do you think Akko can keep it up?
She flounders and suffers, and yet she keeps
reaching out for things beyond her grasp.
Isn't that just because she's an idiot?
And a stubborn one at that.
But that part of her is amazing.
What's this?
Kagari Atsuko
"Trick or Treat Plan"?
Why? Why can't I do it?
Lotte? Sucy?
You really are someone who can't do anything by herself, Akko.
But the three of us just might
be able to make something happen.
We did some thinking, and it would be best if you handled the metamorphosis magic by yourself.
It'd be much more interesting
with us as your assistants.
Even if you mess up, we can cover for your mistakes.
Then...
Watching you brought back memories.
I remembered the excitement I felt talking to faeries for the first time as a child.
Back when magic meant nothing but fun to me.
Maybe having fun with you isn't such a bad option.
Thanks, you two!
Too tight!
I... I'll definitely make this work!
It's the long-awaited Samhain Festival!
Alumna have gathered from around the world via the leylines.
Vajarois's Vestige should be in here...
...somewhere.
The lights have been lit above the stage on Luna Nova's sports ground.
With our guests of honor—Miss Marjolaine, Minister Dorlin, and Madame Ural—in attendance,
the Samhain Festival committee chair,
Diana Cavendish, will deliver the opening statement.
I hereby declare the start of the Luna Nova Samhain Festival.
Also, at the close of the Samhain Festival, the most exceptional witch out of all the students will be chosen
and earn the title of Moonlit Witch!
Now, who will claim the crown?!
Not this one, or this one either!
Little Witch Academia
The Samhain Festival is already underway!
Quite the performance, wasn't it?
On cleaning duty! Enjoy the Sweeper Girls' dance!
Constanze!
It ate her!
Let go! Let her g—
Nothing to write home about,
just like every year.
It's no wonder magic is dying out.
This is what you get when you let Holbrooke head the school.
Hang in there! Don't give up!
You'll be fine! Just fine!
Akko sure is late.
She's probably practicing until the very last minute.
Has Akko arrived yet? There's precious little time left.
Maybe she's finally realized how worthless she is...
...and made herself scarce?
She ran away from her responsibilities, leaving all the burden on your shoulders.
Diana, you're up next.
How pathetic.
You have my condolences, being forced into a group with her.
Akko wouldn't run away!
She's pouring everything she has into
making what she believes in happen!
She may be stubborn, but that's what makes her Akko!
Metamorphie Faciesse!
It's time for the headliner!
Stepping forward is committee chair
Diana with her summoning magic!
It's the Cavendish's girl, Diana.
I'll see if she's worthy of carrying on her prestigious family's name.
It's finally time.
Luna Nova's star!
Indeed.
Behold this water summoning magic,
passed down from ancient times.
Shurial Muryuelle.
Creature of the holy mane...
Absorb the light of the stars and rise from this gushing spring!
Tiphillie Lirullianae!
Magnificent!
As expected of Luna Nova's star!
Sounds like Diana did great.
Yeah, well it is Diana.
Sorry I'm late!
Akko!
Geez, you took your time!
Sorry, my bad! I lost track of the time practicing.
All right. Lotte, Sucy.
Let's do everything we can!
Yeah.
We've reached the last act of the Samhain Festival!
As soon as the midnight bell tolls,
the ritual sacrifice will begin!
This year's sacrifices are Lotte Jansson,
Sucy Manbavaran, and Atsuko Kagari!
Akko...
Watch me.
Are you ready, folks?
It's time for the super fun sacrifice show!
"Fun"?
Sacrifice "show"?
Headmistress!
Vajarois the Wailing makes her grand entrance!
Akko!
Over here!
What's this? Have they left Akko to be the sole sacrifice?
Look at me, Vajarois!
Metamorphie Faciesse!
Metamorphie Fac—
The poor girl has fallen prey to Vajarois...
W-Wait?!
What a surprise! She transformed
into a mouse to avoid the danger!
This is unprecedented! The sacrifice is escaping!
Wh-What has she done?!
Let it be.
Come on, Vajarois! Catch me if you can!
The stage is getting destroyed, but what about Akko?!
They've changed things up this year.
I must admit it's rather interesting.
And now Akko has turned into a flying elephant!
How adorable!
Headmistress!
I can't keep afloat!
Nice support. Guess I should help out too.
What's happening now?
Mushrooms! Mushrooms have begun to sprout!
Thanks, guys!
Akko, look out behind you!
Now! Lotte, Sucy!
We're on it!
Yahoo, Vajarois!
Don't be so sad! Let's turn that frown upside down!
This is so vulgar.
Hea—
What are they doing?
Look at her head!
Vajarois! Are you having fun?
Blow away your sadness with a smile!
Metamorphie Faciesse!
Show me that smile of yours, Vajarois!
Akko just never gets it right.
But she's getting laughs, and that's what counts.
What's with that crappy magic!
This is actually rather intriguing.
Nice one, Akko!
How's that, Vajarois?
Having fun y—
Lotte! Sucy!
Doesn't seem like Vajarois herself is having much fun.
Huh?
Vajarois...
I've finally found it!
I was worried it was gone forever.
Triutoi Estida!
O ancient faerie, heed my call.
What is the truth of Vajarois's curse?
This is... the seed of sorrow?
"Having lost many a friend, Princess Vajarois swallowed the seed of sorrow so as not to forget them.
The seed spreads its roots within whoever
swallows it, making their sorrow eternal..."
So, what now?
Vajarois... why are you so sad?
The rod!
Vajarois has sneezed them high up into the sky!
Akko! Akko!
Professor Ursula's familiar!
And the Shiny Rod too!
Listen carefully, Akko.
A seed of sorrow has spread its roots inside Vajarois.
A seed of sorrow?
She cast a curse of eternal sorrow on herself so she'd always remember her friends.
You have to pull the seed of sorrow out!
Use Chariot's magic! You three can surely succeed!
Okay!
Where's the source of her sorrow?!
Hey, isn't that it?
It can't be anything else.
Okay! Let's do this, Lotte, Sucy!
Vajarois, think back! Remember all the smiles and laughter you shared with your friends!
Arae Aryrha!
And pull!
What's this! Something's happening to Vajarois!
Akko...
What could possibly be happening inside Vajarois?!
Vajarois...
Your friends wouldn't want you to live in sorrow!
They surely want to see you smile, Vajarois.
Open your heart!
Let's laugh together!
Arae Aryrha!
That's Vajarois's... original form?
Th-This is incredible! The three sacrifices
have done the unimaginable!
That wasn't half shabby!
It was well worth seeing.
With this, Luna Nova should have
no more reason to conduct the ritual sacrifice.
Yes.
You did it, Akko.
Lotte! Sucy!
I couldn't have done it without you!
Wasn't that fun, Akko?
I give it a passing grade.
Diana!
They haven't finished counting yet,
but you're on track to be the Moonlit Witch.
What about Akko's group?
They broke the rules, so they're out of consideration.
But they sure did do a nice thing.
There's the award ceremony coming up, so get ready.
Back to Akko! She's so moved by breaking Vajarois' curse that she can hardly speak through the tears!
What is it...
That has filled me with this emotion?
I lost sight of everything else
muchuu ni natte oikaketeta
Chasing after a shooting star
nagareboshi tadotta saki ni
Longing to know more about this world
hirogaru sekai wo shiritakute
Just wishing won't make it come true
kanaetai to negau dake ja nai
But if you only push open the door
tobira wo akereba hora
You'll be one step closer
chikadzuite yukeru yo
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
The scenery may be ever-changing
keshiki wa kawatteiku kedo
But under this shining sky
kagayaku sora to
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
Thank you for staying by my side
soba ni itekurete arigatou
See you tomorrow
mata ashita ne