The Words are reviving.
Noctu... Orfei!
Aude Fraetor!
Phaidoari...
Afairrynghor!
Arae Aryrha!
Akko has revived three of the long-lost Words of Arcturus.
There are seven Words of Arcturus in total.
Revive the remaining Words.
Chariot.
The time to reveal everything to Akko has come at last.
Take action!
Raise your hands!
Release the shutter on this scene like it's the moment of a lifetime
"One scene" shattaa kiru you ni setsuna wo utsushite
Turn it into a story that can speak for itself
tsukuriageru na mo naki hitotsu no story
Every single one of us can become a hero
watashitachi wa dare datte hiiro ni nareru
The possibility hides within us, don't you think?
kanousei wo himeta sonzai, sou deshou?
Your first steps forward can be small to start
fumidashita ippo ga hajime wa chiisaku tatte
Keep it up, and we can create a brand-new future
kitto atarashii mirai wo egaki daserunda
I'll always believe no matter what
donna toki mo shinjiteiru yo
In this world and in my dreams
kono sekai wo, jibun no yume wo
This uncontrollable urge is compelling me to begin
osaekirenai shoudou wa hajimari no aizu datte sa
Telling me to go out and find the me I haven't become yet
mada watashi ga shiranai watashi ni deau tame
So off I go!
kimeta yo
Don't be afraid to try again
osorenaide try again
Keep getting up and fly away
nando datte fly away
It's showtime!
Oh I don't want to miss a thing
Starting from here
kono basho kara
Little Witch Academia
It sure feels like autumn arrived
as soon as Samhain Day passed.
The new semester starts today, and I heard we're getting a new professor.
"New"? I bet she's at least a hundred years old.
But man, never thought I'd see Akko steal the show like that.
Gotta admit you impressed me!
Right? Wasn't she amazing?
Lemme see that magic again, Akko.
No can do.
Come on, it's not like you'll run out.
Nuh-uh. It's not so easy that I can do it whenever I want.
I'm finally starting to understand.
Most of the time, I can huff and puff all I want,
but the Shiny Rod won't so much as make a peep.
But whenever push really comes
to shove, my feelings get through to it.
How mysterious.
It used to be Chariot's staff, right?
Akko found it in Arcturus Forest.
For real?!
Isn't that that forbidden forest?!
It has a really strong barrier,
so you normally can't enter it.
Rumors say it's hiding some huge secret.
And that legend's been going around for a long time.
Why did Chariot disappear, and how are
Arcturus Forest and the Shiny Rod related?
I feel like it'll all make sense once I find Chariot.
Professor, good morning!
G-Good morning.
What did you want to talk about?
I was thinking of telling you something very important.
Listen carefully. It is your fate to—
Professor Ursula!
Please come as quickly as possible!
What is all this fuss about?
It's a strike!
A strike?!
Return to your posts!
Do not think your actions
will be without consequence!
My word, faeries forming a labor union is entirely unprecedented!
It's an omen.
Their work stoppage means that all of the cooking, laundry, and cleaning has been suspended!
So, what are their demands?
It appears they wish to use more energy from the Sorcerer's Stone.
Can't we accommodate their request?
We cannot!
Oh my, what a textbook downward trend.
This is the amount of energy our school draws from the Sorcerer's Stone each day.
And this is the Sorcerer's Stone's maximum energy output per diem.
There is virtually no excess to speak of.
But without the faeries doing their work,
the school will be unable to function.
I've got it! Aren't some of our graduates using Sorcerer's
Stones for farming and a shoe factory and such?
Why not ask them to share some energy?
If we request a little at a time, wouldn't that leave us with enough to satisfy the faeries for now?
We all have the same issue; nobody has any leftover energy.
We'll try every witch we can find!
That's hard labor!
We aged witches couldn't possibly...
Yes, perhaps we couldn't...
Huh?
I don't have the time for this...
Being young is suffering.
What?
Then Professor Ursula isn't here?
Yeah, she said she'll be back in two or three days.
We're stuck with this until she returns.
There's not much else we can do because of the strike.
What?
I used flavor magic to make it so disgusting
your eyes would pop out of your head.
That's weird.
Hey! Knock it off already, Sucy!
I said to stop!
We can't use magic?
Hey! Stop what you're doing, fairies!
Whoa!
They're putting up magic isolators to cut off the flow of magic from the Sorcerer's Stone!
What? That's a thing?!
Headmistress, what shall we do?
What is even going on?!
Oh yes, Croix was scheduled to arrive
today to fill the new teacher position.
Huh? She's our new teacher?!
Headmistress, it's been far too long.
You certainly came right in the middle of trouble.
What's this thing?
How is it flying? There shouldn't
be any magic available to it.
This is a sorcery unit created by utilizing magitronics.
Basically, you could call it an evolved broom.
An evolved broom?
How convenient.
Everyone, allow me to introduce to you
the new teacher of modern magic, Professor Croix.
Please come to my classroom if I piqued your interest.
We will contemplate the future of magic there!
Whoa! Are they going to clean up the entire sky next?!
The future... of magic?
It's getting worse.
Even the lights are out...
The strike isn't over yet.
But anyway, Professor Croix sure was cool.
I wonder what you learn in modern magic.
I heard from some of the girls who took it that they use tablets Professor Croix developed.
Wow, tablets?
This is a precursor to the impending apocalypse.
It most certainly is not.
You are forbidden to use items
such as those during lessons.
Also, I heard that you placed some sort of new-fangled machinery for personal use inside the New Moon Tower.
Are you referring to my research tools?
You'll be cursed!
I believe I won't.
Be that as it may!
Please do not add to the troubles already on our plate, Professor Croix.
It's cold!
It sucks that the heating's out.
Hey, hey, what's going on?!
Since there's no hot water, not being able to shower
has sapped everyone of their energy.
If we can't use magic, what'll happen to our classes?
Until the strike is over,
all lesson plans have been altered to memorizing spells!
I'll go talk to them!
They need to stop striking right away!
Lotte, be my interpreter!
Clean those ears and listen very closely to me!
Little Witch Academia
We must somehow mollify them
until Professor Ursula returns.
Hello, it must be rough out here in the cold weather.
You are to disband this instant!
Unity
Miss Kagari?
We demand an increased share of energy as our salary!
"We"?
I'm sorry. She tried to convince them to end their strike,
but ended up getting convinced by them instead.
We demand pay!
Unity
Let us use the Sorcerer's Stone!
That is quite enough!
Unity
I ask of you—what will you do if we lose Luna Nova?
Allowing witches to use the Sorcerer's Stone is necessary for the academy's continued existence.
Do you not all wish to continue working here?
Without your jobs, you will have no place left to live.
Are you willing to accept that?
Now, call off your strike this instant!
The bourgeoisie is blind to the concerns of the working class!
Unity
Akko?!
She has a huge and luxurious room all to herself.
Unity
That's right, she's an aristocrat! Aristocrat!
Aristocrat! Aristocrat! Aristocrat!
To think I had revised my opinion of you after the Samhain Festival.
Unfortunately, I seem to have been mistaken.
You're always looking down on others!
Unity
You have no idea how hard the people of
the lower classes are working!
Unity
This is a waste of time.
There are other things that require your attention more urgently.
Unity
We'll never be able to use magic again at this rate.
Are you fine with that, Akko?
It's not like I want that, either...
Unity
But the faeries say they can't even
live without the Sorcerer's Stone.
Right, they couldn't even move back when the dragon stole it before.
They need it a lot more than we do,
but they're making do with what little they have.
We witches use ninety percent of its energy.
This is a magic school. It's only natural
that witches would need to use magic.
I know, but...
You know how I want to become a witch like Chariot and use amazing magic to make people happy, right?
But I don't want to trouble anyone just for that cause.
Unity
It just wouldn't be fair if someone else had to bear my burden...
You've only got yourself to blame for trying to think so hard.
I'm starving!
Unity
But I'm glad. You're actually
giving this proper thought.
What's this?
"We made some soup, so please help yourselves."
Unity
Thanks! I'll gladly have some!
This was made from frog warts and bat eyes.
Unity
Huh?
Was it my imagination?
I call to order the negotiation with the labor union!
Unity
Miss Kagari?
I ended up becoming their General Secretary.
My, you're really climbing the ranks!
Unity
Oh please...
We demand a ten-percent increase of our energy allotment!
T-Ten percent?!
In addition, we request a separate energy allowance for health and living requirements—
We refuse!
At least think about it!
Unity
Realistically speaking, it is impossible!
Unfortunately, energy isn't something you can create.
What if you could?
Unity
Professor Croix!
Using the Sorcery Solution System
I'm developing, SSS for short,
we can create energy!
Unity
Sorcery?
Magic is weakening by the year!
Whatever shall we do if magic ever runs out completely?
But! If you install this SSS, you can say goodbye to such outdated worries!
The Sorcerer's Stone absorbs magic
from leylines before emitting it again.
Throughout the day, it continuously refines raw magic
and wastefully discharges the precious resource.
But we can convert the previously wasted energy into
another form for storage, maintenance, and efficient use!
That is the Sorcery Solution System!
That sounds very complex.
Assuage your fears, for magic can be used exactly as it has been.
You'll be able to ride brooms and perform summonings as you wish.
As proof, this sorcery unit is flying by the power of an SSS.
Unity
But isn't it expensive?
True, it does require a research expenditure.
Unity
But if we create a research lab at Luna Nova,
we'll be eligible for a government subsidy.
A subsidy?!
Therefore the net cost is zero!
Unity
Zero?!
It automatically collects energy from the Sorcerer's Stone while the witches are sleeping.
Unity
The energy is then converted
into a semipermanent form.
That would allow the witches and faeries
to fairly and equally use the energy.
Unity
Amazing! We approve of the Sorcerer Whatchamacallit!
We oppose.
Unity
What?!
We witches have a duty to uphold the traditions of Luna Nova passed down by our predecessors.
Professor Croix, at the risk of
sounding like a broken record,
Unity
please refrain from bringing modern machinery to our school.
End of discussion.
Tradition this, tradition that...
You can't blame them. It takes courage
to accept the new and unfamiliar.
Professor Croix...
Oh, I forgot! Thank you for saving me when you got here.
I'm Kagari Atsuko.
Modern magic is incredible! It left me speechless!
Then, Miss Kagari?
Please call me Akko!
Come visit me during my next modern magic lesson.
Sure!
Please!
We'll keep it a secret, so let us take just one shower!
Look, we even brought your favorite thing.
Will you let us take a shower?
It's cold!
What's going on?!
Stop!
Don't!
Don't touch me!
What's happening?!
Looks like fun.
They're really angry.
"Flame faerie is hurt.
Never forgive the witches."
You're kidding!
W-We understand, we'll accept your demands!
Akko, what are you planning?
We have to release the magic!
Heave, heave! Ho, ho!
Something's here.
Hear us out! The teachers accepted our conditions!
We won! The strike is over!
Please, let us use magic!
Lotte, do your thing!
What's he saying?
This faerie has no emotions.
I can't tell what he's thinking at all.
It's as if...
it's a machine.
Akko!
Activating system!
Begin emosearch!
Emotional pattern: red.
Heleiphaea Gryffa!
Wh-What is...
Breathe life once more into the injured faerie!
Fuel spirit injection!
Looks like he's in good spirits again.
Are you okay?
Any injuries?
No!
I'm glad.
This is the Sorcery Whoseawhatsit?
It really saved the day, Headmistress.
So it truly can use magic even without a Sorcerer's Stone, can it?
Don't forget about the subsidy!
Where did the faeries even get something like this?
Mail order?
In any case, the issues have been resolved.
Good work.
Preparations are complete.
"The academy reconciled with the labor union on the condition of installing the Sorcery Solution System.
In addition, a research lab was created
in the New Moon Tower to support it,
and the restriction on digital devices has been lifted.
Thus marks the dawn of a new era for Luna Nova."
No way, I can't believe this!
Huh? You don't like that?
Why this picture?!
That part?
Anyway, isn't Professor Croix just the coolest?
Headmistress!
I apologize for the delay!
Here they are.
Well done, Professor Ursula.
But we don't actually need those anymore.
What?!
The times are a-changing.
Well, no matter.
The fuss has died down, so now I can
have a nice, long chat with Akko.
About the truth.
Akko!
It really is convenient, isn't it?
The Sorcery Whatchamacallit!
Sorcery Solution System.
Croix?!
Even though I just learned another spell
oboetate no jumon ja
The things I want to do are still out of reach
kanawanai koto bakari dakedo
My skills are no match for my fantasies
imeeji suru no wa ima yori takaku
Yet my heart leaps out to meet them
tobitachi odoridasu kokoro
Breaking my tiny shell one layer at a time
chiisana kara nandomo nugisutete
I won't let my reckless abandon go to waste
gamushara dake de owarasenai
I'll leave who I was yesterday behind
kinou no watashi wo koeru you ni
Unfurling my transparent wings to the sky
toumei na tsubasa habatakasetara
I feel I can get closer to the tomorrow of my ideals
akogareteta ashita e kitto chikadzukeru ki ga shiterunda
Putting together the shards of a starry sky that I found
mitsuketa hoshizora no kakera musunde
I'll keep on chasing my dream to learn even more
motto shiritai yume wo ou yo