Akko disappeared?
There was a bit of a commotion in town,
and then we got separated.
Still, she's way too late!
A commotion, you say...
We spent a lot of time looking for her after that...
Then we checked whether she'd already come back, but she's not here either.
What should we do?
Do you think something happened to her?
Calm down. Could you please tell me what happened in more detail?
I understand. Our first course of action
should be informing Professor Ursula.
Yeah, probably.
I'll go tell her now.
Allow me to go. Akko may come back at any time.
Please wait for her in your room.
Okay. Thanks, Diana.
Take action!
Raise your hands!
Release the shutter on this scene like it's the moment of a lifetime
"One scene" shattaa kiru you ni setsuna wo utsushite
Turn it into a story that can speak for itself
tsukuriageru na mo naki hitotsu no story
Every single one of us can become a hero
watashitachi wa dare datte hiiro ni nareru
The possibility hides within us, don't you think?
kanousei wo himeta sonzai, sou deshou?
Your first steps forward can be small to start
fumidashita ippo ga hajime wa chiisaku tatte
Keep it up, and we can create a brand-new future
kitto atarashii mirai wo egaki daserunda
I'll always believe no matter what
donna toki mo shinjiteiru yo
In this world and in my dreams
kono sekai wo, jibun no yume wo
This uncontrollable urge is compelling me to begin
osaekirenai shoudou wa hajimari no aizu datte sa
Telling me to go out and find the me I haven't become yet
mada watashi ga shiranai watashi ni deau tame
So off I go!
kimeta yo
Don't be afraid to try again
osorenaide try again
Keep getting up and fly away
nando datte fly away
It's showtime!
Oh I don't want to miss a thing
Starting from here
kono basho kara
Little Witch Academia
I've had a dream ever since I was a child.
It was to become a witch who could make everyone smile.
I had no doubt it would come true.
But when it came to the actual magic,
I stumbled from one blunder to the next.
You've gotta believe. A believing heart is magic.
"No matter how much I may fail, I still want
to give people a fun and exciting time."
It was that feeling that kept me going.
And then, as I stayed true to my belief,
a staff of seven stars appeared before me.
If I could revive the seven Words with that staff,
I would obtain the world reconstruction magic, Grand Triskelion.
I had no doubt it was a fantastic magic,
able to bring joy to people's hearts!
Following Professor Woodward's guidance,
I searched for the seven Words.
Nothing went wrong all the way through reviving the sixth Word.
However, the final Word just wouldn't appear.
"I want to make everyone smile even more!
That will definitely allow me to revive the seventh!"
"A believing heart is your magic!"
That's some wonderful magic.
How do you like the idea of showing it to an even bigger audience?
Bringing smiles to more and more people!
I started traveling the world.
But with time, their responses began to change.
You need to invent some magic that'll up the excitement!
It's been quite the while, Chariot.
Croix!
I want to live up to their expectations and show them magic like they've never seen before.
What do you think about trying out the magic I'm currently researching?
Though it's still at an experimental stage.
What kind of magic?
Dream Fuel Spirit.
It turns the audience's dreaming energy into magic.
Chariot will then be able to use still greater magic,
in turn giving people even bigger dreams to see.
Dream Fuel Spirit raised my magic to a new level.
It was a huge success!
Did you see all their smiles?
Yes, that was marvelous.
This power is incomparable.
Huh?
With this much, the magic world
will once more be reinvigorated.
What?
In exchange for that, there's no need to be concerned over a few trifling sacrifices.
Sacrifices?
Dream Fuel Spirit absorbs the dreaming energy
of those it's used on, converting it into magic.
You never... said anything about that.
I didn't? Well, it wasn't even worth mentioning.
Y-You can't be...
What happens to the people you absorb from?
Nothing much. They merely lose a certain ability.
What's the problem with normal people losing an ability they'd ordinarily never even use?
Well, I guess there might be an issue if a child
from a magic lineage was sitting in the audience,
but why would any self-respecting witch
allow them to see a heretic like you?
Why, Croix?
If I had known that, I never would have used it!
I never asked for that kind of power.
You never asked for power?
Enough with your naiveté!
This is exactly why you still haven't gotten the final Word!
You have a responsibility as the chosen one.
A duty to obtain the world reconstruction magic!
And yet!
What the hell are you thinking,
wasting your time on these ridiculous shows?!
Croix...
What is a "Shiny Rod" supposed to be?!
Don't give it such a strange name.
Are you telling me the Claimh Solais
chose you just for this?
This utter absurdity?!
Why...
Why were you chosen...
I don't know either.
All I want to do is use magic to make people happy.
That's all I can do...
You don't understand a thing.
Your shows will soon be shunned and forgotten.
Magic will... be forgotten.
I can't take the same path as you.
I must go my own way.
Goodbye.
After that, I stopped using Dream Fuel Spirit.
What are you doing?
People are always yearning for something new, something bigger...
Magic will...
...be forgotten.
Didn't you bring any new magic?
I want more fun magic!
Something more!
Noctu Orfei Aude Fraetor!
Incredible...
Crap—amnesia magic!
This is Diana.
I have an urgent message regarding Akko.
Can I help you?
Akko has yet to return from her trip into town.
Do you know anything about that?
Did you not meet Akko in the city?
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
While we're at it, may we continue our conversation from this afternoon?
I'm a little tied up with other things right now.
Then I'll get right to the point.
There are no records of a student by the name of Ursula Callistis attending this school.
Your real name is Chariot du Nord.
You are Shiny Chariot, correct?
Yes, that's right.
You ran into Akko earlier, didn't you?
Please tell me what happened!
Fine.
Those who saw your show became unable to use magic?
I hurt Akko.
And you didn't chase after her?
Are you saying you left her alone in that condition and returned by yourself?
Professor Ursula!
I...
I can no longer be of help to Akko.
What are you saying?! Now is the time she most needs you by her side!
I'm sorry, but there's something else I must be doing.
How can anything possibly be more important
than worrying about Akko right now?!
I understand. That's enough.
We'll find Akko.
I'm more disappointed in what you did today
than all that you've done in the past.
Please... take care of Akko.
Little Witch Academia
Akko still hasn't come back?
Yes, she may still be somewhere out in town.
Did you learn anything new?
That can't be...
You're kidding. It's really Chariot's fault that Akko can't fly?
There's no chance Akko could've imagined that.
You don't think she's not planning to come back...
Of course not!
Akko would never leave over something like that...
Y-You're right.
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
But how does Professor Ursula know all that?
I'll tell you in due time.
The most important thing now is to find Akko.
We're going too!
Me too!
Well, then we'll start looking around the terminal.
Understood. I will start my search from the Leyline.
Got it. Let's go!
Akko!
I swear, if Akko doesn't come back,
she'd better hope I don't find her.
Seriously, Akko's a genius at making people run themselves ragged.
Sucy!
I couldn't find her at the terminal.
She's not on this side either.
Maybe she's not in the area.
We should check out the plaza, just in case.
Come on.
I hate this.
I don't want Akko to go away!
I've never even considered the thought that Akko might leave.
What should I do? If Akko never comes back...
It'll be okay.
Akko's an idiot.
She'd never think about anything that difficult.
Yeah...
Don't worry. She'll come back moaning
that she's hungry, like she always does.
Akko!
Have you warmed up somewhat?
You must have been freezing. I was shocked
to see you sitting out there in the cold.
I asked Professor Ursula about what happened with you and Chariot.
Come to think of it, there was something I wanted to show you.
The Chariot premium card...
I believe you were collecting them as well.
Why do you have this?
Because I used to look up to Shiny Chariot as a child too.
Huh? You looked up to her?
I was infatuated.
At that point, those from the world of magic
were already looking down on her.
I couldn't collect these cards but in secret.
Pressure from those around me made me give up on seeing a show myself.
Countless nights, I could only dream of seeing Chariot's show.
But one day, my mother arranged for me to see one overseas, where nobody would notice.
Huh? You went that far to see her?
Yes, to your country.
Then you were at that show too?
It was fantastic.
I can remember that night as clearly as if it were yesterday.
There was a time when Diana became
completely unable to use magic.
Does that mean that when you became unable to use magic...
You knew about that?
Yeah, Andrew told me.
He also said you never gave up and worked hard until you got your magic back.
I see.
What happened to us was an unfortunate accident.
But I will not give you my sympathy.
I am the greatest proof that it is possible to regain that lost power.
Of course you are, Diana.
Even though your ability was sucked up too,
you worked hard and became an amazing witch.
But here I am, still unable to even fly.
Do you know why I didn't give up?
Because you had to become the Cavendish family head?
That is one part of it, of course.
But as a young girl, that reason alone could not have compelled me to keep going.
I am the same as you.
Huh?
I, too, was charmed by Shiny Chariot's magic.
It was the first time I saw Chariot's magic.
My heart was racing with pure happiness.
I felt the preciousness of magic deep inside me.
Chariot filled me with emotion.
That in itself was my greatest support back then.
Unfortunately, the more I learned of magic and the more aware I became of the expectations placed on me,
the further my heart grew away from Chariot.
"I can't continue with these childish dreams."
Telling myself I had to become an adult, I closed the lid.
Even so, the true reason I entered Luna Nova
was because it was the school Chariot went to.
When we first met, I couldn't stand you at all.
Huh?
You went around telling everyone you loved Chariot,
and your grades and magic couldn't have been worse.
You always acted without thinking
and caused trouble for everyone.
But at the same time,
you were able to do things I couldn't.
Your magic had a mysterious charm to it.
I was envious of you.
You were?
Thinking back, the reason I tried to leave Luna Nova
might have been to run away from you.
I wanted to avoid facing the reality of you being far closer to Chariot than I was.
Diana...
I will give this to you.
Accept it with the meaning of the card.
"A believing heart is your magic."
I believe as well.
I believe in your believing heart.
Your magic is stronger than anyone else's.
Lotte?
I found you, Akko!
Wai—Lotte?
You won't go anywhere, right?
Huh?
You won't quit school, right?
Lotte...
Of course! I'll never quit, not until
I become a splendid witch!
Really?
Really! I'm sorry I made you worry.
Thank you...
You here, Akko?!
Amanda! Constanze and Jasminka too.
Akko says she isn't going anywhere!
See? That's exactly what I told you.
Come in, you kids must be freezing.
Drink up! It's on the house.
Thanks!
Hey, Akko, don't tell me you were crying.
I wasn't crying! The cold just made my eyes—
You're full of it. I can still see the tears.
That's not it!
No, you certainly were crying.
Perfect timing.
I was just thinking about how I wanted you to see this.
What is that?
Noir Fuel Spirit.
I harvested it from all around the country.
But I couldn't have done this without you.
It was your Dream Fuel Spirit experiments
that helped me complete this.
I figured you deserve some gratitude.
It's time. My plan has entered its final stage.
I won't let you.
I swear I will stop you.
Even though I just learned another spell
oboetate no jumon ja
The things I want to do are still out of reach
kanawanai koto bakari dakedo
My skills are no match for my fantasies
imeeji suru no wa ima yori takaku
Yet my heart leaps out to meet them
tobitachi odoridasu kokoro
Breaking my tiny shell one layer at a time
chiisana kara nandomo nugisutete
I won't let my reckless abandon go to waste
gamushara dake de owarasenai
I'll leave who I was yesterday behind
kinou no watashi wo koeru you ni
Unfurling my transparent wings to the sky
toumei na tsubasa habatakasetara
I feel I can get closer to the tomorrow of my ideals
akogareteta ashita e kitto chikadzukeru ki ga shiterunda
Putting together the shards of a starry sky that I found
mitsuketa hoshizora no kakera musunde
I'll keep on chasing my dream to learn even more
motto shiritai yume wo ou yo