Say, Mother, won't you tell me that story again?
The tale you love so dearly?
"The Wise Woman Beatrix".
The witch who started the Cavendish family!
That's right.
And also one of the Nine Olde Witches.
Sybilladura Lelladybura.
When traditional and modern powers mingle,
the gate to an unseen world will open.
Traditional and modern powers?
Mother!
Diana, I believe that you can be the one to open that gate.
You can create a new future for the Cavendish name.
Mother...
Take action!
Raise your hands!
Release the shutter on this scene like it's the moment of a lifetime
"One scene" shattaa kiru you ni setsuna wo utsushite
Turn it into a story that can speak for itself
tsukuriageru na mo naki hitotsu no story
Every single one of us can become a hero
watashitachi wa dare datte hiiro ni nareru
The possibility hides within us, don't you think?
kanousei wo himeta sonzai, sou deshou?
Your first steps forward can be small to start
fumidashita ippo ga hajime wa chiisaku tatte
Keep it up, and we can create a brand-new future
kitto atarashii mirai wo egaki daserunda
I'll always believe no matter what
donna toki mo shinjiteiru yo
In this world and in my dreams
kono sekai wo, jibun no yume wo
This uncontrollable urge is compelling me to begin
osaekirenai shoudou wa hajimari no aizu datte sa
Telling me to go out and find the me I haven't become yet
mada watashi ga shiranai watashi ni deau tame
So off I go!
kimeta yo
Don't be afraid to try again
osorenaide try again
Keep getting up and fly away
nando datte fly away
It's showtime!
Oh I don't want to miss a thing
Starting from here
kono basho kara
Little Witch Academia
I'm starving...
I hope they still have some leftovers.
And you are absolutely certain that we cannot convince you to reconsider, Diana?
I am truly grateful for the kindness you have shown me.
However, I have made my decision
after thorough deliberation.
Diana's going to leave Luna Nova?!
She got a letter from home yesterday.
And then, when she read it, she suddenly said she'd return home to become the family head.
What's up with that?
The Cavendish family has a lot going on...
There have been some awful rumors
going around, especially as of late.
But that doesn't mean Diana has to quit school!
Now's the only time she can!
Huh?
She says the ritual to pass the title down can only be held now,
and if she misses it, there won't be
another chance for several years.
Everyone expected her to inherit that position eventually...
But to think she wouldn't even get to graduate first...
And we just heard...
That late tonight...
She's going to leave Luna Nova!
Today?
Professor!
Akko?
Diana... Diana said...
That she's going to quit school!
Did you know?
Yes. The Cavendish family has been
facing issues for quite some time now.
And the teachers tried to stop her, right?
We did, but...
Diana's not really going to leave, right?
That can't happen.
Akko...
Akko's late.
She's probably getting chewed out by Finneran again.
Is that her?
Huh?
Oh, she's coming back.
Ak...ko?
Something must've happened.
Diana!
Are you serious about leaving?
But why? It isn't like you to leave something unfinished!
I heard your family's having some trouble, but does that really mean you need to go back yourself?
Let your parents handle it.
There's no reason for you to quit!
It shouldn't be too late even if you wait
until your school years are over.
Won't you change your mind?
Hey!
Say something! Don't just ignore me!
Those who depart Luna Nova are to do so secretly,
in the dead of night. That is our custom.
Even speaking to you like this is against the rules.
Now that you understand, withdraw at once!
Who cares about customs?!
Anyway, I won't accept you just up and leaving!
I had almost forgotten your disposition.
This attitude of yours, the disdain you display
for tradition and history, truly infuriates me.
In any case, I do not recall requiring your permission to drop out.
I-I can't just sit idly by while my rival's running away.
I have never once viewed you as my rival.
If you have vented to your satisfaction—
Is this really what you want, Diana?
You know, coming to Luna Nova
has always been my dream.
I idolized Chariot, so it was my dream to go to the same school as her.
But now, that dream has grown.
Everything I experienced and all the people I met here are important to me.
I love everything here just as much as I love Chariot!
Don't you love Luna Nova too, Diana?
Can you really throw it all away so easily?
This is a house of learning. Everyone must leave the nest eventually.
My time simply came sooner.
I am the heiress of the long-standing House of Cavendish.
And it is my duty to protect it.
But why do you have to go so far?!
I'm hardly surprised to see you not understand, given how ignorant you seem to be of past wonders.
S-Still...
Instead of worrying about me, shouldn't you be
putting more effort into finding the Words?
You know about the Words?
Yes, I learned of them by way of my own research.
The Grand Triskelion, sealed by the Nine Olde Witches.
I wanted to know exactly what it was.
If I were to acquire its power,
I could save a great many people,
not to mention restoring the dignity of the magic world.
Just as my mother wished...
Then why don't you look for the Words too, Diana?!
Only the person chosen by the Shiny Rod can do so!
Akko, you are the chosen one!
The... one?
Tia Freyre!
Apply yourself, and become a witch worthy of the Grand Triskelion's Words.
I did not dislike any of this, neither the professors I had nor the friends I made.
Diana!
Diana...
Farewell, Luna Nova.
Professor Ursula!
Professor, please tell me where to find the Cavendish family!
What do you plan to do there?
Diana has an iron will.
I know that.
Even so, I must...
They live in Wedinburgh.
Thank you so much!
Lotte, Sucy.
Here.
Take this too.
You're going to bring Diana back, right?
Get going already.
Yeah! I'll be back!
Little Witch Academia
Welcome home.
Anna, thank you for the timely warning.
My sincerest apologies. I had wished to hold her off at least until your graduation.
Enrolling was originally my own selfish request.
I should have resolved myself to do this sooner.
It had always been your dream...
This much was enough.
I have more than satisfied my desires at this point.
That said...
I did not expect to see this state of disrepair.
The majority of the servants have already left.
Only a few remain.
Well, well, I was wondering who it could be at this hour.
If it isn't Diana.
When I heard someone's footsteps,
I assumed it was a burglar.
I apologize for startling you, Aunt Daryl.
Oh, you certainly did surprise me, arriving without so much as a call.
Not to mention at this time of night.
I wasn't aware you were on holiday.
There is something that concerns me, so I will be staying for the time being.
I couldn't be happier to hear that.
We'll be hosting a visitor who you are well acquainted with today.
It will surely prove to be an entertaining dinner party.
A visitor?
This is hardly the time for an extended conversation.
We can discuss the details later, at our leisure.
Yes, I concur, Aunt.
Then let us speak again later.
I can't walk any more...
And I'm so hungry...
Hitchhike!
It's over.
I was wondering why you looked familiar.
Then it turns out you were that witch who ruined our party.
Ruined? It did take a strange turn,
but our guests sang nothing but praises of it.
In any case, it should be a simple matter
for a witch to fly to Wedinburgh.
Well, that's...
What does it matter? We were
on our way there ourselves.
You can chalk this encounter up to a whim of fate.
When the referee counted the goal just before the end of regulation time, our national supporters' rage erupted.
The irate supporters turned into a rioting mob,
attacking the opposing nation's supporters
and throwing the stadium into chaos.
I am honestly ashamed that a silly ball game would turn into this uproar.
Every single one of them is a mindless buffoon.
Hey.
Why are you and your dad going to Diana's house?
We were invited.
It seems they have something to show us.
Oh yeah, you two are related.
That we are.
Anyway, what brings you all the way out to the Cavendish estate?
I came to bring Diana back!
Isn't that...
Thank you for honoring us with your visit!
We have been awaiting you, Lord Hanbridge.
You must be exhausted after your long journey.
Please, come inside.
I am so truly grateful that you've come.
Minister of State Paul Hanbridge,
as well as the ever-handsome Andrew!
Who might this be?
U-Um, my name is Kagari Atsuko.
Akko!
Diana!
My, is she a friend of yours?
Why are you here?!
I still haven't accepted it!
And what does it matter whether you have or not?!
Honestly, you must be touched in the head.
And would you care to explain
why you've arrived together?
Why hello, Diana. We just happened to pick her up off the side of the road.
Carter, lead them inside.
As you wish.
This way.
Bye.
You...
Are you one of Diana's friends? I'm not well acquainted with the lineages of Oriental witches.
I'm not from a witch lineage.
What?!
She does indeed feel like a poor imitation of a witch, doesn't she?
Oh, how the mighty Luna Nova has fallen.
Is she one of Diana's fans?
Perhaps she's come in an attempt to worm her way into the Cavendish family.
Regardless, she is no more than an uninvited guest.
I trust you can find the door on your own.
What's that—
She is as much of a witch as I am!
I will not tolerate such a disrespectful tone towards my guest.
Come with me.
Wait! Hang on, Diana!
You're pulling my arm off!
Young Lady...
Diana, stop!
What's with their egotistic attitude?
They're like three times as bad as you! Besides—
Akko!
I am sending you home first thing tomorrow morning.
Just keep quiet until then.
Anyway, you've got a nice mansion here!
Miss!
Yes?!
Please listen to the Young Lady's request.
Okay...
Ow!
This is anguishing me.
We did not diligently store this dress away only to lay it out again for some girl from who knows where.
Um, I can hear everything you're saying.
And I am saying it for you to hear me.
I do not mind, Anna.
Your mother prepared this dress specially for your eleventh birthday.
Eleventh?!
I can no longer wear it even if I wanted to.
And who knows what Aunt would say had she remained in that dirty uniform.
That may be the case...
I don't want to admit it, but it's a perfect fit.
Just let it go, Anna.
That aside...
So this is Diana's room?
It's basically what I expected...
Oh, except for that.
Diana, did you use to have a soft spot for cutesy stuff?
Don't touch that!
S-Sorry.
I'll head out first. Anna, please take care of the rest.
Of course.
Goodness, I've never met a witch so undeserving of care before.
Are you really a student of Luna Nova?
Just leave me alone if I annoy you so much.
That is out of the question. The Young
Lady has tasked me with this job.
Goody me, is that so?
The motto of the Cavendish family is "Affection".
Be grateful for the Young Lady's kindheartedness.
Kindhearted? Diana? You must be jesting.
I can assure you that the Young Lady
is kind. She takes after her mother.
Diana's mom?
Diana's becoming the family head.
Then, that means...
She lost her parents at a tender age.
I didn't know...
And I said all sorts of things to her...
Are you planning to take the Young Lady back to Luna Nova?
Of course!
I'm afraid you will have to give up on that. If the
Young Lady does not become the family head now,
the House of Cavendish will perish!
That couldn't possibly—
It can, and it will!
If Madam Daryl, the proxy head, continues to do as she wishes, the scant remainder of our assets will vanish!
The Young Lady must take her place as the rightful heir and return the family to its former glory as the new head!
Is that woman really so horrible?
Cheers to a splendid night!
Cheers to a splendid night.
Now then, Daryl. I presume there was a reason you invited me to the manor.
You are correct, Paul. That will expedite the process.
I'm certain there will be at least
one thing to catch your fancy.
These are?
Various items that I would appreciate you purchasing, rather than anyone else.
This is a candle holder made from the scales of the seventh Cavendish head's favorite mermaid.
This is a mythril chess set.
And finally:
The Tapestry of Beatrix!
Wh—
Beatrix?
The inheritance of the first Cavendish witch,
none other than one of the Nine Olde Witches, Beatrix the Affectionate!
What?!
Diana is descended from one of the Nine Olde Witches?!
Nine Olde Witches? Is that really worth getting so surprised over?
You must forgive me, as I cannot grasp the value this holds.
If this is all you wanted, I see no reason to overstay my welcome.
W-Wait!
Paul, please, couldn't you take at least one?
O-Oh, Andrew, didn't any catch your interest?
Yes, I'll give you a discount!
Enough!
How much more must you trample over the
Cavendish history until you are satisfied?!
There you go again.
How is your obsession with the old working out for you?
My sister spent all her time helping others for free because of those traditions.
And how did that turn out for your mother?!
The only reason our house has continued to hold out this long is because of all the work I'm doing.
All you've done is sell off the priceless and precious things that our ancestors left us for money!
Have you no pride as a Cavendish?!
Can your "pride" put food on the table?
You really are your mother's daughter in that regard.
The age where magic reigned supreme has ended.
You, too, will have to accept this reality in due time.
I am fully aware of your intentions, Aunt.
As I suspected, I can no longer leave this house in your hands.
I see. So that's why you returned in such a rush.
What do you mean?
I thought the ritual to become the family head
could only be held on a night when the stars align?
And tonight is that very night, coming just once every several years.
What?!
Tonight, I shall conduct the ritual in the shrine, and once and for all...
Become the Cavendish family head!
Even though I just learned another spell
oboetate no jumon ja
The things I want to do are still out of reach
kanawanai koto bakari dakedo
My skills are no match for my fantasies
imeeji suru no wa ima yori takaku
Yet my heart leaps out to meet them
tobitachi odoridasu kokoro
Breaking my tiny shell one layer at a time
chiisana kara nandomo nugisutete
I won't let my reckless abandon go to waste
gamushara dake de owarasenai
I'll leave who I was yesterday behind
kinou no watashi wo koeru you ni
Unfurling my transparent wings to the sky
toumei na tsubasa habatakasetara
I feel I can get closer to the tomorrow of my ideals
akogareteta ashita e kitto chikadzukeru ki ga shiterunda
Putting together the shards of a starry sky that I found
mitsuketa hoshizora no kakera musunde
I'll keep on chasing my dream to learn even more
motto shiritai yume wo ou yo