The Nine Olde Witches sealed the Grand Triskelion within Arcturus Forest.
Only the seven Words and the staff bearing the seven stars can break the seal.
Early morning lessons, day seven. Are you ready, Akko?
Yes!
Monkey.
Metamorphie Faciesse!
Eek!
Eek?
N-Not too bad.
Next, an elephant.
Metamorphie Faciesse!
G-Good, you're doing well.
Wha—wait!
Oh? Oh no no!
Get away! Shoo, shoo!
Professor Ursula, thanks again.
I think I had it perfectly at the start!
S-Sure...
I'll keep practicing, and get better little by little.
And the moment I master metamorphosis magic...
I'll become a Moonlit Witch, like Chariot!
Moonlit Witch
Chariot was chosen as the Moonlit Witch
during Luna Nova's Samhain Festival.
Moonlit Witch...
It's proof that you're the best witch around.
I heard she earned it after showing off her miraculous metamorphosis magic.
Shouldn't you know that, Professor?
Y-Yes, I do know!
That's what happened. Right, definitely.
The Samhain Festival will be here soon.
I'll train my hardest and try to inch closer to Chariot!
Now then, what should I transform into tomorrow...
Akko revived the first Word as well.
With this, she has also revived the second.
There are seven Words of Arcturus in total.
Revive the remaining Words.
Chariot.
You will aid her.
I'll become the Moonlit Witch!
Here where our long journey has finally led us
kakedashita hibi ni yukitsuita kono basho
We can push open the door
fureta tobira hiraite
In the footsteps of our dreams far beyond the stars
hoshizora no kanata yume no ashiato
Pick up the pieces with a song
hiroiatsume utau yo
Keep the destination of your dreams nestled in your heart
yume ga kaketeku basho ima mo kokoro ni himete
And envelop the night
yoru wo tsutsumikomu
Cast a magic spell
mahou kakete
And start to dance
odoridasu
The landscape looks like it's burning brilliantly
yaketsuita you ni irodzuita fuukei wa
But you can't see it fallen on the ground
koronda kurai ja tokenai kara
The world will keep on turning
sekai wa tsudzuku yo
Embrace the moment as if it'll never come again
hakanai mama no ima wo dakishimete
Let's keep walking as we are with the light in our sights
kawaranai mama jikan to hikari mitsumete aruiteku
Little Witch Academia
Extra! Extra!
The witches invited to the Samhain
Festival have been announced!
The rock star, Miss Marjolaine?!
Minister Dorlin from the East Mogiana Republic!
And Madame Ural too! Impressive lineup this year.
Madame Ural is a Nobel Laureate in literature and considered the leading authority on magic novels.
Look at all the witches from around the world!
I'm so excited! The Samhain Festival is going to be amazing!
Doesn't Akko know?
How am I supposed to tell her now?
I can't wait to meet all those witches from faraway places!
On the upcoming day of October 31st,
we will be holding the Samhain Festival,
a tradition spanning back sixteen hundred years.
This is our opportunity to demonstrate the might and mettle of Luna Nova to alumnae from around the world.
All students are to prepare
displays of magic in their teams.
This was offered during the previous Samhain Festival.
Boiling of toads for enchantments.
Memorizing ten thousand incantations.
Ancient dark dance.
A full course medieval magic dinner.
Seriously?
The Samhain Festival is this lame?
At the close of the Samhain Festival, the most exceptional witch will be chosen.
She will be granted the title of Moonlit Witch.
Chariot was chosen at the Moonlit Witch!
We will now assign Samhain Festival duties to the teams.
Each team, please send one representative up to draw your lot.
Who should do it?
You, right?
I can't! I have the worst luck in lotteries!
Well, so do I...
Hey! You kids are in charge of fireworks!
Fireworks magic?!
Lucky you...
Already taken, huh.
You ladies shall do the decorations.
That's okay, I guess.
Your team is assigned to summoning.
Summoning?!
That's the showpiece of the Festival!
Hmph. You maggots get cleaning duty.
Cleaning duty?
The remaining teams should send their representatives at once!
We need to pick something.
Go do it, Akko.
There's no way!
Representative of that team, get up here now.
Sucy! No, Lotte!
Hurry!
Akko!
Um... this one?
No, I've got a bad feeling. Maybe...
Choose now, or I'll be choosing which of your nails to tear out!
Oh, fine!
You can be the sacrifices.
Sacrifices?
What kind of duty is that?
You want to know what the sacrifices do?
This pot contains an age-old ghost,
"Bachoalawy the Bewailing".
Bachoalawy the Bewailing?
Bachoalawy wakes with the midnight toll at the close of the Festival, wailing and flailing about.
That is when the sacrifices are offered.
After consuming them, Bachoalawy rests once more until the dawn of the next Samhain Festival.
The people on sacrifice duty die?!
There is no danger to your lives.
The sacrifices pass through the ghost's bowels and are safely excreted.
That's gross!
Sacrifice duty! It's like poetry!
You couldn't pick a more fitting role for Akko if you tried!
Silence!
We must focus on our Samhain Festival duties at hand. Save your prattle for later.
Exactly.
Also, Diana Cavendish.
You have been voted in as Luna Nova's youngest ever Samhain Festival committee chair.
How wonderful, Diana!
You're the best, Diana!
Ladies, rally around Diana and work together
to make this Samhain Festival a success.
Yes!
What's with the whole sacrifice duty?
Wasn't the Samhain Festival supposed to be fun?
So why do they have to include this ghost eating sacrifices stuff?
"Bachoalawy the Bewailing was a member of the royal family of the Book Kingdom in the second century BCE.
He spent his life in happiness surrounded by friends.
However, after he lost his friends in the last years of his life,
Bachoalawy mourned, saying 'This world has nothing but sorrow', and eventually turned into a ghost of bewailing."
What, just because of that?
It goes on to say that since he's crying even in
his sleep, he needs to eat sacrifices to sate his hunger.
Want one?
Come on, Bachoalawy!
It's your own fault for crying all the time!
You're making me feel like crying here, geez!
All my hard work trying to be the Moonlit Witch
like Chariot is going to go to waste.
Hang on, Akko. Are you really trying to be chosen as the Moonlit Witch?
Huh?
I don't think that's going to happen. Diana will likely end up being selected.
Yeah, probably.
Right?
And what makes you so sure?
Because Diana comes from a prestigious family.
She was born with talent running through her veins.
Does that mean you don't care about being the Moonlit Witch, Lotte?
I'm only here so that I can properly inherit my family's magic item shop.
What about you, Sucy?
The thought of passing through the inside of a ghost is giving me shivers!
Unbelievable...
You're telling me.
I can't believe it.
Right?!
I don't mean her.
You're the one I can't believe, wanting to be the Moonlit Witch when you can't even ride a broom.
That's true.
Yeah.
It can't be helped. Our duties fell to us randomly.
You got your hopes up by putting your head in the clouds.
Isn't this the perfect role for you?
Okay, we should prepare for our sacrifice duty meeting—
How can you all accept this?!
We're in charge of preparing the mirror for the Samhain Festival,
and there's something we need your advice about.
We collected all these mirrors, but we're not sure which one to use.
Could you pick the one you think is best?
Certainly. If these are our options...
Yes, this one contains the most magic power.
Unfortunately, it appears to be a prankster.
Polishing it with fairy powder should rein in its mischievous spirit.
Really?
I'll request the powder from the teachers.
Let's go pick it up together.
Thanks, Diana!
No wonder you're the committee chair!
We can always rely on you.
You're a shoe-in for Moonlit Witch!
Thank you. But we cannot yet say for sure
who will be selected as Moonlit Witch.
That was close!
Wait, why am I hiding?
You stubborn thing.
Be honest—you wish you were born with talent running through your veins.
Just like... this.
Wh-What the?!
D-Diana?
Oh, Diana.
The program you submitted for the Samhain Festival is impressively thorough.
U-Um...
Let's hold a meeting to discuss it.
Ow! The pain!
My stomach...
Oh, are you unwell?
Please—Please excuse me...
Oh, the pain...
Little Witch Academia
Why? Why did this happen?!
Diana!
We're in a bit of a pinch.
We can't figure out how to read the summoning spell by ourselves.
It's the one on this page.
Please, teach us!
W-Well...
D-Diana?
What a fine mess we are in.
Now that you two have laid eyes on this spell...
You are already under its curse.
Curse?!
If nothing is done, you will become eighty-two years old within twenty-four hours!
Eighty-two...
...years old?
N-No!
Save us, Diana!
Place both of your hands atop your head.
L-Like this?
Yes, very good. Now then...
Allow me to write the curse-breaking spell!
That should do it.
Now stay like that until tomorrow morning, and the curse will be lifted.
Just don't move until tomorrow morning?
Got it!
Bye, I have other business to attend to.
Thank you, Diana!
You're our savior!
Oh crap!
Well, if it isn't Lady Diana. Please forgive me.
I have just completed my cleaning of your room.
Oh, Diana's room must be this way.
Lady Diana.
Were you not returning to your room?
Y-Yes, I was! I was just on my way there now.
Too close, too close!
So this is where Diana and them live.
But sneaking into someone else's room
is definitely crossing a line.
Lady Diana.
I forgot to pass on a message for you.
As I was cleaning, your classmates
came by in a rush, looking for you.
I-I see. Thank you for telling me.
Goodbye.
Thank you again.
Just give me a break... huh?
Whoa...
Is this Diana's... diary?
No, stop! I definitely can't look at this!
Diana?
Y-Yes?!
I could hear her voice.
She must be back!
We're coming in.
Diana.
We need your help.
And how can I be of service?
It's about the Samhain Festival's Welcome Objet d'art.
We managed to get the statue of Great Witch Jennifer out here, but Professor told us to change her pose.
We want to use life-breathing magic
on it, but it's too hard for us.
You're our only hope.
L-Leave all your hopes in these capable hands of mine!
Th-There is not a thing that I cannot possibly do!
Thanks, Diana!
Stand back, everyone!
I-I can make this work! I've been practicing metamorphosis magic every day!
Th-This is nothing.
Ansolew Aroae!
Ansolew Aroae! Ansolew Aroae!
What's wrong with Diana?
Maybe she's having a bad day.
Isn't that the wrong spell?
Um...
Ansolew Airo!
Akko?!
H-Huh? I'm back?
Th-There's a very good reason behind this...
This was the work of the mirror,
I presume. It's easy to imagine.
Diana!
More importantly, I just had a meeting with Lotte and Sucy about your sacrifice duty.
Were you really so irresponsible as to forget?
S-Sorry. I just can't get on board
with being a sacrifice.
And you think that justifies your pointless prank?
Whenever something doesn't go your way,
you sulk and lose all motivation.
You play at being Chariot without the slightest knowledge of the history or tradition of magic.
You have no right to learn at this academy!
I am motivated! I'm serious about following in Chariot's footsteps!
Serious? You are?
I'll prove it to you.
That my passion for magic is the real deal!
Kagari Atsuko will be chosen as the Moonlit Witch during the Samhain Festival!
What's with her?
Who knows.
Diana sure is amazing.
"This world was once abundant
with the power of good magic.
In our current era, however, magic is ever dwindling.
I plan to seek the ultimate power of the Grand Triskelion to revitalize magic once more."
And what am I, compared to her?!
I heard you claimed that you'd become the Moonlit Witch in front of everyone.
Professor Ursula.
It just came out...
Even though I have zero chance of winning...
Zero?
I don't want to admit it, but everyone's right.
Diana is amazing.
She's more mature than I can even imagine being, and it's like she lives in a totally different world.
When I put myself next to her, all I see is a little kid.
Akko, it's true that you have a tendency to leap before you look that you should consider fixing.
But you know, I bet that even Chariot failed and worried and got discouraged more than you'd expect.
What would Chariot do?
The Big Dipper is so pretty.
Twinkling past the far edge of it is the North Star—Polaris.
Professor Ursula?
If Chariot was here, she might say something like this:
"Don't compare yourself to others.
Do what only you can do."
Watch over this for her.
O-Okay.
Profes—
Have a good night.
What only I can do...
This light...
Isn't this...
Just like back then, it's the Fountain of Polaris.
Tell me what only I can do.
Chariot!
You came!
This is from when someone was watching Chariot...
What happened? You're covered in dirt.
What am I to do with you?
Watch me!
Chariot looks like she's having so much fun.
I can feel power in my heart when I say this chant!
Arae Aryrha!
H-Huh?
I'm getting dizzy!
Geez... here.
Arae Aryrha!
Open your heart!
Chariot is so great.
Laugh with me!
Arae Aryrha!
Could it be that Chariot wasn't practicing to become the Moonlit Witch?
It was more pure...
Arae Aryrha...
Huh? A spell?
The staff...
That's it! This is what I can do!
I lost sight of everything else
muchuu ni natte oikaketeta
Chasing after a shooting star
nagareboshi tadotta saki ni
Longing to know more about this world
hirogaru sekai wo shiritakute
Just wishing won't make it come true
kanaetai to negau dake ja nai
But if you only push open the door
tobira wo akereba hora
You'll be one step closer
chikadzuite yukeru yo
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
The scenery may be ever-changing
keshiki wa kawatteiku kedo
But under this shining sky
kagayaku sora to
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
Thank you for staying by my side
soba ni itekurete arigatou
See you tomorrow
mata ashita ne
Until tomorrow...
Morning, right?