Outdated magics burdened by their dark history are quickly falling out of relevance in today's world.
I firmly believe that magic must reinvent itself to retain its place in our times.
For instance, take this leyline router.
Those are leylines.
Equipping a broom with this leyline router
will automatically couple it with a leyline,
Wow, amazing!
allowing the use of magic even outside
the range of a Sorcerer's Stone.
Did you come up with all of this
by yourself, Professor Croix?
Of course. I am the sole developer.
You're a genius!
Now then, activate your leyline routers and begin the simulation.
Isn't it incredible?
Damn, it's awesome!
Magic and science can actually go together!
Take action!
Raise your hands!
Release the shutter on this scene like it's the moment of a lifetime
"One scene" shattaa kiru you ni setsuna wo utsushite
Turn it into a story that can speak for itself
tsukuriageru na mo naki hitotsu no story
Every single one of us can become a hero
watashitachi wa dare datte hiiro ni nareru
The possibility hides within us, don't you think?
kanousei wo himeta sonzai, sou deshou?
Your first steps forward can be small to start
fumidashita ippo ga hajime wa chiisaku tatte
Keep it up, and we can create a brand-new future
kitto atarashii mirai wo egaki daserunda
I'll always believe no matter what
donna toki mo shinjiteiru yo
In this world and in my dreams
kono sekai wo, jibun no yume wo
This uncontrollable urge is compelling me to begin
osaekirenai shoudou wa hajimari no aizu datte sa
Telling me to go out and find the me I haven't become yet
mada watashi ga shiranai watashi ni deau tame
So off I go!
kimeta yo
Don't be afraid to try again
osorenaide try again
Keep getting up and fly away
nando datte fly away
It's showtime!
Oh I don't want to miss a thing
Starting from here
kono basho kara
Little Witch Academia
Oh, if it isn't Diana.
Are you doing more research?
You're always so dedicated.
I was reading through the registers, hoping to learn more about Professor Croix.
About Professor Croix?
It appears she was an excellent student.
She garnered acclaim for her magic development despite her young age.
Her thesis on the conversion of magic energy is particularly innovative.
That's right, Diana. She was a prodigy who could rival even you.
Her unmatched passion for magic was surely inspired
by some greater goal she wished to accomplish.
But back then, she gave the impression of a rather reserved person.
Were you personally acquainted with Professor Croix?
Sh-She was famous among all the students.
We weren't all that close,
but I heard of her exploits often.
Oh—I should be going now.
Not a quiet minute in the day!
Being a run-of-the-mill teacher sure is demanding...
Ursula... Ursula Callistis...
Her target must be the revived Claiomh Solais.
Croix...
Professor Croix is the best!
Strong, smart, and beautiful!
I've never seen a teacher like her before!
Oh yeah? "Modern magic", was it?
Ain't this a pain in the ass?
You're crazy—this is the best! Witches have gotta get with the times!
The future is now!
The future, huh...
But then there'd be no difference
between magic and science.
Thanks to the Sorcery-thingamajig she made, we'll be able to use magic even off school grounds!
There's an article on Professor Croix's past here.
"New professor Croix Meridies graduated from Luna Nova ten years ago."
"Praised as a 'prodigy' during her student years due to her exceedingly high marks,
she received various awards, including the Golden Ash Prize and the title of Moonlit Witch."
Moonlit Witch?! That's just like Chariot!
So Professor Croix was here at the same time as Chariot.
I wonder if they were rivals!
Girls, you shouldn't be playing with those toys here.
Professor, were the two of them rivals?
Not in the slightest.
Croix and Chariot were nowhere
near the same level back then.
Croix worked hard and put in the effort to improve her magic.
On the other hand, Chariot's grades were always in the gutter.
I will admit that Chariot had a natural sense for magic.
However, in addition to neglecting her studies,
she even committed the sin of using our sacred magic for her frivolous entertainment shows.
Now the public's got the wrong impression of magic, and her reputation among witches couldn't be worse.
In stark contrast to her,
Croix was seen as carrying the torch of magic into the future...
This is amazing! You need to check this out!
The site's got another eyewitness account on it.
No way, it's still flying around?
Just look!
Wow, LOL!
Ladies.
You are forbidden to use computers outside of the classroom.
Okay.
She called it a computer!
To think that she's adopted this magic science nonsense over the last decade...
I couldn't be more disappointed.
Huh?
Akko?
Professor Croix!
I didn't know you were Chariot's upperclassman!
Shiny Chariot!
Yes, I remember her. She called herself
"Chariot du Nord" back in those days.
She was a charming witch with the ability to attract the attention of everyone around her even as a child.
You're the first person I've heard praise Chariot
since I got here, so I'm getting a bit emotional.
They all say she went down the wrong path and stuff...
Chariot du Nord loved the sensational
and eye-popping kind of magic.
It earned her the scorn of the more orthodox witches.
But I prefer not to be bound by such dated preconceptions.
What she did was meaningful, regardless of the results of her actions.
Professor Croix, you really are the best!
Do you know why Chariot disappeared, or where she is now?
Are you really that interested in her?
I want to meet her so that I can thank her for giving me a dream and changing my life!
If you have anything that might be connected to her,
I could try analyzing it with my magic science.
Something connected to her?
Like for example...
The Shiny Rod! I have Chariot's staff!
I found it in Arcturus Forest!
In Arcturus Forest?
I'll go get it!
Hold on, Akko.
I don't have the necessary equipment in this classroom.
Meet me in the New Moon Tower after school.
In the New Moon Tower?
My laboratory is there.
I'll be able to analyze it there,
your... rod of something.
The Shiny Rod! I'll bring it for sure!
Oh, Professor.
Is Akko here?
She went to the New Moon Tower earlier.
The New Moon Tower?
I think Professor Croix asked her to bring the Shiny Rod or something.
Akko's in danger!
Where's Professor Croix's laboratory?
Will you lead me there?
Welcome, Akko.
I brought the Shiny Rod! Please analyze it!
Put it down there. I'll analyze it.
Oh, sure.
It appears the Shiny Rod reacts to high levels of spirit energy.
What does that mean?
Its magic activates in response to synchronization
with the wielder's emotional energy.
So, um...
In the past, it reacted to Chariot's heart. And now...
And now?
Has the Shiny Rod ever reacted to your emotions?
Y-Yes, it has.
Why does the Shiny Rod react to you,
and what situations cause it to activate?
Let me take a look for you.
I want to be like Chariot!
I'll become an amazing witch and touch the hearts of people around the world!
A believing heart is my magic!
Personality analysis.
Emotional pattern: yellow.
Predictive ability: zero.
Objectivity: zero.
Traits: impulsive, selfish, pushy, simple, clumsy, carefree.
So you've come, Chariot.
Little Witch Academia
Akko!
Vega Varulus!
Belga Veeda!
Quite a few years have passed since last we met, Chariot du Nord.
You were testing my powers, Croix!
Ten years ago, you shed the name of Shiny Chariot.
I had presumed your powers would have weakened considerably,
but it seems you've retained
a bit more than I had expected.
Akko!
What have you done to Akko?!
I simply collected some data.
Though it was all within expected parameters, considering what I learned
from secretly observing her over the past several months.
I couldn't glean anything worthwhile.
I have a pretty good idea of why you returned to Luna Nova now.
I have a pretty good idea of why
you returned to Luna Nova now.
You want to obtain the world reconstruction magic!
You haven't changed one bit, especially how you want everything for yourself!
You, however, have changed.
You're hardly a shadow of your former self.
To think I was once blinded by your brilliance.
In any case, regardless of what it is that I'm plotting,
you're powerless to stop me, Chariot.
No, I suppose I should call you Professor Ursula now.
Have you revealed your secret to her?
Even if I can never shine again...
I will protect Akko!
Akko...
Professor... Ursula?
Huh? Wasn't I in Professor Croix's laboratory?
You started to feel sick, so I brought you back here.
I was... having a dream.
Like Chariot was talking about something...
Reconstruction magic or something...
I've been meaning to speak to you about it eventually.
About the true meaning behind why the Shiny Rod revealed itself to you.
And about the "power to change the world" inherent in the world reconstruction magic, Grand Triskelion,
and what that magic actually does.
Only the Nine Olde Witches know everything.
The origin of the Grand Triskelion dates back several thousand years.
Back then...
Yggdrasil's branches encompassed the entire world.
Its branches held even the stars and planets in place.
It was from there that witches drew their infinite magic.
But its power withered with time.
Its decline signaled the end of the great age of magic.
Only traces of it remain as what we now call the leylines.
But that original power was passed down in secret.
The Nine Olde Witches sealed it within Arcturus.
That itself is the magic which can reconstruct the world—
Grand Triskelion.
"Grand Triskelion"?
We know that only the revival of the seven Words may break its seal.
Those are the seven Words.
It's written in the Luna script.
I can't read it at all.
The ancient witches learned it from the moon and stars.
There are hardly any witches who can read it now.
The seven Words have been lost for a long time.
Simply reciting them will not activate it.
Only when the one reciting it breathes life into their revival will the magic be released.
When the one reciting... breathes life into them?
You have already revived three of the Words.
I have?
Do you remember the day you arrived at Luna Nova?
You breathed life into the first Word.
If I reach out, it's sure to begin!
Thrilling and exciting, my very own story!
Noctu... Orfei!
Aude Fraetor!
That was the first Word?
Its meaning is "strive for your ideal place".
"Those who try to achieve their dreams must go through hardships.
There may come times when you fail and lose sight of that dream.
But you must never let the flame in your chest go out.
Burn that flame bright,
and strive for your ideal place."
That is what it means.
Noctu Orfei Aude Fraetor.
The second was at Blue Moon Abyss.
That which is dreamed cannot be grasped.
But work towards it, day after day,
and you will find it in your hands!
Phaidoari Afairrynghor.
And the third you recited at the Samhain Festival.
Open your heart!
Let's laugh together!
Arae Aryrha!
You and the Shiny Rod revived the lost Words.
I did?
There are four Words remaining.
Four... what do they mean?
That is for you to learn for yourself.
Do you know them, Professor?
All except for the very last.
When you will have grown by your own power
and breathed life into all seven Words,
the seal on the Grand Triskelion will break.
I see... so that's why.
Professor, I finally got it!
Chariot!
Chariot's been searching for the Words!
That must be why she disappeared!
If I keep chasing after the Words too,
I know I'll run into her!
I'll find them! All seven Words!
Even though I just learned another spell
oboetate no jumon ja
The things I want to do are still out of reach
kanawanai koto bakari dakedo
My skills are no match for my fantasies
imeeji suru no wa ima yori takaku
Yet my heart leaps out to meet them
tobitachi odoridasu kokoro
Breaking my tiny shell one layer at a time
chiisana kara nandomo nugisutete
I won't let my reckless abandon go to waste
gamushara dake de owarasenai
I'll leave who I was yesterday behind
kinou no watashi wo koeru you ni
Unfurling my transparent wings to the sky
toumei na tsubasa habatakasetara
I feel I can get closer to the tomorrow of my ideals
akogareteta ashita e kitto chikadzukeru ki ga shiterunda
Putting together the shards of a starry sky that I found
mitsuketa hoshizora no kakera musunde
I'll keep on chasing my dream to learn even more
motto shiritai yume wo ou yo