Sosomme Tiextrilla!
You can do it!
One last piece!
It's upside down!
I did it!
Oh, goodness.
So close!
Restoration magic attempt one hundred, "fell just short".
That was the one hundred and first...
Don't let that get you down! You'll get it right tomorrow...
I hope.
Yeah, me too.
Here where our long journey has finally led us
kakedashita hibi ni yukitsuita kono basho
We can push open the door
fureta tobira hiraite
In the footsteps of our dreams far beyond the stars
hoshizora no kanata yume no ashiato
Pick up the pieces with a song
hiroiatsume utau yo
Keep the destination of your dreams nestled in your heart
yume ga kaketeku basho ima mo kokoro ni himete
And envelop the night
yoru wo tsutsumikomu
Cast a magic spell
mahou kakete
And start to dance
odoridasu
The landscape looks like it's burning brilliantly
yaketsuita you ni irodzuita fuukei wa
But you can't see it fallen on the ground
koronda kurai ja tokenai kara
The world will keep on turning
sekai wa tsudzuku yo
Embrace the moment as if it'll never come again
hakanai mama no ima wo dakishimete
Let's keep walking as we are with the light in our sights
kawaranai mama jikan to hikari mitsumete aruiteku
Little Witch Academia
I've been getting afterschool lessons from Professor Ursula for a whole month already.
She must be a really kind person
for helping you every single day.
And here I am, not improving one bit...
What if I have no potential to get better?
Wow, Akko's in low spirits?
Is an apparition going to come to life next?
I want to see Chariot.
I want to ask her how I can be more like her.
It's been ten years since her last magic show.
Where did Chariot go?
Why did she suddenly disappear?
Where are you now?
Chariot must have fallen prey to forbidden love!
She set off after her lover to the ends of the earth.
Or maybe someone petrified her with poison.
Chariot isn't some dimwit who'd let that happen!
You think Professor Ursula might know something?
Both of them used to be students here.
They're about the same age,
so maybe they were classmates—
Classmates?!
Or something like that.
I'll go ask!
Huh?
Professor Ursula!
This late at night?
She's probably in her room!
Welcome to the Land of Magic!
Professor! I want to talk!
H-How can I help you?
Huh?
Professor, your glasses.
How embarrassing, it's been
so long since I last had a visitor.
Wow, so you have a crow as your familiar.
Good evening. I'm Akko!
W-Would you like some tea?
Now then, what did you want to discuss?
Professor, you used to be a student here, right?
Huh?
Have you ever met Shiny Chariot?
Or maybe you were even classmates.
Yes...
Really?! Classmates?!
P-Perhaps we were...
I can't believe it was true!
Wow! What kind of person was Chariot?
Did she stand out in class?
I-I suppose...
She must've been so pretty!
Some might've agreed...
Why did Chariot disappear? Where is she now, and what is she doing?
I can't say...
I see.
I'm sorry I can't be of more help.
You know...
Yes?
Ever since I saw her show,
it's been my dream to be like Chariot.
I still believe in it now.
But, sometimes...
I get scared.
If I ever get to meet Chariot, I want to ask her whether I can really become someone like her.
Professor?
In the past, I also had a professor I looked up to.
Once, she told me something.
"Phaidoari Afairrynghor".
Phaidoari... Afairrynghor?
"That which is dreamed cannot be grasped.
But work towards it, day after day, and you will find it in your hands."
In any case, take good care of the Shiny Rod.
The moon looks so blue tonight!
Come to think of it, tonight is the blue moon.
I see. Our latest intelligence confirms that the number of witches continues to decrease?
Yes, and previous reports about magic weakening across the world remain true.
The great Nine Olde Witches.
They founded this school in an era
when magic was still abundant.
That was sixteen hundred years ago, back when Luna Nova existed in its full glory.
I wonder when it was that we witches became unable to use magic without a sorcerer's stone.
Excuse me, this is Diana.
Oh, Diana. Do come in.
I am searching for a certain book—an ancient tome regarding the Nine Olde Witches.
I did not find it in the library, so I wondered
if you might know of its whereabouts.
If you're looking for a book about ancient magic, the place to search is Luna Nova's reference archives.
You need special permission to gain access.
I trust that you will use this responsibly.
I am most grateful.
Oh yes, Diana.
Go when the moon is high in the sky.
Tonight is a blue moon.
The magic of the blue moon may reveal a secret to you.
Phaidoari Afairrynghor.
That which is dreamed cannot be grasped.
But work towards it, day after day,
and you will find it in your hands.
Come to think of it, tonight is the blue moon.
A dream?
That's right!
Found it!
Hey, do you know what a blue moon is?
Shiny
Chariot
When there are two full moons in a month,
the second one is called a blue moon.
It only happens once every few years.
Blue Moon
"An apparition of yore, emerging but during a blue moon—"
"Though hard to please, knows of the past, present, and future.
Drawing on its boundless knowledge, it will answer the questions of those who can appease it."
Answer... the questions.
Tonight is my last chance for the next several years.
The apparition will show up in the Blue Moon Abyss.
Little Witch Academia
"At the base of Luna Nova's New Moon Tower,
underneath the chapel, lies a cave known as the Blue Moon Abyss.
That is where the apparition will come forth.
Legends say the entrance to the cave only opens on the night of a blue moon."
The cave's entrance...
This leads to the Blue Moon Abyss...
"There exists a hidden art that witches have passed down from the megalithic ages.
The hidden art known as the Grand Triskelion
has the power to change the world."
"In the seventh century, the Nine Olde Witches
sealed the Grand Triskelion within Arcturus.
Only the staff bearing the seven stars,
Claiomh Solais, may break the seal.
To use it, one must speak the seven Words of Arcturus."
The seven Words?
Noctu Orfei, Aude Fraetor.
Strive for a place of idylls.
The day she arrived at Luna Nova,
Akko revived the first Word.
The staff!
Noctu Orfei!
Noctu... Orfei!
Aude!
Fraetor!
Shiny Arc!
Oblivious of the truth...
Akko!
Chariot might've been here too.
Why have you come?
Begone...
Begone!
Chariot!
We meet... at last.
I saw your magic show!
I came to Luna Nova to become a witch like you.
How can I become more like you?
You are who I dream of being!
Haven't you realized it by now?
No matter how much you reach out,
your dream will never come true.
You're lying.
Chariot would never say something like that!
Chariot taught me that a believing heart is my magic!
Who are you?
The blue moon apparition?
Did you create that fake Chariot?
Were you mocking me?
What have you come for?
There's something I need to ask you.
Can't you answer any question about the past, present, and future?
I know not everything.
However, that which I have no answer for
cannot be answered by anyone else.
Please reveal my future to me!
Can I really become a witch like Chariot?
How pointless.
It's more important to me than my life!
Is this the future you wish for?
My dream...
Enter the gate.
This future can be yours.
However, in exchange for this radiant future, you will lose your past.
What do you mean?
Grasping this future comes at a cost.
Surrender your past.
Erase your unneeded past.
Wait!
Don't erase it!
It's full of failures and mistakes I've made,
but I don't want it to be erased!
Why? There is no value in retaining it.
The tears and frustration and laughter, they're all part of me!
It's my life, and it doesn't belong to anybody else!
I've lived it as hard as I could!
I won't erase it!
Are you certain?
Will you give up on becoming Chariot?
I won't!
I'll work hard and become an amazing witch!
It's just like Professor told me.
That which is dreamed cannot be grasped.
But work towards it, day after day,
and you will find it in your hands!
Phaidoari...
Afairrynghor!
It has been a while.
Quite a few years have passed since
we last met, Professor Woodward.
Is that you, Chariot?
It appears the lost Claiomh Solais has been revived.
I see you were testing her.
Just as you did of me.
She's quite the stubborn one.
She revived a Word.
Phaidoari Afairrynghor.
Akko revived the first Word as well.
With this, she has also revived the second.
There are seven Words of Arcturus in total.
Revive the remaining Words.
Chariot.
You will aid her.
Akko, I promise to tell you the truth one day.
I lost sight of everything else
muchuu ni natte oikaketeta
Chasing after a shooting star
nagareboshi tadotta saki ni
Longing to know more about this world
hirogaru sekai wo shiritakute
Just wishing won't make it come true
kanaetai to negau dake ja nai
But if you only push open the door
tobira wo akereba hora
You'll be one step closer
chikadzuite yukeru yo
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
The scenery may be ever-changing
keshiki wa kawatteiku kedo
But under this shining sky
kagayaku sora to
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
Thank you for staying by my side
soba ni itekurete arigatou
See you tomorrow
mata ashita ne