Welcome to the Land of Magic!
Chariot!
Reach out, and it will begin!
Your very own story!
Noctu Orfei!
Aude Fraetor!
Shiny Arc!
Never forget.
A believing heart is your magic.
Little Witch Academia
I've finally made it! This is the holy land the world's greatest witch, Shiny Chariot, grew up in!
Wahoo!
Barf.
This is where I'll become a witch!
Hello!
Hi there!
Could you tell me where the bus stop for Luna Nova is?
It's the school Shiny Chariot went to!
Do you know where I can catch the bus to Luna Nova?
Hey there, got a sec? I'm looking
for a bus stop around here.
We don't have any buses in this town.
That's weird...
It does say there's a terminal here...
But seriously, this map's way too vague.
How am I supposed to find my way with it?
Found it, found it!
Ow, ow, ow...
S-Sorry about that...
Is this yours?
Are you entering Luna Nova too?
Heading to the matriculation ceremony now?
Score!
I was feeling kind of lonely about heading to the witch academy all alone.
I'm Akko! Ever since I saw Shiny Chariot's magic show when I was six, it's been my dream to become a witch!
Or more like, that's when my fate was decided?
You must know who Shiny Chariot is!
Look, a rare card of Chariot. It's my treasure!
I'm sure they love Chariot in the magic world.
Where I'm from, nobody else really seems to care...
They always ask me if I'm stuck in the last decade.
But Chariot's the only witch that amazing, don't you think?
And then there was that moon...
Whoa, puppet magic!
I've never seen it done in real life.
Good girl, come over here. I won't hurt you.
Come on—
My eye! My eye...
Hey, that was mean!
W-Wait up!
What's your name? How'd you make that magic?
I ordered a magic learning kit online,
but I had no idea what to do with it.
I don't even really understand the basics all that well...
But I'm hoping to learn the kind of magic Chariot uses in school.
U-Um...
O-Oh, uh...
Let's get along!
Get off! Get off! Get—
For crying out loud, what's with that girl?
Luna Nova uniforms!
How was your spring break?
Awful, with all the tourists swarming the place.
Speaking of awful, I heard a rumor about the new students.
It seems one of them isn't of witch blood.
Seriously?!
Geez, they've been letting too many commoners in recently!
I heard the academy's having financial issues and can't keep operating without accepting non-witches.
This is the worst.
There goes Luna Nova's reputation.
What if she can't ride a broom?
How absurd!
There hasn't been a witch in Luna Nova's entire history who couldn't ride a broom.
And you are?
K-Kagari Atsuko.
I'm a new student.
Oh, so it's you.
E-Excuse me...
I sure hope the bus gets here soon.
Bus?
Huh? Isn't this the bus stop?
You've got no idea!
Do you truly believe a bus would come here?
Tia Fraere!
This is a broom stop.
The Leyline Terminal.
This location is connected to Luna Nova through a leyline.
Magic energy has flowed through the leylines since ancient times.
You can fly to Luna Nova by riding that energy.
This is a magic highway!
It's common sense to witches!
Let's hurry.
We'll be permanently expelled from
the magic world if we're late to matriculation.
What now?
Come on...
Aw man, I'm so late!
Darnit!
Mom and Yanne gave me way too many gifts to bring back.
Thanks.
Tia Frae—
A-Aren't you coming?
The matriculation ceremony starts soon.
Since I don't recognize you, does that mean you're new?
Luna Nova is really strict about its rules.
Not only will they shut the doors on you
if you're late, you'll be expelled too.
I don't have a broom.
And even if I did, I couldn't ride it.
S-Sorry, I don't want to be late.
Want a ride?
I've never flown double before, but I might be able to pull it off.
Really? Thank you!
So there are nice witches too!
I'm Kagari Atsuko! Call me Akko!
I-I'm Lotte.
Be quick, we're running out of time.
Okay!
Let's take off.
Fly, my broom.
Tia Fraere!
No way, no way!
We're flying! We're flying! We're flying! We're fly—
I think your luggage is too heavy.
Open, gateway to Luna Nova!
What is this? What is this? What is this? What is this?!
I can't do this! Get me off this thing!
Settle down a bit!
My stuff!
"Normal witches are unable to enter the legendary forest of Arcturus."
This has never happened before. Something's off!
Please don't tell me you're carrying salt.
Salt?
Leylines hate salt!
Maybe it's this?
What's that?
Pickled plums.
Toss it!
But I can't survive without pickled plum—
Please, throw it away!
F-Fine!
My treasure!
Stop, it's dangerous!
Ouch!
Little Witch Academia
What's the matter, Alcor?
It couldn't be—Arcturus Forest?!
Thank goodness! My treasure is safe!
Sh-She's dead!
You are the very definition of trouble.
Y-You're alive!
Something like that won't kill a witch.
Lotte!
Are you all right? Did you get hurt?
I'm fine, but my broom isn't.
It appears we reached my destination.
Destination?
Then this is Luna Nova?
Where's the ceremony?
This isn't the place. I've never seen this forest before.
It's Arcturus Forest.
Arcturus?
No way! The forbidden forest?!
What's that?
It's a forest of ancient legend. This is sacred land, protected by a magic circle.
They say that even witches can't escape
once they've wandered in.
What, that's no good! How am I supposed to make matriculation now?
You should worry more about being stuck here your entire life.
Hey, don't scare me like that!
Found some of my stuff!
Gotcha.
Akko, get back!
Hurry!
What the heck is that thing?!
It's a mandrake, a poisonous plant.
This way!
There.
Ouch...
Hey.
Come here for a sec.
What is it?
Stand in here.
Juras Haras Haras.
What is this?
Cast the spell.
Spell?
Will that help us get out?
Kutchur Katela Flala.
Kutchur Kat... F-Fla-fla?
Shout it from your belly!
Kutchur Katela Flala!
Wh-What's going on?
Heya.
What's this thing? What did that spell just do?
You said "Hey stupid, come eat me
if you want to shut me up."
What?!
That's a mythical cockatrice which lives only in Arcturus Forest.
They say its feathers contain a deadly poison.
A collector of deadly poisons can't ignore such a super rare item.
Distract it for me.
I'll grab a feather in the meantime.
What?! Are you saying you used us as bait?!
Nope, you're a sacrifice.
Shout that line one more time!
Heck no!
Good job, keep on dodging.
You'll be petrified if you get caught in its breath.
Petrified?
No way!
You're mine.
W-W-We can't stop!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
We have to get out of here.
There's no way we'll make it
if we keep on wasting time!
Ow!
My leg...
It's over, we can't get there in time...
Don't say that!
I'll never give up!
I have to go...
I'm going to be a witch!
If I reach out...
It's sure to begin!
Thrilling...
And exciting...
My very own story!
That's... Chariot's magic staff!
Lotte, wait here and hide.
Huh?
Kutchur Katela Flala!
Hey!
Birdbrain, here I am!
Try to catch me if you can!
Looks like it worked.
Hey.
Hop on.
Thanks, um...
It's Sucy. Sucy Manbavaran.
Thanks, Sucy.
He doesn't know when to give up!
We can't all get away on one broom!
This is terrible!
Now he's breathing fire!
What are they doing in such a place?
Oh no, we're burning!
That's...
The Shiny Rod!
Hot hot hot hot hot!
The magic words!
Cast the spell!
The staff!
Noctu Orfei!
Noctu... Orfei!
Aude!
Fraetor!
Shiny Arc!
Everyone, did you have an enjoyable vacation?
Our academy has raised countless great witches in its long history.
By crossing its threshold once more, you pledged yourself
to act with pride, decorum, and a sense of modesty.
Devote yourselves to the study of magic.
Now, we shall commence the matriculation cere—
Oh, yeah!
We made it!
Yay!
My word, that was an unprecedented ceremony.
It is only due to the headmaster's special permission
that you have been allowed to enroll.
Make certain not to forget your debt.
Yes.
Greet your roommates.
For the next three years, you three can expect particularly strict instruction.
I'm Kagari Atsuko. Let's be friends!
Here where our long journey has finally led us
kakedashita hibi ni yukitsuita kono basho
We can push open the door
fureta tobira hiraite
In the footsteps of our dreams far beyond the stars
hoshizora no kanata yume no ashiato
Pick up the pieces with a song
hiroiatsume utau yo
Keep the destination of your dreams nestled in your heart
yume ga kaketeku basho ima mo kokoro ni himete
And envelop the night
yoru wo tsutsumikomu
Cast a magic spell
mahou kakete
And start to dance
odoridasu
The landscape looks like it's burning brilliantly
yaketsuita you ni irodzuita fuukei wa
But you can't see it fallen on the ground
koronda kurai ja tokenai kara
The world will keep on turning
sekai wa tsudzuku yo
Embrace the moment as if it'll never come again
hakanai mama no ima wo dakishimete
Let's keep walking as we are with the light in our sights
kawaranai mama jikan to hikari mitsumete aruiteku