Return to the bookshelf!
I said to return!
Noctu Orfei Aude Fraetor!
Guess it's no good.
Um... Professor?
Ursula. I teach magic astronomy.
Professor Ursula?
Yes.
Can I help you?
Right, I came to tell you I was
appointed as your mentor.
Mentor?
Feel free to ask me about anything
you'd like. I'll be glad to help you.
This is the broom the school has provided you.
Wait, that staff...
Oh, you mean this?
It's Shiny Chariot's magic staff.
Professor, do you know about Chariot?
Well, I suppose...
I heard from Lotte.
Huh?
She told me I need to turn in any lost property I find.
But I'm sure that holding on to this
will eventually lead me to Chariot.
I promise I'll give it back once I find her!
You're the one it revealed itself to, which makes you its rightful owner.
Fate and magic will surely guide you.
Professor, can I put my name on my new broom?
Now I'll finally be able to fly!
A believing heart is my magic!
It's my time! Yeah!
A believing heart is my magic, huh.
Here where our long journey has finally led us
kakedashita hibi ni yukitsuita kono basho
We can push open the door
fureta tobira hiraite
In the footsteps of our dreams far beyond the stars
hoshizora no kanata yume no ashiato
Pick up the pieces with a song
hiroiatsume utau yo
Keep the destination of your dreams nestled in your heart
yume ga kaketeku basho ima mo kokoro ni himete
And envelop the night
yoru wo tsutsumikomu
Cast a magic spell
mahou kakete
And start to dance
odoridasu
The landscape looks like it's burning brilliantly
yaketsuita you ni irodzuita fuukei wa
But you can't see it fallen on the ground
koronda kurai ja tokenai kara
The world will keep on turning
sekai wa tsudzuku yo
Embrace the moment as if it'll never come again
hakanai mama no ima wo dakishimete
Let's keep walking as we are with the light in our sights
kawaranai mama jikan to hikari mitsumete aruiteku
Little Witch Academia
Akko, relax.
As if I could!
My first flight magic lesson is about to start!
I'll get to learn how to ride a broom at long last!
Lookie, how do you think I got this scar?
I don't know.
I fell out of a tree trying to fly when I was little.
This one is from when I rolled all the way down a hill.
And I got this one falling off a roof.
Nobody can fly outside the range of the Sorcerer's Stone.
The only reason we can use magic freely on campus
is because the Sorcerer's Stone is here.
You can't blame little me for not knowing.
How could I have guessed that magic energy
comes from the Sorcerer's Stone?
I just believed I could fly and practiced my heart out!
And now I can fly for real!
My childhood dream is coming true!
I-I get it, just calm down.
I'll be instructing the class on flight magic.
The new students are having a special lesson. Everyone else is to practice high-speed flight.
Hop to it!
Tia Freyre!
New students, over here!
Flight magic is the most basic of essentials in a witch's repertoire.
But take it lightly and you'll injure yourself, so be careful.
Yes!
First, firmly grip your broom.
Then, pay your respects to the broom.
Straddle your broom.
Imagine yourself taking to the sky, cast the spell, and kick off the ground!
Tia Freyre!
Huh?
Tia Freyre! Tia Freyre!
Focus more!
Funnel your magic into the broom!
Tia Freyre! Tia Freyre! Tia Freyre!
Tia Freyre!
You'd have no problem winning a shouting match.
I've never seen anyone with your lack of skill before.
Yahoo!
Alley-oop!
Amanda!
No acrobatics during class! Get that
through your thick skull already!
Wow, way to kill my fun.
Hey! No sleeping on your broom!
8.02 seconds!
Such speed! That's a new record, Diana!
Diana's the clear favorite to win this year's broom relay.
Well, if it isn't Akko!
You're still unable to ride a broom?
I know just the thing for you.
Oruihon Deance!
What did you do?!
You'll be able to fly if you keep practicing.
And here I had confidence in my athletic ability.
What are they doing?
Oh, they must be practicing their baton passes for the broom relay coming up.
Broom relay?
The Luna Nova Cup broom relay.
It's a long-standing tradition where teams of three
race to carry a baton all the way to the goal.
Chariot?
It's Chariot!
Hey look, this is Chariot!
That's awesome! Chariot entered too, and she won!
Awesome, I wanna do it too!
I'm gonna win and get my picture put next to Chariot's!
But Akko... you can't fly.
Weren't you the one who just told me
I'd be able to fly if I keep practicing?
Y-Yeah... but there's barely any time between now and the broom relay.
Isn't Chariot just the coolest?
Anyway, I need to stop by the magic item café
to pick up the broom I had them repair.
Magic item café?! What's that?
Akko, wanna come?
We'd already be there if we'd taken a broom.
The Sorcerer's Stone's power is weak out here in the village, so we can't use all that much magic.
Hey, what kinda place is the magic item café?
They service various magic items,
and you're even served tea while you wait.
Cool.
We're here.
Here?
Hm?
Welcome!
I'm here to pick up my broom.
Let's see... right, this one.
Sit tight.
So where's the café?
Not quite what I was imagining.
Frog's foot juice?
Chameleon tongue candy...
Smells like a scam.
A broom?
Don't I recognize this?
It's the legendary broom, Shooting Star!
Shooting Star?
They say a witch was able to cross the entire Atlantic Ocean on it.
It can fly even without power
from the Sorcerer's Stone.
The legendary broom itself is filled with magic.
It truly resembles a shooting star streaking across the sky.
A broom filled with magic...
I want it.
Hey, hold it!
Get your paws off that.
That thing's been sealed.
Sealed?
Yep. It's a dangerous broom that'll fly to the ends of the Earth with no reservations about flinging witches off.
But as long as it's got this thing on,
we can cage it even if it escapes.
This broom brings disaster.
If it ever gets out though,
the boss will seriously chew me out.
Is it really that fast?
There are rumors of it outflying a jet plane.
Please lend me Shooting Star!
Akko?
I bet even I could fly if I rode it, and I know
I'll be able to win the broom relay too!
Just for one day! I'm begging you!
You?! Win the broom relay?
Yes, I want to win.
No way, there's nobody out there
who can tame this wild broom.
Besides, the cup's totally going to li'l Diana this year!
"Diana is the runaway favorite to win and also the number one in popularity."
A legendary broom, huh...
Every single one of them is Diana this, Diana that.
I'm a contender to win too!
As soon as I learn to fly...
Miss Kagari.
Professor Ursula.
It seems you can't ride your broom yet.
I thought this could give you a few tips.
"My First Flight Magic."
This is an elementary school-level textbook,
but it explains the fundamentals of broom riding—
I bet I can fly with this!
Thanks, Professor!
Let's see here... "Brooms love to clean."
"Use your broom to clean on a daily basis
in order to improve your communication with it.
Let the broom know that you are its rider."
Let's sweep together!
You sure love to clean, don't you?
Tia Freyre!
Your rider is me!
Do you know what'll happen if you don't fly?
Watch this!
Tia Freyre!
Please! I'm begging you to fly!
It was just a hunch before, but now I'm sure Akko's a moron.
Sucy! If we don't do something,
there's no way we'll win!
I couldn't care less about competing.
You're racing too!
I already put in our application.
What?! When did you do that?
Guess we'll just lose by default.
We're going to win!
We're going to win and have them put our picture up next to Chariot's!
It says the winning team gets a trophy as well as a prize from Professor Lukić.
Oh, Lukić!
Who was Professor Lukić again?
Remember? She teaches magic pharmacology.
She's also known as a professor of the occult.
Huh, I wonder what the prize is.
Something I'm sure to find very useful.
Hey, what is all this?!
We have no shot at victory if you can't even ride a broom.
People like you need to learn these things with your body.
Help me!
Whaaaat?!
You tryin' to kill me?!
You should be about ready to fly now.
Huh?
Let's see the results of your training!
Are you sure? Yeah, I think I can feel it!
Okay!
Tia Freyre!
Guess I'll come up with something else.
I now call to open the broom relay of the 1333rd Luna Nova Cup.
Little Witch Academia
To the victors, fame and honor.
They will also receive a prize from Professor Lukić.
May the best witches win.
How are you doing, fans of the broom relay across the world?
Live coverage of this event is brought to you
by the Luna Nova News Network!
It looks like all the competitors are on the scene and raring to go!
E-Everyone else looks really fast.
Here we have the dark horse, Amanda O'Neill.
How do you feel?
Well, I'm planning to just enjoy it.
Hey, keep it down!
Uh, n-never mind me!
So Amanda's group entered too.
Who's that I spot?
I'm Kagari Atsuko. I feel that—
It's the favorite to win, Diana! A word for your fans!
I have none. I will simply be flying as usual.
Participating teams, line up!
The broom relay will take place along the Luna Nova special course.
Make certain to charge your brooms with energy from the Sorcerer's Stone!
First leg flyers, confirm your hold of the baton!
Any damage, loss, or poor handoffs of the baton
during the race will result in disqualification.
First leg flyers, head to the start line!
Second leg and anchor flyers, go to your relay points!
Look, Akko is participating.
Shall I outfit your training wheels again?
What's with you?!
Let them mouth off. We'll be the ones to win.
Sucy, you sound confident, but I'm not that fast a flyer.
Don't worry. Just fly like you always do, Lotte.
On your marks, get set!
Tia Freyre!
What happened?!
I just gave your brooms a bit of nourishment.
With no competition, we can just coast to victory.
Tia Freyre!
We're off to an unexpected start!
Their brooms can't take off!
Leading the pack is "Miss Glasses",
our average, ordinary everygirl, Lotte Jansson!
And close behind is...
Constanze Braunschbank Albrechtsberger!
A name that would make any announcer cry!
And she's riding...
A broom?
Wow! Constanze overtook her before the relay point!
Coming out on top is the "Speed of Sound
Tinker Techie", Constanze!
She customized her broom!
No wonder the nutrients had no effect.
Sucy!
Lotte! Over here!
In second is Sucy Manbavaran!
And holding on to the top spot is "The Magic World's Food Fighter", Jasminka Antonenko!
What a dignified sidesaddle!
Oh no, what has overcome her?!
Jasminka has left the course!
Eat to your heart's content.
I'm Amanda, a rebel cut from the same tree as you.
Let's be buds.
Ouch!
Damn you!
Get down here!
Listen to me!
There ain't no broom in the world I can't ride!
In the lead by a mile is the "Mushroom Poison Queen", Sucy!
Sucy! Over here!
Akko, get ready!
What is the meaning of that uncouth riding style?
Who cares, as long as I win?
Catch ya later!
Could this be a breach of conduct?
She's frog-hopping on her broom!
Can the ribbiting Akko-tan make it all the way?!
What is keeping them?!
Tia Freyre!
The rest of the contestants who were held up at the start line take off at top speed!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit!
Hip, hop—
Ow, ow, ow...
Isn't that...
Ouch...
I knew it! It's the legendary broom!
Hold it! You won't get away!
I did it! I'm flying a broom!
I'll never let you go!
Look out!
Move! Move!
Diana!
Th-Thanks, Diana.
Consider my debt paid with this.
Debt?
You're covered in injuries.
Withdraw and call the rescue squad.
It's impossible for you to continue.
Right, my broom!
What's an injury or two or three or four or five or six?!
If I say I'll ride a broom, then I'm gonna ride it!
Don't even try to shake me off now.
I won't even let go to the very depths of hell!
In first place is the "Trustworthy and Talented Cool Beauty", Diana!
Will she pull away until the end?!
I hope Akko is okay...
She probably gave up somewhere along the way.
What? Something's approaching...
Akko?!
It's Akko flying on her broom!
No way.
Akko?!
Bringing up third is "The Wild Dark Horse Tomboy", Amanda!
That's my broom! Give it back!
Amanda is disqualified! She failed her baton pass!
In fact, that's not a baton but a donut!
What a twist!
It's Diana and Akko, neck and neck!
That's incredible! Akko's flying on a broom!
Looks more like she chained herself to it.
It's still amazing!
Akko, go for it!
What an intense dead heat!
They've rounded the final bend!
Who will claim victory?!
Congratulations on your win.
I was certainly surprised that Miss Kagari
took second, despite her inability to fly.
As was I.
It seems she has passion, if nothing else.
Yes, just passion.
But one day...
I lost sight of everything else
muchuu ni natte oikaketeta
Chasing after a shooting star
nagareboshi tadotta saki ni
Longing to know more about this world
hirogaru sekai wo shiritakute
Just wishing won't make it come true
kanaetai to negau dake ja nai
But if you only push open the door
tobira wo akereba hora
You'll be one step closer
chikadzuite yukeru yo
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
The scenery may be ever-changing
keshiki wa kawatteiku kedo
But under this shining sky
kagayaku sora to
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
Thank you for staying by my side
soba ni itekurete arigatou
See you tomorrow
mata ashita ne