Those who commit fraud through magic
shall have their tongues branded with a hot iron.
Those who kill another through magic...
Will be eaten alive by mice, their incisors sharp as blades.
I don't get what's so funny.
And finally, those who try to bring back the dead through magic...
Imagine something so fearful you would rather die than face it.
They shall suffer a punishment one hundred times as agonizing as that!
Professor!
Will this be on the test?
That it will.
Huh, acting strange? Me?
I mean, you usually doze off during magic law class.
Hey, Constanze built a film projector in secret.
She's gonna hold a double feature with Merman Apkallu and Revenge of Apkallu.
I'll pass! We have exams coming up soon.
Don't tell me you're going to study?!
I want to work hard and try to reach Chariot's level!
Here where our long journey has finally led us
kakedashita hibi ni yukitsuita kono basho
We can push open the door
fureta tobira hiraite
In the footsteps of our dreams far beyond the stars
hoshizora no kanata yume no ashiato
Pick up the pieces with a song
hiroiatsume utau yo
Keep the destination of your dreams nestled in your heart
yume ga kaketeku basho ima mo kokoro ni himete
And envelop the night
yoru wo tsutsumikomu
Cast a magic spell
mahou kakete
And start to dance
odoridasu
The landscape looks like it's burning brilliantly
yaketsuita you ni irodzuita fuukei wa
But you can't see it fallen on the ground
koronda kurai ja tokenai kara
The world will keep on turning
sekai wa tsudzuku yo
Embrace the moment as if it'll never come again
hakanai mama no ima wo dakishimete
Let's keep walking as we are with the light in our sights
kawaranai mama jikan to hikari mitsumete aruiteku
Little Witch Academia
Freely controlling objects requires unbroken concentration.
Professor, how much sugar do you take?
Two cubes, if you would.
Splendidly done, Diana.
Even I can do that much!
Whoops...
Professor Ursula! Have you not been acting as a mentor to Atsuko Kagari?
Care to explain exactly how you are instructing her?
Um...
Depending on her results on the upcoming exams,
we may have to review our policies for her case!
Well, I...
I'm sorry.
In any case, let's study for those exams.
We'll begin with basic object control magic.
Try opening that window.
O window, open!
Focus harder!
Open! Open!
Open Sesame!
I said open, so open already!
We will now begin the bird language
listening comprehension exam.
The most common familiars
in use are owls and crows.
One must able to understand crows
at the very least before calling oneself a witch.
Transcribe the utterances of this crow onto your examination sheet.
Now, begin.
I couldn't understand a thing...
You did the best you could for your first time.
I'm hungry, caw!
Feed me, caw!
Bird language is just my worst subject!
You mean it's another one of your worst subjects, right?
Though it's hard to imagine you having a best subject anyway, Akko.
Your next exam is basic white magic.
It's a practical test of fixing something broken, so I'll teach you restoration magic.
Restoration magic?
Sosomme Tidiare!
There! I made a bent spoon all straight again!
Next, Lotte Jansson.
Oh, here!
Um, I'll be repairing this boot.
Turuto Estida.
It's amazing how you got an A+ in white magic.
Only you and Diana did that well.
My best shot was a C-.
It's only because I've been summoning faeries since I was young.
Your family runs a magic tool shop, right?
Yeah, but a lot of people say we're outdated for still doing repairs with magic.
But since I'm here at Luna Nova, I at least want to get my magic tool maintenance license.
Maintenance license? What's that?
It's a national qualification. You didn't know?
You need the right qualifications to get a job in handling magic tools.
Job?
This contains a list of alumnae.
Some specialized in modification magic
and became cosmetic surgeons.
Others made use of white magic to join the force as forensic investigators.
"Michelle, an expert in astrology, has worked as a fortune teller in London since her days at Luna Nova."
What about you, Akko? What do you want to be?
I want...
I really do want to be Chariot!
I'd like to become a witch who can make people happy, like Chariot did!
I see.
What about you?
Was it your childhood dream to become a teacher?
Akko! Our flight magic exam is starting soon.
No way, it is?!
See you later, Professor!
My childhood dream, huh.
Yahoo!
Come on, make way!
And a perfect landing!
Amanda O'Neill! Dangerous flying leads to broom accidents!
C-!
For real?
Next... Atsuko Kagari!
Fly! I said to fly, so fly!
Aw man, a D-.
I'm more surprised you got any grade at all for just straddling your broom.
And what about you? If you flew more normally, you'd get an A for sure.
I only fly free, just the way I like it.
Do you want to be a broom dancer or something in the future?
I ain't even considered it. Having fun now's good enough for me.
Oh, that reminds me.
Wanna hit up a club tonight? My bud's the DJ,
and he'll let us in through the back door.
I have to study.
Huh?
We have our culinary magic and fundamental alchemy
tests tomorrow, so I need to go through the practice exams.
Hey, Sucy. Did you feed Akko some freaky mushrooms or something?
All right!
I need to dig in if I want to be like Chariot! Time for an all-nighter!
Crap, I feel asleep!
Next, Jasminka Antonenko.
Bouden Dariard.
You increased the sweetness through flavor magic.
However, eating during the exam is not allowed! A-.
Next, Atsuko Kagari.
Here!
Bouden Dariard.
Constanze Braunschbank Albrechtsberger.
Fantastic.
But I would have preferred if you had transformed it into something more practical. B+.
Next, Atsuko Kagari.
Yes!
Everyone else is getting judged at stuff they're good at.
You have good points as well, Akko.
I do? Where?!
Um...
Where? Where?
Anyway, I believe your next exam is in magic astronomy. I have high hopes for you.
Right.
According to the horoscope, Luna Nova
will overcome a number of difficulties.
Very good. That was quite the complex astrology reading.
She just said stuff that'll happen no matter what.
Would you like for me to peer into your future as well?
All you're gonna see is me being
an amazing witch, like Chariot!
I can see it. Akko will...
She will depart from Luna Nova.
That's nonsense!
You think? Diana's predictions are always right.
I can't imagine you graduating either.
Looks like you'll be dropping out.
What'd you—
What are you doing?!
Akko!
Hey, let go!
Stop that!
What is the meaning of this?!
You fed your professor a poison apple, caused an explosion at a test site, and now incited violence.
Hannah started it.
I will not hear your excuses!
Miss Kagari, I do not sense the slightest
trace of potential as a witch in you.
If you fail your final exam,
you will be expelled.
Huh? Wait, I don't want to be expelled!
I-If I may...
This academy cannot afford a witch
who can but drag its level down.
Headmistress, I presume you have no objections.
I suppose I must agree.
Wait...
Akko.
Do you think I'm bad too?
Am I really that hopeless?
There's no way I'm getting expelled!
My last exam is in magic philosophy.
Magic philosophy?
So that's what you chose as your elective.
But what do they expect us to know
in a class with no teacher?
No teacher?
It's always self-study. Everyone spends all period just staring at a goldfish bowl.
Hold on, that's no goldfish.
It's Professor Pisces!
Pie?
Hey, is that goldfish Professor Pisces?
Yes, so?
Is she talking?
Of course.
Understanding fish language is complex, so only students in advanced magic linguistics can take it.
For the record, I scored 960 points on the Fish TOEIC.
What's she saying?
"The exam will include the nature of altruism in witch ontology
as well as reciprocal altruism with members of other species."
I see.
I'm in despair!
I don't even understand what's on the test!
How am I supposed to even figure out what I should study?!
All I can do is wait to be expelled!
Looks like Diana's prediction was on the mark.
Diana's prediction?!
Like hell I'm gonna let her be right!
My expulsion papers haven't been signed yet!
I'll do this, and then shove it in her face!
It's on!
That was a fast recovery.
Professor, your fins are gleaming so marvelously today.
They're so vivid and beautiful.
I brought you this rather expensive water that even celebrities drink.
Hopefully it'll be to your liking.
And so, in regards to today's exam, I was hoping you might keep this in consideration while grading...
What do you think?
P-P-P-Professor Pisces?!
What do I do?! Artificial respiration?
No, she's a fish, so artificial gillspiration?
That's not even a thing!
Professor Pisces!
What?! You flushed Professor Pisces down the drain?
Little Witch Academia
Id wash an aggshident!
Why did you think it was a good idea to give a fish mineral water?
I said it wasn't on purpose!
What a development.
Things are getting interesting now.
What now?
How about looking in the sewers?
She shouldn't have been swept too far from here.
Right!
Wait, Akko!
Professor, cover for us!
Professor Pisces!
We're not on the school grounds, so why don't we use this chance to transform into fish?
That'll let us speak with fish, so it might help find her faster.
Sure.
Metamorphie Faciesse!
What happened?
This is great, you turned into a merman!
It's so lame!
I'm gonna recast the magic.
Wait! Our batteries only have enough magic left for one more spell.
We need to save it for when we go back.
Huh?
I never get bored when Akko's around.
Don't laugh!
We have to hurry, or you'll miss the exam!
Um, uh...
Professor! Professor Pisces!
Please respond if you can hear me!
We've come pretty far out.
Sob sob. Sob sob.
Akko, where are you going?
Hello!
Have you seen a colorful fish with a long tail around here?
Haven't seen. Haven't seen.
I can understand what this fish is saying!
So sad. So sad.
Wait, were you the one crying just now?
Family gone. Very sad.
Is he lost?
Akko, we need to find Professor Pisces fast and get back.
So sad. So sad.
Don't worry! Me, your family, look together!
Huh?
So don't be sad!
Thank you. Thank you.
We don't have that kind of time!
But I can't just ignore him. We can look for Professor Pisces as we go.
Professor Pisces, I brought your exam sheets.
Oh? Did you change your look?
Bubble bubble bubble!
You're under the weather? That's no good.
All right, I'll help you proctor the exam then.
Bubble bubble! Bubble bubble!
We look out for each other in times of need.
We'll now begin the magic philosophy exam!
Professor Pisces?
What's that?
Father!
Mother!
Little sis!
Little bro!
Big bro!
Little sis!
Trapping isn't supposed to be allowed in this lake.
It won't open!
Only one thing to do!
Stop! If you use up your magic now, you'll never make it in time for your exam!
Oh, right.
Family! Family!
Akko, let's go back to school for now.
Yeah...
Family...
Open Sesame!
Are you kidding?
Yes, I did it!
Huh?
Professor Pisces?!
Thank goodness!
We need to hurry back!
Look!
Little sis!
Here we go.
Damn, only got one. Wonder if my trap broke.
Poaching. Bad! Got it?
Y-Yes!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
We made it...
Professor Ursula, you were supposed to be with her.
I'm so sorry.
You even put Professor Pisces in grave danger.
Professor Pisces says it was fun to be able to swim around in a large lake after all this time.
Yes, that is quite correct.
She also says you've received
an A in magic philosophy.
You impressed her by putting what you learned in class into practice of your own volition.
Akko, you can understand fish language?
Huh? I guess so.
That is no excuse!
We cannot overlook what you have done.
"Merman sighted at the lake"?
What?! From back then?!
This is Miss Kagari?
Our school has never been this shamed since its founding!
I request the expulsion of Atsuko Kagari on grounds of disgracing the dignity of our academy!
Stop right there!
You may see Miss Kagari as just a poor student unable to use magic if you compare her to her classmates.
But she has learned to understand fish language,
and although she has yet to master it,
she's continuously improving her metamorphosis magic!
You should not be comparing her to other students, but to how she was on the day of her enrollment!
Nobody can deny that she's continuing to grow through her failures!
She has absolutely no value as a witch.
Should you not be appraising how she is unable to ignore those suffering before her,
putting their feelings above her own desires?!
Putting grades or outward appearances above that...
Is pure foolishness!
I approve of her!
Pardon me, Headmistress. We've received an incomprehensible phone call.
They're asking if the merman is a student of Luna Nova.
You see now?
Who is on the line?
It's the Environmental Agency.
They wish to commend the merman who saved an endangered species of fish from poaching.
I guess those fish were endangered.
Please tell them that the merman was one of ours.
I trust you're fine with that, Professor Finneran.
What about her expulsion?
One of our students is receiving a public commendation.
Don't you agree we should keep her here with us, Miss Merman?
I'm saved...
This is great, Akko!
However, we cannot ignore how you
attempted to cheat on your exam.
You must be punished for that.
How does this sound?
For the next week, we will share mealtimes and nighttimes as I drill the expectations of a witch into you.
First, as per the rules, we will retire at nine o'clock!
Then we wake at four! Keep in mind that a filthy room houses a filthy soul.
Always keep it clean!
Why did I get roped in?
Professor Ursula, I didn't know that's how you thought about me.
You really sounded like a teacher.
Thank you!
Excuse me, but I am a teacher!
You two! Move your hands, not your mouths!
Okay!
I lost sight of everything else
muchuu ni natte oikaketeta
Chasing after a shooting star
nagareboshi tadotta saki ni
Longing to know more about this world
hirogaru sekai wo shiritakute
Just wishing won't make it come true
kanaetai to negau dake ja nai
But if you only push open the door
tobira wo akereba hora
You'll be one step closer
chikadzuite yukeru yo
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
Let's go on a journey to find
the next page of our story
machikirenai monogatari
no tsudzuki wo sagasou
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
You're not the only one
who believes in the future
mirai shinjirareru no
wa hitori ja nai kara
The scenery may be ever-changing
keshiki wa kawatteiku kedo
But under this shining sky
kagayaku sora to
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
I'll never let go of the
treasures we collected together
meguriatta takaramono
itsumademo hanasanai yo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
Through the tears and
laughter, eating and sleeping
sou naite waratte tabete nete mo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
And all of the times
we were beset by worries
kuyo kuyo shichaisou na toki demo
Thank you for staying by my side
soba ni itekurete arigatou
See you tomorrow
mata ashita ne