[https://tieba.baidu.com/p/1217288664?pid=14451726906&cid=0&red_tag=1620898065#14451726906]
[Script Info]
Title:Futakoi_Alternative_SP
Original Script:百度双恋2吧
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H001F0A79,&H90000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00150861,&H90000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,8,30,30,10,134
Style: biaoti,方正粗宋_GBK,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,65,134
Style: jinggao,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,2,15,15,10,134
Style: OPJ,DFGHSMincho-W7,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H33333333,&H50000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,9,128
Style: OPC,方正大标宋_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H33333333,&H50000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,5,134
Style: EDJ,DFGHSMincho-W7,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0066E959,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,9,128
Style: EDC,方正大标宋_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0066E959,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,5,134
Style: INJ,DFGHSMincho-W7,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H33333333,&H50000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,9,30,30,9,128
Style: INC,方正大标宋_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H33333333,&H50000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,9,30,30,5,134
[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.90,0:00:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树:无可取代的重要时光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.77,0:00:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沙罗有恋太郎的三人时光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.60,0:00:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泡了咖啡的话就和沙罗与恋太郎一起喝
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.01,0:01:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了蛋糕的话就和沙罗与恋太郎一起吃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.10,0:01:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,河边吹起清爽的风时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.88,0:01:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个人就一起在河边散步
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.01,0:01:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢这样的每一天
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.06,0:01:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙罗:无可取代的重要时光
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.12,0:01:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有双树有恋太郎的三人时光
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.21,0:01:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,播放喜欢的音乐的话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.16,0:01:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和双树与恋太郎一起聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.05,0:01:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来到录影带出租店的话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.03,0:01:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和双树与恋太郎一起借录影带
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.15,0:01:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天上高挂美丽的月亮时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.25,0:01:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个人就一起赏月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.00,0:01:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢这样的每一天
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.06,0:01:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树：即使没有工作委托也很快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.09,0:01:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙罗：早上起床
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.10,0:01:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说声早安
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.12,0:01:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起围在桌子边
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.13,0:01:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树：晴朗的日子里洗洗衣服 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.20,0:01:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做做日光浴
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.13,0:01:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙罗：三个人一起去做晚饭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.08,0:01:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树：是的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.10,0:02:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回忆并非特别的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.22,0:02:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这日常的一切…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.12,0:02:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树沙罗：就是幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.19,0:03:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树：虽然知道无法在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.14,0:03:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是暗自期望著
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.19,0:03:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为遇见恋太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.13,0:03:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和沙罗感到很幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.19,0:03:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我彷佛找到了自己
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.08,0:03:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又失去自我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.01,0:03:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他将我解救出来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.25,0:03:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树沙罗：我们彷佛找到了自己 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.13,0:03:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又失去了自我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.08,0:03:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他将我们解救出来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.11,0:03:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树：已经失去的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.59,0:03:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经四散纷飞的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.57,0:03:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经破碎凌乱的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.21,0:03:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汇集这点点滴滴的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.09,0:03:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向恋太郎提出最后的搜查委托
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.13,0:03:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树：我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.07,0:03:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩我一个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.08,0:03:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋太郎! 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.11,0:04:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙罗她… 沙罗她…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.00,0:04:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树沙罗：以前我们三个人在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.16,0:04:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是我们三个人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.13,0:04:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能只有两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.13,0:04:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要有我们三个人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.19,0:04:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树：我想要三个人在一起 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.20,0:04:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沙罗和恋太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.15,0:04:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙罗：我想要三个人在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.17,0:04:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有双树和恋太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.03,0:04:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双树沙罗：我们三个人…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.05,0:04:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能三个人在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.03,0:04:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能三个人在一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.08,0:04:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的, 三个人…