Valentine For You
Picture Drama
Tachibana-kun, here! Have this!
Huh, Morishima-senpai?
What's with that cute box?
Come on, are you still half asleep?
These are chocolates for Valentine's Day.
It's a box of chocolates.
What?!
You... You're actually giving me chocolates?
Life is so sweet!
Aww, dry those tears.
Good boy.
Hey, can I eat them now?
Who cares? I'm gonna eat 'em!
Stay!
Don't be so grabby; you'll get them soon enough.
I will?
Yup!
I wonder how'd you like me to feed you.
You're going to... feed me?!
Hmm... I wonder how I should do it?
Should I make you say "Ahh"?
Or maybe...
Or... Or maybe...
Mouth... to... mouth?
Just kidding!
Tachibana-kun, this is for you.
Huh? Ayatsuji-san, is that...
That's right. As you've already guessed, these are chocolates.
You got those just for me?
Yes, I did.
I made time in my busy schedule to go buy these for you,
but only because you're so special.
Why, thanks.
So, you best be grateful.
Yeah, of course I am!
These chocolates are from you, after all.
Too right!
Oh yes, when you eat them, be sure to yell, "Thank you very much, Tsukasa-sama!"
And you'll weep...
as you kneel before me and eat.
Are we clear?
Wait, I'm not...
Are you saying you won't?
No, I'd be happy to!
Excellent.
Jun'ichi, here you go!
What is this, Rihoko?
What are you talking about? These are Valentine's Day chocolates, silly!
What?! Those are mine?
Mm-hmm!
Thank you!
Say, can I open it now?
Go ahead.
Oh! Are these...
These chocolates are really delicious!
I can't get enough of the ones with the milk filling!
Rihoko... Why are you staring at me?
Hey, mind if I have a nibble?
Come on, I did buy them!
As always, you love to eat.
I know, you can feed me!
Go on! Ahh!
Ahh...
Wait, shouldn't you be feeding me?
They're so good!
This is bliss!
Um, Senpai.
What's up, Nanasaki?
Please have this.
It's chocolate for Valentine's Day.
Huh? For me?
We're the only two here, aren't we?
Y-Yeah, we are.
I guess I was a little overwhelmed.
You're acting funny.
Could this be... a chocolate cake?
That's right.
You like them, don't you?
Yeah, I love 'em!
Huh?
How did you know that?
You told me on one of our dates.
You said you love chocolate cakes.
Huh? I-I said that?
I forgot all about that. I'm surprised you remembered.
Of course I did.
I remember all of our memories together.
Nanasaki?
Happy Valentine's Day, Senpai!
Tada!
What's with the box, Kaoru?
It's Valentine's Day chocolate, obviously!
Oh, you're giving me some?
Wait, this isn't more of your...
Don't worry!
These aren't leftovers from work like last year!
Oh, really?
In that case, I'll gladly accept.
I splurged on this, so you better be thankful when you eat it!
Never would've expected that from you.
Well, excuse me!
And another thing...
What is it?
Since I'm so full of surprises, I'll give you one more.
Oh? I get two gifts this year?
Yeah.
Hey...
Close your eyes.
What are you trying to pull?
Just do it!
Fine.
There, they're closed.
It's a free kiss.
Oh, God! I shouldn't have done that!
Uh... um... Senpai?
Here.
I-Is this...
Yes.
It's Valentine's Day chocolate.
You're giving it to me?
Th-Thank you!
I worked hard on it.
I hope you... like it.
What? You made it?
Y-Yes.
U-Um...
D-Don't you want... chocolate I made?
Nonono! That's not it!
I never even dreamed that I'd ever
get homemade chocolate from a girl!
I'm on cloud nine!
A-And also... um...
A-Actually...
I also have... one more present.
I'm getting two?
Ah, y-yes.
Uh, Sae-chan?
What's the other present?
T-Today...
Yeah?
I-I...
"I..."?
...am your present!
"I am your present"?
Whaaat?!
Th-That line was written in a gentleman's magazine.
Miya-chan told me to tell you that.
B-But... it was so embarrassing!