I'm spending the night at Tachibana-kun's house.
This is a little exciting!
No.
My heart is actually going a mile a minute.
I hope this time he comes to sneak a peek.
I wonder how I should freak him out when he does?
One.
Haruka's fantasy
number ONE
I'm here.
Eeek!
Tachibana-kun, you creep!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Take that! And that!
Maybe that way.
Two.
number TWO
Haruka's fantasy
I've arrived.
Eeek!
Tachibana-kun, what are you trying to look at?!
Owie!
Or that way.
Three.
Haruka's fantasy
number THREE
Good evening.
Huh? Where is she?
Wow!
*slip*
the end
I think the last one is the best!
So Tachibana-kun has been living here all his life.
He used this bath ever since he was a kid.
That sort of shines a new light on things.
You're such a coward, Tachibana-kun.
All right, I'm going in!
That was refreshing!
What?
S... Senpai, why are you wearing that?!
Huh, do I look weird?
N-No...
It's not that you look weird...
He's blushing!
I can never hate him, even if he
doesn't come to peek in on me.
Actually... he's really cute!
Uh, Senpai?
Can you change into something different?
Huh? Why?
I brought it along so I can show you.