I can't believe it'd start pouring like that!
What should we do if someone wanted to use the phone?
Looks like there's no fitting a third person in.
It's already a tight squeeze as it is.
It sure is.
Oh no!
What?
You're all wet, Jun'ichi!
It's not that bad.
Yes it is! It's winter right now, you'll
catch a cold if you're not careful!
There, you should be fine now.
So soft...
Uh, forget what I said.
Let me wipe you off this time.
That tickles!
Um...
I-Imagine if someone were to see us now.
Yeah.
It'd be even worse if it was someone we know.
The glass is fogging over.
You're right.
It's so strange.
What?
I've been with you all this time, yet
we've never made any memories like this.
We'll be making a lot of new memories from now on.
Hey, can you feel how my heart is racing?
Yeah, I sure can.
Mine's also going a mile a minute.
It's snowing!
It has been chilly enough.
Wanna go home?
Sure!