Bathroom... bathroom...
K... Kaoru?
Wh... Why is she sleeping like that?
C... Could this be...
...my chance?
No! No! No! No!
What am I thinking?
My "chance"? Kaoru's sleeping for Pete's sake!
That's just low!
But... we are officially a couple.
And we took this trip so we can have some alone time.
And here we are alone,
at night,
at a hot-springs inn.
But still...
Still...
Wh-What?
What is Jun'ichi coming over for?
What is he trying to do?
Wait a second, how do I look right now?
I don't feel the blanket covering me.
And I can feel a draft in a few areas.
My yukata must be messed up!
I'm probably exposed... in a few places!
Oh no! Even with my eyes half open I can't tell!
Eh? H-Hey, Jun'ichi!
Wait! What are you trying to do?
What's going to happen?
What's going to happen to me?
Maybe I'll just go with the flow...
No, I can't!
I don't want that to be what I remember from this trip!
But... I did make sure to wear my favorite underwear.
Wait!
A monkey took my bra!
Jun'ichi hand's...
His hand's...
Eh?
Huh, what just happened?
That was a little scary.
These kinds of memories don't come too often.
Thank you, Jun'ichi.