GIVE ME CHOCOLATE!
This society's all about Valentine's Day!
You go around town, you see girls running left and right
literally giving the candy companies their obscene profits!
But not one of those chocolates that are flying off the shelves will ever reach our hands!
Nope, not one.
They'll never come.
What can you do? We don't have girlfriends.
Valentine's Day is just some fictional event that happens in games and animes.
We'll fly magically through the air or get attacked by an army of zombies before we get any chocolates.
Quit being so negative, Captain!
There might be a slight, miraculous,
God-only-knows, one-in-a-million chance
that one of us might get a box of chocolates containing the feelings... of a cute girl.
That doesn't make me feel better in the slightest.
Fine, then let's start practicing!
Huh?
We'll imagine that we're getting Valentine's
Day presents from cute girls as a
si... shimi... shumi... what was it again?
"Simulation".
Yes, that! We'll do it as simulations!
But how are we going to simulate it?
Well, for example we could...
Imagine you're getting one from Morishima-senpai!
I'm getting Valentine's Day
chocolates from Morishima-senpai?
Here are your Valentine's Day chocolates!
Whoa, stay!
Geez, don't be so grabby. I'll give it to you in time.
I wonder how you like me to feed you?
Should I make you say "Ahh"?
Or maybe...
Mouth... to... mouth?
Just kidding!
Umehara...
I'm not sure this will amount to any sort of "practice".
Actually, I have my doubts too.
But we came this far so there's no turning back!
This time, you act the part, Captain.
Huh? M-Me?
Let's see...
How about Ayatsuji-san?
Ooh! Sounds good!
Go ahead!
Here, I got you chocolates.
I made time in my busy schedule to go buy these for you, so be grateful when you eat them.
Oh yes,
make sure you yell out, "Thank you very much, Tsukasa-sama!"
And kneel down before me sobbing while you eat them.
Are we clear?
Wow...
Is that what you're into?
Ayatsuji-san would never say that.
No, that wasn't what I was going for...
I dunno, that just popped into my mind for some reason.
Still, you're starting to get into this, right?
Yeah!
It's actually fun once you start doing it!
It sure is!
Now next up is...
Yeah, let's go with Sakurai-san!
Rihoko?
Jun'ichi!
Here are your Valentine's Day chocolates!
These chocolates are really delicious, you know.
The ones with the milk fillings are to die for!
Hey... can I have a bite?
Come on, I was the one who bought them anyway.
Say, can you feed me?
Ahh...
That was awesome!
Totally!
It's hard to beat my power of imagination!
But it's not good enough, Umehara!
Now it's my turn!
Oh, who're you gonna do?
The number one cool beauty on the swim team, Nanasaki!
Um, Senpai.
Here.
It's a Valentine's Day chocolate.
Senpai...
You said on our date that you love chocolate cake.
Of course I remember.
I remember all our memories we have together.
Happy Valentine's Day, Senpai.
That was sweet!
Playing it cool with just a hint of dere!
Well, it was you playing her, though.
Don't mention that!
Just replay that in your mind using her voice!
You're up next, Umehara.
It better not be a half-hearted
fantasy or else you're not going to win!
In that case...
Let's go with Tanamachi!
Kaoru?
Imagining her won't do anything for me!
I wonder about that?
Tada! Here are your chocolates!
Don't worry! These aren't leftovers from work like last year.
I splurged on these, so you better be thankful when eating them!
Um... and also...
Close your eyes for a second.
Just do it already!
It's a free kiss.
Topping it off with a kiss?
That's beyond sweet!
What say you? Did I win this showdown!
No, we're not done.
I still have one last card left to play!
What?
My last card...
is the one with the enchantingly soft
and squeezy body, Nakata-san!
U-Um...
Senpai? Here is your... Valentine's Day ch-chocolate.
I worked hard making it.
I'll be glad if you... like it.
A-And you also... have...
another... present.
And th... that present is... me.
Ah, I'm so embarrassed!
That...
That absolutely killed me!
Giving yourself as a present?
Nobody thinks like that!
What do you say, Umehara?
You know I won this match!
Yeah, I'll manly own up to my defeat.
You won, Captain!
Dude, I applaud your fantasies!
Your fantasies aren't half bad either.
Huh?
When did this turn into a fantasy showdown?
Beats me.