The Adventures of
Little Red Riding Hood
Lalala... laa-lala.
I'm the cute and adorable Little Red Riding Hood!
I'm bringing a fondant bûche de
noël chiffon gateau chocolat cake
to Grandmother's house!
Is that a...
What a bother.
I... I'm a bear,
a-and I have to fill my tummy with food before I hibernate.
I'm sorry,
but I am going to eat you.
Roar!
Hey, you're not supposed to play dead.
Wait a minute, Mr. Bear!
Shake! Shake!
I've already shared my precious honey with you because you said you were hungry!
Swish! Swish!
Yet you're still going to eat the adorable Little Red Riding Hood? How cruel!
Shake! Shake!
She's right - hippity! That's cruel - hop!
I feel sorry for cute Little Red Riding Hood - hippity!
If you're that hungry,
then I will take her place - hop!
I-I can't do any more!
I-In that case, I'll take her place - splish splash.
By the way, I'm a salmon who's swimming up the river.
Splish-splash!
S... So...
please eat me up.
You are all such good friends.
But I was only concerned about myself.
I'm a very bad bear.
Pout.
No you're not!
You're a bear with a heart of gold.
I know!
Do you all want to come to my grandmother's house?
There will be hot soup and warm beds.
You'll stay warm and your tummies will be full all winter!
So Little Red Riding Hood and her woodland friends went to Grandmother's house.
It was there that they spent a long, joyful winter.
And they lived happily ever after.
the end
That was an amazing performance, Sae-chan!
Thank you, Director!
I'm getting so many ideas!
Let's film another tale, Sae-chan!
Okay, Director!
And the two of them spent their
cheerful, joyful days together.
And they lived happily ever after.