Are you okay, Senpai?
Uh, yeah. Sorry.
You were even kind enough to pay me a visit.
It's okay, don't worry about it.
I still can't believe you'd catch a cold with your college entrance exams coming up.
I guess that cram camp really took a lot out of me.
And you were too lightly dressed during Christmas Eve.
I'm sorry.
If only I noticed sooner...
No, it's fine.
That had nothing to do with this, honestly.
Today I'm going to work extra
hard to nurse you back to health.
Really?
Thanks.
I'm going to prepare the food I bought along the way.
Okay, thanks.
I guess getting a cold isn't so bad after all.
Here.
Say "ahh".
How is it?
Tastes great!
Okay, here comes another.
Say "ahh".
Do you like it?
Yeah!
Want another spoonful?
Yeah, let's go again!
What's this?
Ginger tea.
It'll warm you up.
Bear with it.
That flavor is good for colds.
Tachibana Jun'ichi
Take 3 Times A Day For 7 Days
sama
To Be Taken Orally
Are you cold?
I'm all right.
Then all you need is a good sleep.
Yeah, you're right.
Oh yeah, I just remembered something.
What?
My parents used to make me sleep
with them whenever I catch colds
since they said sweating will help speed up my recovery.
Wha... Senpai!
I need to sweat a lot to recover quicker.
But this is...
H-Hey, Senpai!
That tickles!
Sorry.
I guess I gave you my cold.
It's okay, don't worry about it.
Besides, if you stay with me too much, you'll get another cold.
That I don't mind.
That way maybe I can give it back to you again.
Just kidding.
I swear...
I don't know what to do with you.