Room Camp
Room Camp!
Hmm?
Seems like in different countries,
the camping style's different too.
Really?
Enjoy the Great Outdoors
AMERICAN
CAMPING STYLE
In America, for example, camping with a motorhome's
apparently pretty common.
Oh?
In one of those, you can have a nice,
comfortable camping trip with your whole family.
Comfort camping...
Sounds great!
By the way...
Hunting's really popular in New Zealand,
so I've heard it's tradition to enjoy
a bit of sport while you're camping.
Wow, really?
Everyone carries guns around the campgrounds,
so people from other countries get real surprised.
That's... a bit scary.
Oh, right, and also...
In Canada, it's typical to put your equipment
in a canoe and camp while paddling downstream.
Wow, really?
And in Switzerland, most people go ski camping.
They'll strap their stuff to their backs
and then ski down the Matterhorn.
Wow, reall—
Nadeshiko.
Listen up.
Look closely. Those eyes...
are the eyes Inuko makes...
when she's spouting bull.
There's all sorts of different camp styles.
Bull Camp!
Hey guys, I'm back!
Welcome back, Aoi-chan!
Huh?
Aoi-chan, did you get smaller?
Huh? Sure it's not just your imagination?
But it feels like your chest's gotten flatter too...
It was always like this.
I'm back.
I went to go borrow the new issue of Bivouac.
Ah?! It's a big Aoi-chan!
Then you must be...
Mini Inuko!
5th Grade
Class 1
Inuyama Akari
Aoi's
Little Sister
So you've noticed, Aki-chan.
Aoi-chan, you've got a little sister, huh?
Sure do.
But Akari, what are you doing here anyway?
Cosplaying as you.
And also, I came to apologize to everybody.
Huh?
Sobaudon
ITOU
HOUSE
Sobaudon
Because of the joke Aoi-chan made earlier
about sobau don,
soba and udon shops from all over
have been calling in,
blowing up the phones with complaints.
So I thought I'd issue a formal
correction and apology.
D-Did you, now...
An Apology and Correction
SOBAU
SOBAU DON
The “sobau” bird my sister talked about
does not exist.
As a result, even if you go to a soba and udon shop,
you will not be able to eat sobau don.
SOBAU
SOBAU DON
She was spouting bull.
My sincerest apologies.
SOBAU DON
SOBAU
Stop making that face, you bull sisters!
SOBAU DON
What do you mean?
SOBAU
SOBAU DON
Bull Camp!
Oh!
Akari-chan, are you perhaps also a fan of Mt. Fuji?
Nadeshiko-chan, do you like Mt. Fuji too?
I love it!
Mt. Fuji looks so pretty from Shizuoka,
but it looks just as pretty from Yamanashi!
The view of Fuji from Yamanashi is...
just as pretty?
Huh?
That's no good, Nadeshiko-chan.
Huh?!
Both we Yamanashi girls and the Shizuoka girls
think our respective Mt. Fujis are better.
Because of that, our prefectures
have been in a state of conflict for years.
What?!
Sometime next year, the Mt. Fuji dispute's
finally gonna boil over into a real war.
That's what everyone says!
Everyone!
A war?!
You were originally a Shizuoka girl,
so you'll end up branded
an enemy of the prefecture!
Enemy of the Prefecture
You'll be locked up for the entire rest of your life!
Your life!
Quit bullying Nadeshiko, you bull sisters.
What do you mean?
Bull Camp!
Time for me to get back!
Nadeshiko-chan, Aki-chan, see you later!
Sure! See you, Akari-chan!
Later!
You're too gullible, Nadeshiko.
You've gotta remember to be a bit more skeptical.
You think so?
I think Nadeshiko-chan's fine the way she is.
No, she's gonna run into way more bull
from people like you out in the real world.
Got a minute?
Huh?
Rin-chan?!
I want to devote myself to winter camping,
so I've decided to move to Alaska.
What?!
Since we won't be able to see each other anymore,
I came here to say farewell.
N-No way!
Just kidding!
I won't be fooled again,
Akari-chan!
Excellent work, Nadeshiko!
You saw right through her bull!
Rin-chan's not that small, you know!
Got a minute?
Huh?
A-A big Rin-chan?!
Wh-Wh... What?!
I wanted to try summer camping too...
I wanted to try summer camping too,
so I've decided to move to Africa.
What?!
A small Rin-chan... and a big Rin-chan...
Which one's the real one?
Good question.
You oughta decide that one for yourself.
Rin-chans here, Rin-chans there...
So many Rin-chans...
Ri-Ri-Ri...
Rin-chan!
Which one's you ? ? ?
What are those guys doing?