Room Camp
Room Camp: Episode 0.
It's cramped!
This room's basically a closet...
Well, we're lucky we even got a clubroom.
I guess.
So anyways, how 'bout we get to tidying up?
Oh! Before we do that...
Check this out!
Whoa, an outdoors magazine!
I found it in the school library.
Nice one, Inuko!
Flipping through these really gets you pumped.
Oh!
Having fun with
a campfire chat
Enhance your camping experience.
A collection of elegant camping gear
sure to make
for a wonderful time.
This one's about “Having fun with a campfire chat”.
Sounds great!
Make a three-star dinner!
Making a three-star dinner, huh...
They've got a section on knives too.
Uh, the newest tents and useful tool—
It's all too rich for my blood.
Camping gear can cost a pretty penny.
They're being fancy and calling it “gear”,
but for instance, look at these outdoor knives.
Can't you just use a kitchen knife from home?
Aki!
Hey!
Yeah, no.
And instead of a sleeping bag,
you could just bring your futon...
Are you an old-timey thief?
Sup!
And instead of this, it should be easy enough to enjoy
cooking outdoors with just the stuff we've got on hand.
Big Katsu
You're gonna get arrested!
Maybe camping's a little too hard for just us alone.
All I wanted...
It happened back in kindergarten.
I went camping with my family.
We ate curry outside,
slept in a tent,
and had so much fun that I'll never forget it.
All I wanted was to do something like that again.
This time, with my best friend.
Aki...
What's up?
And done.
Here, look at this!
It's basically the same!
Isn't it?
We might be able to pull this off!
Let's look through all these boxes, top to bottom!
Hardtack
Picnic
tarp
There!
That's pretty much everything we need.
Huh? S-Sure is...
Listen up. Close your eyes and imagine it.
Imagine?
First, we lay out the tarp and build a tent
with the vinyl umbrellas on top.
Next, we cut out the middle part of the trampoline
to turn it into a table.
Then we put the tripod in the middle,
and use the deflated balls on either side as chairs.
Finish it off with the disco ball beneath the tent...
See? It's basically like the magazine, but hobo-chic...
Yeah, hobo-chic...
R-Right? Hobo-chic...
It's way too hobo!
Let's give up and at least buy a real tent.
Okay, Aki?
Add to Cart
Add to Favorites
GIANTTREE Tent
Lightweight Compact
Sold out   Color: Blue
Qty: 1
Whoa, this one's cheap! Only 980 yen!
But it says it's sold out.
We're coming up on Golden Week, after all.
We'll order now, and it'll be here
before we know it.
And... click.
Thank you.
Your order has been confirmed.
A confimation email has been sent.
GIANTTREE Tent Lightweight Compact
Qty: 1
Continue shopping
As long as we've got a tent,
we can figure out the rest somehow.
Sure will.
When we finally go camping,
we'll do all sorts of things!
Sure will.
Even this, that, and the other thing!
Sure will!
Wait!
When the heck did fall start?