Help us, please!
Survival Camp.
Isn't this great, Rin-chan?
We're going winter camping in the summer!
Strange Ecology
Though I would've liked to try
summer camping too.
I can't believe we're going camping in Australia!
Traveler's English Phrasebook
“Just kidding”...
That's weird, isn't that usually “it's a lie”?
One, two, three, go...
Traveler's English Phrasebook
One, two, three, go, and then jump...
Hey, Aki, aren't you a bit too worried?
David takes this private plane to visit my dad
all the time, so there's no need to worry.
Y-Yeah, you're right.
We can always turn back if you're that scared.
Wh-What?!
I-It's not that I'm scared or anything, it's just that...
First, spreading wings and flapping from the nest...
Second, softly, gently, fluttering to the ground...
What's that you're singing? It sounds pretty inte—
D-Don't crash!
C-Calm down! Calm down, Nadeshiko!
Got it? One, two, three, and go!
One, two, three, go!
Where...
...is this?
Rin-chan!
Thank goodness!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Where even is this? I'm not getting any cell service.
Can't see any buildings, either.
Everyone, listen up!
Judging from my experience,
I fear we're most likely...
Experience?
Most likely, we're lost in the South Sea,
on an isolated and unforgiving...
desert island!
Help me down.
The five are stranded on a mysterious,
uninhabited island.
Will these girls—who have only ever done
leisurely camping—
really be able to overcome
their extreme situation?
Of their fate,
only that song knows...
The Second Day ▲
It's so hot...
rumble
Aren't there any bananas or something
around here?
Banana.
Let's look somewhere else.
What are you doing?
Banana.
rumble
Pass me one too.
Sure.
There aren't even any boats passing by.
Yeah. I wonder what country we're closest to.
We're back.
Oh, how'd it go?
Not a soul around.
And in terms of food, this is all we could find.
Coconuts, huh?
Also, banana.
Hah?
Here, Nadeshiko-chan.
Thanks.
Here.
Oh, dear...
What'll we do?
What if we're stuck here forever?
No good being down about it.
I mean, look! Shima-san caught us a fish...
We've got some coconuts, too!
I'm sure we'll manage somehow.
Right, Ena-chan?
She's smiling in her sleep.
Saitou's just as usual.
Just as usual, let's do some camping!
Camping to survive...
Survival camp, huh?
rumble
So sweet!
I'm on my fifth one...
Same here!
Thanks, Banana-san!
Don't mention it.
How did you even find all these?
Hmph!
The bananas, you see, were calling to me.
What were they saying?
Let's see...
Banana
Maybe?
Rin-chan!
Got 'em.
All right!
The prep's all done!
Now we just take this,
dip it in some of our boiled seawater,
cook it on a stone, and...
all done!
Let's eat!
It's great!
Sure is, eh?
Delicious!
Tasty!
Fish really are in a league of their own
when it comes to food, huh?
I'm aiming for an even bigger one next time.
Third, in unfamiliar lands descending down...
Fourth, feeling the winds of night
causing your heart to shake...
Fifth, a chance encounter
with a blessed, yellow tree...
Sixth, a giant, big catch from the ocean blue...
That's the same song you were singing
on the airplane, right?
It's pretty weird.
My mom used to sing it from time to time.
I just kind of picked it up.
And when that happens,
you can't get it out of your head, right?
You got that right.
Oh, looks like they're just about ready.
Banana!
Tasty surprise succeeded!
They get so much sweeter when you cook them!
These are top-shelf sweets!
Unbeatable!
Can't we make something
with the banana leaves too?
I think they use them in Thai food or something.
Then tomorrow, let's use the banana leaves
to steam the fish!
Banana! Banana! Ba-na-na!
Over here, over here!
Nice banana!
Banana!
All right, here we go!
Seventh, lightheartedly playing in the waves...
Eighth, with coconuts for pillows on the beach...
Somehow it feels like we'll
be camping here forever!
Forever...
Tanuki monster!
R... Roe.
Evening primrose.
E... E...
Eel skewer!
Huh?
Ena-chan fell asleep.
Right in the middle of shiritori, huh?
Then I'll just go next.
R... R...
Roc.
C? Carp.
Paper form.
M... M...
Minobu manju!
U-Uroboros.
Spiny bitterling.
Gogh.
Houtou!
Deep-fried hot spring egg!
Lake Motosu!
Fujisan!
I ended with “n”...
W-Wait a second! This is no place
to be having fun camping!
Moreover, we're not camping!
We're stranded!
Help us, please!
Ninth, as memories of home come rushing back...
Ten leagues away from here, Fuji standing tall.