Green light... Red light.
Red Light,
Green Light
I only just noticed
Tattaima hajimete kizuita
Koi ni ochita no da naa
that I fell in love
24h kimiOkimiOkimiO
You are on my mind all day, day, day
Ishiki sezaru wo emasen!
and I can't do anything about it
Nanka
Somehow
Itsumo to chigau kimi to
while having an awkward conversation
Futari
with you
Gikochinai kaiwa masaka
you seem different from usual, could it be...
Ryouomoi
Mutual love?
Iya kataomoi
Nah, it's one-sided
Yabai! Shisen acchatta!!!
Oops, our glances met
Nani nani!? kono dokidoki!?
What's up with this excitement?
Shikoukairo gucchagucha konsen...
My train of thought slips into chaos
Konna koto hajimete da yo
This is the first time it has happened to me,
Netsu demo aru no kanaa
maybe I have a fever?
Kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
My love took a sudden turn
Acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
And I instantly blushed a deep red
Ba.ba...baka na!? Te ga furueru zo
N-n-no way! My hands are trembling
Kore ga zoku ni iu "koi" na no!?
Is this what's commonly referred to as "love"?
Yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
I st-st-stuttered through our conversation
Kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
Awkward silence, mmhmmhmhm
Kimi no
I want
Kimochi shiritai yo
to know your feelings
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Hatsukoi!!
My first love
Itsumo no tsuugakuro
on my normal way to school
Pikapika hikaru
glitters brightly
I DO fall in love!
Sora mo tobesou sa
I feel like I can fly in the sky
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Shoot! Shoot, shoot!
Homeroom is about to start!
I used "I was helping my
grandmother" the other day.
"My mother wasn't home"
isn't much of an excuse.
What should I do? How
can I get out of this?
Couldn't one car drive by?
How did I get stopped
by four red lights?
It'll be first period
when I enter...
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 40
What's with this obvious trap?
There's no way I'd
fall for a classic trap like...
Double!
What? Why am I being
punished for being late?
What did I do
to deserve this?
Besides being late...
Well, I can just sneak
in through the back.
There's no reason I
have to get yelled at.
I knew it! It's locked!
I know! Why don't I sneak
in through the lower door?
I'll enter silently,
like the wind,
and smoothly join the class...
Why is this happening?
I had a feeling
this would happen!
She's the only one who'd
do something like this!
If I quietly try to
enter from below,
I'll get in even more
trouble if I'm caught.
If I'm going to be discovered,
I might as well enter from above!
They put stained glass in!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Why am I running?
Running from the classroom
won't solve anything.
I have to go back...
That's right.
I need to figure out
the best entrance to use.
If I'm getting in trouble
no matter what I do,
I may as well make a grand frontal
assault, and fight to my last breath.
Wouldn't that be cool?
My best option...
is the chalkboard
eraser in the front!
I'll take an eraser to the face
while grinning ear to ear.
Good morning!
And the entire class
will burst into laughter.
What time do you think it is?
You're hopeless...
Hurry and take your seat.
It'll work!
That's right, Yukko.
You must be a bright
and cheerful clown!
Let's go!
And a very good morning to you!
Just kidding!
First period will be
in the LL room.
Soap
Daiku Bread
Invincible
Alien
Daiku Bread
I'm an invincible alien!
Why are you acting stupid?
You're not a grade schooler.
Invincible aliens are immune
to any and all attacks!
Sorry! Are you all right?
Blue
Note
Shut up!
Miles would turn in his grave!
Oh, sorry. We just got so into it.
You were listening, Sakamoto?
Was I listening?
What kind of torture is this?
It's ruining my ears!
I'm gonna play again. So listen, okay?
You listen to me!
Flowing noodles
in the park at noon.
I heard they were having
flowing noodles in the park,
so I decided to check it out.
I've only seen flowing
noodles on TV before,
so I'm really excited.
Do I have to stand near
the front to get any noodles?
I haven't eaten today,
so I'll stand near the
front and eat my fill!
Flowing
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 41
Here it comes!
What are you doing?
I've never seen such a lousy customer!
Next round, coming up.
Uh, e-excuse me, um...
What do you want?
Are you quitting before
you've had a bite?
Even if the law may
forgive you, I shall not!
Well, um... I don't
have any chopsticks.
Who do you think you are, kid?
Come on, let's go!
Um, sure.
I-I'm sorry, but these
have been used...
We're recycling.
Next round!
Time waits for no one!
I have no choice.
I'll use the back ends.
It's transient humor.
The next one will be different!
I'll show you true hell!
Don't expect us to
have infinite water!
So you'd better eat it all.
Excuse me...
Don't be such a wallflower!
Why not try to savor the flavor?
Stop dawdling!
It won't stay fresh forever!
You haven't changed a bit.
Egi Masaharu (51)
Flowing Noodle
Researcher
Masaharu...
Masaharu!
The moment I heard there were
flowing noodles in the park,
I knew it was you.
I've been doing this...
because I believed you
would return someday.
It's been thirty years since you left in
search of the perfect flowing noodles.
Did you find them?
I've eaten so many kinds of noodles,
I just don't know anymore...
I raided our savings to take this trip,
but the money's run out.
I'm sorry.
Please let the flowing noodles slide.
I will.
What are you looking at?!
This isn't a show!
I'm sorry,
but could you make like a
flowing noodle and flow away?
Short Thoughts
The first-years are all here?
Listen up.
Some people respond to praise,
and others respond to criticism.
I'll use my intuition to tell you apart.
Got it?
I respond to praise,
but I never receive any.
NASA
If I say it like that!
What!?
Whaaat!!?
Nano!
Look, look. I tried
tying up my hair.
Does it look good?
Professor! You look
a bit more mature.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 42
Hey, how much more
mature do I look?
What? You look pretty mature.
What about you?
How mature are you?
Oh, well... I don't
think I'm that mature.
Whoops! Yeah, I guess you aren't.
I'll have to clean this up for you.
And this.
Oh, Nano...
I'm still reading that...
Oh, Nano.
You, too, Sakamoto.
What are you doing?
You'll catch a cold.
What's gotten into you?
What are you planning?
Sakamoto...
What?
You'll catch a cold.
No, I won't!
If you're going to put
something on me, use a blanket.
Why would you use a book?
Sakamoto, you're always complaining.
What do you think you're doing?
I'll go do the laundry.
I'll do it.
It's okay, Professor.
I just have to turn the dial.
You're hopeless.
I'll turn it for you.
No, really. I just have to turn it...
I said I'd turn it, so I'm turning it!
U-um...
Thanks, I guess.
If you need anything
else, let me know.
O-okay.
Hooray!
Oh, dear.
Nano, you're
hopeless. Let me cook.
Oh, it's okay. I'm making
something right now...
I'll make something better.
No, wait! That's dangerous!
Come on. I'll do it.
It's okay.
No, it's not okay. Really!
Come on, come on.
Really, Professor. No!
Ow!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Are you okay, Mr. Sakamoto?
What are you doing?!
I-I'm sorry!
Sakamoto, you're hopeless,
walking there like that.
I'm not the hopeless one!
You two are the ones messing around!
Now now, Sakamoto, getting
angry won't help anything.
That doesn't make any sense!
Let's just make it again.
I'll do it.
No, the rest of the food will get cold,
so I'll make it quickly.
Oh, Nano... I'll do it.
Professor! That's dangerous!
You'll drop an egg!
It's okay.
Hey, watch out!
It's fine...
You're hopeless.
You're the hopeless one!
What's with this kid today?
I think she's trying to act mature.
I am mature.
Hey, kid.
What?
Did you know that mature
people don't eat snacks?
Ta-dah! It's actually just me!
Liar.
River Fishing
I hooked a big one!
A boot!
This is it!
A kettle!
This stuff's crazier than
fish would be, right?
If I knew I'd have this much fun,
I'd have invited someone else.
I'll come back.
Chic things.
Eating sushi with your bare hands.
Damn it...
I don't want to do my homework...
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 43
Why do I have to do
homework, anyway?
Well, my grades suck,
so I have to do it.
But I know I can fix them.
So I should be able to pass.
I think...
Then I'll graduate.
But I don't want to go all
the way to college, so I guess...
I'll get a job?
But I heard on TV the other day that it's tough to find a job.
Maybe it's harder to find
work without a degree...
High school.
College.
Employment.
And I can't get through it without taking a college entrance exam.
But...
I really don't want to study!
How will the stuff I'm studying now
help me in the future, anyway?
No, hold on.
What do I...
want to do?
"What I Want to Do" by Aioi Yuuko.
When I grow up,
I wanna be a frill-necked lizard.
Frill-necked... Frill-necked...
I don't want to study!
I don't want to study,
and I don't want to
be a frill-necked lizard!
Hold on.
If I became a lizard,
I wouldn't have to
worry about this stuff.
But if I'm becoming something else,
I should just become
a living national treasure
Clay-
like
subs-
tance
and be the center of attention.
Clay-
like
subs-
tance
How much does a living
national treasure make per month?
Paycheck
How do I become a
living national treasure?
And...
what is a living national treasure?
No, no, no.
I need to think realistically.
What do I want to be?
I can't think of anything.
Well, I'm still a high school freshman.
I've got three years to think about it.
If I still haven't found
anything by then, I'll...
go to college!
Exams!
Which leads back to...
I don't want to study!
No, no, no.
Being depressed won't
get me anywhere.
I can't think of anything because I'm thinking of what to be.
I should think of what I want to do!
What do I want to do?
Mom!
Quit your banging!
Do you know how late it is?
Well, I'm not good
at thinking too hard.
I'll just work on my homework!
Asa okite ha wo migaite atto yuuma gogo juuji
I wake up in the morning, brush my
teeth, and before I know it it's 10 PM
Kyou mo takusan waratta na takusan tokimeita na
We laughed and had a lot of fun today
Tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawaideru toki ni mo
and at times I and my friends chatted noisily like nitwits
Chirachira tte me ga au... guuzen da yo ne
When our eyes met, flutteringly... it must be coincidence
Hatsukoi nante ienai kyara ja nainda mon!
It's not in me to say this is my first love!
Nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
Hey, we'll see each other tomorrow, right?
Mabuta wo tojiru to kirakira kimi darake
If I close my eyes, all I see is a sparkling you
Kyou mo tanoshikatta ne aa koi shite da naa
Today was fun again, it must be love
Ureshii na ureshii na hajimemashite koigokoro
I'm so happy, so happy. Nice to meet you, awakening love.
Ashita mata aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you again tomorrow, so good night
Yume de sugu aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you in my dreams soon, so good night
Damn it.
I don't want to do my homework...
I'm a frill-necked lizard.
I'm really hard to
make with origami.
It might take a
couple of extra sheets
before you figure
out how to make me.
The next episode of Nichijou is episode 11.
Narration:     Nozawa Masako
Don't miss it!