Summer Heat
Sold Out
Man, it's hot... It's so hot!
Tanaka, you've been
saying "hot" this whole time.
It's already hot,
and pointing out how hot
it is just makes it feel hotter.
So, I forbid you from saying "hot".
Okay, okay.
It's blistering!
It's blistering, isn't it?
Just kidding!
But it's really
blistering, huh?
It's blistering!
Blistering!
Super blistering!
I guess I'll have to hit him.
Man, it's blistering. So blistering!
Blistering!
I only just noticed
Tattaima hajimete kizuita
Koi ni ochita no da naa
that I fell in love
24h kimiOkimiOkimiO
You are on my mind all day, day, day
Ishiki sezaru wo emasen!
and I can't do anything about it
Nanka
Somehow
Itsumo to chigau kimi to
while having an awkward conversation
Futari
with you
Gikochinai kaiwa masaka
you seem different from usual, could it be...
Ryouomoi
Mutual love?
Iya kataomoi
Nah, it's one-sided
Yabai! Shisen acchatta!!!
Oops, our glances met
Nani nani!? kono dokidoki!?
What's up with this excitement?
Shikoukairo gucchagucha konsen...
My train of thought slips into chaos
Konna koto hajimete da yo
This is the first time it has happened to me,
Netsu demo aru no kanaa
maybe I have a fever?
Kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
My love took a sudden turn
Acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
And I instantly blushed a deep red
Ba.ba...baka na!? Te ga furueru zo
N-n-no way! My hands are trembling
Kore ga zoku ni iu "koi" na no!?
Is this what's commonly referred to as "love"?
Yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
I st-st-stuttered through our conversation
Kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
Awkward silence, mmhmmhmhm
Kimi no
I want
Kimochi shiritai yo
to know your feelings
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Hatsukoi!!
My first love
Itsumo no tsuugakuro
on my normal way to school
Pikapika hikaru
glitters brightly
I DO fall in love!
Sora mo tobesou sa
I feel like I can fly in the sky
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Shiny!
Today, everything's
shining brightly!
The air, the people,
and even this classroom...
Because today...
I actually did my homework!
I'll show it to Mio.
What?
Wha-wha-wha-wha-wha-WHAT?
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 48
It's gone!
No, no, no! That's impossible!
I finally did my homework, for once!
Why? Why, why, why?
Why is it gone?!
Well, I'll just copy hers.
Mio?
Wait.
Hold on.
Just hold on.
Today's homework...
was a worksheet!
What's wrong,
Yukko? It's early.
I forgot my homework...
I'm just hoping that
aliens invade our class...
You forgot to do it again?
Don't insult me!
I did my homework,
but I forgot to bring it!
I wasn't insulting you.
You mean the literature
worksheet, right?
Maybe it got stuck between
something in your bag.
Why not double check?
I already looked
a bunch of times.
There's no way it's...
Oh?
Oh!
Oh...
my god!
What's a rice cake fair?!
What is that?
Th-there, there.
Look, maybe there's
a worksheet in the podium.
No way! You found one?
Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it!
You're going back for it?
You'll never make it in time!
I know... but I'm still going!
Class is starting.
Take your seats.
Idiom
Twist... twist... twist... twist...
Turn, turn, turn, turn...
Slow and steady wins the race.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 49
I was sent to stand
in the hall again.
Go-Soccer
Club
Why do I always
forget my homework?
I even did my homework
today, but I still forgot it.
You're a blockhead, God...
Business Card
Sakamoto...
Here's my business card.
Professor
What's this?
What do I do with this?
What is this?
Professor
What do I do with it?
Vending Machine
I'm sorry...
What's wrong,
Tachibana Misato?
Wh-what?
Some new drinks came out,
so I was thinking
about which one to buy!
I see.
Perhaps this one—
Why would I listen to you?
If it doesn't suit your taste,
perhaps you should
purchase the other one.
Please excuse me.
It's not like I bought this one just because you recommended it!
I heard some stalls
were setting up nearby,
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 50
so I decided to check them out.
I was looking for
a shooting gallery.
I've only seen one on TV before,
so I'm very excited.
But I only have 500 yen.
I wonder if it's enough.
Just 5,000,000 yen per shot.
Lucky me, I have
exactly 500 yen.
I wanted to get
some yakisoba, too,
but I came here today for this.
They only have
caramel and eggplant.
Um, is this everything?
What do you mean by that?
We only carry brand-name goods.
I've already spent
what little money I had.
I have to take
home something.
Miss, you shouldn't start
off with the expensive ones!
They won't fall over easily.
Expensive ones?
Start with something
within your reach!
Within my reach?
The only other choice is caramel!
Close!
The caramel must
be glued down, too.
A few more millimeters,
and you would've had it.
Miss, you're pretty good at this.
I don't suppose you're
a professional gunner?
Just kidding!
This eggplant
won't budge an inch...
C'mon what's
with the long face?
You don't think I've
rigged the game, do you?
We might be stingy,
but lively and honest service
is our stall's hallmark!
No, you've definitely
done something to this!
What is that?!
Hey, hey, look at that!
There's a nail...
I can see the nail!
Wouldn't that
make this rigged?
Why don't you say anything?
And how could you do this?
You were so lively
until just a minute ago!
You must have rigged
the caramel, too!
Why are you pretending to be asleep?
I only have one shot left.
What am I supposed to aim for?
Don't come back again.
What the hell?
Things we think are cool!
Aioi
Mio! Ready?
Nice catch!
Aioi
Oh! SuperBall!
Things we think are cool!
Shoot, so close!
Wow!
Oh! Slipstream!
Thanks.
This old amusement park
is a lot of fun, isn't it?
I'm glad we came.
I'm getting some juice,
so can I have my wallet?
Oh, right.
I'm holding it for you.
Yeah, thanks.
If I had it, I'd lose it.
Yeah, you're right.
Huh?
Wh-what? What?
What? What? What?
I thought it was in here...
It appears that I've
dropped your wallet.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 51
Hey, it might be at
the lost and found!
How much was in it?
4,016 yen.
That's specific...
Lost and Found
It's a brown wallet,
with a snake skin inside.
Here it is.
I'm glad they had it.
I know, right? For a while
there, I was worried.
The following person is lost.
A girl wearing a denim shirt
tucked into denim shorts
with a denim hat is
looking for her mother.
If you have any information,
please contact the
lost persons center.
I really don't like haunted houses.
There it is!
Say "cheese".
Daiku-ya
Coffee Shop
Three lattes for
takeout. Is that all?
Oh, um...
Could I also get this,
this, and this, please?
Izumi
Uh, excuse me.
Could you give me a name, please?
It's Sakurai.
That's not the name I meant...
Oh, right. Sorry.
It's Izumi. I'm Sakurai Izumi.
Uh, I wasn't asking because
you gave me your surname.
People always tell me that both
of my names sound like surnames...
Actually, I was asking
about the product name.
The product name?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
Oh, um... I'm sorry...
Family Restaurant
Ah, that was delicious...
Chopstick Stand
I ate a ton.
Now we just wait for dessert
to make its appearance.
Right.
Oh! Me too.
I did it!
Me, too.
As amazing as always, Mai!
What about you, Yukko?
Are you finished?
Huh?
A crane?
Nano, look!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 52
Ta-dah.
I stuck one on myself, too.
Now we match.
You're right.
I'm you for a day,
so whatever you do,
don't call me Professor.
Got it, Nano.
That was quick!
Done already, Professor?
Nano, you just
called me Professor.
Huh? But didn't you just
take off your key?
I'm just taking a break!
Today, I'm Nano.
Okay.
Professor... I mean,
Nano, would you
like to play a game?
Okay! What are we doing?
You'll be me, and I'll be you.
We'll trade roles.
I'll play!
Okay, Professor... I mean,
Nano, put on your key.
Okay!
And since I'm the professor,
let's remove my key.
Not gonna happen.
What do you want to play?
How about cards?
This snack is delicious.
I was saving that!
Right now...
I'm...
the professor.
I don't understand!
I'll be you, but if you're
me, you'll eat my snacks,
so just be you!
Well, now that I'm Nano again,
I'll go grocery
shopping for dinner.
I'll go, too!
I'm not buying any snacks.
I want shark chocolate
and strawberry juice.
I'm not buying those.
Buy them.
No.
Hey, don't forget my food.
The Shinonome household passed
another peaceful day.
Killing Time
If you use English
from here on, you lose.
Okay.
Mio, you just used English.
You didn't say
start, so I'm safe.
I guess I should use
a bunch of English
before I say to start.
You know a bunch of English?
Okay.
Short Thoughts
Bubbly, carbonated drinks
make you feel awake.
Unintentional
I fell asleep.
It looks like Sleeping Beauty
woke up without a kiss.
How?
What do you mean?
Asa okite ha wo migaite atto yuuma gogo juuji
I wake up in the morning, brush my
teeth, and before I know it it's 10 PM
Kyou mo takusan waratta na takusan tokimeita na
We laughed and had a lot of fun today
Tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawaideru toki ni mo
and at times I and my friends chatted noisily like nitwits
Chirachira tte me ga au... guuzen da yo ne
When our eyes met, flutteringly... it must be coincidence
Hatsukoi nante ienai kyara ja nainda mon!
It's not in me to say this is my first love!
Nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
Hey, we'll see each other tomorrow, right?
Mabuta wo tojiru to kirakira kimi darake
If I close my eyes, all I see is a sparkling you
Kyou mo tanoshikatta ne aa koi shite da naa
Today was fun again, it must be love
Ureshii na ureshii na hajimemashite koigokoro
I'm so happy, so happy. Nice to meet you, awakening love.
Ashita mata aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you again tomorrow, so good night
Yume de sugu aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you in my dreams soon, so good night
Welcome home,
master. I'm cider.
I'll enchant these bubbles
with a spell to make me delicious...
The next episode of Nichijou is episode 13.
Narration:     Korogi Satomi
Don't miss it.