I'm hungry...
That kid is up to
something ridiculous again.
Well, I guess I wouldn't mind
falling for a trap like this.
The bait's worth it.
You fell for it! You fell for it!
Damn it... she really got me!
This was going to be for lunch.
Now we don't have anything.
Sakamoto...
You're guilty, too!
No, you said you
wanted to eat it.
I didn't say that!
Good morning.
What are you talking about?
But you ate it.
It's hot again today.
After school, let's get
ice cream near the station.
Good idea.
Hey, kid.
Don't you think the girl
wants to go to school?
Don't go!
What's gotten into you?
He said you'd leave me.
What? Who told you that?
Sakamoto.
That's not what I said!
Nano, are you going somewhere?
I was thinking of
going shopping soon.
We don't have
anything for lunch now.
I'll go with you!
I'm not buying you anything.
I want shark chocolate!
No.
Buy some shark chocolate!
I told you, I'm not
buying you anything.
Come on, buy some!
No.
Sakamoto said to buy some.
I never said that.
I only just noticed
Tattaima hajimete kizuita
Koi ni ochita no da naa
that I fell in love
24h kimiOkimiOkimiO
You are on my mind all day, day, day
Ishiki sezaru wo emasen!
and I can't do anything about it
Nanka
Somehow
Itsumo to chigau kimi to
while having an awkward conversation
Futari
with you
Gikochinai kaiwa masaka
you seem different from usual, could it be...
Ryouomoi
Mutual love?
Iya kataomoi
Nah, it's one-sided
Yabai! Shisen acchatta!!!
Oops, our glances met
Nani nani!? kono dokidoki!?
What's up with this excitement?
Shikoukairo gucchagucha konsen...
My train of thought slips into chaos
Konna koto hajimete da yo
This is the first time it has happened to me,
Netsu demo aru no kanaa
maybe I have a fever?
Kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
My love took a sudden turn
Acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
And I instantly blushed a deep red
Ba.ba...baka na!? Te ga furueru zo
N-n-no way! My hands are trembling
Kore ga zoku ni iu "koi" na no!?
Is this what's commonly referred to as "love"?
Yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
I st-st-stuttered through our conversation
Kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
Awkward silence, mmhmmhmhm
Kimi no
I want
Kimochi shiritai yo
to know your feelings
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Hatsukoi!!
My first love
Itsumo no tsuugakuro
on my normal way to school
Pikapika hikaru
glitters brightly
I DO fall in love!
Sora mo tobesou sa
I feel like I can fly in the sky
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Mio, good morning...
What's wrong, Yukko?
You can barely stand!
Since I woke up,
now that ya mention it...
Your speech is broken.
You look feverish.
Why did you come
to school like this?
Well,
you know...
I thought I'd perform that
magic trick I told you about...
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 53
What are you talking about?
This is the first I've heard of it.
This isn't the time for magic.
But I practiced.
When you see my magic,
you won't believe your eyes...
It'll be great—
I already can't believe my eyes.
Why don't you sit d—
Yukko...
I...
already see the trick!
I'll just pretend
I didn't see anything.
She came all the way
here in her condition.
But why is Yukko
trying to show off a...
I-it's out in the open!
Your trick is out in the open!
It flew away!
Tissues...
All right, here we go...
O-okay.
Geez, what am I doing?
I just grabbed that on instinct...
So... okay... first...
She hasn't noticed that the
dove and the stick are missing.
How sick are you?
I'll pass a cigarette
through a hundred yen coin.
The hole... is already open.
They're all... aces of hearts.
Right now,
something flew out of her mouth...
What sort of trick
are you trying to...
Yukko!
Yukko...
Rest in peace.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 54
I'm off to the supermarket.
I'll go with you!
You didn't behave,
so I'm not buying
you anything today.
Poor Sakamoto.
She's talking to you.
Let's go.
What are you buying?
Fish, I suppose.
I wonder what I should get...
What? Not today, Professor.
What? But it's not a snack.
Even if it's not a snack,
I'm not buying it.
Then I don't know what to buy.
You're set on buying
something, aren't you?
Shark Sponge Cake
Nano! It's shark sponge cake.
It's a food stand.
They look pretty
good. Let's try some.
Did you forget
already? Not today.
But I'm buying it for Sakamoto.
Mr. Sakamoto also misbehaved,
so he doesn't get anything, either.
But I meant it's really for you...
I made a mistake.
I said no!
If I give in now,
she'll just do this again.
All right, Professor. Let's go.
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
I must steel my heart!
But...
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
But I have to...
But...
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
No, no. I mustn't.
Maybe a little...
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
No! No!
But...
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
No, no...
But...
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
Delicious!
You bought her something.
I'm sorry. I lost.
This kid is always throwing
tantrums to get her way.
Maybe I should scold her.
Hey, kid. Why don't you
learn some self-control?
I have!
No, you haven't!
The Shinonome household
passed another peaceful day.
80 Point Mongolian
80 points is great!
If you really try, you can do it.
Well...
What is it?
What's the secret
behind your high score?
Oh, there's no secret!
What? Come on,
tell me your secret...
80 points, 80 points.
Hey, Yukko. Ow...
Stop it!
Secret
Ow...
Do you want me to tell
you how I got 80 points?
I don't really care. I got a 96.
80 points...
It takes tremendous effort...
...and heart.
Shut up.
A Little Miracle
Aioi.
Uh...
What...?
Hooray!!
Contemporary Japanese Quiz
Reality
Dad, I'm here to make dinner.
Mom's still traveling, isn't she?
Thank you.
Hello.
Hello, Mi.
I'll play with my
grandson all day,
and forget the troubles of reality.
Mi, what do you want to do today?
Hey, hey, where's our official seal?
What?
Hey, where's the official seal?
Where are you
hiding it? Tell me!
Is it in this bookshelf?
Hey, where's the seal?
Hey, where is it? Where is it?
This is... worse than reality...
Come out, come out,
wherever you are...
You're late!
What time did you think
you were supposed to get here?
Sorry, sorry.
I wanted to go on the bus,
but instead I went with the flow.
Let's keep going all
the way to Okachimachi.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 55
Nano...
Hey, Nano, Nano.
What is it, Professor?
I need to use the
bathroom a little bit.
Come with me.
Come on, let's go. Come on, let's go.
Hey, Nano. Hey, hey...
Professor, that's not right.
What?
Borscht is a food!
Not that...
I need to use the bathroom.
Hey, Nano. Nano, hey...
Just go!
D-did you just...
It's okay. It was just a little.
Hurry up and go
to the bathroom.
I'm going to sleep.
Go!
Kindly, Sakamoto
did not say anything.
Geez, kids are so hopeless.
Going to the bathroom alone
at night during a storm...
is just too much for her.
Because she's just a kid.
I'll go with her,
and remind her...
just how grateful
she should be to me.
Hey, kid.
I'll go with you.
Sakamoto, you're small and
weak, so you don't have to.
Don't you think the girl
wants to go to school?
Huh? Professor,
you came over here?
Nano, let's go to the
bathroom together.
But I don't need to go...
I'm just a little scared,
so let's go together.
Why didn't you wake me up?
I tried.
I hear banging.
Maybe someone's here.
It's probably just the chimney.
The rain's coming
down really hard.
Nano, what's wrong?
Hey, Nano. Hey.
Hey?
Professor... Professor...
There's thunder.
I'm here. It's okay.
Hurry up, so we
can go back to bed.
Okay.
It's scary to go alone,
but it's okay if we're together.
You're right.
Nano, do you want
to go to school?
What?
No, I'll stay at home.
But Sakamoto said
you wanted to go!
Well...
Things we think are cool!
80!
Ugh.
Short Thoughts
A month passes quickly,
but Sunday seems so far away.
Elated
Next stop, 80 points, 80 points.
The exit is on the right.
Shut up.
I'll sing you an 80s
number for 80 points.
Shut up.
80 points, huzzah!
Go to hell!
Eden
Quiet down!
I'm announcing the
average test score.
The average score
was 92 points!
Yukko.
Don't!
Just don't...
Excellent Luck
What are you doing, kid?!
What are you doing?
Stop playing around,
and help me fold the laundry.
Starting tomorrow,
you can go to school.
What?
Really?
Why? What's gotten into you?
It's the right thing to do.
Hooray!
Now I won't get scolded for
eating lots of snacks at lunch.
But, Professor,
I can't wear an elementary
school bag with this.
You're going to high school.
But, Professor,
if you don't remove
my key, I can't go to...
Here's your uniform.
Professor, I love you!
Nano! Nano! Nano!
Professor! Professor! Professor!
Nano! Nano! Nano! Nano! Nano! Nano!
Nano!
Professor!
Nano! Nano!
Professor! Professor!
Professor!
Asa okite ha wo migaite atto yuuma gogo juuji
I wake up in the morning, brush my
teeth, and before I know it it's 10 PM
Kyou mo takusan waratta na takusan tokimeita na
We laughed and had a lot of fun today
Tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawaideru toki ni mo
and at times I and my friends chatted noisily like nitwits
Chirachira tte me ga au... guuzen da yo ne
When our eyes met, flutteringly... it must be coincidence
Hatsukoi nante ienai kyara ja nainda mon!
It's not in me to say this is my first love!
Nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
Hey, we'll see each other tomorrow, right?
Mabuta wo tojiru to kirakira kimi darake
If I close my eyes, all I see is a sparkling you
Kyou mo tanoshikatta ne aa koi shite da naa
Today was fun again, it must be love
Ureshii na ureshii na hajimemashite koigokoro
I'm so happy, so happy. Nice to meet you, awakening love.
Ashita mata aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you again tomorrow, so good night
Yume de sugu aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you in my dreams soon, so good night
I'm a string of international flags.
People often ask if I'm a string of
international flags, or the flags of all nations,
but both are correct.
"Don't worry about
the small things"
was the last thing my father said.
The next episode of Nichijou is episode 14.
Narration:     Ogata Megumi
Don't miss it.