Literature
11:30~12:20
The Japanese test is over.
They're really happy.
They must have put
a lot into this test.
How heartwarming.
The test is over...
Rock, paper, scissors!
That's not rock-paper-scissors!
I'm dreaming.
I must be dreaming...
It's over... It's all over!
My parents will give a bag of rice to everyone in this classroom!
Thanks, rice merchant!
We're getting married.
Come on, everyone! Lend a hand.
Ready, and...
What are you doing?
I only just noticed
Tattaima hajimete kizuita
Koi ni ochita no da naa
that I fell in love
24h kimiOkimiOkimiO
You are on my mind all day, day, day
Ishiki sezaru wo emasen!
and I can't do anything about it
Nanka
Somehow
Itsumo to chigau kimi to
while having an awkward conversation
Futari
with you
Gikochinai kaiwa masaka
you seem different from usual, could it be...
Ryouomoi
Mutual love?
Iya kataomoi
Nah, it's one-sided
Yabai! Shisen acchatta!!!
Oops, our glances met
Nani nani!? kono dokidoki!?
What's up with this excitement?
Shikoukairo gucchagucha konsen...
My train of thought slips into chaos
Konna koto hajimete da yo
This is the first time it has happened to me,
Netsu demo aru no kanaa
maybe I have a fever?
Kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
My love took a sudden turn
Acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
And I instantly blushed a deep red
Ba.ba...baka na!? Te ga furueru zo
N-n-no way! My hands are trembling
Kore ga zoku ni iu "koi" na no!?
Is this what's commonly referred to as "love"?
Yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
I st-st-stuttered through our conversation
Kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
Awkward silence, mmhmmhmhm
Kimi no
I want
Kimochi shiritai yo
to know your feelings
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Hatsukoi!!
My first love
Itsumo no tsuugakuro
on my normal way to school
Pikapika hikaru
glitters brightly
I DO fall in love!
Sora mo tobesou sa
I feel like I can fly in the sky
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Oh, Mio.
Good morning.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 35
No, no, no, no.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on...
Aren't you going to be all,
"Why are you wearing that?"
Geez, you're still
mad at me, aren't you?
For putting a knight
in your mont blanc...
It wasn't like I couldn't
eat it, so it doesn't matter.
Like hell it doesn't!
I was looking forward
to that mont blanc!
Why? Why? Why on earth
would you do that? I don't get it!
Why would you
put a knight in it?
Well, I thought it
would look cool.
Head!
She can never take a joke...
That idiot.
They only make ten of
those mont blancs a day.
She always messes with me without thinking about what she's doing.
Now that she's in college,
she really should
learn some sympathy.
But to tell the truth,
I'm thinking about letting my
sister's stupidity slide for today.
Because I've been hiding a shortcake
that they only make five times a day...
King.
Checkmate!
My strawberry!
My rare, only-made-five-times-per-day strawberry,
that I've been looking
forward to since last night!
My... my... strawberry!
Where's the strawberry?
Where's the sweet treat that
belongs in this position?
Amen...
Gut!
Waah, you idiot!
A shortcake without its
strawberry is just bread.
It's just regular sweet bread.
I don't want bread.
Happy birthday to me.
Happy birthday dear me...
Happy birthday to me!
Sister...
Mio...
It's not your birthday!
Faculty Office
Quiz
Soup  and No odles
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 36
I've always wanted to come here.
You said you saw it in a magazine?
Yeah, yeah! Look, I've
even got my coupon.
You don't need to show us now.
I'll have the herring soup.
Oh? Chosen like a
true connoisseur...
Without the herring.
That's just plain soup.
Mio, what are you having?
I'll just have regular cold noodles.
That's the safe choice...
As expected from an amateur.
It doesn't matter.
What are you having?
I think I'll try the fried
summer vegetable bowl.
Ordering a rice dish at a soup
restaurant is pretty bold, right?
Yeah, pretty cool.
Isn't it? And it's a seasonal dish.
If I don't have it now, who knows
when I'll get another chance?
Wouldn't that be in a year?
No, no, no...
You've got to dream bigger, Mio.
The important thing is
the present... right now.
I see.
Maybe you're a bit too
young to understand.
Yeah, yeah.
Excuse me.
I'll take your orders.
One herring soup, one
order of cold noodles, and...
And one fried summer vegetable bowl.
That's one herring soup, one order of cold
noodles, and one fried summer vegetable bowl.
Just a moment.
Apparently, they make
their own noodles by hand.
This place is the real deal.
What are the
"buckwheat dumplings"?
They're those squishy things
made from buckwheat powder.
Oh, really?
Thank you for waiting.
Here is your herring soup
and your cold noodles.
You two go ahead and eat.
Thanks.
Before it gets cold.
Mine was already cold.
My order was from
the limited menu.
They must be taking their
time to carefully prepare it.
They're taking a while
for yours, Yukko.
Maybe it takes time
to fry the vegetables.
Or maybe they're out
getting the vegetables now.
Ah, that would
totally explain the wait.
This place has lots
of a la carte dishes.
Really?
Yes?
It wasn't hers.
Too bad.
Goddamn!
Yukko, calm down!
Why should I calm down?
This is taking way too long!
I don't care about their reputation!
They might keep the flavor,
but they're not keeping the spirit!
What are you talking about?
I'm going to lodge a complaint!
Thank you for waiting.
Don't you agree this took too...
Thank you.
You can read a
magazine or something.
I'll be finished soon.
Things we think are cool!
Young shogi players!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 37
I've got my mosquito traps.
I thought if I waited, it would go away.
But it never vanishes,
the midnight Mogami River.
There! There! There!
Well, even the smallest mosquito
will turn from being trodden on.
Let's relax and sleep peacefully.
I'm talking to you!
Chest!
I've committed a petty murder.
I'll kill you!
No matter how many I kill,
they never learn their lesson.
I'm starting to lose my mind!
Mom!
We can't live here anymore!
We have to move!
Do you have any
idea what time it is?
Shut up and go to bed!
Scatterred sushi.
Go.
Scittored sasho.
No.
Scat-ter-ed-su-shi.
Go.
Scit-tor-ed-sa-sho.
No, no!
Scat.
Ter.
Ed.
Su.
Shi.
Yes!
Scattered sushi.
Go.
Scittored sasho.
Self Control
No Shouting
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 38
Sakamoto, look, look!
Winner
The "Winner" on my popsicle
is sticking out from the bottom.
Huh?
What do you mean, huh?
You shouldn't be
eating that thing.
What do you mean, that thing?
You won't have
room for your dinner.
Omelette rice!
You're definitely still a kid if you're
getting excited over a winning popsicle.
It wasn't just any winning popsicle.
It was a super rare one, with the
"Winner" coming out from the bottom!
Top or bottom,
a winner's a winner.
If you eat enough of
them, you're bound to win.
Geez, it sure is
blissful to be a child...
Getting so worked up
over a winning popsicle.
A crab!
I hardly ever see this
super rare critter!
I'll save it for last.
Thank you for the food.
Huh? You haven't touched
your food, Professor.
Did you snack a
lot this afternoon?
I'm sorry.
Oh, how much did you eat?
All of them.
All of them? You ate all
the snacks for the month?
That wasn't a compliment!
You're unbelievable.
But Sakamoto told me to eat them.
Mr. Sakamoto!
Sakamoto told me that food
spoils fast during the summer.
That has nothing to do with it.
But you said there's
always room for dessert.
What are you, an office lady?
Mr. Sakamoto!
Why are you taking her seriously?
I'm innocent!
If we're talking black or white, I'm white!
You're pure black.
That's right.
Hey, I was born this way!
Just forget it.
There's nothing else to say.
You're not getting
any strawberry juice.
I won't eat any more snacks!
No.
I'll give you my winning popsicle!
I don't want it.
I'll eat my vegetables!
That goes without saying.
I'll remove your key.
What?
I-I'll forgive you this time.
But if you do it again,
no snacks for a month.
Okay!
Well, then...
I get the feeling that if I give this
to her now, everything will fall apart!
You can have your juice
after you remove my key.
Turn around.
Okay!
Loser
Your right hand is a loser.
Why did you put this here?
That wasn't a compliment!
You always act without thinking.
Before you act, please
think a little more.
You aren't listening!
A Little Miracle
Rock, paper, scissors!
Short Thoughts
If you search for it,
you'll find everything.
Mio.
I'm glad you're here.
What is it, sis?
Something came up.
I was hoping you'd help out the
neighborhood association for me.
What? Ask Mom to help you.
Mom went out to play kick
volleyball with her friends.
And they said they'd pay 10,000 yen.
Thanks.
Neighborhood
Association
Rice Cake Fair
10,000 yen sounds pretty
good for a part time job.
I don't have anything
to do, so I'll check it out.
Oh, what's that?
It's super cute!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 39
They tricked me!
This is terrible. What is this?
What on earth is this?
How did this happen?
A
Rice Cake Fair
They're white, pure white...
I can't believe the
Neighborhood Association
Come one, come all.
would put two people
selling rice cakes on the street.
It's embarrassing!
This is embarrassing!
Everyone that passes
by looks at me with pity.
They're expecting me
to attract customers?
This is their mascot, Mr. Rice Cake?
He doesn't have eyes or a
mouth. It's a plain white mask.
This isn't Mr. Rice Cake.
It's just a rice cake!
Wait a minute.
This Rice Cake Fair...
isn't fair at all!
I'm sorr-
This is a total out.
What is that thing? It's creepy!
Take that!
Stop it. That hurts, so cut it out!
H-hey, stop! Stop it...
my lower half is unprotected!
My lower half is unprotected!
Hey, stop it!
Cut it out!
It's angry! Run!
Yeah!
Something's wrong
with that thing!
What am I going to do?
Yukko!
Please don't ruin
the rice cake's image.
I can't watch this.
Come on, take it off.
Geez, part-timers...
Why don't you take care of the store,
instead of just standing there?
I'm making 10,000 yen...
I have to suck it up.
I want to go home.
I miss being at home.
Are these things even selling?
They're lined up really carefully...
Excuse me.
How much does one cost?
A customer!
Um...
How much are we
charging for these?
Excuse me. How much
does one rice cake...
I shouldn't have done this.
I won't run. You
can't make me run.
Uh...
Take one for free.
Lucky me.
Asa okite ha wo migaite atto yuuma gogo juuji
I wake up in the morning, brush my
teeth, and before I know it it's 10 PM
Kyou mo takusan waratta na takusan tokimeita na
We laughed and had a lot of fun today
Tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawaideru toki ni mo
and at times I and my friends chatted noisily like nitwits
Chirachira tte me ga au... guuzen da yo ne
When our eyes met, flutteringly... it must be coincidence
Hatsukoi nante ienai kyara ja nainda mon!
It's not in me to say this is my first love!
Nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
Hey, we'll see each other tomorrow, right?
Mabuta wo tojiru to kirakira kimi darake
If I close my eyes, all I see is a sparkling you
Kyou mo tanoshikatta ne aa koi shite da naa
Today was fun again, it must be love
Ureshii na ureshii na hajimemashite koigokoro
I'm so happy, so happy. Nice to meet you, awakening love.
Ashita mata aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you again tomorrow, so good night
Yume de sugu aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you in my dreams soon, so good night
Mosquito
Hey!
The Shinonome household passed
another peaceful day.
Hello, King here!
Shogi reminds me of Mr. Habu.
Mr. Habu reminds me of Mr. Mango!
I feel like taking
a trip to Okinawa.
It'll all work out!
Narration:     Hirano Aya
The next episode of Nichijou is episode 10.
Don't miss it!