All right! Let's go!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Glico
Looks like I'm first.
Pi-ne-ap-p-le!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Okay! Here I come!
Not like that!
The rules are that you
go one step at a time!
I know!
G-li-co...
...'s bo-nus prize.
Hey!
Huh? What's wrong?
You can't just add words!
Huh? Aren't you supposed to add words?
What do you think, Mai?
Fifty-fifty.
All right. That's fine.
But if you're going to play by your rules,
I'll play by mine as well.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Hey! Next up is Mai!
Chi-yo-ta...
Ni-ke-ra-ha-to...
Ho-ra-su-te...
No-ha-te-ki...
Ra-to-na-ri-ha-shi-te-to.
The Spell of Restoration.
I only just noticed
Tatta ima hajimete kizuita
Koi ni ochita no dano
that I fell in love
Nijuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
You are on my mind all day, day, day
Ishiki sezaru wo emasen
and I can't do anything about it
Nanka
Somehow
Itsumo to chigau kimi to
while having an awkward conversation
Futari
with you
Gikochinai kaiwa masaka
you seem different from usual, could it be...
Ryouomoi
Mutual love?
Iya kataomoi
Nah, it's is one-sided
Yabai shisen acchatta
Oops, our glances met
Nani nani kono dokidoki
What's up with this excitement?
Shikoukairo guchagucha konsen
My train of thought slips into chaos
Konna koto hajimete da yo
This is the first time it has happened to me,
Netsu demo aru no kana
maybe I have a fever?
Kyuuten shogedashichatta koigokoro
Suddenly my first love wavered
Atchuuma kao hakka de makka ka
And I instantly blushed a deep red
Ba-ba-baka na te ga furueru zo
My s-s-stupid hands are trembling
Kore ga zoku ni iu koi na no
Is this what's commonly referred to as love?
Ya-ya yacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
The conversation we h-h-had goes in circles
Kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
Awkward silence, mmhmmhmhm
Kimi no
I want
Kimochi shiritai yo
to know your feelings
Ka-ka-ka-ka-kataomoi
O-o-o-o-one-sided love
Hatsukoi
My first love
Itsumo no tsuugakuro
on my normal way to school
Pikapika hikaru
glitters brightly
I will fall in love
Sore mo tobesou sa
I feel like I can fly in the sky
Ka-ka-ka-ka-kataomoi
O-o-o-o-one-sided love
It's stopped.
Mom, I told you to
wake me up at seven!
Mom!
A
I've gone to play kick volleyball
with my friends from the
Neighborhood Association.
Dear Mio,
Love, Mom
Kick... Kick Volleyball...
Nichijou: Everyday Life
Part 5
Shoot!
I'm the class officer today!
Why did my alarm clock's
batteries have to die today?
If it's running low on batteries,
why can't it just tell me in advance?
That piece of junk!
Either way, I'll run as fast as
I can. If I hurry, then maybe...
Back there, just then, there was...
something weird!
And I get the feeling that...
it's coming!
What the heck?
This sprinter...
Why... is it... following me...
It passed me!
Excuse me.
Did you drop this wooden fish?
Was it a golden fish?
I'm done for.
If I don't do this, I'm done for...
I'm sorry!
Sometimes, I'm a bear.
And other times, I'm...
a... bear...
But my true identity is...
S-Sorry, sorry!
Ta-dah! That's right, it's your sister!
I was wearing your school's
uniform, so you didn't notice.
That was f-
What a spectacular corkscrew
we're seeing this morning.
It's quite amazing!
It was dark at night,
so I had a tough time
stopping your alarm clock.
That was you?!
Hey now, don't be like that.
Here, I'll treat you to ramen.
That's my money!
Chi-yo-ta...
Spell
Ni-ke-ra-ha-to...
Ho-ra-su-te...
No-ha-te-ki...
Ra-to-na-ri-ha-shi-te-to...
Please enter the Spell of Restoration.
Incorrect spell.
Nichijou: Everyday Life Part 6
A shark.
Shark...
I'm home.
Huh? What are you doing, Professor?
Nano, that cloud looks like a shark.
Which one?
Oh, it really does.
Isn't it cool?
It is.
Oh, that's right.
Professor, I bought some milk.
Hey, 4.5%? 4.5%?
Yes, it's extra rich.
But why the sudden craving for milk?
Well, you see...
I got a roll cake!
What kind of modifications
have you been making to me?
Just roll cake.
I don't understand.
Nano, 4.5% milk!
I don't mean the milk!
Why do I have to live
with a roll cake in my arm?
It's so cold and tasty...
That's not the issue!
If someone outside
saw this, I'd...
Professor...
What?
Um... could I have some, too?
Sure.
Just a minute.
Here you go!
Thank you very much.
Um, could I also have
some roll cake, too?
Oh, yeah! Nano, you
can have a sweet bun.
Here you go.
It went back in!
Oh, sorry. I pushed
the button on accident.
Why did you make this?
If this popped out in public,
what do you think would happen?
What would happen?
Without a doubt...
Wasn't Commando
Sambomaster the best?
Yeah, right?
It was the be...
I'll give you a music
playback function, too.
That's not what I want!
Why do you want to modify me so much?
Please listen to me...
I'm full!
What is it?
Sweet bun...
No. You already ate your roll cake.
What? Professor?
Fine! I still have a log cake!
You don't mean... Where
is it this time? Top? Bottom?
P-please, just put them all in
the refrigerator to begin with!
No!
What?
Shinonome Laboratory
First comes rock!
Then comes paper...
You can't throw all of them,
rock, paper, scissors!
I'm so tired...
Mio!
Why are you smiling like that?
Let me see your notebook!
Did you forget your homework again?
It's kinda embarrassing...
You'll have a tough
time on your exams again.
I know! But just this once!
Please, it'll be the last time! Okay?
Yukko, you said the
same thing last time.
A warrior never goes
back on her word!
You just did.
Wh-What? Oh, really?
Oh well...
Just this once, all right?
I'm serious.
I know.
Everyone should have
their own personal Mio.
Yukko, I got that
thing I told you about.
I'll give these back as soon
as I've copied them, okay?
Really? Show me, show me!
Huh? Did I forget something?
Last night, I finished
my homework, and...
I finished my homework, and...
I happened to doodle...
I happened to doodle something!
And I forgot to erase it!
I won't let you do that.
I forgot!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 7
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 7
I know, right?
Totally.
Yukko!
Sorry, sorry! I forgot
my homework, too!
I can't believe it!
So, I'll be taking that back now.
Sorry!
What? There's nothing to see...
Oh, cut it out. I told
you, I'll do it next time.
Later. Thanks for waiting!
Oh, no...
This isn't good...
If she sees that drawing, she'll definitely think I'm a weirdo.
If it's Yukko who sees that drawing,
the news will spread...
at the speed of sound!
Yukko!
Th-that's my Japanese notebook.
This is the one for math.
What? But it says "Math" right here...
Y-y-y...
you're wrong!
I-it hurts!
My stomach hurts!
Oh, okay...
I'll have them copied soon,
so just hang on a second.
It's over.
If she sees it here, it's over.
My high school life will be over.
Yukko, I'll buy that
notebook for 1,000 yen!
Why are you running away?
Yukko!
It's not like that! That
notebook... That notebook...
It'll explode!
It's no use.
There's no way for me to
catch up to Yukko on foot.
My life is over...
Thank you, life.
It's been fun up until now.
Not everything was perfect,
but it was a happy life.
But this is the end! My life is over!
My banquet of men... is gone...
I! Can't! Let! That! Happen!
My life is on fire!
I still can't reach her...
Yukko! Don't run...
...in the hallway!
Are... Are you okay?
Here.
Pass your notebooks to  the front.
Anyone who forgot their
homework should tell me now.
I was worried for a minute there,
but I'm relieved that nothing happened.
Now I can return to my everyday life...
I didn't erase it.
What's wrong, Naganohara?
Teacher, I forgot my homework!
There we go.
Cleaning
Professor, could you please clean up the mess in this room a bit?
It might be a little early for that.
I'm going out to play.
Um...
Student
Adviser
Excuse me, Annaka.
Do you have a minute?
Yes?
Uh, it's  a bit large, isn't it?
Your ribbon, I mean. I think...
Bzzt. Just kidding!
Cake
This cake is delicious.
It is, isn't it?
Tikomato
Spring Horsetail Lunch Boxes
Welcome.
A
Sold Out
Family-Size Cake
Nichijou: Everyday Life
Part 8
Sasahara, you do realize that you're
a festival committee member, right?
How about being a little
more serious about this?
I am being quite serious.
As president of the drama club, I'm always doing my part.
Can't you understand
that, Tachibana Misato?
No, I can't!
This is sweet...
Listen!
We're here to decide on what we're doing for the Cultural Festival!
Your drama club is another issue!
We changed brands.
How did I end up in a group with this guy?
Delicious.
My kendo competition is coming up.
I shouldn't have volunteered for the festival committee...
Hey, you! Why are you reading comics?
Until we turn something
in, we can't go home!
Sorry, it's a new volume.
Don't you have any ideas?
Was my wine-tasting
suggestion not a good idea?
It's definitely not good! No way, no how!
Absolutely not!
Hey, Sasahara?
What are you doing?
Sorry, I was out of ideas.
Sasahara, what do you think you're doing?
I must use the restroom.
I don't believe it...
She seems to be in a bad mood today.
I didn't think that my
wine-tasting idea was bad.
And she hasn't come up with a single idea.
But if I mention that, it'll cost me my life.
Which means that I can't
go home until I get an idea.
But, can I lower myself to
think on a commoner's level?
I suppose I'll give it
some serious thought...
Y-you're nothing
special to me. Got it?!
Asa okite ha wo migaite atto yuuma gogo juuji
I wake up in the morning, brush my
teeth, and before I know it it's 10 PM
Kyou mo takusan waratta na takusan tokimeita na
We laughed and had a lot of fun today
Tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawaideru toki ni mo
and at times my friends and I chatted noisily like nitwits
Chirachira tte me ga au guuzen da yo ne
When our eyes met, flutteringly, it was coincidence
Hatsukoi da tte ienai kyara ja nainda mon
It's not in me to say this is my first love
Nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
Hey, we'll see each other tomorrow, right?
Mabuta wo tojiru to kirakira kimi darake
If I close my eyes, all I see is a sparkling you
Kyou mo tanoshikatta ne aa doushite kana
I wonder why today was so much fun again
Ureshii na ureshii na hajimemashita koigokoro
I'm so happy, happy, that my love awakened
Ashita mata aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you again tomorrow, so good night
Yume de sugu aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you in my dreams soon, so good night
The naivete of Asia.
I'm a sweet bun,
and I'm unpopular in Kansai.
Many people don't know whether
to pronounce my name
as "amashoku" or "kanshoku".
The next episode of Nichijou is episode 3.
Narration: Ikeda Masako
Don't miss it.