Mai, let's walk home together.
Can we stop by the fire cistern?
There you go again.
High school girls shouldn't
go to places like that!
By the way, Mai,
want to stop by
Daiku Coffee on the way?
They've changed their
system quite a bit.
It might be kinda tough for you.
So I'll show you how it works.
Mai.
That...
It's asymmetry.
Yeah, I see that!
That's completely beside the point!
It's way beyond
fashionable asymmetry!
I was just kidding.
That's too fast, even for a fastball...
Mai, there's something
wrong with you!
The heavens must favor Mai...
jou-jou-yuujou magi magi kaichou
The best, friendship, perfect harmony!
hai icchai mashou kimi wa best, best friend!
Yes, let's go, you're my best friend!
chotto fuza kete mitara
If you try being annoying
motto fuza ke kaeshite kuru
Then I'll be annoying in return
iigokochiitta aryashinai!
If I speak of comfort, it goes away
iiyana koto attatte
I had things I hated
sokko wasurechaunda
But I forgot them in one swift stroke
itsudatte janjan yarimashou!
Let's go do something non-stop!
nijyuuyon jikan isshodemo mondainai
We can be together 24/7!
Almost like twins, a parent and a child or cloned cells!
marude futago ka oyako ka kuroom saibou
kore ja renai suru hitsuyou to ka nakunakunai?
Don't you cry when you fall in love?
Those are totally different things!
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
kenka shichatta toki mo
Even when we fought
kanari e konda toki mo
Even when we felt really blue
hitori de itai you na toki mo
Even when we want to be alone
We are next to each other
futo kizukeba chikaku ni iru
Until death do us part
shi na ba morotomo
Why, I wonder?
nande daro
soba ni itainda
I want to be by your side
When I'm with you
kimi to isshonara
tokei hyaku baisoku
Time flies a hundred times as fast
tanoshii na
It's so much fun
tanoshi sugirunda
It's too much fun
sasuga saikyou furendo
Always the same, with my best friend!
nan nano yo
What is it?
yabai shinkuro mo
Man, we're even synchronized
itsumo oosawagi
Always such a rage
kanari go kinj omeiwaku
Annoying everyone around us
ima nanji?
What time is it?
tatoe yororeihi
Time to yodel!
wakewakan nai nai!
What are you talking about?
soure-do-shi-ra-
What am I going to do?
so-zo-i-jo-
More than imagination!
nante iu ka saikou
What should I say, awesome!
Whatever you say, we're friends!
a-dako-da itte temo tomodachi
wasshoi!
Hooray!
jou-jou-yuujou
The best, friendship!
magi magi kaichou
Perfect harmony!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 68
What should I make
for dinner tonight?
Onions are cheap, so I'll
make something with them.
But the professor
doesn't like onions...
Nano! Nano!
Nano.
Nano, look! I caught a crow!
Unbelievable!
What are you doing?
That's dangerous!
It could peck you!
It's okay.
Just hang on.
Not here...
I might die!
It's not here, either.
My scarf disappeared somewhere.
Hello, I'm a crow.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's a good thing
he's so polite.
That's because he's a crow.
The pleasure is mine.
I wonder if he'd
drink strawberry milk.
Do you think he might?
It'd be cute if he did.
Unbelievable.
He killed a bug for us.
No need to thank me.
It's just part of my job.
What a crow.
Mr. Sakamoto,
where's your scarf?
Without his scarf,
we can't understand him!
I shall listen and
interpret for him.
Hm, hm.
I see, I see.
It seems that he
would like my scarf.
I see.
It isn't yours!
Professor, did you give
Mr. Sakamoto's scarf to the crow?
Such a shame.
But what about
poor Mr. Sakamoto?
I know... I'll make one.
A splendid idea.
I did it!
Biscuit #1!
That has nothing
to do with my scarf!
Excuse me, Professor.
What are Biscuit #1's functions?
Good question, Crow!
It has a rocket punch!
I'll show you!
Ready...
Launch!
Professor, you should return
Mr. Sakamoto's s-scarf...
Hold on.
It still has its left hand!
Ready...
Launch!
I'll kill her... I definitely will.
I had a lot of fun today.
But it appears my shenanigans have gone on long enough.
Please return this
scarf to Mr. Sakamoto.
I am glad to have had the chance to speak the human language.
Crow...
Don't go, Crow!
Professor!
Perhaps we shall meet again...
Farewell, everyone.
See you again!
Crow!
Crow...
He took it with him!
Love-like
That's impossible, sir!
No, it's fine. Leave it to me.
But...
What? Don't you trust me?
No, that's not...
I trust you completely, sir.
Good. Then give me your hands.
Well, but...
Ow, ow, ow!
How is it?
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 69
A
Slow
Behind the Gymnasium,
Part 1
Yesterday, behind the gymnasium,
I dug a pit filled with adhesives...
Extra
Strong
Adhesive
Wide Gel
A
I'll use this letter to summon
her here and trap her.
Miss Shinonome Nano
I'll capture you today,
Shinonome Nano.
She's here!
All right!
I didn't realize that Sakurai Makoto was Ms. Sakurai's younger brother.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 70
I must learn more about
Ms. Sakurai from him.
That kid...
can really play Go-Soccer!
Interesting!
Hey, Sakurai.
Yes?
Is there any boyfriend
in the picture?
No future!
This always happens! I... I'm...
Uh, no, there isn't...
There isn't... There isn't...
Yes... yes...
Yes!
Why am I cheering?!
Uh...
Sorry, sorry.
Please forget about it.
Oh, right! You play Go-Soccer?
Yeah, I do...
Hey, Teacher...
you like my sister, don't you?
Don't be ridiculous!
I just happen to have
more Go-Soccer experience!
Teacher! You played Go-Soccer?
Of course I did!
Believe it or not,
I was my high school's MVP!
Teacher, our Go-Soccer club
doesn't have a faculty advisor.
If you'd be our advisor,
I'd do everything I could to
hook you up with my sister.
But it's... not like I like her...
If you won't be our advisor,
I'll tell everyone you like my sister.
Why, you little...
What'll it be?
Will you become our advisor?
Um...
Or will you not?
Um, but being an
advisor's a lot of work...
Hey, everyone! Listen up!
Gonna move!
A-after him!
Teacher!
Nakanojo's been buried
behind the gymnasium...
What?!
You have to come right away!
What?
Hey, Mr. Takasaki is...
Teacher!
Listen closely.
Okay.
Nakanojo hasn't been buried!
What?
That's right! It could
just be a hole-in-one!
What?
But his hair came off!
What?!
Draw it in!
What?
I'll try it.
What?!
Hold on!
What?
What is the meaning of that?
Hey, tea.
A student exposing
another's private life
requires my attention,
over a buried student,
as, a... uh, as a teacher!
Mr. Takasaki!
Yes?
I haven't said anything.
I look forward to
having you as our advisor.
That kid...
Annaka! Let's go!
Okay.
We should hurry.
After all, I'm a teacher.
It's this way!
That way...
I know I was caught up in the moment,
but maybe I shouldn't have cut his hair.
I guess I'll help him.
Behind the Gymnasium,
Part 2
He doesn't know it was me.
What? What is this?
Huh? What?
Where am I? Where is
this? This is strange!
What is this? I can't move!
Huh?
Uh, um...
What? What is this?
My hair...
Run away!
Help me...
My hair...
Swim, swim.
Shark, shark, chomp.
What is this?
This is Chichi!
Behind the Gymnasium,
Part 3
Miss Shinonome Nano
What is this?
Help me!
My hair...
Huh?
What is this?
Help me!
What's the matter-
Hair...
What? What is this?
Help me!...
What?
Please help me...
Help me!
So dangerous...
What?
Help me!
My hair...
See you later!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 71
I won't call her out today!
Besides, this is Mai's fault.
She throws out jokes like a machine,
and I always call them out...
At this rate, it'll be an endless loop
of jokes and comebacks!
We're just maidens...
Right... innocent maidens
who could make flowers blush.
But...
We can't even talk like
ordinary high school girls.
Starting today, I won't mention it!
My will is harder than diamond.
Yukko, good morning.
Mai, good...
Double glasses!
It's strong! It's strong today!
It's really strong today!
But I won't lose!
I... no, we will change!
Mai, selamat pagi.
All right! It's time to
let our girl-talk bloom!
Hey, Mai.
Did you watch
Muscle Lament yesterday?
Which... wh-wh-which one?
My glasses... My glasses...
Wh-what's with these
high-paced jokes?
It's like she's just waiting
for me to say something...
No. I mustn't do it!
Yukko, this is a trap!
Huh?
Huh, Minakami? You're
wearing two pairs of glasses.
Tanaka, you jerk!
My line...
That was supposed to be my line...
No! No, no. It wasn't mine.
That wasn't my line at all!
Oh, right. Is Japanese
first period today?
Yeah. I heard the science teacher, Nakamura, collapsed again.
Is she all right?
Oh, right. Is Japanese
first period today?
No... You just asked...
That was close!
Why would that girl say
the same thing twice?
She's a sharp one!
A real sharp one!
All right, give the instructions.
Stand.
Bow.
Set down.
Let's get started.
Open to page 82...
Set down...
What's "set down"
supposed to mean?!
And everyone else let it slide!
Would anyone like to read this?
Yes.
Mai!
Okay, Minakami.
Yes.
"Darkness fell quietly on the mountains,
If she's reading this...
and scattered lights came on, in the village.
It was his first visit,
If she's reading this, then...
but nostalgia sprouted, somewhere inside.
Then...
He drew a cigarette from his breast pocket and lit it with the spark from a rock.
She memorized it?!
Calling the joke out...
It feels... so...
...wonderful!
I'm sorry I shouted.
I'll go and stand in the hallway!
O-Okay.
Yes. This is how it should be.
This is my path, and...
This is Mai's path.
Yukko.
Since this morning, I've been wearing...
contact lenses.
Then what's the point
of those glasses?
Heated Table
Professor, Professor.
If you don't sleep in your
bed, you'll catch a cold.
Professor...
Just a little longer...
Huh? A little longer?
She got me!
In a desert baked by the scorching sun
Makka na taiyou shizumu sabaku ni
a large monster lived free of cares
Ookina kaijuu ga nombiri kurashiteta
When one morning it awoke
Aru asa mezametara
It heard the bells of a caravan from far away
Tooku ni kyaraban no suzu no oto kikoeta yo
Without giving it much thought, it screamed
Omowazu sakenda yo
"I want to see the ocean, I want to love someone!"
Umi ga mitai hito wo ai shitai
"Even monsters have a heart!"
Kaijuu ni mo kokoro wa aru no sa
"I will leave and abandon the desert"
Dekakeyou sabaku sutete
"and go where I may find the ocean and my love"
Ai to umi no aru tokoro
Atarashii taiyou wa moeru
A new sun burns down
Ai to umi no aru tokoro
where it may find the ocean and its love
Short Thoughts
There we go.
Mr. Sakamoto...
Mr. Sakamoto, let's go to bed.
Okay.
She always ends up
carrying her to bed.
Three of spades here!
In the  President game, I begin as the weakest card.
But with a revolution, I become the strongest!
A real man overthrows his superiors.
The  next episode of Nichijou is episode 18.
Narration:     Nakai Kazuya
Don't miss it.