What beautiful weather.
I should wake the
professor up soon.
Maybe I'll go for a
walk after breakfast.
Huh? What...
I only just noticed
Tattaima hajimete kizuita
Koi ni ochita no da naa
that I fell in love
24h kimiOkimiOkimiO
You are on my mind all day, day, day
Ishiki sezaru wo emasen!
and I can't do anything about it
Nanka
Somehow
Itsumo to chigau kimi to
while having an awkward conversation
Futari
with you
Gikochinai kaiwa masaka
you seem different from usual, could it be...
Ryouomoi
Mutual love?
Iya kataomoi
Nah, it's one-sided
Yabai! Shisen acchatta!!!
Oops, our glances met
Nani nani!? kono dokidoki!?
What's up with this excitement?
Shikoukairo gucchagucha konsen...
My train of thought slips into chaos
Konna koto hajimete da yo
This is the first time it has happened to me,
Netsu demo aru no kanaa
maybe I have a fever?
Kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
My love took a sudden turn
Acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
And I instantly blushed a deep red
Ba.ba...baka na!? Te ga furueru zo
N-n-no way! My hands are trembling
Kore ga zoku ni iu "koi" na no!?
Is this what's commonly referred to as "love"?
Yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
I st-st-stuttered through our conversation
Kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
Awkward silence, mmhmmhmhm
Kimi no
I want
Kimochi shiritai yo
to know your feelings
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Hatsukoi!!
My first love
Itsumo no tsuugakuro
on my normal way to school
Pikapika hikaru
glitters brightly
I DO fall in love!
Sora mo tobesou sa
I feel like I can fly in the sky
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 31
Mio, Mai. Selamat pagi.
Yukko, good morning.
Good morning.
It's nice outside today.
Yesterday, they
said it would rain.
Well, the weather's not real bad...
so maybe I should buy a keypad!
Just kidding.
Wha-wha-what's with
their lack of reaction?
Terrible... these girls are terrible...
Could they think that I'm...
actually going to buy a keypad?
Oh, that's it.
That joke was a little
too highbrow for them.
I need to make jokes that
everyone can understand.
Okay!
Man, it sure is hot.
This hot spot...
is giving me a bald spot!
Just kidding.
Terrifying, terrifying...
the virtual age is terrifying!
But, I guess...
it's in bad taste if they know
someone who's really balding.
Wait!
I feel a little guilty.
All right!
I'll use the ancient weapon!
The noble treasure!
Hey, listen!
What did the man say when
a centipede attacked him?
"This bug's...
really bugging me!"
I'm shocked!
I'm shocked...
What's wrong with these girls?
How can they still
keep a straight face?
Wait a minute!
Maybe they didn't hear me.
If they didn't hear me,
it's not their fault.
All right!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, listen!
What did the man say when
a centipede attacked him?
"This bug's...
really bugging me!"
These girls are true warriors...
no, they're on the level of kings!
Could it be...
Could it be that they're expecting me to
surpass my own level of skill,
to surpass...
myself?!
If I give up here...
I'll betray their expectations!
I can't turn back!
Can't turn back!
So...
I can't...
give in!
My grade for astronomy will be...
...astronomical!
I've got an explosive desire
to visit a bomb shelter!
The gully is happy! Golly!
I'll... make... you... see...
my makeup!
In this equation,
substitute this for x
to determine the answer.
Take this y, and...
Go-Soccer Club Part 5
President.
Ogi!
Why haven't we seen
you around for so long?
For the last three months,
I thought you were dead.
How've you been?
Yes.
You've got great timing.
I've got nothing to do.
Let's do something together.
What do you want to do?
We can play this.
I came to quit the club.
Popcorn
Short Thoughts
Why do I cough
just before the movie starts,
at the movie theater?
And then I...
Weboshi! Fet!
Have you seen Sasahara?
Sasahara?
I saw him taking the
stairs up to the roof.
Thanks!
Misato's already
busy this morning.
That's youth for you...
Let's go take a look.
They might be up to something!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 32
Across the blue sky,
a single flying right hand
leaves a trail of clouds.
Sasahara.
Not bad.
Sasahara, do you understand
what you've done?
The weather is beautiful,
so I came up to the
roof to compose a poem.
Not that.
I'm talking about this.
Don't you remember this?
That's mine.
Why do you have...
What are you talking about?
I picked up your litter for you!
Oh no, I did not throw this away.
I simply dropped it by accident.
This is not garbage.
It's a handker-
Everything you own is garbage!
How did you know this was mine?
Our homes are in completely
opposite directions.
You even ironed it...
A-are you stupid?
Don't get the wrong idea!
I just happened to
be walking that way,
while I was thinking about stuff!
Thank you for your
kindness, Tachibana Misato.
You always drop
things in the morning...
I never noticed. Do I?
You're littering the streets!
B-but... I don't mind...
picking up your garbage for you...
Don't get the wrong idea!
That's just my
volunteer spirit talking!
Misato's never going to change.
Weboshi...
What do I do with this?
Why did you bring that?
What do I do with it?
Get rid of it!
But what do I do with it?
Just get rid of it!
Things we think are cool!
Super-car bicycles!
Danger
I give up.
Daiku Security
No one's coming to save us.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 33
There is no God.
No Buddha.
Yesterday, I had...
...pork cutlet?
Oh, well.
Huh?
How long have we been here?
I think...
...I just fell asleep.
Oh, well.
Do you want to play shiritori?
Orange.
Oh, sorry.
Say it one more time.
What did I say?
Say.
Can I say something
totally different?
Eggplant.
She's dead.
Help isn't coming.
I'm paralyzed.
Go-Soccer Club Part 6
It's down to just
you and me, Sekiguchi.
We'll have to disband
if we don't have at
least three members.
If only we had a way
to recruit members...
President.
What does our club do?
Oh, I thought you came up with a good way to recruit people.
We don't really do anything.
Start
On your mark...
Get set...
Go!
Stop! Hey! Don't take my uniform!
Come on, Seki.
Give me your uniform.
B-but I haven't even
scored a single point today!
I don't care.
This uniform commemorates your retirement!
B-but the uniform of a player who couldn't score a single point in their last game must be worthless!
That's not true.
I started playing
soccer because of you!
W-wait! Fine! Fine!
Just let me take it off
when I'm ready, okay? Okay?
Just let go of me!
What?
Fine...
There's my opening!
This is my way of life!!
Sorry, I guess...
Tail
Listen up!
From now on, be sure
to respect your elders.
Okay.
Geez, she's completely hopeless.
Oh, man! This is so fun!
Wait up!
Go-Soccer Club Part 7
In the beginning,
I thought I could make a
new kind of club,
combining go and soccer.
Go of the West
Soccer of the East
Smells Like Youth
That's why I made this club.
But...
I couldn't come up
with any good ideas.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 34
First you draw a boomerang,
then a triangle, and then a square...
Professor, let's go to bed.
Okay!
Professor, did you have a snack?
No, I didn't.
Why did you look away?
I might have looked away.
That doesn't make any sense!
Look! Why are you
having a snack before bed?
Well, that wasn't me, so...
Who am I looking at, with
crumbs all over her face?
I think I caught a cold.
What are you doing?
Why do you keep eating snacks
before bed even when I tell you not to?
It's not my fault!
Sakamoto told me to eat it!
He's making a snot
bubble. How silly.
Don't change the subject!
Sheesh.
Brush your teeth before
you go to bed, okay?
I already brushed my teeth.
You mean you brushed your
teeth before your snack?
Yes. I brushed them.
Why are you embarrassed?
But you only have to
brush your teeth once.
That's not true! You had a snack.
Then, did you brush your teeth?
I brushed them!
Then, then...
I'm ready to go to bed.
You're the one who isn't ready.
You're a robot, so
you can't get cavities!
Nano, um, uh...
You might get a little cavity.
Really?
Really.
You're lying...
Oh, but you can rust, though!
Rust...
Uh, um...
I'll give you a cavity feature!
Don't worry. I'll really do it!
Promise?
That's the truth!
Nano, come brush
your teeth with me!
Okay. It's my second time, though.
It's already 10 PM.
Yes, it is.
Let's go to sleep after this.
Asa okite ha wo migaite atto yuuma gogo juuji
I wake up in the morning, brush my
teeth, and before I know it it's 10 PM
Kyou mo takusan waratta na takusan tokimeita na
We laughed and had a lot of fun today
Tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawaideru toki ni mo
and at times I and my friends chatted noisily like nitwits
Chirachira tte me ga au guuzen da yo ne
When our eyes met, flutteringly, it was coincidence
Hatsukoi da tte ienai kyara ja nainda mon
It's not in me to say this is my first love
Nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
Hey, we'll see each other tomorrow, right?
Mabuta wo tojiru to kirakira kimi darake
If I close my eyes, all I see is a sparkling you
Kyou mo tanoshikatta ne aa doushite kana
I wonder why today was so much fun again
Ureshii na ureshii na hajimemashita koigokoro
I'm so happy, happy, that my love awakened
Ashita mata aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you again tomorrow, so good night
Yume de sugu aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you in my dreams soon, so good night
A Little Miracle
Geez, Sasahara never
takes anything seriously...
We're a double-yolked egg!
We are!
Hot... Hot, hot, hot!
Hot! Hot!
The... the next episode of Nichijou is e-episode 9.
Narration:  Seki Tomokazu
Don't miss it! Hot!