Twice Cooked Pork
Thanks for waiting.
This is all I can make.
Here.
Amazing. It's twice cooked pork.
I was just feeling really hungry.
I wonder if you'll be able to
identify the secret ingredient.
You must have gone all out,
to use a secret ingredient.
Thanks for the food.
I can't taste
anything but miso...
Her secret ingredient
isn't secret at all.
In fact, the more I chew,
the worse this secret
ingredient tastes.
I'm against this
secret ingredient!
I only just noticed
Tattaima hajimete kizuita
Koi ni ochita no da naa
that I fell in love
24h kimiOkimiOkimiO
You are on my mind all day, day, day
Ishiki sezaru wo emasen!
and I can't do anything about it
Nanka
Somehow
Itsumo to chigau kimi to
while having an awkward conversation
Futari
with you
Gikochinai kaiwa masaka
you seem different from usual, could it be...
Ryouomoi
Mutual love?
Iya kataomoi
Nah, it's one-sided
Yabai! Shisen acchatta!!!
Oops, our glances met
Nani nani!? kono dokidoki!?
What's up with this excitement?
Shikoukairo gucchagucha konsen...
My train of thought slips into chaos
Konna koto hajimete da yo
This is the first time it has happened to me,
Netsu demo aru no kanaa
maybe I have a fever?
Kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
My love took a sudden turn
Acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
And I instantly blushed a deep red
Ba.ba...baka na!? Te ga furueru zo
N-n-no way! My hands are trembling
Kore ga zoku ni iu "koi" na no!?
Is this what's commonly referred to as "love"?
Yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
I st-st-stuttered through our conversation
Kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
Awkward silence, mmhmmhmhm
Kimi no
I want
Kimochi shiritai yo
to know your feelings
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Hatsukoi!!
My first love
Itsumo no tsuugakuro
on my normal way to school
Pikapika hikaru
glitters brightly
I DO fall in love!
Sora mo tobesou sa
I feel like I can fly in the sky
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Nichijou: Everyday Life Part 23
Not bad!
Mio, Mio.
What is this?
A kappa?
Isn't he cool?
Why did she draw a kappa?
And what does she
mean by "isn't he cool"?
Well... it might be fun
to draw something
fantasy-themed this time.
Something like a
giant demon, or a kappa.
Kappa... it could work.
Kappa. Kappa, huh?
Kappa... kappa-pa... pa... pa...
Parasite.
Just kidding.
I guess we're playing
picture shiritori now.
Here, Yukko.
Thanks.
Parashite?
Is this what a
parashite looks like?
This arrow must mean...
she's challenging me to
a game of picture shiritori.
I accept her challenge...
Parashite, huh? Te... te...
All right.
It's huge!
And it's a tengu.
She must have read
"parasite" as "parashite."
Well, whatever.
Tengu, huh?
Tengu... gu... gu...
Gu... gu!
You can't be serious!
Tengo!
A tengo? What's a tengo?!
No, wait a minute!
There's no way a high school student would make such a childish mistake.
She drew a picture of a tengu
before adding the words...
I don't understand.
I don't get it, but
I guess I'll use "go"...
Here.
Draw smaller!
What's with this Goku?
Huh? Goku?
I thought I drew a tengu...
I guess I can see how
"gu" might become "go"...
I'll get a juice from her later.
Let's see! U, huh?
Okay.
I can't draw
it well!!
Uni. No, usa...
I can't draw
it well!!
It's a cow?!
I can't draw
it well!!
This cow is terrible!
Here.
Tongue! It's a tongue!
That gives me ta. Ta... Ta...
Taxi...
Here.
Y-y-you've
got to be kidding!
This isn't a "taxi", it's a "taxy"!
I'll just draw whatever...
Breaking out the slang, are we?
shiSu
She must be getting into it.
Okay, okay, okay!
Oh, no... I can't end on "n"!
Superman
No, wait... I-I'll
just fix this here, and...
Here.
Supermans
Go-Soccer Club
Go-Soccer Club Part 3
There's nothing to do...
There's nothing to do, Sekiguchi.
Hey, Sekiguchi.
Let's have a contest.
I'll start.
Ready, and... two!
Sekiguchi...
There's nothing to do. Won't you play with me once in a while?
President.
Sekiguchi...
Nichijou: Everyday Life Part 24
Forgot my homework...
And had to stand in
the hallway, Mogami River.
Yukko.
I can't believe I'm
standing in the hallway
over a forgotten assignment...
How shall I spend
this time, Mogami River?
Yukko.
E-everyone,
th-there's a deer...
Wh-What is the principal
doing to that deer?!
Th-the principal...
th-the deer...
Principal!
Hey... Hey everyone...
the principal is... going to...
Is that...
a deer biscuit?
Hey... everyone...
the principal is... d-dying.
He got up.
He climbed up...
He jumped!
And fell down!
He climbed up again!
He climbed down!
It's a stalemate!
Principal!
Principal...
Everyone...
death... the principal is... death.
He stood up!
Hey, everyone...
Everyone, listen!
Uh, um...
Th-th-the pri...
Pri...
All's quiet in the hallway!
That was the truth,
from the bottom of her heart.
She was neither trying
to protect the principal,
nor too lazy to explain the scenario.
Perhaps she wished
to show respect
for the two who
had just fought.
Gather the early summer
rains, Mogami River.
What does that even mean?
10-Yen Soccer
All right.
You'll be the referee, Mio.
You don't need a
referee for 10-yen soccer.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
You don't get it, do you?
It's all about the mood.
Let's kick off!
I guess I have no choice.
Bring it on!
Okay.
First comes rock,
then comes paper...
You can't throw all of them,
rock, paper, scissors!
Chomp.
Nichijou: Everyday Life Part 25
What am I going to do?
I caught a cockroach...
C-careful...
I've got to be careful!
I've got to come up with a plan to prevent these disgusting things
from spreading
into the house again.
Bug spray!
No, I can't.
It won't die in one spray,
so it might escape.
Besides...
I don't want to see it squirm!
What about detergent?
I'll trap it by covering
the area around the bowl
before targeting it directly.
N-no!
With nowhere to run, it'll fly.
If it takes off, it's over.
It'll charge right at people.
If it touches my body...
or worse, my face...
No!
If it gets inside my mouth...
If this thing gets in my mouth...
It's a one-shot rock and roll!
This is it! I have no choice!
Once I lift this bowl, my only
options are kill or be killed!
Death or die!
I've got to... I've got to do it!
What are you doing?
Mr. Sakamoto! Please help me.
Under this bowl,
there's a ro-roa... a roach...
A what?
You mean a cockroach?
Fine. I'll take care of it.
Thank you.
Hey.
Yes?
What are you doing?
I'll get it, so lift the bowl.
What?
No... I'm telling
you to lift the bowl.
If you don't, I can't get it.
Hey!
Wha... what are you saying?
You want me to release
this minion of evil?
This is Pandora's box!
When I open it,
it's death or die!
No, no, no.
How am I supposed to get
it if you don't lift the bowl?
Lift it yourself!
How am I supposed to do that?
What am I going to do?
Mr. Sakamoto left...
Nano, what's today's snack?
Good timing!
The professor isn't bothered
by bugs, so she'll help me.
Professor, there's a
cockroach inside this bowl.
I-I'd appreciate it if
you'd take care of it.
Sure.
R-r-r-rock and roll!
Thank you. Please do.
Okay.
I'll knock it out with a single blow.
Head strike!
I missed.
I-I'm clearly upset by this,
but she... but she...
I hate you, Professor!
She's crying?
I-I'm just kidding! Gosh...
There's no way I would hate you.
Professor, I love you.
Nano!
Oh, Professor...
Now, it's time to rock and roll.
Count To 10
It's hot. Can I get out?
What? You just got in.
But it's hot.
You can get out on 10.
20 log root 10!
What?
I got to 10. Can I get out now?
Um...
You have to count, 1... 2...
What?
Oh, come on.
Go-Soccer Club Part 4
Everyone said they had
cram school and left...
And you're no fun, Sekiguchi.
Don't you go to cram
school, Sekiguchi?
You're joking!
Nichijou: Everyday Life Part 26
Delicious.
Yukko, how's the curry?
It's almost done.
I'm pretty hungry.
Yeah, me too.
Mai, how are things over there?
A big one's coming.
We'll have a feast tonight.
All right. This should be good.
Thanks for waiting.
The crazy delicious
super-curry is done.
These will take a little longer.
We should have started
them before the curry.
Well, they say you
have to be patient.
Oh, we should have
brought mayonnaise.
Don't you think mayonnaise
goes with curry, Yukko?
M-mayo...
What do you think, Yukko?
B-barf!
Just kidding.
No, no. Th-this isn't
what it looks like...
Here, lo-look. We've
still got jelly noddles.
Jelly noo... just kid...
What color...
Mio?
What color is your blood?
Sorry, Mai!
There's no curry
or rice for lunch!
Mai?
We still have jelly noodles.
Mai!
Release.
Well.
Here, we have a single
package of jelly noodles.
Just one?
I think we should pass
it around and share it.
However, you and I are to blame...
So, Mai, you eat first.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes!
Just don't eat it all in one bite!
I wouldn't do that.
I'm not mean.
I'll eat first.
I choked...
I know! Let's play cards!
No.
At this rate, we'll remember this as a disappointing camping trip!
Let's give it a happy ending!
I know!
What's up?
I completely forgot.
At times like this,
adults drink, right?
Yeah.
Don't you agree, Mai?
I actually brought some.
You're not serious, Mio.
I'm dead serious.
A delinquent.
There's a delinquent here.
Ta-dah!
Vinegar
Let's chug it!
Mio, stop! You'll kill yourself!
We've still got Mai's!
This is cider.
Asa okite ha wo migaite atto yuuma gogo juuji
I wake up in the morning, brush my
teeth, and before I know it it's 10 PM
Kyou mo takusan waratta na takusan tokimeita na
We laughed and had a lot of fun today
Tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawaideru toki ni mo
and at times my friends and I chatted noisily like nitwits
Chirachira tte me ga au guuzen da yo ne
When our eyes met, flutteringly, it was coincidence
Hatsukoi da tte ienai kyara ja nainda mon
It's not in me to say this is my first love
Nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
Hey, we'll see each other tomorrow, right?
Mabuta wo tojiru to kirakira kimi darake
If I close my eyes, all I see is a sparkling you
Kyou mo tanoshikatta ne aa doushite kana
I wonder why today was so much fun again
Ureshii na ureshii na hajimemashita koigokoro
I'm so happy, happy, that my love awakened
Ashita mata aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you again tomorrow, so good night
Yume de sugu aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you in my dreams soon, so good night
Short Thoughts
After a bath,
I drink a glass of milk
and pretend to be drunk.
I'm Peso!
I'm 10 yen!
I'm a Wadou Kaichin!
No, no! You can't measure
a person's value in money!
The next episode of Nichijou is episode 7.
Narration:
Tachiki Fumihiko
Don't miss it.