I bet she's really good at doing math in her head!
Who is?
Nano!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 59
She's a robot, so she ought
to have some robot-like functions.
What are you talking about?
There's no way she's a robot.
What?
But she has that key on her back!
That's the only thing
that makes you think she's a robot?
That's ridiculous.
No, just think about it.
She's a robot.
It's amazing!
It's, you know... amazing!
What? That's not a reason at all.
Which is why I'm thinking
we should find out if she really is a robot.
What?
Don't do that...
Don't worry! I've got a plan.
jou-jou-yuujou magi magi kaichou
The best, friendship, perfect harmony!
hai icchai mashou kimi wa best, best friend!
Yes, let's go, you're my best friend!
chotto fuza kete mitara
If you try being annoying
motto fuza ke kaeshite kuru
Then I'll be annoying in return
iigokochiitta aryashinai!
If I speak of comfort, it goes away
iiyana koto attatte
I had things I hated
sokko wasurechaunda
But I forgot them in one swift stroke
itsudatte janjan yarimashou!
Let's go do something non-stop!
nijyuuyon jikan isshodemo mondainai
We can be together 24/7!
Almost like twins, a parent and a child or cloned cells!
marude futago ka oyako ka kuroom saibou
kore ja renai suru hitsuyou to ka nakunakunai?
Don't you cry when you fall in love?
Those are totally different things!
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
kenka shichatta toki mo
Even when we fought
kanari e konda toki mo
Even when we felt really blue
hitori de itai you na toki mo
Even when we want to be alone
We are next to each other
futo kizukeba chikaku ni iru
Until death do us part
shi na ba morotomo
Why, I wonder?
nande daro
soba ni itainda
I want to be by your side
When I'm with you
kimi to isshonara
tokei hyaku baisoku
Time flies a hundred times as fast
tanoshii na
It's so much fun
tanoshi sugirunda
It's too much fun
sasuga saikyou furendo
Always the same, with my best friend!
nan nano yo
What is it?
yabai shinkuro mo
Man, we're even synchronized
itsumo oosawagi
Always such a rage
kanari go kinj omeiwaku
Annoying everyone around us
ima nanji?
What time is it?
tatoe yororeihi
Time to yodel!
wakewakan nai nai!
What are you talking about?
soure-do-shi-ra-
What am I going to do?
so-zo-i-jo-
More than imagination!
nante iu ka saikou
What should I say, awesome!
Whatever you say, we're friends!
a-dako-da itte temo tomodachi
wasshoi!
Hooray!
jou-jou-yuujou
The best, friendship!
magi magi kaichou
Perfect harmony!
Nano!
Y-yes?
I have a question.
What's 3,260 plus 260 divided by 320?
Um, 3,260 plus...
If it's too hard,
you could use all of your functions.
Wait, Yukko, this is your plan?
I'm sorry...
Then, I'll accept your offer.
Got her!
It's an abacus!
Um, from the top...
She's serious!
Uh, one, two, three...
Sh-sh-sh-sh-sh...
she's a beginner!
Um, 3,260 plus...
She's not even using the abacus!
Hey, Yukko?
Aioi?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I have a feeling you were right...
Didn't I tell you that she wasn't a robot?
Are you okay?
Do you want something to drink?
Is that...
Could this be...
oil?!
It's soup!
Yukko?
Uh, um...
Minakami.
Here.
It's a fastball!
Oil?
Here.
Uh, are you sure?
Thank you.
She's drinking it!
A swing and a miss!
You can have this, too.
A curveball!
Monkey wrench!
Oh, thank you.
You really saved me!
She's eating it!
Another swing and a miss!
Both of you, cut it out, already.
You're bothering Nano.
Bonding...
I just wanted to be friends.
Sheesh...
This isn't the way to do it.
If anything, it'll make her hate you!
Sorry...
I don't believe you...
Don't worry about it.
What? But...
Oh, I know.
If you don't need this, I'll drink it.
See? You heard her.
What are you talking about?
Did my tooth come out?
Why don't you put yourself in her shoes?
I want to know how someone could create something of such high quality.
Shinonome Nano,
who transferred here the other day...
That presence...
That key.
She must be a robot...
Who would refrain from
announcing her existence,
and send her to this school instead?
Examine her...
I want to examine her!
And I want to make her mine.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 60
Ms. Nakamura, here are the books you wanted.
She's here! I'll make my move!
Please excuse me.
Shinonome, hold on.
Why not have a cup of coffee?
Huh? Oh, I wouldn't want to trouble you...
Don't be shy. I just made some.
Let me thank you for bringing me those books.
Have a cup.
Then, just one.
First, I'll see if tranquilizers work on her.
If not,
I'll sic my "Mr. Short Circuit"
that I made yesterday on her.
Drink up.
Thank you.
I drank it.
Endure it...
Endure it!
Please excuse me.
But still, Mr. Short Circuit...
Mr. Short Circuit...
Oh, right.
I heard that Nakamura,
the science teacher, fainted.
Nakamura seems to faint a lot.
Today was a close call...
But Aioi and Minakami
seem really nice.
Maybe we could...
Eat this!
Rocket Punch!
Boom!
This is the Rocket Punch's maximum power!
Professor, Professor!
Oh, Nano, welcome home.
Why did you say that twice?
Forget it.
Please remove this...
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 61
Why?
"Why"?
Because it's hard to sit in chairs,
and everyone gives me weird looks.
Someone even videotaped me.
But so far, I've managed to fool everyone.
What? But it's cute...
As long as I have this key,
nobody's going to treat me
like an ordinary girl.
I'm sure it'll be popular.
I don't care.
I want to have an ordinary...
Why did you give me this weapon?
I'm just glad this didn't happen at school.
Nano, why don't you want anyone to know you're a robot?
Because it's not cute, of course.
Robots are cute!
They are not!
They're cute.
Even this gun?
Even the toe USB?
They're cute!
Even the sweet bun in my forehead?
Professor, you're a mad professor!
They're cute!
I want to be more ordinary!
Yay! Fish cake!
Fish cakes are delicious.
Three... Two... One...
It's four o'clock... It's four o'clock...
Rice Cake Fair
Part 1
Hey! We've got rice cakes.
They're cheap.
We've got rice cakes!
Mr. Nakanojo, I can't thank you enough!
Rice cakes shouldn't speak!
I'm sorry, but I...
Rice Cake Fair
Part 2
I don't just wear this half-heartedly!
I'm betting my life on this—
Don't make me say it again!
Damn it! I made a mistake.
I knew it was rash to use tranquilizers.
Ms. Nakamura,
Mr. Short Circuit
She's a robot.
It'll take a strong blow to knock her out.
So, I'll use my currently untested
anti-robot weapon,
Mr. Short Circuit!
I'll use this to knock her out,
and then I'll kidnap her.
It's almost time.
Run!
Ms. Nakamura!
H-hey! Button your shirt up all the way!
Pipe down. I'll do what I want.
No, you won't! I'm the student advisor.
Seriously? How'd you manage that?
How rude! Let me see that.
I'll do it myself. You're embarrassing me!
Uh...
What?
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 62
Makkie, you can't do it yourself.
Aw, shut up...
Makkie?
See?
What're you doing?
Stop it!
Just let me do it.
Here, I'll do it for you.
You? Do it for you?
Jeez...
Don't talk to me so much at school.
Talk to me?
What exactly is your relationship?
It came off again.
Yeah, perfect. Well, I've got stuff to do.
Hold on!
If you walk around looking disheveled,
people will make fun of you.
So? You always look disheveled at home.
At home!
Dis... Dis... Dis... Dish...
Disheveled!
Disheveled! Great!
No! No! No! What am I, stupid?
How would a china dress
make her look disheveled?
It must be a more ordinary
kind of disheveled!
What am I thinking?
Aren't you embarrassed
to call yourself a teacher?
Disheveled in an ordinary way...
Ordinary...
Disheveled!
Nice!
Enough, you idiot!
It's fine, I'm going.
What about your button?
This is the Oguri Cap
Stupid!
It's fine, I'm going.
What about your button?
After him...
Mr. Takasaki!
Nakanojo fainted in the science room!
What?!
You have to come right away!
Wait!
Give it up already!
Listen closely.
Okay.
Nakanojo did not faint!
What?!
That's right! He might just be taking a nap!
What?
But his pupils aren't visible!
What?!
Draw them in!
What?
I'll try it.
What?!
Hold on!
What...
What is the meaning of that?
Immoral sexual activity
requires my attention
more than an unconscious student,
as a... uh, as a teacher!
That's Ms. Sakurai's younger brother.
Let's go.
Okay.
Here we go...
We should hurry.
After all, I'm a teacher.
It's this way!
Love-like
Take Home
Next stop, Tokisadame Station North Entrance.
Stop requested.
You don't get off at the next stop.
I just felt like pushing the button.
Didn't you just push it earlier?
Someone wanted to get off anyway,
so it worked out.
I see. You were just helping them out.
See? Someone wanted to get off here, too.
Amazing!
Mom, do we have a daily calendar?
Isn't it in the drawer?
Professor, Professor...
Nano, welcome home.
Why won't this key come off?
It really gets in my way at school.
During PE today,
I could only do a belly roll on the high jump!
When we were playing soccer,
I was called offside because of it...
I can take it.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 63
You can take it off?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Okay. I'll take it now.
Every day of my youth is precious.
Now I can finally live
an ordinary high school life.
Could you take it right now?
Stare...
Professor, are you...
I took it.
Again...
Don't make stupid, old puns like that.
Sorry, sorry.
So, does the key come off?
Well...
I don't need any more of your jokes!
Does it come off? Does it?
It does. It does...
I've taken tons of keys.
Taking yours will be no sweat.
Coin, coin, coin, jump!
You said coin, coin...
you said coin, jump!
Professor! I have a question.
I can't...
I'm laughing so hard, I can't breathe...
Professor,
I've been reacting strangely today.
Did you do something to me?
Yesterday, I gave you
a new reaction function.
Hey! Why would you give me
a function like that?
Why would you do that?
Because it's funny.
Goal!
I'm going to die. I'm going to die...
Isn't it funny?
It's not funny at all!
Professor, we'll deal with the key later.
Please remove this function.
One hundred yen.
Cheapskate!
toki ni wa naze ka oozora ni
Every once in a while, I wish
tabishitemitaku naru mono sa
To take a journey into the vast sky
kikyuu ni notte doko made ikou
To get on a balloon and go forth
kaze ni notte nohara wo koete
To ride the wind across the fields
kumo wo tobikoe doko made mo ikou
I'll soar through the clouds to the ends of the Earth
soko ni nani ka ga matteiru kara
Because there's something waiting for me
Short Thoughts
I'll use all my reserves.
Oil here.
My boss tells me I'm slippery,
but I can't help it. I'm oil.
Who is my boss, anyway?
The next episode of Nichijou is episode 16.
Narration:   Sakakibara Yoshiko
Don't miss it.