Hey, you two.
How much longer do you
plan on not paying your rent?
You're up to 60,000 yen this month.
We're sorry.
I don't want your
apologies, I want your rent.
The last time I came over, you'd promised to pay this month.
Hand over the rent.
Pretending to be asleep
won't do any good!
I'm not leaving
until I get the rent.
Um...
It's a sparrow's tear
in the bucket, but...
I only just noticed
Tattaima hajimete kizuita
Koi ni ochita no da naa
that I fell in love
24h kimiOkimiOkimiO
You are on my mind all day, day, day
Ishiki sezaru wo emasen!
and I can't do anything about it
Nanka
Somehow
Itsumo to chigau kimi to
while having an awkward conversation
Futari
with you
Gikochinai kaiwa masaka
you seem different from usual, could it be...
Ryouomoi
Mutual love?
Iya kataomoi
Nah, it's one-sided
Yabai! Shisen acchatta!!!
Oops, our glances met
Nani nani!? kono dokidoki!?
What's up with this excitement?
Shikoukairo gucchagucha konsen...
My train of thought slips into chaos
Konna koto hajimete da yo
This is the first time it has happened to me,
Netsu demo aru no kanaa
maybe I have a fever?
Kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
My love took a sudden turn
Acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
And I instantly blushed a deep red
Ba.ba...baka na!? Te ga furueru zo
N-n-no way! My hands are trembling
Kore ga zoku ni iu "koi" na no!?
Is this what's commonly referred to as "love"?
Yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
I st-st-stuttered through our conversation
Kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
Awkward silence, mmhmmhmhm
Kimi no
I want
Kimochi shiritai yo
to know your feelings
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Hatsukoi!!
My first love
Itsumo no tsuugakuro
on my normal way to school
Pikapika hikaru
glitters brightly
I DO fall in love!
Sora mo tobesou sa
I feel like I can fly in the sky
KakakataOkataomoi
O-o-one-one-sided love
Number one: Honduras slider.
Number two:
northern ornate box turtle.
Number three: red-bellied,
short-necked turtle.
Number two.
The answer is number three.
You're all correct.
Shut up!
Oh, you're still awake?
How's your cold?
Mmph hm.
Then go to school tomorrow.
Don't you have
a test coming up?
Okay.
You missed three days,
so be sure to ask your friends about what'll be on the test.
And about what they
went over in class.
Okay.
Don't get cocky.
You got a terrible
grade on the last test.
Are you listening?
Don't you ever stop talking, Mom?
My final exams are...
tomorrow!
Not a Winner
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 44
You were late!
Your warning was late!
You couldn't study in bed.
I did! I did it in my sleep!
You did?
No!
Which is it?
I'm saying your
warning was too late!
Would you have studied
if I'd warned you?
No.
If you fail, I'll kill you.
Don't sound so serious!
Super ultra great
delicious wonderful crap.
Well, I've just gotta study.
I've got about ten
hours until school starts.
Fortunately, tomorrow's tests
are English and music!
Final Exam Schedule
Day 1:
English
Music
Day 2:
Health
Day 3:
Literature
Math
Science
History
Final Exam Schedule
Day 1:
English
Music
Day 2:
Health
Day 3:
Literature
Math
Science
History
I can focus on English.
That's right.
What I need to do now is to
say goodbye to my old self,
and just concentrate!
To live today without regrets.
To live tomorrow with a smile,
even though I cried yesterday.
No matter how many times I fall,
I will not give up.
Because I want to
live, always smiling.
Boat headed out to
the distant ocean,
keep on charging
toward that distant light.
Keep moving forward,
keep moving forward.
Now, cast off your chains.
Yukko.
I'm done
with my poem.
Things we think are cool!
Aw, it's nothing...
A factory worker's shy smile!
I'll gamble.
I don't know what's
on the English exam,
so I have to take my chances!
I'll have to stick with
English vocabulary.
"Attempt."
To try.
"Love."
My love.
"Always."
We've always been apart.
"Confirmation."
Your love.
"Teleportation."
Leap through time.
Which is why...
"Cosmos."
Through the sky.
"Midnight submarine."
I want to ride with you.
"Forever", for an eternity.
"Forever", with you.
"Forever", always.
I'm done!
With my poem!
I know! I know!
Studying now won't help!
It's hopeless,
Mom's going to kill me.
Why did I have to get
over my cold today?
Having a cold is a hundred
times better than dying.
If I only had three more days...
And now...
My plan is perfect!
That's right.
If I don't want to take my exams,
I should just catch another cold!
It hurts, but I know
it'll do the trick.
Sitting in an icy bath just
after getting over a cold
will definitely make me sick!
Come on, come on!
I can feel it working!
This is it.
I just have to endure this!
I can do it!
If I can get a fever, I'll be all set.
I'll make it a sure thing by
eating some shaved ice...
turning the air conditioning
up to maximum...
and sleeping on
top of the blanket.
I'm perfectly healthy!
Yukko, wake up.
If that's how it's going to be...
Thermometer!
Match!
Raise the temperature!
Are you up?
Aren't you going to school?
Yukko.
Hot! Hot, hot, hot, hot! Hot!
What are you doing?
I got a fever.
My cold is back.
What's your temperature?
Uh, um...
88.8 degrees.
What? Why'd you break it?
It's not broken,
I've really got a cold!
You seem perfectly healthy.
It's probably the nice water.
Daiku Power
Thank you.
I didn't realize that the club
application form's deadline was today.
Our club was nearly disbanded.
Even if you turn in the form,
your club'll still be disbanded if you don't get more members.
Don't worry about that.
Anyway, I'll buy you some
juice tomorrow as thanks.
You don't have to do that.
There's no need to be shy.
See ya.
On the way home, I'll need to
buy a mixer and an apple orchard.
Yes, sir.
That must be the
power of Daiku Industries.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 45
There's no string.
I won't be able to make a straw doll to put in the principal's shoe locker.
I don't have the necessary straw.
I don't have the money to buy any.
Wife's Reunion Trip
I've got no wife around to ask for money.
I'm hungry, but I have no rice.
Times like this make me want
to down a bottle of brandy.
But I've already destroyed my liver.
A
Liver
Hilar bile duct
Gall bladder
Bile duct
Pancreas
Duodenum
Bi-
lia-
ry
tra-
ct
Hanshin lost.
Maybe they're just going green, but the
cheeseburger I bought didn't have any cheese.
The hit counter on my
website has stopped.
Big Chat Party
7PM Tonight
No one came to my
chat party yesterday.
Chat Participants                1/20
The fact that nobody
came reminds me...
when I got on the bus yesterday,
everyone else got off.
School Trip Log
The fact that everyone
got off reminds me...
School Trip Log
Kamakura Home Tour
On my high school trip...
I'm turning off the lights.
Two minutes after the lights
were turned off, I asked...
"Is everyone awake?"
but everyone was asleep.
The fact that they were
asleep reminds me...
lately, I can't sleep.
I've started eating before
bed to help me sleep,
but I've gained weight.
Thinking about food reminds me...
Last month's birthday
present was just...
a butter roll.
No, no. Stop dwelling on the past.
I must think happy thoughts.
Who could that be?
I'm coming.
Kimiko.
Mom's away on her trip, isn't she?
I thought I'd make dinner.
That'd be a big help.
Hello.
And hello to you, too.
Mi, you've grown, haven't you?
That's right.
I'll spend the day playing with my
grandson without a care in the world.
Hey, listen...
I made dumplings
earlier, in the park.
You can have some.
This is...
You must be hungry, so eat up.
Mi...
They're all chocolate,
so you can eat them.
I see, I see. Thank you.
Why are you crying?
You've always been
so quick to cry.
Well, I'll be in the kitchen.
Sure.
I see. Life is more than pain.
There are wonderful things like this.
They're all chocolate, so eat them.
What?
Hey, hurry and eat them!
They're delicious, so hurry!
But, this is...
Come on, hurry!
Start eating them!
They're delicious!
Surely...
Surely happiness
must taste like mud.
Mommy, grandpa fell over.
Short Thoughts
Here you go.
Peacefully, peacefully.
Nothing could be better.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 46
Is it trying to kill me?
It's finished!
What is?
Superglue.
Glue
It's pretty huge.
Because it's super.
I'll spread this all
over the hallway
and immobilize
Nano and Sakamoto.
You're up to something weird again.
Who'd ever fall for
such an obvious trap?
You did.
I didn't fall for anything!
Hey, hurry and
get me out of here!
I've got places to be!
It'll come off with water.
Then get some water!
Hurry and get some water!
Ah! It's snack time.
LISTEN!
I'm going to eat my snack,
so you'll have to excuse me.
Stop!
Huh?
Huh? What? Huhwha?
Hey.
What're we gonna do?
This sucks.
Sakamoto, you look like a
cockroach trapped on sticky paper.
This isn't funny!
Besides, you're trapped too!
Huh? Huhwha?
Serves you right!
It's divine retribution.
Huh? That's weird.
You're always up to no good.
Huh? Huhwha?
Sakamoto, what do we do?
Huh? Sakamoto's gone.
Sakamoto? Sakamoto?
Sakamoto!
We can't get it
off without water.
At this rate, I won't get my snack.
I might get hungry
while I'm stuck here.
I might starve to death.
I might die.
I might really die.
I'm home.
It's Nano.
It sure is hot out...
I heard it's 35 degrees outside.
What are you doing?
While I was playing with the glue,
it squirted out.
But if we put water on it...
But I'm stuck in it, too.
But if we get some water, Nano, Nano...
What? Water?
Yes.
Anyway, get up first.
If you lie in the hall,
your clothes will get...
What is this?
Um...
Hey, my hand!
What is this?
My hand! My hand!
State
Competition
Congratu-
lations,
Go-Soccer
Club,
on attending
the State
Competition
Money
President.
This must be the power
of Daiku Industries.
A Little Miracle
I'm glad it stopped raining.
Next,
Sakamoto
Guess who.
Is that you, Professor?
Yup!
What gave me away?
Well, it was obvious.
You're the only one here.
Now it's your turn.
What? Uh, okay...
Guess who.
Nano.
The Shinonome household passed
another peaceful day.
Hey Nano, am I right?
Sakamoto Medicine
Yes, you're right.
Okay, now it's my turn again.
Sure.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 47
Crap, crap, crap.
Final Exam
English
Physical Ed.
I'm completely lost
at the very first question.
Choose the word that
best describes the picture.
What is this?
This thing that looks like
it'd be killed by a poof spell?
What word could
possibly describe it?
Wait. I've seen
this problem before.
What was it? I asked
Ms. Sakurai about it.
I think it was...
What is this?
Did you draw this thing that looks like it'd be killed by a Poof spell?
This thing that looks like
it'd be killed by a Poof spell?
Yeah! That killed-by-a-Poof thing!
That doesn't help!
Calm down. Just calm down, Yukko.
If I panic, I won't even be able
to answer the questions I know.
If it's flying, the word must be...
"Fly", I think.
No, no. That seems
too strong for this.
What is this monster doing?
Monster?
This isn't an English test.
It's a logic test.
But this is all I can do right now.
I'll just move on
to the next question.
The same monster is
holding a tennis racket...
which means that the answer to
the previous question isn't "monster"...
What kind of weird trick is this?
I'll erase the previous answer
and start from square one.
My eraser...
...isn't here!
Wh-wh-what am I gonna do?
I'll have to...
Mai!
Everyone should
have such great friends!
A sand eraser?
It'll tear... This thing
will tear the paper!
Hey, I don't have time for this!
Mai, do you have a normal-
She's asleep.
You have ten more minutes.
The time. Time is...
Just calm down.
That's right.
Calm down, and...
feel nothingness.
Nothingness...
The test is over.
What?!
The rain...
My heart...
Asa okite ha wo migaite atto yuuma gogo juuji
I wake up in the morning, brush my
teeth, and before I know it it's 10 PM
Kyou mo takusan waratta na takusan tokimeita na
We laughed and had a lot of fun today
Tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawaideru toki ni mo
and at times I and my friends chatted noisily like nitwits
Chirachira tte me ga au... guuzen da yo ne
When our eyes met, flutteringly... it must be coincidence
Hatsukoi nante ienai kyara ja nainda mon!
It's not in me to say this is my first love!
Nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
Hey, we'll see each other tomorrow, right?
Mabuta wo tojiru to kirakira kimi darake
If I close my eyes, all I see is a sparkling you
Kyou mo tanoshikatta ne aa koi shite da naa
Today was fun again, it must be love
Ureshii na ureshii na hajimemashite koigokoro
I'm so happy, so happy. Nice to meet you, awakening love.
Ashita mata aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you again tomorrow, so good night
Yume de sugu aeru ne oyasuminasai
I'll see you in my dreams soon, so good night
Open
Good morning!
Good morning.
No way! I got a love letter!
No way. Who's it from?
It says it's from
class Q's Tanaka.
Let's go see him.
I'm mud.
I'm a steel ball.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm molded while I'm hot. Clang!
The next episode of Nichijou is episode 12.
Narration:   Shiraishi Fuyumi
Don't miss it.