Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 72
It's true. Daiku Coffee reopened.
Really?
Here we are.
You're right. It's a café now.
Welcome.
I've been here before,
so you can order first.
Huh? Really?
Well, then...
I'd like a grande white
chocolatemocha frappuccino.
Huh?
Could I also get
a short single-shot,
caramel sauce,
hazelnut syrup, chocolate chip,
extra-whip espresso?
Go to hell!
Yukko, where are you going?
jou-jou-yuujou magi magi kaichou
The best, friendship, perfect harmony!
hai icchai mashou kimi wa best, best friend!
Yes, let's go, you're my best friend!
chotto fuza kete mitara
If you try being annoying
motto fuza ke kaeshite kuru
Then I'll be annoying in return
iigokochiitta aryashinai!
If I speak of comfort, it goes away
iiyana koto attatte
I had things I hated
sokko wasurechaunda
But I forgot them in one swift stroke
itsudatte janjan yarimashou!
Let's go do something non-stop!
nijyuuyon jikan isshodemo mondainai
We can be together 24/7!
Almost like twins, a parent and a child or cloned cells!
marude futago ka oyako ka kuroom saibou
kore ja renai suru hitsuyou to ka nakunakunai?
Don't you cry when you fall in love?
Those are totally different things!
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
kenka shichatta toki mo
Even when we fought
kanari e konda toki mo
Even when we felt really blue
hitori de itai you na toki mo
Even when we want to be alone
We are next to each other
futo kizukeba chikaku ni iru
Until death do us part
shi na ba morotomo
Why, I wonder?
nande daro
soba ni itainda
I want to be by your side
When I'm with you
kimi to isshonara
tokei hyaku baisoku
Time flies a hundred times as fast
tanoshii na
It's so much fun
tanoshi sugirunda
It's too much fun
sasuga saikyou furendo
Always the same, with my best friend!
nan nano yo
What is it?
yabai shinkuro mo
Man, we're even synchronized
itsumo oosawagi
Always such a rage
kanari go kinj omeiwaku
Annoying everyone around us
ima nanji?
What time is it?
tatoe yororeihi
Time to yodel!
wakewakan nai nai!
What are you talking about?
soure-do-shi-ra-
What am I going to do?
so-zo-i-jo-
More than imagination!
nante iu ka saikou
What should I say, awesome!
Whatever you say, we're friends!
a-dako-da itte temo tomodachi
wasshoi!
Hooray!
jou-jou-yuujou
The best, friendship!
magi magi kaichou
Perfect harmony!
Ms. Nakamura
The sleeping medication had
no effect on Shinonome.
So I'll use this!
Now with increased oxidizing power,
Mr. Oxidation Plus!
as well as a backup
paralyzing agent,
Mr. Oxidation Plus!
I'll get Shinonome to drink this,
and then capture her in one fell swoop.
Once I've secured her,
I'll have some real fun with her...
Whoops...
Science Room 2
- The Perpetual Change of Geomagnetism
- The Earth's Magnetic Field
What am I going to do?
We're using compasses today.
Nano, did you get your compass?
Yes!
Hey, everyone...
Today's class is study hall!
Hooray!
Did Ms. Nakamura collapse again?
Nakamura seems to collapse a lot...
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 73
Sasahara,
why are you skipping
cleaning duty again?
But I cleaned my own area.
There's still a ton of dust!
Is that so?
Return to your area.
How did you know I was on the roof?
Are you an idiot?
I heard it was a nice day out,
so I just happened to walk by!
I see.
Thank you for going out of
your way to check my area.
Don't get any weird ideas!
It's not like I did it for you!
Crane
Game
Tokisada
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 74
Tokisada
A day off...
Today, I'm meeting Mai
in a neighboring town.
We're gonna get some free candy!
Would you like some bread?
Huh?
No, thank you. I ate before I left...
Aren't dogs... against
the rules, or something?
All right!
No, thank you.
We're almost there,
so I guess I should stand!
Just kidding...
We will soon be arriving
at Tokisada Toiyamachi.
Nice timing!
This stop is Tokisada Toiyamachi.
Okay, time to leave.
Exit to the right.
And now, traingoers, goodbye!
Well, well, well...
I'm leaving from this side.
Endure it, endure it!
Don't lose your cool over this!
E-excuse me. I was in a hurry.
Oh, come on...
It's all right.
I'll never see that girl again.
I'm in a neighboring town.
Nobody knows me here!
Let it go! Let it go!
Wait a sec...
is she following me?
Just my imagination.
I'm a little tense today.
There should be a Daiku Burger
right outside the station.
Where is it?
Mai's map is all wiggly.
It'd probably be faster
to just ask someone...
Daiku Burger Here
All right!
Excuse me. Do you know
where Daiku Burger...
Hey! Why are you following me?
That's gotta be against some sort of, you know, copyright law!
Daiku Burger's on the
other side of this building.
I'm also meeting someone there,
so I could take you if you want.
Welcome.
Sorry, Sis. I was at my club.
You're late!
She really is meeting someone here.
Thank you for waiting.
Mai isn't here yet...
Am I just having a bad day?
That was so embarrassing!
Well, whatever.
It's a neighboring town.
Right!
Think of it as a practice
run, for real life...
Yeah!
I overcame that embarrassment...
I can overcome anything!
Yukko.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Mai!
Is that... possibly...
Trick or treat.
I have no choice.
I've gotta get some candy!
Trick or treat.
Halloween was last week...
This is a Crow!
If you must pass a crow that's
attempting to intimidate you,
make sure you maintain eye contact.
Sleep
I'm not that sleepy...
They say counting sheep jumping
over a fence will help you sleep.
Okay! I'll try it!
One sheep...
She's out after the first one!
Professor, that's amazing! I'll try, too!
One...
That sheep didn't make it over the fence...
Volunteer
Spirit
There you go.
Thanks, Sis. You're amazing.
Did Sasahara teach
you how to do this?
Wh-why would he have
taught me everything?
Aren't you two good friends?
No! Not at all! Really, not at all!
Calm down...
Didn't you iron a handkerchief recently?
That was just some trash I happened
to come across in the street...
You didn't iron it
because it was Sasahara's?
I-I told you that wasn't why!
I was working out my arms,
and an iron happened to be there.
And a handkerchief
happened to be under that...
Or something...
something like that!
It's so obvious...
But you looked so happy
when you were ironing.
D-don't be stupid!
I... it was...
The Earth had just
entered the Photon Belt!
So, yesterday...
What happened?
I talked to Ono.
What? That's great!
Two hours by train,
then one hour by bus.
I left the bustle of the city
for the countryside Town S.
While believing I'd never
find it, but unable to give up,
I've been searching for a single book.
That phantasmal book
that brought color into
my gray childhood...
Because I entered this library...
I can read that book again.
I thanked those who helped me,
and took the book in my hands.
The
Color
of
Autumn
Trying to calm my pounding heart...
I...
slowly opened the book.
Love-like
Time's almost up.
Remember to sign your names.
Ten, nine, eight...
seven...
six... five...
four... three...
two...
one...
Zero!
Please pass your papers to the front!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 75
Halloween ended a while ago...
This coffee isn't very coffee coffee!
Huh? Not coffee coffee?
What does that mean?
I don't really get it, either.
But... it's just not coffee coffee!
Just try it! Here.
What does "not coffee coffee" even mean?
It's not coffee coffee!
Everyone, it's finally finished!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 76
It's Biscuit #2.
I am Biscuit #2.
Oh, that thing from the other day...
Hardly any reaction.
Hey, I want you to look at it...
But I already saw the other one.
#1 and #2 are different!
This one's even more amazing!
I see...
My name is Biscuit #2.
I am a Biscuit Robot
made by Professor Shinonome.
True to my name, biscuits
are my power source.
I run on biscuits...
Professor, my biscuit!
What? This is the last one...
Biscuit #2's specialty is speed reading!
Go ahead.
Done.
Yes!
Why aren't you surprised?
Well, I can read fast, too...
Then why do you
always read so slowly?
I think this way seems
a bit more normal...
What's wrong, Biscuit #2?
Books with lots of
words make me sleepy.
That sounds pretty normal to me.
Why won't you tell me I'm awesome?
I'm super awesome!
Is that what you're upset about?
It's important...
You're already awesome, Professor.
That's right.
I may have made a slight mistake.
I don't think you made a mistake...
Hey, how awesome am I?
Uh, about as awesome as
the Chichibu Mountain Range.
I don't get it...
Then, you're as awesome
as the Nullarbor Plain.
I want something bigger!
Like a whale?
That might work.
Whales are certainly large.
They really are...
Short Thoughts
There is no "that's fine."
There is no "this is fine."
And that's just fine.
What are you going to do?
Snakes and Ladders!
What'll you do?
A quiz!
Quizzes are fun for everyone.
But getting paid to entertain the princess
seems like a lot of fun...
You've got to have fun
like this once in a while.
Yeah.
I just put the ball in here...
Actually, it's over here.
Way to go, Sixty-six!
I didn't know you could do that...
I'm actually hoping to become
the king's personal magician.
If that happened, you'd be set.
Yeah!
I'm starting to feel it, too!
I'm gonna make some money!
Hey! It's time!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 77
Quiet!
Servant
You will follow the order indicated
by the lots you received.
First person, step forward!
I'm first.
Starting off with Sixty-six.
We'll be earning money from the first guy...
The king's personal magician, huh?
Follow your dream, Sixty-six.
So, where is the ball?
Huh?
I wanted to be the king's personal...
Next.
What?!
Second person, step forward!
It's my turn...
It's my turn to show
the world what I can do!
I'll turn this pinch into a chance!
Who's that?
Four of Humor... maybe his jokes will work.
Hey, is that...
Yeah! He came.
Four, reporting for duty.
Next.
I never thought Four would...
Number three, step forward.
Hey, are you okay?
It's my turn...
Huh? Didn't you say
you were quizzing her?
I never expected this,
but my quizzes are all I've got...
I have to make sure
the princess gets it right!
I'm fine.
Mistakes won't be forgiven.
I have to make it really easy...
I-I am Six, and I will be doing a quiz.
Wh-What kind of bread can't you eat?
There are two possible answers!
First, a breadbox! Second, melon bread!
Which is it?
He...
I don't know.
That's... that's correct!
I have but one regret.
It's over!
The quizmaster's gone, too.
Next.
S-Seven! I shall list all the cities
that have hosted the Olympics...
We shall not forget your courage, Seven!
What's wrong with you?
Can no one entertain the princess?
Wh-what am I supposed to do?
I was going to act like a cheerleader...
Moron!
I'm splitting disposable
chopsticks with my butt.
I'm giving a Nanjing Lily performance!
I'm dicing cabbage!
We're all going to disappear...
Hey, I hope you haven't forgotten me.
Y-you...
In the world of comedy,
your comedic mannerisms
place you second to none.
You're Comedian Thirteen!
I've got a joke that'll
get the princess to laugh,
and then turn this situation around...
Wait, Thirteen! It's too dangerous!
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Did you think I'd only
perform Swan Lake?
Well, keep watching...
I'll show you what true comedy is...
Comedian Thirteen!
Huh?
Why me?
Next! Number five!
How long will you make us wait? Hurry up!
Who's number five?
Is it you?
No! This is just the number on my hat!
Who is it?
Hey, you're number five...
It's over.
Hey, five! Show yourself!
Who is it?
What? Really?
Next. Anyone will do.
Just go.
There's nothing we can do.
It'd be hopeless, no matter
how many lives I had!
I can't deal with this stupid game!
I'll go stand in the hallway!
aru hi
One day
papa to futari de katariatta sa
I was talking with my dad
kono yo ni ikiru yorokobi
About what joy it is to live in this world
soshite kanashimi no koto wo
And about sadness as well
guriin guriin
Green, green
aozora ni wa kotori ga utai
Little birds sing in the blue sky
guriin guriin
Green, green
oka no ue ni wa rara midori ga moeru
On the little hill the blossoms show
sono toki
That day
papa ga itta sa boku wo mune ni daki
My dad told me, as he held me to his chest:
tsuraku kanashii toki ni mo rarara naku n ja nai to
"Even when all is hard on you, you shouldn't cry"
guriin guriin
Green, green
aozora ni wa soyokaze fuite
A gentle wind passes through the blue sky
guriin guriin
Green, green
oka no ue ni wa rara midori ga yureru
On the little hill the blossoms sway in the wind
midori ga hirogaru
The blossoms spread
I'm the sweet grande white chocolate
mocha frappuccino, ordered with a
short single-shot, caramel sauce,
hazelnut syrup, chocolate chip,
extra-whip espresso.
The next episode of Nichijou is episode 19.
Narration:     Aikawa Rikako
Don't miss it.