Shinonome Nano.
I've used anesthetics,
Mr. Short Circuit, and pitfall traps.
To have evaded all
the traps I've set for her,
she must be better
than anticipated.
I want her!
Until now, I've attempted to capture her at school in order to avoid suspicion,
Ms. Nakamura,
Part 2
but...
Could that be...
Wait! Wait!
Wait! Stop!
Let's eat!
Go get your father.
What?
Sis, where's the remote?
Yesterday, it was
under the kettle.
It's not him.
Hey! Who's out there?
What are you doing?
A burglar?!
Crap.
What? A woman?
joujou yuujou! banji maji kaichou!
The best friendship, everything is perfect!
hai icchaimashou kimi wa Best Best Friend!
Yes, I'll say it, you're my best friend!
chotto fuzakete mitara
If you try being annoying
motto fuzakekaeshitekuru
Then I'll be more annoying in return
If I speak of comfort, it goes away
igokochi ii ttara aryashinai!
iyana koto attatte
I had things I hated
sokkoo wasurechaunda
But I forgot them in one swift stroke
itsudatte janjan yarimashou!
Let's go do something non-stop!
nijyuuyo jikan isshodemo mondainai
We can be together 24/7!
Almost like twins, a parent and a child or cloned cells!
marude futago ka oyako ka kuroon saibou
kore ja ren'ai suru hitsuyou toka nakunakunai?
Isn't it not unnecessary to love, then?
Those are totally different things!
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai!!
kenka shichatta toki mo
Even when we fought
kanari hekonda toki mo
Even when we felt really blue
hitori de itai yo na toki mo
Even when we want to be alone
We are next to each other
futo kizukeba chikaku ni iru
Until death do us part
shinaba morotomo
Why, I wonder?
nande daro
soba ni itainda
I want to be by your side
When I'm with you
kimi to isshonara
tokei hyakubaisoku
Time flies a hundred times as fast
tanoshii na
It's so much fun
tanoshisugirunda
It's too much fun
sasuga saikyou Friend! Hey!
Always the same, with my best friend!
nan nanoyo
What is it?
yabbai shinkurokan!
Man, I feel we're synchronized!
itsumo oosawagi
Always such a rage
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
Annoying everyone around us
ima nanji?
What time is it?
tatoe yororeihi
Let's see, yodelayheehoo!
wake wakannainai!
What are you talking about?
so-re-do-shi-ra-
What am I going to do?
souzou ijou!
More than imagination!
nante iu ka saikou!
What should I say, awesome!
Whatever you say, we're friends!
a-dako-da ittetemo tomodachi
wasshoi!
Hooray!
joujou yuujou!
The best friendship!
banji maji kaichou!
Everything is perfect!
It's Nano.
S-sorry.
Those must be heavy.
Not at all.
Thank you.
Can you carry them yourself?
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 102
Mio! Mio! Big news!
I'm writing a report. Tell me later.
Now's not the time for
that! I saw something!
I saw something crazy!
What was it?
Sasahara and Nano
were walking together!
Huh.
Huh?
I expected a bigger reaction.
So?
Uh, yeah...
They seemed to be having
a friendly conversation.
Huh.
Well, I'm sure that sort of
thing happens all the time.
What?
They're people.
Of course they'll talk.
What? Was that all?
Uh, yeah. That's it.
Listen, I have to finish
this report by next period.
I need to focus.
Uh, yeah. Sorry.
That was boring...
Well?
Huh?
So... what was it?
What was what?
I'm asking what they
were talking about.
You there, Yukko?
Oh, um...
Sasahara said her
books looked heavy.
And?
That's it.
Yukko, are you stupid?
I always thought you were stupid,
but I never thought
you were this dumb!
I can't believe you said
you had big news!
Your idiocy must be a
miracle, don't you think?
A miracle moron? Just kidding!
Well, Nano and
Sasahara were kissing.
Th-th-th-there you go again...
After greeting each
other with a kiss,
they went to buy bread together.
Once they finished
their conversation
about the bread they'd
bought, Sasahara...
Sasahara...
... removed his clothes.
Removed his clothes!
Then, motivated by Sasahara
saying "delicious", they...
They...
While in the courtyard...
In the courtyard!
I totally forgot! I have
to do that report, too!
Oh, no...
We have to think
of our own topic...
In the courtyard... In the
courtyard... In the courtyard!
You bought a fried
noodle sub, didn't you?
But I like it!
You always get that.
Would that make you
the fried noodle princess?
W-well, what did
you get, Koujirou?
Me?
I bought a red bean bun.
That makes you...
What is it?
Nothing at all!
That makes Koujirou...
the red bean prince!
Delicious.
That makes you...
What is it?
Nothing at all!
That makes Koujirou...
That makes Koujirou
a beautiful man!
Let's eat in the courtyard.
Let's!
And then the teacher
ate a wild whale.
Is that true?
It's true...
If it's true, that would be outside the
200 nautical mile exclusive fishing zone.
That's not a problem.
That teacher is an Eskimo.
Nano...
You have a bit of
bread on your face.
That delicate moment
floated in on a spring breeze.
Our gentle time together...
In the courtyard In the courtyard In the courtyard In the courtyard In the courtyard
Rendezvous!
No progress! No progress!
I can't finish my report like this!
Yukko!
I had just thought of a topic!
What did they do
in the courtyard?!
Shut up, already!
Uh, um...
Addis Ababa!
I have to...
I have to go to the courtyard!
I have to enter that
off-color Garden of Eden!
Thank you.
It was nothing.
Farewell.
Huh? Naganohara, what's wrong?
Nano...
Yes?
I heard that you ate a fried noodle
sub with Sasahara in the courtyard.
Sasahara?
Oh, him?
He just picked up my book.
That's all?
Yes. That's all.
Really? No noodle subs?
What are you talking about?
Helvetica Standard
Aw, come on.
Tell me who you like, Yumi.
I don't know...
I promise I won't tell anyone.
If I ever do, I'll give
you one million yen.
Really? Promise, okay?
Okay!
Takashi.
Listen up, everyone!
Yumi likes Takashi!
Unfasten
I see.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 103
Head!
Thank you.
Here.
Knight
That damned genius.
It's rare to see you come to the dojo.
With the tournament coming up,
it's better to practice here,
with an instructor, than at school.
Besides, I'm glad Naganohara came.
She hasn't been
showing up at all lately.
What? Really?
She says practice makes her weaker.
She's a monster.
Who do you usually
practice with, then?
The instructor, and...
oh yeah, Sasahara's
been stopping by a lot.
Sasahara?!
Why would he come by?
Why?
You've gone to the same
dojo since middle school,
so why wouldn't he come?
Well, yeah, but...
And why didn't
you already know?
Don't you talk at school?
Aren't you in the same club?
No, we're not.
He's been in the acting
club since our first year.
What?!
The acting club?
Why isn't he in the kendo club?
How should I know?
If you subtract kendo from Sasahara,
all that's left is a funny guy.
You're only saying that because
you've only seen him at the dojo.
What does that mean?
Listen, the Sasahara who
joined the school acting club
is out of his mind.
It's grape juice.
I can see that...
Right?
But why didn't you invite
Sasahara to join the kendo club?
It's a waste.
What? Why do I have to invite him?
He can do what he wants.
But Sasahara could
make it to the nationals!
Who cares?
Besides, he's an idiot for joining the acting club without saying a word.
An idiot, an idiot... a huge idiot!
Well, but...
if you insist,
I guess I could invite him.
She's so easy to read...
Well?
When does Sasahara usually come?
Lately, he's been stopping by about once every three days.
So he'll probably be there tomorrow...
I see... I mean, it's not like I care.
Hey, Sis.
What?
Why don't you confess
your love to Sasahara?
Middle schoolers are too
young to say stuff like that!
I'm going on ahead!
Sis, you're too pure-hearted.
Love-like
It's cold...
Cold attack!
Later!
Jump
I see.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 104
That was delicious.
Thank you for the food!
Professor...
You have to eat your onions, too.
I think I might be a
little young for onions.
What does that mean?
Either way, you need
to finish your food.
But onions are bitter,
so I don't really get them.
If you don't finish your food,
then starting tomorrow, no snacks for you.
You should follow
Mr. Sakamoto's example.
He always eats...
Sorry. I can't help you...
Mr. Sakamoto, what's wrong?
A-are you okay?
Don't worry. It's just a cold.
A little rest will cure it...
But you haven't eaten anything.
You should have something.
No, I'm fine.
Do you want some milk?
No...
This is a problem.
What can you eat?
No, I don't want
anything right now.
But...
Sakamoto wants to eat onions.
Are you trying to kill me?
Is there anything you want?
No.
I'll leave out some milk.
If you want anything
to eat, just let me know.
I'll go buy it.
Okay.
Huh?
Since I'm sick, too,
I think I want some chocolate.
Please eat your
onions, Professor.
What?
Why does Sakamoto get
whatever he wants, but I don't?!
Because Mr. Sakamoto is sick.
I'm sick, too!
You're perfectly healthy.
When I'm sick, I want
chocolate! I have a cold, too!
If you have a cold,
you have to take medicine.
Do you want some medicine?
I give up!
Oh, Professor!
Professor...
Go away!
You don't like me, so you're
mean to me about onions!
You like Sakamoto more, so you
don't make Sakamoto eat onions!
That's not it.
Cats can't eat onions.
I've never heard that before!
Oh, well.
I like you more, Professor.
Really?
Yes.
Then, can I have some chocolate?
Let me think...
if you eat your onions, then sure.
What? Why?!
You said you like me more!
Then I like Mr. Sakamoto more.
What? Which is it?
I like you both.
What does that mean?
Sakamoto, what does it mean?
Hypnosis
Short Thoughts
Which floor?
Seven, please.
Thank you.
Now that I think about it,
I haven't been shy this year.
Student Adviser
Uh, Naganohara, your
plan for the future is...
Cartoonist
...to become a cartoonist?
Y-yes.
Naganohara,
you certainly are good at art.
Oh, not really...
I encourage you to
pursue your dreams.
Please do your best.
Let's see... Yukko wants melon juice.
What should I get?
Well, money's tight this month,
so I'll get plain old banana juice.
Oh, thank—
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 105
Sa... Sa... Sa... Sa...
Sa... Sa-Sa-Sa-Sa...
Sasahara!
What's wrong?
You look like a dove
that's been shot.
Oh, s-s-sorry!
Uh, um... what should I do?
I have to say something.
U-um...
Nice weather we're having.
What am I saying?!
It's super-overcast!
How deep.
Yes.
Does this coin belong to you?
Ah, yes.
I see.
Thank you very much.
Huh? Oh, sure.
What a surprise, for this to happen.
What?
I happened to forget
my wallet today.
I came to this vending machine,
in the hopes of quenching my thirst.
There, I found a coin.
Heaven must have smiled upon me.
This beverage I am
about to consume
is holy water from the heavens.
Um...
This vending machine...
is quite the trickster!
Y-yes!
For this vending machine
to fool me like this...
What an unusually bold
machine it must be.
I like you! I shall give
you a single coin!
S-Sasahara...
I have no proof, but...
I feel like I've gotten
closer to Sasahara.
Mio, where's my melon juice?
Knight
Was she trying to
tell me something?
Naganohara's so strong,
people say she's invincible.
Knight. A knight...
Speaking of knights...
Why don't you confess your love?
Sis, the bath's open.
I wonder if Sasahara's
also looking at this moon.
Sasahara, you're pretty good.
Let's practice together
again sometime.
All right!
Next time, I'll teach
you my finishing move!
Sis!
Look, look, look, look...
Sisters!
Don't come in without permission.
What were you thinking about?
Shut up! Who cares
what I was thinking?
Don't get so embarrassed.
I'm not embarrassed!
Just leave me alone...
mukashi girishia no ikarosu wa
In days long past, Ikarus in Greece
rou de katameta tori no hane
fastened bird feathers with wax
ryoute ni motte tobidatta
He wore them on his arms and took flight
kumo yori takaku mada tooku
past the clouds and farther yet
yuuki hitotsu wo tomo ni shite
with only courage on his side
oka wa gungun toozakari
Steadily the hills draw into the distance
shita ni hirogaru aoi umi
and underneath him stretches out the blue sea
ryoute no hane wo habatakase
Flapping the wings on his arms
taiyou mezashi tondeyuku
he flies towards the sun
yuuki hitotsu wo tomo ni shite
with only courage on his side
bokura wa tsuyoku ikiteyuku
We live each day to the fullest
yuuki hitotsu wo tomo ni shite
with only courage on our side
Always out of change when
you have no ten-yen coins.
That's me, the law of
the vending machine.
The next episode of
Nichijou is episode 25.
Narration:     Nagai Ichiro
Don't miss it.