Heno Heno
It's gotten colder lately.
Sakamoto...
Mr. Sakamoto...
H-h-h-hey... stop. Stop, stop!
Mr. Sakamoto.
Just calm down, already!
First, tell me why
you're doing this!
jou-jou-yuujou magi magi kaichou
The best, friendship, perfect harmony!
hai icchai mashou kimi wa best, best friend!
Yes, let's go, you're my best friend!
chotto fuza kete mitara
If you try being annoying
motto fuza ke kaeshite kuru
Then I'll be annoying in return
iigokochiitta aryashinai!
If I speak of comfort, it goes away
iiyana koto attatte
I had things I hated
sokko wasurechaunda
But I forgot them in one swift stroke
itsudatte janjan yarimashou!
Let's go do something non-stop!
nijyuuyon jikan isshodemo mondainai
We can be together 24/7!
Almost like twins, a parent and a child or cloned cells!
marude futago ka oyako ka kuroom saibou
kore ja renai suru hitsuyou to ka nakunakunai?
Don't you cry when you fall in love?
Those are totally different things!
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
kenka shichatta toki mo
Even when we fought
kanari e konda toki mo
Even when we felt really blue
hitori de itai you na toki mo
Even when we want to be alone
We are next to each other
futo kizukeba chikaku ni iru
Until death do us part
shi na ba morotomo
Why, I wonder?
nande daro
soba ni itainda
I want to be by your side
When I'm with you
kimi to isshonara
tokei hyaku baisoku
Time flies a hundred times as fast
tanoshii na
It's so much fun
tanoshi sugirunda
It's too much fun
sasuga saikyou furendo
Always the same, with my best friend!
nan nano yo
What is it?
yabai shinkuro mo
Man, we're even synchronized
itsumo oosawagi
Always such a rage
kanari go kinj omeiwaku
Annoying everyone around us
ima nanji?
What time is it?
tatoe yororeihi
Time to yodel!
wakewakan nai nai!
What are you talking about?
soure-do-shi-ra-
What am I going to do?
so-zo-i-jo-
More than imagination!
nante iu ka saikou
What should I say, awesome!
Whatever you say, we're friends!
a-dako-da itte temo tomodachi
wasshoi!
Hooray!
jou-jou-yuujou
The best, friendship!
magi magi kaichou
Perfect harmony!
Mai, add some tones here.
And Yukko, use the pencil to write the page numbers here.
Fill in the hair, too.
Okay.
Amazing!
Naganohara, I didn't
know you drew manga.
Oh, it's no a big deal.
She used to hide it from
us and draw in secret.
Who cares about the past?
Really?
Yeah.
But when I sent my
last submission in,
I got a letter that said they were looking forward to my next one.
It made me think it was a bit weird to keep my drawing a secret.
They must think you have talent!
That can't be true...
Could I take a look?
U-um, Nano?
Sorry, sorry.
Nano, you don't need to read it.
Nano!
E-excuse me. I'm going outside for a bit...
Are you okay? Want me to come?
No, it's fine.
You came to help
Naganohara with her work.
I'll be back soon...
Nano has a lot on her plate.
Shoot! It's getting late!
We don't have any time to waste...
Let's keep working until Nano gets back.
The deadline's tomorrow.
Roger that!
I'm not a bad artist myself.
Let's wrap this up.
All units, attack! Just kidding.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 83
Yukko, don't give up so soon.
Here.
That was quick...
Let's look over your work.
Don't make me hit you.
Don't...
Hold it, Mai! What are you drawing?!
Saint Kuuya.
That's not what I meant!
Why are you drawing at all?
I heard the empty background crying.
What?
Erase that with White-Out!
Just put the tone there...
and don't do anything weird!
This has to be the worst pain
I've ever experienced.
I guess I'll fill in the hair.
Huh?
Um...
Wait wait wait wait!
What? This... What? What?
Oh, right. If you make a
mistake, tell me right away.
Right away?
I can't do that! I have to
fix this as soon as possible!
Here.
You're done?
I hope you didn't draw
anything this time.
Don't make me kill you.
Don't...
Do...
...n't make me kill you?
What is this?
A graveyard.
You idiot!
This is a fancy palace in Daikanyama!
And I told you not to draw anything...
Why would you do this?
Because there was space there.
I can't handle this!
Forget it. Just erase it.
Just erase it, okay? Just erase!
Okay.
L-looks pretty good...
It looks pretty good, but it just...
doesn't look right!
Would it fan the flames
to show her this?
I'm done.
Did you erase it properly this time?
I really need you to
stop messing around.
Why?
What is this?!
I erased it.
Do you want me to erase you?!
Why would you do this?
Because this comic
isn't very interesting.
You just hit a nerve!
I'll give you a new sheet, so draw in
panel borders. Just like that page...
Okay.
Just the borders, okay?!
Helvetica
Standard
10 seconds.
20 seconds.
1, 2, 3,
4, 5, 6, 7,
8, 9, 10.
Time.
This... this is out of control!
It's not even about
looking similar any more.
Who the heck is this?!
Showing this to her will
definitely fan the flames!
I'm done.
You really just drew in panel borders?
Once upon a time, there was
an old man and an old woman.
The old man went to cut
grass in the mountains...
It's a private born from a peach.
I don't care about that!
Mai, just read a book...
Okay.
Th-this...
is hopeless!
I feel like the more I
panic, the worse it gets...
Aw crap. What am I
gonna do? What can I do?
Mai!
Leave it to me.
C-can she really
do it? Can you, Mai?
Of course not... there's just no way...
What? Mai!
So good! Unbelievably good!
She's too good! But this...
This is unbelievably different!
I want to go back to the time...
before I knew right from left.
When everything seemed so new...
And I'll tell myself...
to stay like that.
I'm sorry!
Please draw this again!
But...
I don't have any more paper!
Morals
Um, don't run in the hallway...
Sasahara!
Short Thoughts
That brat-
I can't get this thing off!
There wasn't any point.
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 84
You're open!
Naganohara?
What are you doing here?
No, no, no. Me, too!
Oh...
What are you doing?
Oh, um... nothing much.
I see...
Actually, I just couldn't focus during practice,
even with the meet coming up.
When you were in high school,
did you ever feel this way?
For some reason,
my armor feels really heavy.
She's not listening...
Shiitake Zanmai's
a weird comic, isn't it?
She can't do anything but kendo.
Huh? What? Did you hear
something interesting?
Forget it.
Naganohara, isn't the
national meet coming up?
That's true.
Right? Mihoshi said you
hadn't been by the dojo...
I came to shop!
Huh? But...
Have some crackers.
Huh? What?
Later!
What was that about?
Hey, Sis!
What are you doing here?
Naganohara was just here.
What? Isn't she going to the
national meet tomorrow?
What? It's tomorrow?
Did she say anything?
Not really.
Oh! She left these.
Do you want one?
Okay.
Whoah, they're really red.
They are...
Hot!
Melon Bread
Best before date located
on back of bread.
Expiration
Love-like
Hey, Mio... check this out.
How does this look?
I thought it might be
fun to change my image.
Does it look good?
Yeah, it suits you.
Ready?
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 85
Not yet.
Ready?
Ready!
Okay, here I come!
Professor, where are you?
Ready.
Mr. Sakamoto, found you!
Luck's a scary thing.
I'm sorry.
I don't usually play
kiddy games like this.
But I guess I should play with
you guys every once in a while.
I see.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Let's get going!
Yes!
Professor...
Where are you?
Hey, kid!
Professor?
Where is that kid hiding?
We can't find her anywhere.
They'll never find me here.
That kid could be hiding outside.
You're right. Why
don't we take a break?
Sure. But, you know...
What if we never found her?
Professor...
Did you make this yourself?
Why did you come out?
That's not how you play
hide-and-seek, you know.
I thought you wouldn't
be able to find me...
Well, we couldn't.
Professor...
Did you just blow your nose?
Yeah.
Professor, now there's more to wash...
You really are hopeless.
I'm "it" this time! Let's play!
Then I'll wash it.
You'd probably mess it up, so it's okay.
I wouldn't mess it up.
No, I'm sure you'd mess it up.
I can do it...
This is Pyon!
What did you say?
No, but...
No buts!
Nichijou:
Everyday Life
Part 86
I'm glad you want to help.
But you were the one
who spilled the ink, right?
I didn't have any more paper.
So, when I was forced
to ask you to get some,
what did you say?
What was it you said?
Which of us should go buy it?
I'll let...
...this decide.
That's ridiculous!
You spilled the ink,
so you go buy it!
I still have lots of work to do!
But that's fine.
Once you ended up going
to buy it, what did you say?
Hold on...
What did you say?!
Hey, how old do I look?
Who cares?
If you don't hurry, the
stationery store will close!
Why are you asking me this now?
You look your age!
But that's fine.
So, you were going to the store.
And when you put on
your shoes, you said...
It's cold today...
Oh, I feel a little under the weather.
Just suck it up!
How long are you gonna drag this out?
And it's not cold today, either!
But that's still fine!
And you ended up buying...
What is that?!
Yeah, but...
I asked you for paper!
When I told you to stop with
the jokes, you gave me...
Here.
No, thank you!
I can't use that!
What do you expect
me to do with it?
When I said that, you said...
Forgive me, hyacinth.
Hyacinth!
This isn't some minor problem!
And where'd the hyacinth
come from, anyway?
But I still believed in you.
I believed that you bought me paper...
That's a hard gag!
But when I asked you for
the paper, what did you say?
Mio, you need to
pacifyacinth yourself.
Pacifyacinth!
Who needs to pacify herself?
Who needs a hyacinth?
Yeah, that's why...
I asked you again if
you actually bought it...
And what did you say then?!
Forgive me.
What happened to the hyacinth?!
Who cares about hyacinths, anyway?
The paper!
And you gave me...
Here.
Yes, yes, yes, perfect...
Time to write...
You idiot!
How much stupidity do you have to put me through before you're satisfied?
When I asked you what
you were trying to do...
Did you know that the
truth isn't always correct?
Yes, it is!
You were completely useless,
so I tried to ask Nano for help!
I asked her to buy paper for me, and...
She was totally spaced out!
Her eyes were glued to
the page! It was a cry of joy!
I had no choice, so I asked Mai...
Mai, could you go and buy it for me?
I'm
going
home.
A
She went home!
She left without making a sound!
Mai always does
everything her own way...
It's Mai's way or the highway!
When you saw the letter, do you
remember what you said?
It must be a divine trick.
Some kind of devilish trap.
This is a devilish trap!
It's been a devilish trap
since you guys arrived!
When I said that, you...
I don't get it!
Well...
Stop it!
I don't want to hear
your excuses, you moron!
No, no, no. That's why...
I don't have any more peanuts, you...
Peanut-head!
But this...
There you go again!
What...
F-forgive me, hyacinth...
ano subarashii ai wo mou ichido
Let's relive our wonderful love
inochi kakete to chikatta hi kara
Ever since the day I pledged my life away
suteki na omoide nokoshite kita noni
although wonderful memories remain
ano toki onaji hana wo mite
we, who back then saw the same flower
utsukushii to itta futari no
both as something beautiful
kokoro to kokoro ga ima wa mou kayowanai
no longer speak to each other's hearts
ano subarashii ai wo mou ichido
Let's relive our wonderful love
Hello, I'm comic manuscript paper.
Now is the time to boldly illustrate your dreams and drop them in the mailbox.
The next episode of Nichijou is episode 21.
Narration:     Koyama Mami
Don't miss it.