No, really! I only got 32 points.
Then show me.
You said we'd show each
other on the count of three.
I showed you mine.
I told you, I got 32 points...
Then show me.
I'm telling the truth!
Think about it, it's 32 points.
Why would I lie about
such a realistic score?
Just 32 points.
Thirty-twelve!
You mean thirty-two, right?
So let's leave it at that, okay?
Fine.
It's not like seeing it will change anything.
My score isn't that great either,
so I got a little carried away...
Gotcha!
Everyday
Compliments
That's all I can do...
Uh... this is, uh...
Way to go, Yukko!
No no no!
I didn't mean "way to get a 1," I meant...
Remember how you forgot your
homework the day before yesterday?
No, no. That's not what I meant!
You did your homework but
forgot to bring it in, right?
So...?
It's that mindset which counts!
You don't usually do your
homework, but that time you did!
That's really hard to do.
It's the same with dreams and ambitions.
The first step is always the hardest.
And you've done that, Yukko!
You've cleared the hardest part!
The hardest part?
Yeah! The hardest part!
The most difficult part!
I... cleared... it?
Yeah.
You're amazing, Yukko,
and you may not have noticed...
But to a normal person, that's a
really hard thing to accomplish!
Well, I guess...
...you're right!
Yeah!
Yeah, that's right!
All jokes aside, I respect you for that.
I guess.
But you're definitely better than me, Mio-chan.
After all, you always do your homework.
It's just a habit to always do it.
I'm doing homework as a habit.
In your case, you're doing
something you don't usually do.
This is...
This bite...
I've got her!
But you know...
Did you know this, Yukko?
Trains and cars both use the most
energy when they start moving.
If you think about it that way, you may have
immense amounts of power within you!
I...
...see!
Don't fret.
Little by little...
But Mio-chan, you're giving me too much credit.
I'm just a normal person.
I fail a lot, and despite how I look,
I get depressed a lot too.
Oh, come on. There's no need to be so modest.
I-I'm not being modest...
Everyone already knows you're amazing.
No, well... you know, the
will to challenge yourself?
I guess I can't say I don't have that at all...
Right?
I'm nothing compared to you.
When I was working on my manga, I started
to think, "this probably won't get an award."
Then I got scared and never handed it in.
Well, you are a chicken.
Don't call me that, you 1-pointer...!
Yukko, come here.
Read this!
Test ethics.
Number one: Always try your best.
Yes! That's exactly it!
That's the most important thing!
Yukko, you're always trying your best!
You're already doing the
most important thing!
But I only got 1 point...
I-I can't...
I'm sorry, Yukko!
I got carried away with grades
and forgot about what's important.
I guess I was a little jealous of you,
since you're already golden!
Er, but...
Since I'm always doing my homework as a habit,
I don't really know if
I'm giving the tests my all.
The same goes for my manga.
But Yukko, you're different.
You're always trying your best!
You're like a fresh breath of mountain air!
I really want some of your positive attitude.
But that's all I have.
I told you, that's what's important!
Well, I suppose you're right.
How did you gain the confidence
to take that first step?
Simple.
Though I shouldn't really brag about it.
I guess you just have to
avoid thinking negatively.
You need to do your best to look straight ahead.
It's important to know what you
believe in and that you won't lose.
Something like that.
Straight ahead?
Well, in my case, I guess that
came out subconsciously.
Perhaps that's my natural disposition.
Or maybe even...
A talent.
That's your talent, Yukko!
No, no. It's not a talent.
But maybe...
I guess that's what it... is.
If it's part of your subconscious,
then it's something you were born with.
It's not something you can acquire just by trying!
I'm jealous of your innate talent!
Innate Talent
Genius
Oh, Mio-chan!
Are you really Mio-chan?
Maybe I'll give you 100 yen! Just kidding!
What are you doing?
I'm trying to receive as much of
your good fortune as possible.
No way, no way, no way!
There's no way I could give good fortune!
That's not true.
You're probably spreading
happiness around as we speak.
Really?
But they do say to give everything a try.
I don't really get it, but...
Maybe I got some.
The courage to take the first step, that is!
Gosh, you're not going to get anywhere
by complimenting me so much!
Did some of my motivation rub off on you?
I told you, that motivation is what's best!
All right!
I can't sulk around over getting 1 point.
I got away with it!
I knew her depression was
nothing to worry about.
She'll bite right away if you set it up just right.
Well, all I did was compliment the heck out of her.
I just hope it leads to her studying a bit more.
Mio-chan.
I turned the source of this whole
ordeal into a paper airplane.
By sending this flying...
I, too, will fly towards greater heights.
This is denial.
Here I go.
Good-bye, oh light of youth!
Owie.
Nano, what are we going to play?
An Everyday
Cold
Here, blow your nose.
Let's give you some medicine, Professor.
What are we going to play?
Please, drink your medicine.
Sakamoto, what are we going to play?
Let me think...
Sakamoto-san!
Why me?!
You've had a runny nose since yesterday.
I told you to go to bed,
but you wouldn't listen.
You won't even eat meals regularly.
Here it is.
I'm going to go play over there.
No.
I'll go get the water, so make sure to take it.
But he said I wasn't really sick,
so I don't have to take any medicine.
Who did?
Sakamoto.
I never said that!
Sakamoto-san!
I said I didn't!
Sakamoto said he loves medicine,
so he wants to drink mine too.
When was this?
Sakamoto-san!
You're seriously believing her?!
And Sakamoto likes medicine
so even if you say no—
Blow.
Anyway, drink your medicine.
You won't get any better if you don't.
But the medicine's kind of bitter.
You'll be fine.
It will all be gone in no time, okay?
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
Yes you are!
Last time, it didn't go away in no time.
All right, if you have this
you'll be better in no time.
Does it taste good?
I wrapped it in a wafer so
that you won't taste it.
All you have to do is swallow it.
That's suspicious...
Here. Say, "Ah."
All right, just swallow it.
No, you have to swallow it down with water!
Quick, or the wafer's going to melt and—
Nano, you liar.
That was because you wouldn't
swallow it right away.
Geez, what a brat.
Leave this one to me.
Are you sure?
Just watch.
Hey, brat.
You like sharks, don't you?
Sharks?
Yeah.
Did you know that sharks hardly ever get sick?
Really?
Yeah.
Even if they get scratched,
their injuries go away like magic.
People are different, however.
That's because we aren't as cool as sharks.
Yeah.
So humans have to eat
a lot of different things.
When they get sick, they have to take—
Take!
Sakamoto-san!
Professor, I'll take some with you.
So please, have your medicine.
We'll do it together!
Since I can't bear it and Nano can,
Nano should drink all of it!
That's not how it works.
Then Sakamoto should take it.
What's the point of having me take it?!
Your cold won't get better if you keep this up!
I don't care if my cold doesn't get better...
Sakamoto-san, grab me a tissue please.
Sure thing.
Sakamoto-san!
Crap! I can't stop!
No, you'll dirty your coat if you wipe it there!
It's not dirty!
And I'm not going to take the medicine!
Fine.
If you won't take your medicine,
then we won't have any snacks today.
What a waste, I even made pudding.
Pudding...
He said I could eat a snack!
Who did?!
Are you going to blame me again?!
Geez.
She won't even eat her meals?
No.
Geez.
Come here, girl.
This is your fault, you know.
Even if you force her, that
brat won't take her medicine.
I know.
But I don't know what to do.
Convincing her is going to be difficult.
There's only one way.
There is?
Mix it in her snack.
I see!
Dock it on her favorite food and
camouflage it like a ride-on thing.
We'll call it Operation Snack Mash-Up.
Great idea, Sakamoto-san!
You're a master strategist!
You're hopeless without me.
I'll go make it right away.
Wait!
Yes?
You only have one chance.
You won't get a second one if she catches on.
Understood?
Yes!
Shark... Shark...
Professor!
Here she comes.
It's snack time.
Would you like some pudding?
Really?!
Yes.
Eat up.
Pudding!
It's in plain sight!
Come here, girl!
Oh man, that scared me.
Are you nuts?!
Do you want her to see it?!
Did I mess up?
I told you that you only had one chance!
Anyone would doubt that to be whipped cream!
You have to mix it, mix it, and sprinkle it inside!
Sorry, I'll mix it right away.
Geez, you guys are useless without me.
Good thing I'm around—
Sakamoto-san!
Delicious!
Seriously?!
This pudding is great.
It's kind of crunchy, but then
it becomes all pudding-like.
R-Really?
Thank goodness!
Eat it all up.
We did it, Sakamoto-san.
Well, I guess this happens once in a while too.
Nano, can I have one more?
Crunchy pudding!
Sure thing.
But the next one isn't going to be crunchy.
Why?! Sakamoto said he
wanted crunchy pudding.
Why me again?
Shinonome Laboratory had yet another peaceful day.
Sakamoto-san!
Everyday
Reserving
Huh?
The train should be coming soon, right?
Yeah, in about a minute.
There's nobody here!
Seems like it.
There aren't many people
around in the afternoon.
Do we have the whole place to ourselves?
In that case...
Nobody will get angry if I do this?
Wow, Yukko.
You too, Mio-chan.
Nobody seems to be around, anyway.
R-Really?
Okay.
Here I go!
How was that?!
Mio-chan, that's wrong!
It's here.
Mai-chan, do you like trains?
Somewhat.
Nobody's here! It's like we reserved it!
I'm really getting fired up now!
Mio-chan, let's do the pushing game!
Here we go.
One, two...
Mai-chan, you're the judge!
Make sure you watch...
Bunk bed.
Triple bunk bed!
For some reason, I feel like I'm
the only one who's losing out.
An Everyday
Episode 0
tan tan tatan tan tata~ ta~
tan tan tatan tan tatan ta~
tatata tatata ta~ ta~
tatatatan, lalatatan,
tan tan tatan tan tata~ ta~
tatata tatata ta~ ta~
tanlanlanla, tantantanta, ta ta...
ta, ta, ta, ta,
ta, ta, ta, ta...
tan, ta, la, ta...
tan tan tatan tan lata~ ta~
tan tan tatan tan tata~ ta~
latata tatata ta~n la~
latatatan, lalatatan,
lan tan tatan tan tata~ ta~
tan tan tatan ta tata~ ta~
tatata tatata ta~ ta~
lanlalata, tantanlanla ta ta~