Sensei!
What's up?
I just saw someone suspicious!
What? Wh-What did they look like?
Um, he was really big, like a bear,
with really shaggy hair!
Shaggy?
And he had eyes like a beast,
targeting its prey!
That can't be anything but a bear!
Interviews with Monster Girls
Someone is sitting in the hallway, crying.
That looks like a school uniform,
but not this school's...
And such nice blond hair.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Pretty boy!
Succubus-san Is Inquisitive
I'm Satou Sakie, the math teacher.
Nice to meet you.
Sakie-sensei...
My name is Kurtz.
Are you part German, by any chance?
Yes, I am.
I'm surprised you could tell.
A lucky guess.
I happen to have studied a
bit of German in college.
So...
So what are you doing here, Kurtz-kun?
Well, I came here with someone,
but we got separated.
Was it your parents?
Were they filling out transfer paperwork?
Y-Yes...
That's right.
Doesn't look like it.
It looks he isn't really a transfer student,
but he doesn't seem like a bad kid.
Oh, Satou-sensei...
Hello!
Hello.
That girl's head was...
Yes, she's a demi-human. A dullahan.
Really? She is?
Oh? Are you interested in
demi-humans, Kurtz-kun?
No, not especially.
He totally is.
Guess I should ask why he's really here.
But will he actually tell me the truth?
I should use my aphrodisiac
effect to make him talk—
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Why am I suddenly thinking like that? Ah!
Um, where are you going?
I'll go and look for your parents.
That will probably be faster.
Off, I go!
Hey, wait—
Oh, no—
The effect isn't working?
That does sometimes happen with people
who haven't much sexual desire.
But he doesn't look that way.
Maybe he's actually more...
Satou-sensei!
Takahashi-sensei?
Is something wrong?
Yes, Hikari told me she saw someone
suspicious in the school.
Huh? Someone suspicious?
Hikari saw them,
so she may have exaggerated
some of the details,
but I wanted warn to you.
Suspicious... Could it have been...
Sakie-sensei has such a
serious look on her face.
She must be scared of the suspicious person.
She doesn't seem to fully trust me, either.
If I want to allay her suspicion of me...
No, to thank her for her kindness to me...
I'll do something about the suspicious person!
Who's this?
Let's go!
Well... His name is Kurtz-kun.
I'll take that suspicious person,
and give 'em this and this!
He was separated from the
people he came here with.
You just wait, suspicious person!
I wonder if the suspicious person
she mentioned was one of them.
I see.
Actually, she said the person was a
huge man, who looked like a bear.
Someone like you, I wonder.
Huh?
Nah, I'm sure he was much bigger than—
Get back!
Ouch!
Ow, ow, ow!
Are you all right, Sakie-sensei?
Y-Yes, that was amazing, Kurtz-kun.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ugaki-san?
U-Uh...
Hey, Kurtz... I thought you'd disappeared.
What brings you here now? Huh?
Senpai?
He's your kouhai?
Oh, um... He's a police detective I know.
A police detective?
Ah, what if you'd been wrong?
I'm sorry.
You know each other?
Yes, for quite some time, you might say...
And this boy— I mean, Kurtz-kun...
Oh, he works for me.
That's right.
Why are you at the school, Ugaki-san?
Well, I guess you could say...
Um, did you check in?
Check in?
To enter the school, the rule is that
you have to register your name.
Oh, sorry about that.
Okay, Kurtz, you go do that.
Huh?
Don't look so obviously peeved!
He seems young for a police detective,
and he looks foreign.
That's true.
Guess the police force is
pretty broad-minded...
If you'll buy me takoyaki on
the way home, I'll do it.
You little...
So broad-minded.
Indeed.
No outside shoes allowed in the school.
Put on the slippers.
Oh, sorry about that.
It's been a while since I've
been in a high school.
Why are you here?
We usually meet at a coffee shop.
Yeah, well...
When I heard that there were
four demis at the same school,
I thought I should at least see
them, given my line of work.
Also, uh...
Kurtz-kun?
Oh? Did something happen
between you and him?
Hmm? Hmm?
Well... Sort of...
Just the fact that you and he touched
makes my coming here worthwhile.
Right?
You're infuriating!
I can't give too many details, but...
Put your name and address here.
Okay.
So, what kind of work do you do?
Gulp...
I-It has nothing to do with demi-humans!
Really, it has nothing to do
with demi-humans at all!
Not demi-humans!
Basically, Kurtz is
our weapon against succubi.
Something like that.
Stop trying to make this
sound like some anime.
Sorry.
So, how have things been lately?
You doing well?
How have things been?
Just like always. I'm getting by.
Honestly, I think you're doing great.
Given the depth of their natures,
succubi generally either live apart from society
or just throw caution to
the wind and live boldly.
Usually, we police deal with the
troublemakers in the latter category.
Among succubi, upright members
of society like you are rare.
Of course, the government is facing the
tough situation succubi are currently in—
Smoke in the smoking room!
I fully realize you consciously
live as a functional adult.
But isn't it about time you thought about
settling down and starting a family?
I can introduce you to some guys.
Where's this coming from?
Nowhere special.
It just makes me worry to see a
young woman living all alone.
Especially you, having known
you since you were little.
You sound like a father, Ugaki-san.
Who are you calling a father?
But you do more fatherly things
for me than my actual father.
You aren't supposed to say that.
I'm sorry.
Marriage, huh?
Actually, there is someone I'm interested in.
Seriously?!
What's with that reaction?
You're the one who brought it up.
Uh, yeah, sorry.
But you always make excuses
when this subject comes up.
Like you don't want to use your aphrodisiac
effect to get a boyfriend,
or you don't know what real love is.
I never thought you'd find a man yourself!
Don't make me touch you.
Hey, don't!
Getting too worked up is
hard on a man my age!
Hmph. Pathetic.
The man I'm interested in doesn't
have much sexual desire.
My touch doesn't even affect him.
Huh?
There's no way that's possible.
Other than gays,
there's no man your aphrodisiac
effect wouldn't work on.
But he... He didn't seem affected at all...
That just means he didn't look affected.
I bet he knows a lot about demis, right?
Y-Yes...
Even if your aphrodisiac effect
did work on him,
he was probably making
an effort not to show it.
He didn't look affected,
but he really was?
He really was?
Yes! Your aphrodisiac effect
did its job on him!
He isn't special!
Are you disappointed?
Are your feelings for him real?
Can you still say you like him?
When that happened, Takahashi-sensei
was affected by my aphrodisiac effect?
He was excited by me?!
I see, I see.
If you can believe that it's okay
to use your aphrodisiac effect,
that would mean you truly love him.
W-Would it really?
I only took interest in Taka—
in him to begin with because
when I touched his hand,
there was no indication that he'd
felt my aphrodisiac effect.
Learning that it really had affected
him did excite me a little,
but it contradicts the very reason
why I took interest in him...
Which means my excitement is transient,
and can't be called the real thing, but...
I'm pretty sure I read in a
romance how-to book that
the beginning of love is often
mistaken or preconceived...
I mean, as an educator, I feel that love
carried by momentum is... is...
But... But if someone seriously
pursued me, I'd...
If a succubus fell under
an aphrodisiac effect...
I couldn't bear to watch.
Darn it!
Interviews with Monster Girls
Maybe I shouldn't have said that...
I hope no one's figured out my
connection with demi-humans.
Someone suspicious?
Yeah.
What was he like?
Well, he was huge, like a bear...
A bear?
And he had shaggy hair...
Shaggy?
And he had eyes like a beast,
targeting its prey!
I can't picture anything but a bear.
But it looks like I was wrong.
Sorry, Sakki!
Wait, you aren't her.
I'm sorry.
It's that demi-human.
You're a foreigner?
Uh, yes.
We never see foreigners at this school!
You're even blond!
That's right. They're very uncommon here.
So are we.
Oh, right!
Huh? Your uniform's different, though.
Gulp!
Oh, I get it! You're transferring here?
Th-Th-Th-That's right.
W-Well, bye!
Doesn't look like he's transferring here.
Really?
Why did I mistake him for Sakki?
He's a boy, for one thing...
He was acting a little suspicious.
Was he?
That was too close.
I think they almost started to suspect me.
Look at this!
Th-This is...
Right?
Sexy, right?
Yeah...
But, Satake, isn't this peeping?
Calling it a dirty trick is an understatement.
Shut up!
The picture is sexy enough,
but the real thing was even more intense!
Being hit by a succubus's... pheromones?
I couldn't help it!
I kind of get how you feel, but...
Don't look at Sakie-sensei
with such lascivious eyes!
Wha?
Who are you?
I'm a passing pol—
A passerby!
I meant specifically!
You took this... in secret, didn't you?
How cowardly!
As a man, aren't you ashamed
to do things like this?
You heard him.
I do think what I did was pretty low.
But I'm a high school kid!
I'm a healthy adolescent!
With a succubus like Satou-chan as a teacher,
it's weirder to tell me not to take interest!
Is it because she's a succubus?
Are you interested in Sakie-sensei
because she's a succubus?
My taking that picture might have
had something to do with that.
But even if she weren't a succubus,
I still think Satou-chan is cute!
I know that's kind of shady!
Good answer.
Try not to forget that feeling.
Just this once, I'll give you
permission to keep that photo.
What was that about? He sure was weird.
I think you were pretty weird, too.
Anyway, where did Ugaki-san go?
Smoking Room
That's delicious...
Hello.
Hello... Uh...
Oh, my name is Takahashi.
I'm Ugaki. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Ugaki-san.
Here.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Anyway, so you smoke, huh?
Yes, occasionally.
Occasionally, eh? How often is that?
I guess it's been about two years.
That's a little too occasional.
What made you suddenly
decide to smoke today?
Is today special?
Huh? Me?
Yeah.
I heard your work involves demi-humans.
Who told you that?
Was it Kurtz?
Yes, sort of.
That idiot!
Well, it's nothing worth hiding, I guess.
Kurtz and I work for what's called
the "Demi-human Division."
Oh! You're policemen from
the Demi-human Division?
I've never met one before!
Well, there aren't many demi-humans,
which means incidents involving
them are even rarer, right?
Then, what kind of work do you do?
My work has nothing to do
with demi-humans at all.
Huh?
What kind of expression is that?
Though, back in the day, I was pretty busy...
The world used to be a lot harsher
toward demi-humans.
Since they had it rough both
socially and psychologically,
we'd often see demi-humans
causing problems.
But lately, you never hear of that happening.
Because the government took action?
The guarantee system?
That's probably part of it,
but as a whole, society sort of mellowed out.
I realized that again today.
Today?
This school has three
demi-human students, right?
I haven't heard any bad rumors,
but a part of me was scared to look into it.
But once I actually did, I was
surprised  by what I found.
They look like they're having a great time.
It almost made me want to cry.
I started to think the world's
heading in a good direction.
I'm sure how they were raised is part of it,
and they're probably blessed
with good teachers, too.
Sorry I took your Demi-human Division job.
Bold words!
But unfortunately, I have a job that
you can never take from me.
Meaning?
The majority of incidents
caused by demi-humans
are incidents involving aphrodisiac effects.
Aphrodisiac effects?
You mean incidents caused by succubi's
aphrodisiac effects, right?
Let's say a succubus is molested.
It isn't always true that the succubus used
her aphrodisiac effect accidentally.
Some of them intentionally
use it to get molested.
Serves you right!
Determining whether the succubus
used the aphrodisiac effect
deliberately is extremely difficult.
What teacher could actually steal that job?
W-Wait a second.
Huh?
You mean there's a way to make the
correct judgment in those cases?
There's no failsafe method.
All we can do right now
is to maintain communication with
succubi in our jurisdictions,
and determine in advance
if they're malicious or not.
I bet succubi don't like you much, huh?
I'm basically interrogating them about
things that may or may not happen.
All I can tell them is that it's my job.
It isn't like I want them to hate me.
So you haven't reached any compromise?
Well, I do occasionally meet succubi I
get along with, for whatever reason.
There's one rather unusual one...
By the way, I hear you're pretty
knowledgeable about demis.
Oh, not really...
But you do know about
the nickname "demis."
Sensei, take care of Sakie, will ya?
What about the other demi-chans?
Right.
Take care of all the demi-chans,
including Sakie,
Sensei...
I'll do my best to make this a world
where demis can feel at ease.
You just do your best to look
after each of them.
Give them lots of good memories.
Okay... You can count on me.
When you interact with demis, is there
anything you're careful about?
Rather than try to make them like me,
I try to make them not hate me.
Smoking Room
If being hated by girls is "100,"
and being hated by demis is "100,"
then being hated by demi girls would
be 100 x 100, which is 10,000.
You can really express it
with such simple math?
It's only an example.
That's just how complicated it is.
You might find yourself distanced from
them for surprising reasons, too.
Please don't try to scare me.
Sensei!
Speak of the devil.
Are you done talking now?
Yeah, I guess.
Hi there, little lady vampire.
My name's Ugaki.
I'm Takanashi Hikari, from class 1-B!
Nice to meet you!
"Little lady," he said!
Yeah, good for you.
Huh?
Sniff, sniff. Sniff, sniff.
Uh, what?
You stink!
I hate cigarettes!
I guess she's sensitive to cigarette smoke.
So, anyway, that's how I
deal with demi-humans.
Occasionally, I go out to meet
demi-humans out of my jurisdiction.
But I don't think the police will have to
do anything about those demi-chans.
It's just that succubus.
Someday, I'll probably need to have
you do some serious work for us...
Takoyaki is so good!
I'll smack him later...
Next Time
Demi-chans Want to Learn
Next time on Interviews with Monster Girls:
Demi-chans Want to Learn.