Interviews with Monster Girls
Thank you for taking the time to visit.
Takanashi
My daughters have told me about you,
and I was hoping for a chance to talk to you.
The Takanashi Sisters Are Undeniable
Oh, no... I'm the one who's grateful.
Thank you for inviting me over.
My wife is the bread winner in our family,
so I'm in charge of the housework.
Oh, is that right?
At one time, both of us had jobs.
But since we have Hikari, we thought
one of us should stay near her.
Lately, we've been in touch with Machi-san
and Kusakabe-san's parents, too.
Oh? Networking among parents, huh?
That does sound nice.
I heard it was thanks to your help
that those girls became friends.
Nah, I didn't do anything special.
Knowing there's someone like you,
who's knowledgeable about demis,
makes me feel at ease
sending them to school.
I'm sure Hikari-san and Himari-san
have such good sense
because they had good parents
to raise them right.
Hikari-san, however...
I just wish she'd put a little
more effort into her studies.
Y-You're right.
Himari is very responsible about that, but...
I'm home.
Hey.
Welcome home, Himari.
Takahashi-sensei?
I did promise, right?
Thank you for coming.
And... I'm sorry about the other day.
Huh?
About the e-mail my sister sent me.
The one that said you hugged her.
Hugged?
Oh, that?! It's fine!
Hikari explained everything later.
As long as the misunderstanding
was cleared up, it's fine.
That's the kind of person my sister is.
You have my blessing to be
strict and not coddle her.
Right.
Is something wrong?
They're twins, but they're
completely different...
Oh, I'm sor—
I'm home!
Sensei!
There, she is.
Welcome home, Hikari.
Why are you here? A home visit?
I wanted to talk to him,
so I asked him over.
Wow, really?
Wait, whoa...
Sensei, you're wearing a necktie.
That's unusual!
Hey, can I take a picture?
Click, click—
Onee-chan!
H-Himari?
You put your blood pack in this fridge again!
Keep them in your own fridge!
You have your own refrigerator?
Yeah, it seemed wrong to put my blood
where everyone would see it,
so I got my own.
That doesn't even matter.
We're used to seeing it!
Th-Then...
But the deal was that, as long
as you had your own fridge,
you'd follow the rules!
It's probably something foolish,
like you couldn't be bothered
to take them upstairs, right?
Sensei, please say something to this
cold-blooded sister of mine...
It's important to question the rules,
but you should really stick to rules
that you set for yourself.
The gentle way he worded that
stabs right through my heart...
Just listen to this, Sensei.
She does what she wants, just because
she has her own fridge!
She hides the desserts she wants to eat in it,
sticks her feet in it while reading manga,
and worst, sleeps with her
head in it and gets sick!
What do you think of that?
D-Did you have to say all that?
You're making the blood drain from my face.
Himari, say another word, and you'll regret it.
What? Want to fight me?
When we were kids, we used to
hit each other all the time.
It makes my blood boil.
Are you ready?
This is gonna be a bloodbath!
Why do you keep working in
idioms that involve blood?
Since I have the chance,
I thought I'd let Sensei and Dad
see my vampire intelligence—
You always try too hard to
make yourself look good!
What the heck is with this hairstyle that
takes so maddeningly long to do?!
Ow, ow, ow!
I don't see why you have to bring up my hair—
But I do!
Do you know how often helping you
with your hair has made me late?
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Sensei, say something to her!
Huh?
I think that hairstyle looks pretty cute.
Did you see?
Your face is red.
It is not.
Why are you so happy?
I'm not happy.
That's a problem for me, as it is!
How is it a problem?
Are they always like this?
Yeah.
Well, I'm embarrassed to say it,
but they make such a fuss,
I don't know what to do.
I see.
It's clear they're very close, though.
Yes.
Oh, by the way, Sensei...
If you don't have plans after this,
would you care to stay for dinner?
What? Wow, really?
I'd appreciate that.
You two.
Sensei is having dinner with us.
What do you want to eat?
Liver and onions!
Liver and on—
I can understand your liking
liver and onions, but...
That's right!
Maybe Himari's short on blood
because she's always so angry?
Say something to her, Sensei.
Can't fight what's in your blood, huh?
Sensei, not you, too!
Come on, Sensei... Make a good face.
You just took a picture earlier.
But not one with us together!
I've gotta send it to Macchi and Yukki.
Onee-chan, you could at least settle
down a little while Sensei's here.
Oh, you want in the picture, too?
Wha? I never said that!
I'm home.
It sounds awfully loud in here... Oh!
Ah, pardon my intrusion.
This is Sensei!
Hello. I'm Takahashi.
Oh, my daughters always talk about you!
It sounds like you've done
a great deal for Hikari.
Oh, not at all.
Dinner's ready.
Thanks for dinner!
Onee-chan!
You ate the ice cream I was saving, didn't you?
Sorry! I ate it by mistake yesterday.
How do you do that by mistake?
I thought maybe I'd bought it...
You know that'd never actually happen!
It's true!
You said that the last time you ate it!
Honestly, they're always like this.
Ever since she was born, Hikari's hair
has been so bright, it seems to glow.
Oh, that's why you named her "Hikari"?
As for Himari,
we wanted to give her a
name similar to "Hikari."
Hmm...
I'm pretty sure there's still
one left in my fridge.
If you have your own, don't eat mine.
I told you, it was a mistake!
She may be a vampire, but she isn't
that different from other girls.
At least, I used to say that to
make light of the situation...
Of course, I'd be lying if I said
I never felt troubled by it.
If we face it together,
we can think of it as part of
what makes her unique.
Even besides being a demi,
no two people are the same, are they?
Right.
Hikari-san and Himari-san may look similar,
but see how different they are.
I really can't believe you.
How could you forget you ate it?
Sorry. I'll go buy a new one.
Sure, sure. Fine.
So on that note, we're going to buy
ice cream at the convenience store.
We?
I'd be worried, letting my precious
little sister go alone at this hour!
Why do you assume I'd be the one to go?
Go by yourself.
Okay, Hikari, you can go with me.
And you don't have to spoil her like that, Dad!
She always goes alone to buy sweets at night!
I'll go. There's something I forgot to buy.
Really, Mom?
All right, then I'll just—
Oh, Sensei, I'm sorry!
We're stepping out for a bit,
but the store is nearby.
We won't be long,
so you'll have to excuse us
for just a few minutes.
S-Sure...
Himari!
Keep Sensei company.
Okay, let's go.
Fine.
Let's go!
See you in a few!
Sensei, I'll buy one for you, too.
I let the timing slip by.
Everyone's so soft on her.
You two really are close, huh?
What makes you say that?
Your dad's hair is really light in color.
Does he...
Yes, so that Onee-chan won't be too
conspicuous within our family.
Yeah? That's really nice.
Actually, it looks like you've lightened
your hair a little, too.
N-No! Th-This is just... for fashion.
They really are close.
Hey, Mom, what did you forget to buy?
Beer.
Sensei looks like a drinker, doesn't he?
Interviews with Monster Girls
Takanashi
I'm going now—
Himari!
Wait a second!
First, help me with my hair!
No!
And that's how I forced my sister
to become more independent.
You're so harsh, Himari-chan...
I can just picture Hikari's face
when you said that to her.
She's just too negligent.
She's in high school now.
She has to get it together.
Not long ago...
She went to the bathroom at night,
and then fell asleep there.
Huh?
Oh, but don't you think being a vampire
had something to do with that?
Vampires can get by in the middle
of the night, without any light.
In fact...
Yeah, when she uses the bathroom at night,
the light's too bright for her.
For anyone else, that would make
it a lot easier to fall asleep.
Even considering that, I think her
negligence comes out on top.
And what you said a minute ago,
about her hairstyle...
That might have something to do
with her vampire nature, too.
Huh?
Here, look. Vampires don't see
their reflections in mirrors.
Since they can't see themselves,
doing their own hair is difficult.
That's why she relies on you.
That would explain things, but...
Well, that's probably a superstition, though.
It's based on a belief that the link between
a vampire's body and soul is weak,
or that mirrors reflect the soul,
or things like that.
I figure it's just because
Hikari is irresponsib—
Himari-chan?
I might have done something really awful.
H-Himari-chan?
If vampires really can't see
themselves in mirrors...
If Onee-chan was actually
asking for my help...
Onee-chan!
Looks like it's going to rain.
It's supposed to rain this afternoon.
I'll have to call for a ride.
A ride?
Yeah, walking around with an umbrella is dangerous for me.
So when it rains, I have someone
in my family drive me.
Ah, I see.
Himari-chan?
I wonder what's wrong.
Not here.
Oh, if you're looking for Hikari...
I'm sorry, Onee-chan.
I'm sorry I didn't realize...
I just decided that you were negligent,
and acted like I knew everything.
Even though you were going
through so much worse!
Please let me apologize, Onee-chan!
Huh? Mirrors?
I can see myself in them just fine.
Uh... Sorry, Himari-chan.
This happened because I gave
you that weird idea.
No, it's fine.
I was jumping to conclusions.
Yay!
Anyway, when you do my hair for me,
you can also see me in the mirror, right?
That's true... That really is true.
I'm sorry! I guess I really worried you!
You're such a kind girl, after all.
You can't help jumping to conclusions.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
Thanks, Himari.
Then, why make me help with your hair?
Huh?
That's because...
I am, and always have been,
just that negligent!
That hurts! My brains are gonna pop out!
Ow, ow, ow!
Even if vampires didn't cast
reflections in mirrors,
Hikari would never lose who she is.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Himari-chan, who understands
and cares for her,
is always closer to her than anyone else.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hey, Onee-chan! You left this!
Bring it to the classroom with you!
Why do I have to carry it?!
She's the perfect younger sister.
It really did start raining.
Did you bring an umbrella?
Yeah, I'm fine. I have a folding one.
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
Well, I'm gonna head home first.
All right. See you tomorrow.
Now, then...
That staff meeting ran long, huh?
It sure did.
Of course, I'm here till late, either way.
Until late?
Uh, I mean, crowded trains are a bad idea.
Since I'm a succubus and all.
Oh, the aphrodisi—
I mean, yeah, that's rough.
I'm used to it.
U-Um...
Takahashi-sensei...
Yes?
Nothing. Have a good evening.
Thanks. Same to you.
The aphrodisiac effect really
doesn't work on him!
If it's him, even a succubus like me could...
, she's erotic!
It's raining.
Biology Prep Room
Which means she's probably here today.
I don't hear anything, though...
So maybe she's in the library?
She's asleep?
Whoops, I fell asleep...
A blanket?
Sensei, that's a good boy. Just sleep.
Sensei's hair is so coarse.
Our hairstyles are similar,
but the hair is different.
Excuse me.
Hi, Kyouko-chan.
Did I keep you waiting?
Hikari-chan's dad?
Hey.
What brings you here?
Huh?
I e-mailed Hikari. She didn't tell you?
No.
It seems both your parents are really busy,
so I came for you instead.
That's odd...
In the e-mail, I told her to
let you know in person.
Now that you mention it,
right before she left, she had
a funny smirk on her face.
She must have kept it to herself, as a joke.
Sorry about that, Kyouko-chan.
Oh, it's all right. Sorry to trouble you.
It's no trouble whatsoever.
After all, I owe your parents a lot.
As they say, it's give and take.
By the way,
I guess Takahashi-sensei is worn out.
It seems so.
Then, want to leave him
a note before we go?
Sure.
Um, I left my backpack in the classroom...
Oh, okay.
All right! I'll carry your head
to the classroom!
Huh? B-But I couldn't ask that of you.
Nah, I wanted to get used to carrying
you, without shaking you too much.
R-Really?
It's just like cooking.
If you don't keep trying, over and over,
you'll never master it.
Wow, so smooth.
I'll walk a little slowly. Sorry about that.
S-Sure.
He's probably better at that than I am.
Anyway, that's over wi—
Whoa!
I forgot her body was still here...
She's writing a note?
Takahashi-sensei,
My ride is here, so I'll be leaving.
Hikari-chan's dad came to pick me up today.
Also, thank you for the blanket.
It was very warm.
She's so serious.
Still, it takes some skill to be
able to write without seeing.
She must have practiced a lot.
Machi and all the demi-chans
are doing their best.
Their parents are doing their best for
their demi-chan daughters, too.
I need to do more, as well.
I guess, sometimes, it's also
nice to say nothing at all.
Next Time
Succubus-san Is Inquisitive
Next time on Interviews with Monster Girls:
Succubus-san Is Inquisitive.