Interviews with Monster Girls
Succubus-san Is a Real Adult
I am Satou Sakie.
The math teacher at Shibasaki
Prefectural High School.
I'm 24 and single.
My mornings start early.
Aquarius
Luck in Love
Luck in Health
Luck in Finances
Be bold and don't fear change!
You may see unexpected results!
Lucky Item: Ruler
Today's horoscope for Aquarius looks positive.
Be assertive and don't fear change,
and a chance for love might come your way!
Next, for Pisces...
A chance for love, huh?
I can't even hope for a decent relationship.
Because I'm...
a succubus.
That was close...
The first two-car train to Shibasaki
will arrive momentarily.
Please wait behind the yellow line.
Good morning, Satou-sensei.
O-O-Oh... Good morning!
You're always first to arrive,
and you even clean up.
Thank you for all of your effort.
Oh, no, it's nothing.
I really enjoy cleaning!
Actually, it's because I arrived
so early, I had nothing to do.
Oh, Satou-sensei...
Good morning.
Good morning!
Morning, Sensei!
Hey, morning.
With more energy!
Good morning!
You pass!
It's still morning, and you're so hyper.
Yeah, I guess.
By the way, thanks, Sensei.
Hmm?
For getting approval for Macchi's backpack!
Nah, I'm the one who should thank you.
I should have thought of it first.
I didn't mean to say that so forcefully.
But I can't carelessly come
into contact with a man.
Because I'm a succubus.
Satou-sensei...
Yes?
I'm having trouble with this problem.
Ah, for this, you use the formula
I taught you today. See?
Oh, I get it!
Thank you.
You need to know the sin and cos values,
and also how to find them...
What's wrong?
You're so pretty, Sensei.
You should dress up more.
I don't need to do things like that.
I see.
If you have any more trouble, just ask me.
I will. Thank you.
I can't dress up because...
It'd have an aphrodisiac effect!
Aphrodisiac effects mesmerize others,
sexually arousing them.
Succubi are demis with the capacity to
cause aphrodisiac effects on men.
However, succubi have self-control.
By dressing and carrying ourselves so
as to avoid evoking sexual thoughts,
and keeping a good head on
our shoulders at all times...
Just try and say that again!
What's wrong, Satake?
For a second, I felt like I bumped
into someone really sexy...
What overly specific feeling is that?
But... If I remember right,
Satou-sensei is a succubus!
Huh?
And if anything does happen,
this is the extent of it.
Still...
To avoid the dangerous rush hours,
I take the day's first and last trains.
It's rough to wake early and
get home late every day.
I'm getting pretty tired...
N-No, have to be careful.
What the heck's wrong with you?
I just had a super sexy dream!
Huh? What the heck? I don't get you.
Asleep, when I can't control myself,
I give others obscene dreams.
That's why succubi are also
called "dream demons."
Shoot...
For that reason,
I can't live in an apartment building
or a complex housing many people.
I'm home...
I was prepared for this,
but it really is hard for a succubus to
live a decent life in normal society.
If I married and had a family,
could I have a more relaxed life?
Marriage.
Very funny.
I've never even had a real
relationship, at my age.
Marriage isn't going to happen.
As a succubus, it probably wouldn't be hard
for me to build what society would
call a romantic relationship.
If I walked outside in flashy clothes,
the opposite sex would notice and flock to me.
But I don't think that's true romance,
and I think their interest would be fake.
But when I fall in love with a man,
is that feeling any different from
what men feel toward me?
If it really isn't different at all...
That's so good!
The only time I can stretch my
wings is when I'm at home!
Okay! Let's pop open another!
Yahoo!
Today's horoscope for Libra is favorable.
Guess I got carried away and drank too much.
No, no! I can't doze off at school—
Are you all right, Satou-sensei?
Takahashi-sensei—
Th-Thank you! I-I'm sorry! Um, I mean...
You seem pretty tired.
Your students are important,
but take care of yourself, too.
R-Right. Thank you...
We just touched, right?
And yet he's so calm...
I'd never thought about it.
If it's a succubus's nature
to arouse sexual desire,
maybe it has less effect on people without
strong sexual desires in the first place?
Maybe in terms of romance,
that puts us on even footing.
This has never happened before.
Strange to think that reactions
of the least interest
make my heart race even faster.
, succubi are so erotic!
Thank goodness I was able to keep my cool...
The biology teacher, Takahashi Tetsuo,
Interviews with Monster Girls
is a natural lady-killer.
So erotic...
"Succubus, also called 'dream demon.'
Demi-humans with the capacity to have
an aphrodisiac effect on others.
I've also met a vampire, a dullahan,
and a snow woman.
All of these, in such a short time."
Sensei, let me cool down!
Still can't stand sunlight, huh?
Well, it's been getting hotter
and hotter lately, you know?
Being stuck in it for the
whole day is tough...
Sensei! What're ya looking at?
Whoa, it's too hot for this!
Didn't you come here to cool down?
What is this?
"Vam... pi... re"?
That's "vampire."
Oh, an article about me?
Yep, about your reaction
to light, preferred diet,
necessity of sucking blood, and the
stuff about crosses and garlic, too.
I wrote about a lot of things...
Personally,
I was particularly interested in the link
between bloodsucking and romance.
R-Romance?
Oh, sorry... I guess I
shouldn't have said that.
It must be embarrassing, huh?
N-Nah... Not at all!
In fact, I can't say enough about it!
Really?
Then, since you offered, I'll ask.
I've heard that bloodsucking has
sexual undertones for vampires,
but how far does it go?
H-How far?!
Y-You mean, like...
compared to k-kissing... and such?
That sort of thing?
That's right.
Is it more than a kiss, but less than sex?
Se—
Sex. Sex.
Sex...
I-I-I'd say...
It depends on the person.
Well, sure, but I'd like to know
your personal thoughts.
B-But I've never had any romantic experiences!
I know that.
And I've only sucked someone's blood once.
But everyone's seen a scene
like that in movies, right?
Compared to that, is it—
Oh, right!
Of course... It depends on the person, right?
Bloodsucking began as a practice to let
vampires, who tend to be low on blood,
supplement their own with that of others.
But now, you receive blood
from the government,
so it's no longer necessary.
Naturally, you'd value it less.
Th-That's right!
Wait a minute...
Does that mean categorizing bloodsucking
as sexual is wrong, in and of itself?
In terms of traditional culture, which
contemporary people may be losing,
maybe that behavior has a value
that doesn't compare to sex...
T-Two times!
And I'm trying so hard to not
show how embarrassed I am.
Hey, hey...
Gotcha!
Maybe kissing is easier than sucking blood!
I see, I see.
"Kissing is easier than sucking blood."
Don't write that down!
And show a little embarrassment, would you?
Looks like she's still too young for this,
Come on, Sensei! Are you listening?
but I wonder what sort of perspective
demis actually have on romance.
I guess your homeroom teacher
isn't very attentive, Machi-san.
Really, making you carry this box alone...
Sorry about this, Satou-sensei.
It's all right. Don't worry about it.
Reference Room
Confessions of a Mask
Machi-san, this book goes on that shelf, too.
Can you handle it?
S-Sure.
Um, Satou-sensei...
Yes?
You give off the impression of
being a very mature woman.
Where did that come from?
You're beautiful and kind.
I imagine you have a lot of
romantic experience, too.
Huh?
W-Well...
More or less.
Actually, I wanted your
advice about something.
I, um...
I have someone I like.
Oh, you do? That's so nice!
Is it a student at this school?
N-No, he is part of this school, but...
I...
I like Takahashi-sensei!
I do, too!
Kusakabe—
Kusakabe!
On our next day off, wanna hang out?
Huh? N-No, I'll pass on that.
Come on, come on! Just this once!
Really, I'll pass...
Sorry.
H-Hey...
Ow!
Ouch!
Why did you hit us, Tetsu-sensei?
I was trying to talk to Kusakabe.
And you just took that out on us?
This guy's unbelievable.
Sorry... The thing is that I've tried
talking to her several times,
but she keeps running away from me.
Hmm...
Wouldn't she come if you called her on the PA?
Well, I just want to talk to her
out of personal interest.
So I know being too persistent
is a bad approach, but...
What's wrong with him?
What? What's up?
But she is a teenage girl.
Asking her too many questions
might be insensitive...
He's mumbling to himself.
Tetsu-sensei is so weird...
I don't mind it, though.
O-Oh?
You do?
Wait, why make this a competition?
She's a student, and I'm a teacher!
Th-That's surprising.
So what did you want my advice about?
Oh, right, about that...
I'm worried I might be a little too...
well, childish for Takahashi-sensei.
Awakening to Sexuality
I want to be more mature,
but I don't know what that truly means.
That's why you asked me?
I-I'm not sure how to put it, but I see you
as the embodiment of an
attractive, mature woman.
And you look like you'd have
a lot of experience, too.
O-Oh...
Actually, I only look that way.
But you know, Machi-san...
Adults really aren't all that impressive.
I'm sorry if this sounds like I'm
saying you're just a child,
but a lot of the "maturity" that
kids see is just a facade.
A facade?
Yes, we want to appear admirable to society.
We want kids to respect us.
It's a facade meant to achieve that.
I guess adults really are pretty vain.
Especially ones who do this kind of work.
We want to look good.
Is that true for you, as well?
Who can say?
Yes, it is!
T-Takahashi-sensei, too?
Hmm... We are both adults, but he and I
are about as many years apart as you and I.
But the one thing I can say
is that Takahashi-sensei looks
very mature to me, too.
He seems relaxed and carefree,
but he's very reliable.
He's able to connect openly with anyone,
but he doesn't push too far
and end up hurting you.
I think it's pretty impressive.
And really attractive.
B-By the way, what is it you
like about Takahashi-sensei?
Well...
Just like you said,
I guess I like how nice and dependable he is.
I get you.
Also, I like how strong his arms are.
I totally get you!
S-So on that note,
why not start with your appearance?
Like with fashion or your hairstyle?
R-Right, that might be a good idea.
Oh, but as for my hair...
I, um, can't grow my hair out long.
If it's too long, it gets slippery,
so it's dangerous.
Oh, I see! I'm sorry, I didn't notice!
I-It's okay. I can't grow it out,
but I can change the style.
Oh, but when I spoke to
Takahashi-sensei about it...
Hmm, really?
Well, I'm glad you're a dullahan, though.
We sort of match. Isn't that cool?
Isn't that cool?
He said that, and it made me so happy,
I felt like I wouldn't mind keeping
this style forever...
Sensei?
That sounds nice.
That sounds nice...
That sounds so nice!
Like, what, having matching hairstyles?!
And this?
The second shelf.
First Love
Okay.
I am Satou Sakie.
And this?
Also the second shelf.
Okay.
One Hundred Years of Solitude
The math teacher at Shibasaki High School.
And...
Second shelf.
The Agony of Coming Into the World
I'm 24 and single.
Despite all this, I'm a real adult.
Oh, and listen to this. At lunch today...
Uh-huh?
Satake, from class A, was hitting
on a girl in the hall.
For real?
He needs to think about where he is.
Who was the girl, anyway?
Oh, that one chick...
Kusakabe, from class A.
Oh, her?
She's kinda arrogant, don't you think?
Yeah, I think so, too.
Right?
Totally.
I mean, she is cute, but...
Yeah.
I admit she is cute,
but she could hang out with
him once, at least.
Maybe she thinks she's some kind of idol...
Wouldn't an idol try to make
a better impression?
Yeah, you said it!
Bye, Sensei!
Yep, bye.
With more energy!
Goodbye!
You pass! You may go!
Not having a care in the world must be nice.
Yeah, I guess...
See ya!
Be careful on your way home!
Okay!
What is this?
The air feels kind of chilly.
Kusakabe?
Sensei...
Next Time
Takahashi Tetsuo Wants to Protect
Next time on Interviews with Monster Girls:
Takahashi Tetsuo Wants to Protect.