Interviews with Monster Girls
Demi-chans Want to Learn
Our ranks from the last exams are up!
They are.
Midterm Exams Highest Ranking Scores
Year 1
But it doesn't have much to do with us.
Well...
Just take a look at number 2!
Huh? I-It can't be...
2nd: Takanashi Hi
2nd: Takanashi Himari
I'm proud of my little sister!
Oh, that's definitely great, but...
H-Hey, hey!
Hmm?
Look at number 5! Number 5!
Number 5?
5th
Machi
Kyouko
5th: Machi Kyouko
That's a surprise...
I guess Kyouko is really good at her studies.
Right, Hika—
This happened...
Th-This really happened.
You're way too shaken.
Also, you're in Kyouko's class.
You never noticed?
Macchi...
I asked her what score she got,
but she wouldn't tell me,
so I figured it must've been really bad...
Answer Sheet
Machi Kyouko
After seeing your score,
she probably felt bad.
Oh, the results are up already?
Takahashi-sensei!
This is, um...
Isn't Kyouko amazing?
Yeah, very impressive.
But you didn't do too badly yourself, Yuki.
Don't convince yourself that the top-rank
students are beyond your reach.
O-Okay!
I thought Macchi was a goofball like me!
Hikari...
Takanashi Hikari-san...
Y-Yes? Why did you use my full name?
I guess there's no getting out of
supplemental classes for you.
You didn't do particularly
well in any subject.
Three failing scores.
Just because you're a vampire
doesn't mean your exams
should be all red, too...
Instead of being jealous of
your friends' scores,
you should take a good look
at your own mistakes.
S-Sensei!
H-Hug... Hug me?
Don't yell at me...
Bye.
Sensei!
Droop.
It's like some skit.
Yukki, what should I do?!
You're seriously crying?
I don't want Sensei to hate me!
Well, he scolded you for not studying,
so there's only one thing to do.
One thing?
Study and get good scores on your exams.
But the exams are over!
Midterms are over,
but proficiency tests are coming up.
What? More tests?
What do I do, Yukki?!
Help me study!
Oh, good idea.
Let's study together for the proficiency tests.
O-Okay...
I did all right on the exams,
so now I can relax and...
Huh?
The Amazing Van Deursen
The Amazing Van Deursen, volume 7.
I remember this!
My father used to read this all the time.
But why was it lying in the hallway?
Even if someone dropped it, it's a
bit old for kids these days...
Satou-sensei!
Oh, so you dropped the book.
I-I'm sorry for bringing manga to school.
It's fine, as long as you don't
read it during class!
You're just trading with a friend, aren't you?
Our secret.
Yes, thank you!
I'm surprised, though.
I wouldn't have thought you'd like comedy
and gag-type manga like this.
Huh?
Oh, no! I don't!
I had a classmate who wanted to read it,
and I just happened to have it at home!
I see.
My parents love manga,
so we have a lot of it at home,
but I don't read that much!
I see.
I'm not that interested
in silly stuff. I just...
I'm lying! I actually love gag manga!
But it's incredibly embarrassing
to come out and say I like it.
Maybe it's because there
are lots of raunchy ones.
I just have to try not to let it show.
Huh?
Y-Yes?
Isn't this volume 7?
You're lending this one out first?
Oh, I c-confused it with volume 1!
Ah, I can understand that!
Depending on the font, 1 and 7
can look a lot alike.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm lying.
I felt so free after the exams,
I started reading and couldn't stop,
so I was planning to continue
reading it at school!
Back in the day, this Van Deursen
manga was really popular.
Yes...
I know that very well.
Van Deursen, a chivalrous vampire thief,
punishes unjust authority figures
by sucking their blood.
The manga depicted this
with a comedic touch.
Flash
The notes that Van Deursen sent
to his targets were so funny!
Rumble Rumble...
They were written in code.
The answer was always "Not enough blood."
A code . . . ?
Q: Complete the names of the prefectures.
The moment the target solved the code,
Um . . .
To
. . . gi
. . . ba
Van Deursen would show up and attack...
. . . Oh!
Rustle
"Not enough blood?"
The "chi" is missing . . . !!
Flash
Gaaaaah
There is no place of rest . . . !!
Those codes were always so loose!
Yuki-chan?
N-Nothing... Just a little sneeze.
Shoot! The memory made me laugh!
Better change the subject.
Speaking of works with demi protagonists,
I hear that one about a snow
woman is popular lately.
I haven't read it, though...
Oh, Snow Love, right?
It's a ladies' comic about a
snow woman who moves
from Aomori to Tokyo, to try
her best at love and work.
Ever since I moved to Tokyo,
Sad . . .
I heard it's getting a live-action
adaptation this fall.
my heart hasn't felt at ease.
The city's loneliness
chills to the core.
It depicts a grown woman, though,
Tonight,
I found that even my heart
had frozen at some point.
so some of its writing is a bit mature.
Tonight,
I make a connection
with warmth.
My body . . .
feels like it'll melt!
My body feels like it'll melt!
Tick . . .
The magic wears off . . . ?!
Actually, that's clever wordplay, huh?
Yuki-chan?
Oh, it's just... a bug flew into my mouth.
If it has dirty stuff like that,
I should check it out.
Anyway, what about you?
Since Snow Love became popular,
have you been bullied in class?
Huh? Um...
I've been a topic of discussion,
but I haven't really been bullied.
Fiction is still just fiction, after all.
I think everyone understands
that reality is different.
That's why there are disclaimers that say,
"This is a work of fiction."
That's true.
But that might also be because
it's about a snow woman.
What do you mean?
It's also true for Snow Love,
but snow women in fictional
works are more flamboyant,
making snow fall and freezing
anything with icy blasts.
Oh, there was also an action story about
one who shot chunks of ice at enemies!
But snow women in real life have
very little effect on others.
Um...
In that sense, I guess you...
a succubus...
A succubus, um... has that sort of nature,
so maybe they get teased more.
Yeah.
I suppose that did happen to me...
Around middle school, a succubus's
nature becomes apparent.
So I guess rumors spread after people
learned I was a succubus.
Satou...
Then this boy named Takkun, who led lots
of unruly kids, came to start trouble.
Yo, Satou, I heard you're a succubus.
It seems so.
Try your aphrodisiac effect on me, then.
Isn't that why you have that characteristic?
Th-That must have been awful!
Oh, it was fine...
I practiced judo, you know.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Takkun!
H-Hey, Satou... Let him go!
Ow, ow, ow! Stop, stop, stop, stop...
Don't stop!
It hurts... It hurts... Don't stop.
Don't stop! Make it hurt more!
More... More!
Make it hurt more!
Let's go.
Huh? Hey, w-wait...
From then on, his reputation was ruined,
and other bad boys were too afraid
to try and approach me.
It was a happy ending.
Oh, sorry about that.
You don't like hearing that
sort of story, right?
Y-Yuki-chan?
What's wrong?
Does your stomach hurt?
Interviews with Monster Girls
Are you okay?
Do you need to go to the nurse?
Library
Macchi, show me how to do this?
Sure.
Macchi...
Borrowing and Returning
Book Returns
Ma—
Wait.
You're keeping Kyouko from her own work.
Make-up exams are finally over,
and we already have more tests?
I can't deal with this...
I-It's okay, Yuki-chan.
Explaining to others is also
a good way to study.
It doesn't bother me at all.
Really?
Could you teach me that last part, too?
Sure!
Still, it's amazing you ranked fifth, Kyouko.
I was a little surprised. I didn't expect...
Sorry! That didn't come out right, did it?
No, I didn't take it that way at all.
Is it because your parents
ordered you to study?
I don't really remember,
but I think my dad used to be like that.
He doesn't do that to me
much anymore, though,
since I study because I like to.
You study... because... you like to?
Y-You're way too self-aware.
N-Not really.
It's just, gaining as much
as the effort I put in,
and seeing it return as good grades...
I think I just like that sort of thing.
Hmm... So it's kinda like a game?
Y-Yeah, maybe!
It isn't for my future or anything.
I just enjoy doing it.
Yeah, I guess with video games,
you can't watch someone really
good and not get excited.
And it's totally wrong to feel better when
you find someone as bad as you, huh?
Well, I just learned something!
Just kidding.
Nice joke!
Take that.
Well, someone who can't think
of studying as a game
has no choice but to plug away at it.
That's right.
But aren't you doing it for
Takahashi-sensei's praise?
Better work hard.
Yep.
You think Takahashi-sensei will
praise us for studying a lot?
Of course he will!
He is a teacher, after all!
He said you were very impressive, Kyouko.
He did?
Then, next time, maybe I'll try to rank first...
Just kidding!
Hey, you... You're getting carried away!
Biology Prep Room
Demi-humans: Vampire Edition
Their Natures and Thought Processes
Should you really relax so much,
just because make-up exams are over?
Proficiency tests are next week.
It's fine... I'm studying after school.
In the library, with Macchi and Yukki.
You call it studying, but are you sure
you aren't just bothering them?
I'm not! Macchi even said explaining
to others is a good way to study!
She made a joke like,
"Next time, I'll try to rank first."
Well, just don't fail this time.
You can fail a proficiency test?
If your score looks bad,
I'll judge it a failure.
Huh? Sensei, that's no fair!
Demi-humans: Vampire Edition
Their Natures and Thought Processes
That's tyranny!
Wow...
What?
The desire to suck blood
is a combination of wanting
blood and wanting to bite?
Yeah, yeah! I think so!
So you can satisfy the former
with blood packs,
and the latter by chewing
on Himari-chan's arm?
That's right.
Do you have any preferences?
Huh?
You know, like favorite foods.
Do you have a favorite type of arm?
The first "Arm I Want to
Bite Championship":
The First "Arm I Want to Bite Championship"!!
The Hikari Cup
The Hikari Cup!
Yay...
What is this?
Well, as she so loudly declared,
Lady Takanashi Hikari, the only
vampire in this school,
will determine which of our arms
she'd most like to bite.
That's why I had you two come here.
Thank you for joining us today.
Too high-and-mighty!
Huh?
What's this mood she's creating?
Well, why don't we start with Machi?
O-Okay.
Should I roll up my sleeve?
Yes.
The First "Arm I Want to Bite Championship"!!
The Hikari Cup
Macchi
Hmm... The smoothness of
Macchi's arm is nice,
but it's pretty muscular.
It can't be helped, since she carries her
head and exercises a lot, but...
You like softer arms?
Yeah, though that also
depends on the person.
Also, Macchi loses a few points
for having no neck.
Even if I'm biting the arm,
looking at the neck sort of...
gets to me...
Wow, there's a lot to this, huh?
Taking all of this into consideration,
Macchi's score is...
Macchi:  65
65 points.
To use an analogy, she's a bit
like chicken tenderloin.
T-Tenderloin?
Yep, sometimes you just want some.
Huh...
Macchi:  65, Tenderloin
So you can use foods for comparison?
Yeah! Yours really is great!
It's soft and moist,
and its coolness makes it
a true Yukki original!
Macchi:  65, Tenderloin
Yukki:  93, Soft Ice Cream
93 points! Like soft ice cream!
Macchi:  65, Tenderloin
Yukki:  93, Soft Ice Cream
By the way, what's Himari-chan's arm like?
Himari's?
Hmm...
I've been chewing Himari's arm
since we were kids,
so it's hard to give it a score.
Something for when the mouth
feels lonely, I guess?
Like gum?
Is that what it's like?
Yeah! That's it!
Huh? It really is?
Macchi:  65, Tenderloin
Yukki:  93, Soft Ice Cream
Himari:  Priceless, Gum
Well, I guess I'm last.
Here.
It's hard...
It's thick.
I bet hair would get stuck in my teeth.
Don't ever say all that in public.
Well? What's my score?
You fail!
Is this payback for earlier?
Macchi:  65, Tenderloin
Yukki:  93, Soft Ice Cream
Himari:  Priceless, Gum
Sensei:  Fail, Inedible
The winner is Yukki!
Soft ice cream... Soft ice cream...
Come to think of it, some legends say
that snow women seduce people.
Wow, it really does feel good!
Right?
Maybe this is what they mean.
By the way, you two...
She isn't here,
but do you ever want to
chew on Satou-sensei?
Sakki?
I just borrowed it from Yuki-chan
for the nostalgia factor,
but now that I've started, I can't stop!
Hmm... No, I've never wanted
to chew on her in particular.
She's normal.
I see.
Macchi:  65, Tenderloin
Yukki:  93, Soft Ice Cream
Himari:  Priceless, Gum
Sensei:  Fail, Inedible
Tenderloin, ice cream, gum...
If you can compare it to food,
maybe sucking blood is really
based on eating meals.
But Hikari always says it's an
act that has sexual nuances.
So it would seem natural for her
to be drawn to a succubus
that has an aphrodisiac effect.
Actually, maybe if Hikari touched her directly,
then it would affect her...
Macchi:  65, Tenderloin
Yukki:  93, Soft Ice Cream
Himari:  Priceless, Gum
Sensei:  Fail, Inedible
Sucking blood.
Appetite.
Sexual desire.
Aphrodisiac.
Succubus.
Thinking about it logically...
It seems like Satou-sensei
would taste the best...
Satou-sensei would...
...taste the best?
What does that mean?
Huh?
I don't think saying a woman
would taste good is right!
Shameless!
Takahashi-sensei, is Satou-sensei your...
No! I meant from a vampire's perspective!
What kind of educator does that make you?
Yeah! Yeah!
T-Takahashi-sensei...
I'm disappointed in you!
Sensei, you perv!
Takahashi-sensei!
Perv! Perv! Perv!
No matter what the case,
Sensei...
saying a woman would taste good is wrong.
You don't have to jump on me that much!
Year 1 Proficiency Test
With these results, there shouldn't
be a problem.
You did well. Good job.
It really is nice to be praised!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Then you should have tried
harder, to begin with.
Proficiency Test Top 30
They post our proficiency test results, too?
27th: Kusakabe Yuki
Yukki made the list!
3rd: Takanashi Himari
Himari dropped a rank...
How frustrating!
Try harder, Himari...
Okay, who's the scoundrel
who beat Himari?
Roar, roar!
Huh?
Morning, Hikari.
Oh, the proficiency test rankings are up.
They are.
What's wrong, Hikari?
Hikari-chan?
You're awful, Macchi...
I thought you were joking!
Huh?
1st: Machi Kyouko
Huh?!
Next Time
Demi-chans Want to Try
Next time on Interviews with Monster Girls:
Demi-chans Want to Try.