Biology Prep Room
Sensei, um...
Thank you for your help the other day.
O-Oh, no problem.
Is your cold better now?
Yes, thank you. I'm all better.
Oh, good.
Sensei?
Er, sorry. I was just...
thinking about what an odd sight this is.
Interviews with Monster Girls
Machi Kyouko.
She's a dullahan,
an Irish demi, whose legend
is rooted in fairies,
and whose head and body are separate.
Dullahan-chan Wants to Be Coddled
Is it safe to touch the flame
coming from your neck?
Huh?
It's not hot?
N-No... Would you like to touch it?
You're right. It doesn't feel hot at all.
It's like grabbing air.
Feels strange, like
something not of this world.
Wh-What's wrong?
Touching it puts pressure on my nerves.
It's very uncomfortable!
S-Sorry... If you just tell me, I'll understand.
Your body isn't a separate being, right?
No, it's my body.
See? See? See?
Whoa, you're right!
See?
What's the matter?
Nothing. Uh...
By the way, when you collapsed,
was it all right to carry your
head and body separately?
Yes.
They've been as far apart
as Tokyo and Okayama.
Okayama?! That's really far!
What happened?
My mother's parents live in Okayama,
so I visit them every year.
But saying goodbye on the train
platform was so hard,
my body took off on the bullet
train without my head.
I see...
This is pretty crazy.
I'm sure it must be troublesome in daily life.
I work through those issues with
my family, using trial and error.
It's all about experience and ingenuity!
Ah...
For instance, when I eat,
I hold it in place, like this.
When I use the bath or toilet,
I hang it like this, so there's no problem.
This is very informative...
Thankfully, I'm able to handle
most things on my own.
But interacting with others is
what I still struggle with.
Interacting?
Yes, when people see me for the
first time, they're startled.
So getting comfortable with
one another takes time.
Especially at this time of year...
Right, since you just joined this school.
But I got sick and missed
the entrance ceremony.
Then I missed three days.
I forced myself to come to school,
but I ended up collapsing.
No wonder I hadn't seen you around.
Hikari-chan is different,
but I feel like there's some distance
between my classmates and me.
It isn't as if we don't talk,
but they seem to avoid discussing
anything about dullahans.
I would feel better if I could joke with them
about my dullahan aspects.
I see...
Machi.
Y-Yes?
Do you ever make jokes like that yourself?
Huh? No, I don't.
You don't?
Then, maybe that's where you should start.
I should?
If that's the sort of friendship you want,
you should tell some jokes to set a tone,
so they'll know what kinds of jokes
you can share with them.
I see. Jokes, huh?
In short, it's all about
who takes the first step.
Thinking of it that way, your classmates
have the higher hurdle to clear.
Right, since I'm a dullahan!
You're probably the first real,
live dullahan they've seen...
Aren't there only three in the whole world?
Huh? Yes, that's right.
I'm impressed you know that.
Well, I've done my research.
All for my precious students.
Sensei, um...
W-Well...
If you don't want to,
feel free to refuse, but...
Um...
W-Would you please hug me?!
Was that a joke?
No... Only my head.
Your head?
Like this?
Y-Yes! Like that...
I... I enjoy being held like this,
so my parents often used to do it.
But now that I'm in high school,
they told me to get over it.
But I just can't,
and there's no one else I can ask...
Okay.
Alone, a dullahan's head can't do anything.
To get around,
it needs contact with others,
even if that's its own body.
In other words, hating solitude
is part of a dullahan's nature.
Biology Prep Room
Put another way, they get lonely easily.
This dullahan-chan still wants to be coddled.
But you know,
considering that I'm a teacher,
this might look inappropriate.
R-Really?
Well, as long as no troublesome
pests see us, it should be fine.
Like stubborn higher-ups
or that chatty vampire...
Or anyone... like that...
Everyone!
Listen to this!
Hey! Hey! This is big!
I guess this means you're one
of the dullahans now.
Gather around, people!
Eh?
Because your head's going to roll, right?
That's a joke I can't laugh at!
Wait! Hikari!
Hey, listen! Takahashi-sensei was...
Wait, wait, wait!
Thanks, Hikari-chan.
For what?
I'm really glad I was able to
talk to Takahashi-sensei.
Oh, just seeing the panicked look
on his face was enough for me!
Yukki!
Takanashi-san...
Ah, you feel so cool! It feels great!
Do you live in this direction, too?
Yeah.
Then, let's walk home together!
Oh, this is Macchi.
Macchi-san?
I need to stop somewhere on the way.
Really? Can't help that, I guess...
I'm really sorry. Bye.
Bye-bye!
Isn't that Kusakabe-san, from class A?
The snow woman?
Yep, that's Yukki.
She's a little shy, but she's nice.
Oh...
And her body is so cold!
She feels so nice to hug!
So that's why you suddenly
hugged her like that.
My house is that way. Want to stop by?
Hmm... Well, it's already pretty late.
Yeah, that's true.
I bet your parents would worry.
Well, come over again when
you have time to visit.
Sure.
Take care!
Mom
Hi, Mom?
I'm on my way home now.
Sorry, I was talking to my teacher...
No, it isn't anything like that.
Okay, I will. Bye.
There. That should do it.
Now that I'm in high school,
it seems that both studying and
exercising will be a lot harder.
My head... My head can't keep—
My head can't keep up
Use when I'm really busy
Takahashi-sensei was so nice.
Interviews with Monster Girls
I hope I can talk to him again.
You want to go on a date with a guy?!
That sounds great!
Let's do it, let's go! Let's attack right now!
B-But I'm not sure how he feels...
It'll be fine! You're really pretty!
You have a nice figure, so just flash
your boobs, and he's yours.
You think so?
You're so indecisive!
Something weighing on your conscience?
Well, but I'm...
a dullahan...
Why does being a dullahan put you
at a romantic disadvantage?
Well?
Th-There are statistics to indicate such...
I heard there are only three
dullahans in the world.
Didn't think that through, did you?
Using made-up excuses to run away
makes you look pathetic!
Well, maybe it wouldn't put
me at a disadvantage,
but it isn't exactly an advantage—
Sure, it is!
It's no exaggeration to say you stand
atop the romantic pyramid.
Yes, for instance...
When it comes to naughty things,
you're capable of some special techniques.
You're amazing, Hikari-chan!
Do you know a lot about that sort of thing?
Yeah, well...
I don't actually know much.
Anyway, anyway...
What kind of date would you like?
Huh?
You must have some kind of plan
for your ideal date, right?
W-Well, I guess...
Since I'm a dullahan,
I feel most at ease when my head
is being held securely, like this...
And I like it.
Uh-huh.
So, well...
It'd be nice to walk around with the
one I like as he carries my head.
Walk around?
He can decide where we go.
And when I look up, I can see his face.
Little movements could bring
our faces closer together.
Uh-huh.
I-It would be fun to be able to do that.
I guess that's about it.
You're such a maiden...
And? And? Who is this prince
who's captured your heart?
Oh, uh...
Come on, 'fess up!
It'll be a weight off your shoulders!
Ta...
Ta?
Takahashi-sensei!
Hey... Hikari-chan?
Who are you calli—
Wait! Why are you making that face?!
Hikari-chan!
Good! You're both here!
Takanashi
We're doing an experiment!
You two will go shopping!
And you can't return until
sunset, even if you finish!
Got that?!
Yes.
Anyway, Macchi,
you really went all-out, didn't you?
Huh?
That looks too normal.
That's too childish.
That's a bit much...
I know!
Y-You think so?
Your body will be staying
here with me, though.
What?!
I'll take responsibility for keeping
an eye on Macchi's body.
Off you go, then!
I forgot about that...
Okay, you and I will go to the living room!
With just your body, I guess
you can't hear me.
So what kind of experiment is this?
Oh, um...
I-If I ever find someone I like,
there might be chances for just my
head to go out and do things.
So I thought I should work out
any problems in advance.
Hmm, I get it. That's a great idea.
She seems fidgety.
She's gesturing.
Showing me this won't do much good...
What are they talking about?
Not long ago, the cherry trees
here were in full bloom.
It's all green now.
I wish I could've seen them blooming.
Looks like it's going pretty well!
A notebook?
You can write without seeing?
That takes skill.
I'm having a great time.
Thank you, Hikari-chan.
"I'm having a great time. Thank you."
You're welcome!
But it might be going too well.
And that kinda ticks me off!
Wh-What's wrong?
Oh... N-Nothing.
I just remembered something funny...
Something funny?
She's mad! She's mad!
Well?
Y-Yes?
Have you found any problems yet?
S-Sort of...
What's wrong?
You don't look so good.
Uh, no.
Just a bit of motion sickness...
You okay?
Yes, I'm fine now.
Sorry about that. This is new to me.
It's all right.
Um, this is a first for me, too.
B-Being on a d-date with a guy, I mean...
But that means the experiment
did produce results, huh?
Y-Yes! The experiment!
This is an experiment!
I'm so glad I did this experiment!
Class A's Kusakabe?
Yes, she's a snow woman demi.
Of course I know her,
but I haven't spoken to her.
What about her?
Wh-When Hikari-chan and I were walking
home together, we bumped into her,
and Hikari-chan suddenly hugged her.
Yeah, Hikari did say she clings to her a lot.
And when she did, Kusakabe-san...
Did something happen?
I don't think it was that she disliked it, but...
She seemed almost scared.
Of Hikari?
No, not that.
I don't know how to put it.
But it just bothered me a little.
Should I try talking to her sometime?
I can't hold it any longer...
Ow!
What's wrong?
N-Nothing, really.
What's wrong, Macchi?
M-Macchi...
Macchi, here. Write it down.
Bathroom
"Bathroom"...
Oh! You just need the bathroom?
You really spooked me!
I'm home.
Onee-chan, is someone visiti—
There we go, there we go...
Huh? Something's here!
Take your time...
Whew, that was exhausting.
Onee-chan?
Oh, welcome back, Himari!
Who was that... person?
My friend Macchi. She's a dullahan.
Where'd you put her head?!
Next time I see her,
I'll just call out to her.
I shouldn't have had that juice.
Do you feel sick again?
Er, no, it isn't that.
I-It's nothing...
How's this? Do you feel all right?
Yes, this is much better than before.
You're amazing, Sensei.
I just remembered something
I learned in school...
When people walk, their bodies
move up and down.
But they don't feel it because they
unconsciously move their necks
and eyes to balance it out.
But for you, your arms function as your neck.
I see... I'd never thought about that.
So you need to find a dynamic balance.
Or, in simpler terms, be like
one of those balancing toys.
Balancing toys?
Yeah, like using this arm
to correct camera blur...
Takanashi
Thanks for all your help today, Hikari-chan.
Yeah, I really freaked out
that one time, though!
That one time?
Nothing! It's nothing!
Um, thank you for doing
this with me, Sensei!
No, I should thank you.
I learned a lot today.
Then the experiment was a success.
Yep. A great success.
Grmff sffsmfs!
Bye-bye!
See you later!
Hey, Sensei.
What?
About Macchi...
What about her?
Principal, dullahans need to
always carry their heads.
So carrying a regulation
bag takes up one hand.
It's inconvenient. Worse, it's dangerous.
For class 1-B's Machi Kyouko,
couldn't you give permission
to use a backpack instead
of the regulation bag?
That's a good point. I didn't
give that enough thought.
Of course I'll grant permission.
Thank you.
I have one other favor to ask.
What is it?
We should also consider her
homeroom teacher's position.
So could we just say this was your order?
I see. Very well.
Morning, Sensei!
Good morning.
Hey. Oh, a backpack?
Yes. Yesterday, my homeroom teacher
told me I could use this instead.
You're looking good, Macchi!
Right, Sensei?
Yeah, it suits you.
Next Time
Succubus-san is a Good Adult
Next time on Interviews with Monster Girls:
Succubus-san is a Good Adult.