Interviews with Monster Girls
Takahashi Tetsuo Wants to Protect
Oh, her?
She's...
kinda arrogant, don't you think?
I admit she is cute,
but she could hang out with
him once, at least.
Maybe she thinks she's some kind of idol...
Biology Prep Room
Kusakabe?
T-Takahashi-sensei...
What's wrong?
I-It's just... I heard people...
s-saying mean things... about me.
I see.
Well, this isn't the place to talk about it.
Let's go inside.
Is it because I'm a demi?!
If I weren't a demi,
I wouldn't feel like this...
Don't worry. That's not true.
That isn't true, Kusakabe.
Takahashi-sensei...
I have to protect her.
I have to protect this demi-chan!
Generally speaking,
gossip is a trivial issue,
common among high school girls.
But since she's a demi,
this particular issue isn't quite that simple.
Hikari and Machi have accepted that,
and are living normally enough...
Satou-sensei?
Hydrangeas, eh?
There were lots of them in the garden,
so I borrowed a few.
Are you working, Takahashi-sensei?
With the weather like this, staying in
that dark prep room is depressing.
Um... I was wrong about
you, Takahashi-sensei.
Huh?
The thing with Machi-san's backpack...
I happened to hear you asking
the principal to help.
Oh, that—
You're someone so considerate of demis,
and on the day of the opening ceremony,
I behaved that way toward you!
I'm so sorry!
Oh, not at all!
I should apologize for being
insensitive to your situation.
As for the backpack, Hikari...
Takanashi asked me to help.
Takanashi-san? The older sister, you mean?
Yeah.
I work so closely with those girls,
but I didn't understand anything.
I want to understand them better, but...
Um, Sensei?
Yes?
Um...
C-Can I be of any help at all?
Huh?
I'm a demi, after all!
Yes, I've experienced that firsthand.
I mean...
A-And I'm also a teacher!
I have a duty to address the concerns
of my demi students!
With that in mind, I really think I can help!
Oops.
No, I think that sounds perfect...
I'd appreciate your help.
All right!
So, the students who said mean
things about Kusakabe...
It seems they constantly gossip
about others that way.
Then, Kusakabe-san wasn't
being specifically targeted?
Probably not.
But she's convinced that it's
because she's a demi?
What do you think, Satou-sensei?
Even without considering the gossip,
Kusakabe-san seems to avoid contact
with other people, to begin with.
I mean, in a different way than I do.
Yeah, I get that impression.
It may be that she has some reason.
A reason.
You mean something like her family?
I have a feeling it's more connected
to her nature as a demi.
Her nature?
The reason I had the wrong idea about you
was because my succubus nature
made me overly self-conscious.
I see... There's that way of looking at it.
She probably doesn't have anyone
to talk to about it,
which makes it even harder to come
to terms with her demi identity.
I guess I should have tried
to talk to her sooner...
Well, why don't I try to speak to her?
Talking to another demi
might be easier for her.
That would be a big help.
I'm really glad you're on this with me.
N-N-N-Not at all! It's just what
any teacher ought to do!
Talking to Kusakabe is important...
But we should also deal with the
students who were gossiping.
You're right.
Telling them to stop won't work.
They don't want people to
know they feel inferior,
but they're afraid to face their victims.
I believe that mental weakness
is what makes people gossip about others.
If possible,
I'd like them to realize that they
don't have to fall back on gossip.
Yes.
Maybe it would be unfair to expect
that from high school students...
Now, what to do?
Takanashi-san, wait a minute.
Hey, where are we going?
Hey, Takanashi-san...
Takanashi-san!
Hikari?
And they just left it like that.
No way! That's crazy!
Also, I heard the physics teacher, Iwai,
is being sent to another school.
Takanashi-san...
Yukki, I'm going to give them
a piece of my mind.
Really? Why?
You wait here and listen.
He got involved in some
risky stuff, I heard.
What the heck?
I'll let you decide what happens afterward.
With that face, maybe it can't be helped.
You think he went after someone?
No way. He wouldn't have the guts.
What a loser!
Aren't you from class B?
Oh, the vampire.
Takanashi...
Is trashing people behind their
backs all you ever do?
Give it a rest.
Huh?
Oh, is this about Kusakabe?
As a fellow demi, you're out to avenge her?
That's cool of—
No!
Yes, Yukki is a demi, but it doesn't matter!
I'm giving you two a piece of my mind
because that's what I want to do!
Don't try to dodge it by provoking me!
If you don't want to stop blabbing
about people, then fine...
But every time I see or hear you doing it,
I'll call you on it.
If you want to hang around
and badmouth people,
you'd better do it where I can't find you.
Sensei...
We aren't the only ones who talk
about people behind their backs.
Why single us out?
It won't be just you two.
I'll give a piece of my mind to anyone
I catch badmouthing someone else!
Why are you so gung-ho about this?
Everyone talks about people
behind their backs.
I can't stand the excuse
that "everyone does it"!
Everyone hurts people,
so you think you're allowed to hurt people?
Aren't you ashamed to say that?
No one in the world likes being badmouthed!
What, so you never talk about
anyone behind their back?
No. If I want to say something,
I say it to their face.
If I can't, I say nothing.
You think that will keep people
from talking about you?
No, I don't.
I know as soon as I leave,
you two will start griping about me.
Sorry.
It was mean of me to say it that way.
Huh? Er, s-sure...
I know people who don't badmouth
others still get badmouthed.
In fact, they're probably
the easiest to badmouth.
But I've made up my mind!
It's just for my satisfaction, but...
Even if people say mean things about
me, I won't do anything I'll regret!
Are you... crying?
Sorry, I've said what I wanted to say.
I'll go now.
I can't agree with what you said,
but I am kinda impressed.
Still, why would you say all that?
Because I promised...
I promised my sister.
Your sister?
Takanashi Hima—
Ku...
Kusakabe...
I'm sorry!
I, um...
The truth is, things about my
demi nature still bother me,
so I've always avoided contact with people.
If that gave you a bad impression,
well... I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
We're the ones who should...
Sorry.
Wha—
The rain stopped.
You—
You hungry? I'll treat you to something.
Ow, ow, ow!
It hurts when you rub my head
where my hair's tied up!
Sorry about that.
If you're gonna rub it, rub the back!
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Huh?
Don't ask.
Wh-Where'd this come from?
Did something happen at school?
No, I'm fine.
Interviews with Monster Girls
Audiovisual Room
The thing is, a student came
to talk to me recently...
I had my own thoughts about it,
so I called you all here.
Satou-sensei, too.
Someone talked to you? It wasn't me.
Me, either.
Do you guys have no tact?
S-Sorry.
W-We couldn't help it!
Only three of us are here!
Anyway, I know there are many things
demis might worry about now.
I'd like for you three to be able
to help each other out.
You three are the only demi
students at this school.
I'd like you to treasure that link among you.
If you can't confide in your friends,
you can come to me or Satou-sensei.
In particular, Satou-sensei, is a demi,
like you, as well as a woman.
There's no one you can trust more.
I'd rather be the one seeking advice from—
F-Feel free to talk to me anytime, too!
That's all I wanted to say.
I hope you're aware that getting together to discuss things like this is important.
Does anyone have anything they'd
like to talk about right now?
I guess you can't think
of anything on the fly?
That'll be all for today, then—
Me!
I haven't gotten a hug from you yet!
Huh?
Hug?
Hi-yah!
Squeeze...
Hee hee.
Ha ha... What?
Hee hee hee!
Ha ha ha. Seriously, what?
C-Can I have one, too?
Huh?
Sure.
Thank you.
No problem.
Good for you, Macchi!
Yep.
Takahashi-sensei...
I'll take one, too—
No, that's a bad idea...
You're right.
Uh...
How about it, Kusakabe?
If you'd like one, too...
While we're at it.
Huh?
While you're at it?!
Kusakabe...
I won't force you to talk about
what's troubling you.
Like I said before,
I believe it's fate that you're
in an environment
where you're surrounded by other demis.
So... I can't say it well, but I'm
sure it'll get better.
You will have fun.
So don't worry.
Okay?
Yes.
Sensei, Sensei!
Give her a hug, too!
Her? But that's Machi.
Just while you're at it!
Sheesh... Is that all right, Machi?
Uh, sure.
All right, then...
Well, that'll be all for today.
Takahashi-sensei, what was
that weird scream?!
What happened?
Sensei, wait! I have a question!
I want to know what that reaction meant!
He called all the demis
together for a meeting?
Yeah, Takahashi-sensei had them
meet in the AV room after classes.
Takahashi-sensei did?
Hikari-chan said it was a lot of fun.
He seems pretty spacey,
but he's actually very caring.
Hmm...
What?
Oh, nothing.
To tell the truth, I still don't
trust Takahashi-sensei!
I got careless since it was just her
body, and I hugged too hard.
I wonder if Machi noticed.
Yeah, of course she did...
Hey.
Hello.
I didn't know teachers were
allowed to leave so early.
Oh, yeah...
And I see you stayed pretty
late, Himari-chan.
I did. I like the library.
Come to think of it, I hear you did
amazingly well on the last exams.
Th-Thank you.
You always study in the library?
Y-Yes, and I read books to refresh myself.
I see.
You're nothing like Hikari, huh?
That was suspicious.
He's always nice to Onee-chan, but...
What's wrong?
N-Nothing...
Just worried that my sister's
been bothering you.
I've been letting her cool off
in the biology prep room.
Is that right?
Or are you actually looking at her
as an experimental sample?
Oh, the experiment.
I forgot to prepare one for tomorrow's class.
I hope I'll have enough
materials for everyone.
Well, I can do it tomorrow.
I'm overthinking this...
Even if he does love demis,
there's no way he thinks about the nature
of vampires around the clock.
Oh, right!
I wanted to ask you something
about the nature of vampires.
He actually does!
Wh-What would that be?
Hikari seems to have no problem
chowing down on garlic,
but the stories you hear posit
that vampires hate garlic.
I was thinking about whether it was all fake.
R-Right...
They say vampires attack humans at
night, under cover of darkness.
Why do you think that is?
Uh, isn't it because they hate sunlight?
I don't think that makes them scary
enough for people to carry crosses.
Some texts say that vampires
have very keen senses.
I think that's the reason.
Sharp vision, even at night,
hearing that can detect humans,
a sharp sense of smell to pick
up the scent of blood.
That's more than enough for an
advantage over humans in the dark.
What does the sharpness of their
senses have to do with garlic?
Oh, the key point is their sense of smell.
Since their noses are so sensitive,
they hate strong-smelling foods.
I think that's why vampires
in legends hate garlic.
I've been thinking about those things,
but what's the real story?
Does Hikari have sharp senses?
I think that's an accurate perception.
My sister's senses are incredible.
Oh! All right!
Then, how can she eat so much garlic?
That's because...
She just isn't picky enough about her food.
I got concerned and asked her if
she was forcing herself to eat it.
And she said...
It's fine, it's fine!
I love foods that smell really strong!
I wouldn't want her to say that in public.
You can say that again...
Lots of people who talk to
me about my sister say
she doesn't seem like a vampire,
that she's just like a
normal high school girl.
You seem very interested in demis' natures,
so what do you think of that?
Do you think my sister doesn't
seem like a vampire?!
Are you not that interested
in her human side?
Okay, I'll give you a straight answer.
It's true that she doesn't behave
the way I'd expect a vampire to.
But if you asked whether that
makes her unlike a vampire,
I'd say it doesn't.
Hikari does want to suck people's blood,
but she settles for blood bags.
And even though she has a vampire's
keen sense of smell,
she loves foods with strong scents.
That human side is what
makes her like a vampire,
and it's what makes her unique.
It isn't how you're born that
makes you "like" something.
It's how you live with what you are.
But that doesn't mean it's okay to neglect
an understanding of a demi's nature.
The concerns unique to demis
are caused by their natures.
You can't look at things in only one way.
You should look from both angles.
If you just see traits unique to demis,
you'll miss their individuality.
If you only see the human side,
you won't understand their troubles.
Both are precious.
What's important is balance.
That's what I think.
I'm at a loss for words.
Maybe I can trust him...
Um, Sensei...
What's up?
Would you like to come
to our house sometime?
Oh, I did, not long ago.
In front of it, anyway.
I'd like my parents to hear
what you just said.
Oh, okay!
Actually, I was thinking I'd like
to talk to your parents, too.
Sensei...
Hmm?
Incidentally, I have a question for you!
What does hugging my sister let you learn?
Sensei hugged me today!
He totally attacked me!
Was it her vampire nature,
or her human side?!
Shibasaki Station
Hugged? Attacked?!
What is she thinking?
You've got it wrong, Himari-chan!
She's the one who—
You...
Rationalizing, demi-loving teacher!
I don't deny that, but still!
Onee-chan?
Onee-chan, are you oka—
And why send me such
a misleading message?
I'm sorry...
You were so late getting home,
and I was bored here.
I thought if I sent a message like
that, you'd come home faster.
I had no idea Sensei was with you.
If you'd just sent a message asking
me to hurry home, I would have.
Really? I love you, Himari!
Quit clinging to me!
Next Time
Snow Woman-chan Is Cold
Next time on Interviews with Monster Girls:
Snow Woman-chan Is Cold.