What are you doing?
Gulp.
Interviews with Monster Girls
Takahashi Tetsuo Wants an Interview
Good morning.
We have a new teacher joining us today.
Faculty Office
But she doesn't seem to be here
yet, so I'll introduce her later.
She must be awfully impressive
to arrive late on her first day.
By the way, Takahashi-sensei...
Yeah?
Well, that's enough joking around.
Earlier, you said you're researching
demi-humans, didn't you?
I was thinking of making them the
topic of my college thesis.
But dealing with demi-humans
is always delicate,
so a simple teacher can't get permission.
To this day, I've still never
even seen a demi-human.
Well, the number of demi-humans
is really quite low...
Why choose them as your topic?
I want to interview demi-humans!
Why do you bring this up?
Oh, well, actually—
I'm sorry I'm late!
Ah, you're here.
Come up to the front and introduce yourself.
I really am sorry!
Um... My train was delayed due
to a car inspection, and...
The train I tried to take was very crowded!
Ah, yes, of course. I understand.
Would you mind introducing yourself?
Yes, sir!
I can understand her being late,
but is a crowded train an excuse?
Well, I suppose she can't help it.
Oh, what I mean is that she's...
My name is Satou Sakie.
I'll be teaching math.
Also, I'm a demi-human.
I'm a succubus.
The new teacher's a demi-human?
Have you ever met one?
I found one.
In this world,
there are people called "demi-humans"
who possess special qualities.
Succubi, vampires, dullahans...
The demi-humans who have been used
as motifs in myths and fairy tales.
They have also endured persecution in the past.
Demi-human Welfare Division
But discrimination has been less
common in recent years,
and there's even a welfare
system for demi-humans
who live with any sort of disadvantage.
Demi-human Division
Now, being a demi-human is seen as
just another aspect of one's identity.
You can do it.
One, two...
Lower it a bit more.
Did you go anywhere for spring break?
Coming through.
Hey, you two!
Stop chatting and start carrying!
Okay.
So, anyway...
You're gonna keep talking?
Shizaki High School Opening Ceremony: Order of Service
Opening Address, National Anthem, Approval of New Students, Principal's Address,
New Students' Pledge, Current Students' Congratulatory Address,
Reading of Congratulatory Messages, School Song, Closing Address
It isn't crooked... Right?
Satou-sensei.
Yes?!
C-Can I help you?
I'm Takahashi, the biology teacher.
Takahashi-sensei...
Yes.
It's nice to meet you.
Uh... Same here.
Nice to meet y— Ow!
No, I mean... Wait!
Um...
Are you all right?
Yes.
Um, as I said this morning, I'm a succubus.
Yes, that's why—
That's why I dress and act to avoid
evoking sexual thoughts,
and refrain from contact with
others as much as possible!
I'm sorry. I wasn't thinking.
Is it that unusual?
Huh?
I noticed the way you've, um...
been watching me from afar all this time.
Oh... No, that was just...
It's troublesome if you approach
me purely out of curiosity.
If you'll excuse me.
Wait, Satou-sensei, you've got it all wrong.
I...
Okay, maybe not...
I really blew it.
A Few Days Later
Satou-sensei, about the other day...
No, I should apologize for my indiscretion.
I'm sorry...
I'm fine, so please don't worry about me.
Sorry, sorry, sorry...
She'll never talk to me now.
There he is! Sensei!
Sensei! Sensei!
You're huge!
What are you doing at this hour?
Did you forget something?
Ah!
N-Not exactly...
Bye!
Hey!
So you're a new student?
Yep, I am.
And you're a teacher here, huh?
That's right.
What were you doing there before
the entrance ceremony, anyway?
Well... I was trying on my uniform at
home, and I got kind of excited.
So I thought, "All right! I'm gonna
go to school right now!"
But did you have to run off
at top speed like that?
Anyone would run if some weird old guy
they don't know speaks to them.
Weird old guy?
They taught us that in school.
If you're a teacher,
I think you should praise my calm
decision to flee immediately,
as well as my swift response to the situation!
Anyhow, did you need something?
Oh, right! We don't need to talk about me!
Um, uh...
My classmate isn't feeling well!
Help me carry her to the nurse's office!
Okay, I'll be right there... Um...
Class 1-B, Takanashi Hikari!
Okay, thanks for coming to
let me know, Takanashi.
But I hope there's actually
some way I can help.
Huh? Are you the health teacher?
No, biology.
But I'm not a teacher for nothing, you know.
I can judge a student's health
with one look at her face.
She has no face!
Yeah, I can see that.
So she's basically one of
those, right? A dullahan.
A dullahan?
A demi-human whose head is
separate from its body?
I went ahead and carried her
head to the nurse's office,
but her body's too heavy for me.
Gotcha.
A second demi-human... I can't believe it.
Is it safe to touch this flame?
Dunno... It doesn't look hot, but...
Stretcher coming through!
I'll be okay.
I'll be okay once I cool down.
I'm okay...
I'm a snow woman...
I'm a snow woman, so I'm okay.
I'm a snow woman, so it's totally okay...
Wow, we've got a snow woman, too?
Come on, Sensei. Let's get
to the nurse's office, too.
R-Right.
Th-Three of them, so easily...
I'm glad you were the first person I found.
I mean, she's pretty big.
Takanashi!
You seem pretty calm about this.
Aren't demi-humans unusual to you?
Huh? Well, yeah, I'd say they're unusual,
but they don't surprise me.
After all...
I'm a demi-human, too.
I'm a vampire!
Nurse's Office
The snow woman has mild heat
exhaustion from P.E. class,
and the dullahan just has a cold.
What's wrong, Sensei?
Just thinking meeting demi-humans
is easier than I realized.
I'm sort of shocked, I guess...
Sensei, do you hate demi-humans?
Oh... No, not at all.
Sorry, I shouldn't have put it that way.
I actually love demi-humans.
Huh? Oh, really?
I've done all kinds of things to try and
meet them, but nothing worked.
I was just thinking about other
stuff besides how happy I am.
Sorry.
There we go...
In any case, you're saying you're
happy you met me, right?
That's right.
Really happy?
Yeah, really happy.
Hee hee hee!
Ha ha ha. What?
Okay! Well, thanks, Takanashi.
I'll be seeing you.
Yep! Oh, by the way...
Sensei, you call people like us
"demi-humans," don't you?
Yeah.
I used the term to go along
with you, but it's outdated!
Outdated?
"Demi-human" doesn't sound
cute at all, does it?
N-Not cute?
It sounds like it's out of a textbook.
Well...
So high school girls like us
use "demi" instead!
Oh...
Takahashi Tetsuo wants interviews.
Demi...
Interviews with monster girls.
Interviews with Monster Girls
This is why I asked this morning
if you'd forgotten anything!
How could you forget it, like it's
the obvious thing to do?
But I know you'll lend me yours, even though
you're mad, which is why...
I love you so much!
You're always pushing your luck, Onee-chan!
Onee-chan?
Sensei!
Oh, I'll introduce you.
This is my little sister, Himari.
I'm Takanashi Himari, from class C.
Twins?
Yep, we are.
Okay, here.
Thanks!
If you doodle in it again, you'll regret it!
Got it.
If you'll excuse me.
Hikari and Himari, huh?
She seems more responsible
than someone else here.
She's the little sis I'm proud of!
Is she also a demi-hum—
A demi?
Nope.
Oh, by the way...
What?
Well, uh...
Only if it's okay with you, I mean...
You want me to tell you about vampires?
Yeah. Of course, I won't force you.
Only if you want...
Okay.
Yeah, that's what I thought— You will?!
Sure.
Then, if I talk to you,
can I come and hang out in
the biology prep room?
S-Sure, come by anytime.
Sweet! Okay, I'll be there!
Wow... So, Machi-san, you went to the
middle school right next to mine?
I never expected to meet someone
in this school from so nearby.
Me, either.
Then, do you also take the bus, Machi-san?
No, I walk.
Really? Isn't that a long walk?
The bus is crowded during school
commuter hours, so it's dangerous.
You know, with the way I'm built and all.
Uh...
Oh! By the way, I found a really
funny video yesterday!
Yeah? What kind?
Oh, Machi-san, you watch videos online, too?
Yeah, sometimes.
Here, look! This cat is so cute!
Let me see.
Oh, my god!
Isn't it crazy?!
That's wild! It's so cute!
Right?
Demis are more likely to occur as a
result of mutation than genetics.
It's entirely possible for only
one twin to be a demi.
The sisters' relationship aside,
I still don't know anything
about how demis live,
how they interact with others, how they
think, or anything like that.
Biology Prep Room
how they interact with others,
how they think, or anything like that.
If there's one thing I now know, it's that...
This room is so nice and dark and cool!
...vampires get hot easily.
This is paradise!
I did say you could come by anytime, but...
Well, the sunlight is so
bright in my classroom.
And I'd feel bad, making my classmates
go out of their way for me...
Yeah, there are lots of things in here
that shouldn't be in direct sunlight.
Anyway, Sensei, you want to
interview a demi, right?
I charge a venue fee!
Hmm...
In that case, never mind.
Encyclopedia of Vampires
What do you think of the qualities
ascribed to vampires by legend?
Let me see!
Hmm... I do like garlic.
Crosses?
Crosses are only fashionable
through middle school!
Fashionable?
Oh! This!
A stake through the heart
would kill us! Probably!
That would kill me, too.
Do vampires really have to
drink blood to stay alive?
No, I don't think that's true.
Huh?
Do you ever get anemic, Sensei?
Feel short on blood?
Know what I mean?
Well, sometimes, I guess.
It's like we often feel that way.
For that reason, we prefer
to stay out of the sun, too.
So if we're careful about what
we eat, we can get by okay.
What you eat?
Liver! I love liver and onions!
And also tomato juice.
It feels just like drinking blood!
Feels like drinking blood?
Meaning that you really do desire blood?
Well, yeah... Maybe I do.
Vampires are provided with
blood by the government.
We get one pack per month.
Yeah, I'd heard that.
Maybe drinking that makes it so
I can get by on the food I eat.
I see.
Then, there are some vampires who get
by without relying on that blood...
Right.
What do you think of those vampires?
What do I think?
I think they're pretty amazing!
All right, that's enough for today.
Wait, S-Sensei! Give me one
more chance, please!
I'll never ask another favor!
Um, um...
There are vegetarians, right?
Yeah.
They survive without eating meat.
What do you think of that?
What do I think?
I think they're pretty amazing...
Yes! That! It's like that!
Wow, I really get it now.
I understand...
By the way, do you ever want
to take blood directly?
Huh?
Stories say people you drink
from become vampires
or that you can make them your servants.
Isn't that what your fangs are for?
Ever want to use them to suck blood?
Yeah, I do! I want to!
Oh...
Recently... Oh, you know that snow
woman in the class next door?
Yeah, the one from the other day.
Since she's a snow woman,
her body feels so cold!
Boom!
Whoa! T-Takanashi-san?
I can't stand heat,
This again?
Mm, you feel so cool!
so I cling to her a lot.
Aw, what's the problem?
We both hate heat.
And then, when I get a look
at the nape of her neck...
But this feels hot to me...
I think, "Ah, her body is cold,
but I bet her blood is warm,"
and "I bet that contrast would feel
great if I sucked her blood,"
and "I'd love to see how she struggles
and the pain showing on her face."
I do think about that.
I don't do it, though, since she'd hate me.
Huh... That seems a bit erotic.
R-Really? It does?
Uh, yeah. Guess you weren't aware of it.
Do you ever want to suck the
blood of the opposite sex?
Nope.
No? You prefer girls' blood?
Well, it isn't that, exactly.
I think it's probably because
I've never been in love...
In a way, sucking blood is an
expression of sexual desire.
So fantasizing about sucking girls'
blood could pass for a joke,
but you still have some reservations
about doing it with boys, huh?
Yes, I do! You're too quick on the uptake!
Well, not that I'd know, but it seems
like sadistic behavior, right?
And my type is someone who's dependable.
So maybe it would be really hard for
me to do that. Or something!
What?
Oh, nothing, really.
Liar! You were thinking it's nice to be young,
or I'm making the most of my youth,
or some other old man's thought!
You're quick on the uptake.
That's right.
This vampire-chan is at that age.
It was insensitive of me to ask all that...
I'm the one who said you could ask anything.
Hmph!
This has been fun. I've learned
a lot from you. Thanks.
Huh? We're done already?
Don't be silly. We have classes next.
Both of us.
See? There's the bell.
Get back to class. Back to class.
Yes, sir!
Whoops...
So, were you surprised? Were you surprised?
Don't sink your teeth into me,
even by mistake.
Hey! That was kinda erotic!
World History
Bye-bye, Machi-san.
Oh, bye-bye.
Hey, Macchi!
M-Macchi?
Huh? Are you feeling down?
No, not at all.
You have it pretty rough, huh?
I mean, you have to carry your head
everywhere you go, don't you?
Huh?
Going to and from school must be even worse...
Carrying your bag would take one
hand, so that'd be dangerous.
What's wrong?
Not really... I'm used to it.
Yeah, I guess so.
Isn't it inconvenient, though?
A little.
I mean, I'm a vampire, you know?
So I totally get what you're going through!
Really?
Yeah, in my case, I can't
stand strong sunlight...
Oh?
In summer, I can't even wear short sleeves!
But vampires can't stand to be hot, either.
Wow, that sounds awful.
Right?
I just want to cover my body
in cold compresses!
What are you two talking about?
The injustices of this world.
What does that mean?
So, Takanashi-san—
Call me "Hikari."
Hikari-chan...
I never see you during breaks.
Do you go somewhere?
Actually, yeah.
Come in.
Let's see...
You're Machi Kyouko, from 1-B, right?
Er, I guess asking your body's pointless...
To Takahashi-sensei
I'm so nervous!
It'll be fine.
Trust me.
Takahashi-sensei...
Thank you for carrying me to the
nurse's office when I had a cold.
Hikari-chan told me about you,
and I'd be happy to talk to you
about being a demi, too.
I also want to thank you
personally for your help.
May I come and talk to you sometime?
I also want to thank you personally for your help.
1-B Machi Kyouko
Oh.
But you can't hear his answer
with only your body.
Ah!
I wrote my answer for you.
Carry it back, and don't drop it.
Hikari-chan, I did it! I got his answer!
Yeah! Way to go!
Wait, no! Run!
Hey, wait!
Whew, that was nerve-wracking...
I was really surprised.
What does it say?
Machi,
Feel free to come by anytime.
Takahashi
Oh! Way to go!
Yeah.
All right! Let's celebrate!
Celebrate?
Let's stop somewhere on the way
home. We can get drinks!
Oh, okay. That sounds great.
Yay! Where should we go?
What should we drink?
What do you like, Macchi?
Well...
Next Time
Dullahan-chan Wants to Be Coddled
Next time on Interviews with Monster Girls:
Dullahan-chan Wants to Be Coddled.