Interviews with Monster Girls
Oh, you're awake.
Good morning...
Sorry. Did I wake you up?
Demi-chans Want to Swim
No, it's fine... Did you need something?
Yeah! I have a question!
Wow, your eyes really do shine.
Would this be why vampires
can see so well at night?
Yeah, it's the same as
for nocturnal animals.
Nocturnal animals have a mirror-like
layer at the back of their eyes.
That layer reflects the light that
enters through the retina,
allowing them to see clearly,
even in the faintest light.
Oh! So that glow you always
see in pictures of them...
Their eyes are reflecting the light
that humans shine on them.
Wow, that's so cool!
Vampires probably see well at
night for the same reason.
I'm so glad I asked you!
But that same quality also makes
them sensitive to bright light.
I know! That's why you can't
take flash photos at the zoo!
Well, that's also true, but...
You should be careful not
to damage your eyes.
The reason vampires don't handle
sunlight well is probably similar.
Oh.
On sunny days like today, especially,
you should look out for dizzy spells,
and also protect yourself from sunburn.
Right.
Also—
Sensei?
I already know all that.
How many years do you
think I've been a vampire?
Oh, right... Sorry.
It's just, well...
Earlier, I had a dream that
a vampire attacked me.
Was it scary?
It made a lot of sense.
How do I put it?
It made me think that vampires'
tendency to attack in darkness
is something that comes very naturally.
Achieving your goal
by concealing your weaknesses,
while fully using your strengths...
Just as with animals,
that must be the most comfortable
way for vampires to live.
When I think about it like that,
I feel modern vampires,
who adjust themselves to live like
humans, must feel constricted.
So I ended up giving you a
lecture you didn't need.
Nah, I'm really glad you're
concerned for me.
However! You're wrong about one thing!
Stand up!
Take off the lab coat!
Wriggle, wriggle, wriggle...
Ta-dah!
Modern vampires can hunt comfortably, too!
The vampire's white cape flows
as she searches for her prey!
Shiba Shortbread
Is that...
Yes! Time to attack!
Your panties are showing.
Sorry! I'm really sorry!
That was an extremely
insensitive thing to say...
Then, you...
You should also do something silly!
Are you nuts?
Act like a vampire, too!
A vampire?
Hiss... I'm going to suck your blood.
His eyes aren't shining.
He's a fake vampire! Get him!
You little...
Oh, I have another favor to ask you...
This Saturday, could we
borrow the school pool?
The school pool is outdoors.
Wouldn't an indoor one be better?
Nah, it's fine!
Well, I guess it wouldn't be impossible.
Really?
A teacher needs to be present, though.
That's totally fine.
Okay, I'll ask the principal.
Yay!
That doesn't mean anything is decided yet.
I know! Splish, splish, splash.
Takahashi-sensei!
Himari-chan, good timing.
I wanted to ask—
I understand you saw my
sister's underwear?
Sensei saw my panties!
Now I can never
get married~
Care to explain what this is all about?
I understand now... I'm sorry
this keeps happening.
No, I was partially at fault this time.
Sorry for that.
Anyway, what did you want to ask me?
Oh, that's right.
It's just, Hikari said she
wants to swim in the pool.
She did?
Sunlight is hard on vampires, as it is.
Wouldn't swimming outdoors be
really uncomfortable for her?
Sensei saw my panties!
Now I can never
get married!
I just heard the whole story
from Takahashi-sensei.
It seemed wrong to proceed without
permission from you and your parents.
I don't see any problem.
Yeah, I figured...
Wait, you don't?
If that's what she wants, it'll be fine.
The way my sister is...
Spending a summer day, just playing
around isn't unusual for her.
Let her do as she pleases.
Really?
Why don't we go for drinks sometime?
What if we really do end up going?
What should I drink?
I like beer, but that might make
me seem like an old man.
Cocktails? Shochu highball?
A lemon highball seems like
an old man's drink, too!
More importantly, what if something
happens due to the alcohol?
Ugaki-san
Satou Sakie
What do you think, Ugaki-san?
Can we talk about this tomorrow?
Ugaki-san
Goodnight.
Ah... Wait!
Ugaki-san!
Stressing out like this
won't do any good...
Okay!
I'll just stay positive!
Go for it! Right now!
Try to appeal to him, even if it
takes a little aphrodisiac effect!
Takahashi-sensei!
Oh, good morning.
Good morning!
Th-The other day, in that video,
I, um... mumble, mumble, mumble...
Satou-sensei?
Yes?
Are you free this Saturday?
Yahoo!
No diving in head-first!
Ooh, it's cold!
Sensei! Is my swimsuit cute? Is it?
This feels great! I'm in heaven!
Yep, yep. Very cute, very cute.
Yay!
You aren't too hot?
No, I'm fine.
If you need anything, just speak up.
Okay!
Thanks for watching them.
Oh, thank you, too.
Well, I'll leave the rest to you.
Okay... Huh?
You're leaving?
Yeah, this is a good chance for you
girls to spend the day together.
Imori and Kimura will be along later, too.
I'll be in the biology prep room.
Just bring me the key when you're done.
I'll be off, then.
W-Wait!
Yes?
Won't you stay a bit longer?
O-Okay...
Here it comes!
Here you go!
Got it! Hikari!
Attac—
Aw, I messed up!
Ah, what was that?
Yukki!
I see... Hikari-chan asked to do this?
Yeah.
But... I mean, the sun is so strong today.
Will she be all right?
Well...
Yukki! Here it comes!
Okay! Bring it!
I think she'll be fine.
I see...
Well, why don't you go
have some fun, too?
Huh? Oh...
Well, I mean...
Rather than having fun myself,
I wanted you to have some fun today.
Huh?
When Hikari asked me about
using the pool, I realized
that you probably never get to do
things like swim in a swimsuit.
That's true.
At pools and beaches, people are
always around.
So I'm rather reluctant.
That's why I thought, if the school
pool were reserved for girls only,
you could let go and have fun, for once.
Bad luck for the boys, though.
Satake!
Don't fall!
No need to worry!
After hearing the girls reserved the
pool, how could I sit around?
Now, this is quite a...
C'mon, Ohkawa! Get up here!
No, I'm good.
Really?
Here comes another one!
That's why I was in such a
hurry to leave earlier.
Sorry I made it sound like I was
dumping the work on you.
No, not at all!
I appreciate your thoughtfulness.
I'm grateful enough that you noticed,
but to arrange all this for me...
I really...
love...
My aphrodisiac chance...
Okay, well, I'm heading back now.
Have a good time.
Uh, no! I don't think your
staying will be a problem!
But...
My aphrodisiac effect seems to affect
you much less than others!
Huh?
Ah, er...
I guess so...
Right?
Maybe I have some sort
of resistance to it...
I wore a really cute swimsuit.
You should stay, so you can see it!
Here!
See?
Satake!
Yes, it is very cute.
Sexy as hell!
I'm so embarrassed!
Takahashi-sensei, would you
like to swim, too?
It'll be great exercise.
Uh, nah... I'm not a good swimmer.
Do you mean you can't swim?
Okay! Ready!
Because "Tetsuo" means "iron man"?
Huh?
Just kidding...
What's wrong, Yukki?
Just... some water up my nose.
Takahashi-sensei,
what would you do if a student
declared their love for you?
Oh, I saw this drama about
that on TV, and...
Well, the issue of whether any
student is that crazy aside...
I guess I couldn't return their feelings.
I couldn't think of high schoolers
as anything but kids.
And above all, they're my students.
I see.
Well, I'm...
I'm neither a child nor your student.
Sure, I know that.
Are waves not forming
because this is a pool?
Interviews with Monster Girls
What're you doing?
C'mon, play with us!
Sorry, we need a break.
Okay.
With all that playing, I don't
know how they never tire.
Right?
These days, I get tired so easily.
Maybe I'm getting out of shape.
Go for it, Yuki-chan!
I got this!
Hey! Having fun?
Yes! Aren't you going to swim?
Nah...
There!
Screw it all!
I can't join that...
Oops, sorry!
No problem.
Kyouko, you can talk while you
play with us? That's amazing.
Yukki!
Coming!
This is fun. Like watching
a craftsman at work.
All I'm doing is moving my body.
The only thing is that when it's far away,
it starts to feel like it isn't my body.
Sort of like playing a video game, I guess.
Item
Swimsuit
I get it.
If there were a game tournament like
that, you'd definitely place first.
You think so?
There are only two other
dullahans in the world.
Even if you placed last,
you'd still get bronze.
That's true!
Don't you think that
legends of dullahans are a little
different than those of other demis?
Like, how were dullahans associated with
an image of a knight on horseback?
That's true. Not many other demis
have legends that specify classes
or jobs, like a knight.
I tried giving it some thought.
Maybe long ago, a great dullahan
was an accomplished knight,
and his image was the one that stayed
most vivid through history.
I see...
If there were a dullahan knight
of such strength and vitality,
I'm sure he'd be a legend.
And if it started with him, the image's
specificity makes sense.
When you think of it that way,
the other legends fit, as well.
Dullahans are known as
harbingers of death,
which means a dullahan is
the last thing you see.
Maybe the idea that they throw a basin of
blood on those who stand at their door
was what the deaths of people
killed by dullahans looked like.
I've also heard that those
who see a dullahan have their
eyes lashed out, and so on.
Now that I think about it, all the
legends are like that.
Got it!
There!
But aren't there are also other stories?
Like that dullahans can't
cross a flowing stream.
What do you think that one means?
That must be
for the same reason I'm staying
here, beside the pool.
Yeah, that's true.
It's scary to think what would happen if
you dropped your head in the water.
In a pool, it would only be a bit dangerous,
but if it happened in a running stream...
It'd be over. No way out.
I guess that means
even dullahans wouldn't chance
pursuing anyone into a river.
I like that legend. It's one I can relate to.
Macchi...
You're so busy talking, your body's
stopped moving.
Oops... Sorry.
So anyway, so anyway! Listening to
you guys made me think...
You've never gone underwater, have you?
Gone underwater... You mean my head?
Yeah.
You're right, I haven't.
Aw, what a waste!
Everything looks really pretty underwater.
I can't believe you've never seen it!
What a terrible waste!
I'm starting to feel a little nervous...
Who is Sensei talking to?
Macchi's dad.
Sensei wanted to ask permission
for her to go in the water.
Is it really necessary, just for
a few seconds under?
It's very important.
Even if you know you'll get permission,
contacting him to ask is very important.
Sensei, what are you doing with
only your head above water?
I'm still embarrassed to be
seen in my swimsuit...
That's done!
We're ready to go!
I'll hold your head, Machi.
Okay.
Everyone ready?
Yeah!
Okay, here we go.
One, two...
How was that? Could you see?
It was so pretty!
Yeah? I didn't really get that,
but good for you.
Macchi, go under with me next!
Then me!
Sure!
Hey, take it easy. Too much
too soon is dangerous.
You guys, come underwater with us.
It's really pretty.
Uh... No...
Okay, let's do it!
Yuki, get her other side.
Sh-Shizuka?
Okay!
Here we go! One, two...
Wha... Yuki? No... Wait, wait!
You can't get away now!
Go!
Oh, you're still here?
You got sunburned.
Will you be okay?
I'll be fine. After a day's rest, it'll be better.
Is that why you suggested a Saturday?
You were worried about me?
Well, sure.
Sensei, thanks.
Since I planned this,
you prioritized my wanting
to have fun, right?
The idea of a vampire getting in
a pool, under the summer sun...
If Himari-chan hadn't asked me to,
I might have been too scared to let you.
Well, if I'd asked for an indoor pool,
everyone would've seen through me.
And the next time we played, they would
have gone out of their way, right?
I wouldn't want that.
No.
Well, bye!
Yep. See you on Monday.
Shibasaki Prefectural High School
Good morning, Sensei!
Yep, morning.
Hey, Sensei...
This is the spot where we first met, isn't it?
Back then, the cherry blossoms
were in full bloom.
Hey, Sensei, remember what
you said the other day?
That vampires must feel constricted
by living in modern society.
But you know what I think?
Having people who cry with
you when you're sad,
and laugh with you when
you're having fun...
Even if it's a little constricting,
spending time with those people
is much more precious
and much more fun.
So I think vampires today are happier!
I see.
Well, I'll be heading in!
Hey, wait a sec.
What's up?
Write your name before you go in.
List of Tardy Students
Hey, Sensei, do you remember?
Yeah, enough of that. Write.
Come on, please! Listen to me!
Okay, what?
Himari wouldn't do my hair,
saying I should do it myself!
She left without me. And then, and then,
I was late, doing my hair!
Ah, I see. Now write.
Aw...
Please, Mr. Magistrate!
At first, it was purely out of interest.
Hmph. I thought it would work.
I started to have contact with these girls.
And I began to feel a desire to help them.
But many times, I learned
even more from them,
and I got even more help from them.
I haven't spoken with them nearly enough.
Even my dad said I shouldn't
rely on Himari all the time!
Everyone's so mean!
It's the third time, so you get to
stay after school and clean up.
Please! Anything but that!
Well, I have a faculty meeting to get to.
Sensei!
I need many, many more interviews
with these demi-chans!
Interviews with Monster Girls