Very nice. I can see the
picture forming in my mind.
I know, right?
Can we have them do our music?
I'll ask!
Who exactly is this?
I only know them from online, but...
Hot! Hot!!!
That's stylish.
Brought the new track and things got hot!!!
Haven't played here in a while. Still the best.
Crowd was super into it. Thank you!!
Nice change of pace.
Live @ Bossa Cafe
They've been releasing tracks through
music sites for a while now,
and have worked on indie
anime and movies before.
Mizusaki, is that tan going to be a problem?
It could've been,
but I haven't been doing any
modeling jobs lately, so no sweat!
Any offers?
Not sure. Haven't been really
keeping up with them.
Three of a kind!
Mizusaki, could you accept the
occasional modeling job from now on?
And watch the tan lines.
What's this all about, Kanamori?
What do you think the eizouken's
number one selling point is?
Refined and carefully-crafted animation!
It's Mizusaki's fame.
Of course, she will be animating
until her hands fall off, too.
They'll fall off?
But the stardom of the model Tsubame Mizusaki
dimming would be like having
one of our wings clipped.
Incidentally, here's a promotional
plan that Mr. Kashima
from the dandan noodle shop just sent over.
Film
Voice Acting
Audition
The chief judge will be
THE!
Tsubame
Mizusaki
Voice actor auditions?
And I'm the judge?!
Once the idea was proposed
to the chamber of commerce,
they enthusiastically agreed, thinking it'd
be good advertising for the town.
I don't wanna—
You could have the starring role.
Except I know you'd rather not.
Which is why I'm asking for your
help with this instead.
Well, I'll take it over being in the cast.
I'll let them know, then.
And if we're going to secure
music and have auditions,
it'd help to know what the
story was going to be.
A party!
After hearing that music, I was
inspired to make our finale into a dance scene!
It's a party! That seems fun! I love it!
If we're going to be animating to music,
we'll need to get an early demo
of the music for the dance scene!
Why exactly are they partying?
Maybe it's a...
Celebration for a hard-won victory!
"Inspired." "Maybe."
It feels like you're just
submitting scenes you thought up
with no thought to the overall picture.
I don't care what the actual story is,
but it's about time you—
It's lively in here, as usual.
Having a little party, Kanamoney?
Kanamoney!
Quiet, you!
Did you think of another excuse to fine us?
It's not about that.
You've always got your mind on cash, huh?
It's not money that I like,
it's productive activities.
And the money?
The money helps quantify that productivity.
Well, there's a little problem with that...
Turns out, the school isn't thrilled
about you making money on the outside.
Self-Publishing Exhibition and Sales Event
An event for the display and sales of manga and other self-published works
Episode 10        Against Our Independent World!
Keep
Your
Hands
Off
Keep Your Hands Off Eizouken!
Wh-What's wrong, Kanamori?
Are we in trouble?
There's so damn much I can poke holes
in here, I can't bring myself to start.
That's bad. Because the
two of us can't exactly...
Extracurricular activities are
considered a full-fledged part of education.
The government curriculum details
as much, along with the rules involved.
We're fully willing to consider
any directions you have,
if they actually serve a purpose.
Well, it's not very educational to use
club activities to earn money, is it?
Isn't the culture festival a means of
securing profits from
outside of the school, too?
That's... a special exception.
Look, here... "Athletic,
cultural, or technical pursuits
in order to exercise intellectual curiosity,
cultivate a sense of responsibility,
and develop teamwork."
That's what it says!
We all saw your film. It was incredible!
Especially for high school students.
So we think what you're doing is wonderful.
But you can't try and profit off of it.
That makes it something else
than education. Don't you see?
You've been avoiding explaining why,
exactly, turning a profit isn't educational.
I have not!
It's just that, working diligently
with your friends on something
can provide things money can't buy!
I'm starting to wonder if the
government curriculum guidelines
say something about only
fools becoming teachers.
How could you say that?! They're all
great people! I mean, they're teachers!
I think you might have what it
takes to be a teacher, president.
Y-You think?
Let's get to the real issue.
The bottom line is, a lot of people outside
the school, including parents,
aren't comfortable with students
getting involved with money.
And schools don't cope well with pressure.
Which means they don't feel like
the risk your little operation
might incur is worth the trouble.
There are a lot of political
considerations for a school.
To say nothing about the legal—
What's the point of an educational institution
if it won't stand up for its students?
People who don't understand business
will fall behind those who do,
and be worse off for it.
Spewing out superficial pleasantries
about "dreams" and "hard work,"
while turning away from anything
that might cause a headache.
Is that your idea of teaching?
We just can't have you doing whatever you want.
The school has to consider its
relationship with the town, too.
What would you be using this money for, anyway?
For all your talk about how this is
some high-minded business exercise,
aren't you just using the school's
name to benefit yourself?
Indeed, I am.
I'll use anything that helps.
Call it a "means to survive."
You're all still students.
Aren't there things your club
could only be doing while you're still here?
We all want you to cherish
the time you have.
There's no need to rush into adulthood.
Because once you've grown up, you'll have to—
Too optimistic.
"The effort itself was the reward."
It's an extracurricular cliche,
and people who indulge in it learn
the hard truth when they're adults.
Besides, we didn't ask the chamber
of commerce to fund the production,
we proposed a joint operation with them.
And they decided to accept.
I think we're done here.
The point is, you're free
to participate in the event,
but you can't accept any money earned at it.
Understood?
Film
Voice Acting
Audition
The chief judge will be
THE!
Tsubame
Mizusaki
Looking for actors!
Voice Actor Auditions!!
Work Dates
How to Apply
Where to Go
Shiro Hibiki
Advance Tickets Now on Sale!
Audition
Voice Acting
Shibahama
Anime
Tsubame
Mizusaki
Math
Audition Submission Audio
Yo Shintani
Fuga Yamashiro
Kure Seiko
Kotomi Ota
Ryuji Sakida
Atsuki Yamai
Shin Takishima
Shuta Kanbe
Hanako Sato
Takumi Minami
Masaaki Yuasa
Shoko Takahata
Mizuki Kiyama
Kentaro Aiba
Rie Misumi
Ryoko Tanaka
Haruno Yoshioka
Kohei Sakita
Hiroyuki Saito
Asami Murakoshi
Kai Fujisawa
Toma Kimura
Ikki Kawamura
Daichi Nabeta
Audition Response List
Role
Name
Job Experience
Unique Talent
Kanamori
Mizusaki
Comment
Yo Shintani                                                 Monk
Fuga Yamashiro                                                                                                                       Lots of free time
Kure Seiko                                                  Fortune-Teller
Abel Gongora                                             Illustrator                                                              Lots of stamina
Kotomi Ota                                                 Restaurant Worker
Ryuji Sakida                                               Freelancer
Joan Chung                                                English Teacher
Atsuki Yamai                                              Freelancer
Rachel Eunji Choi                                      Astronaut                                                              Trilingual
Shin Takishima                                          Civil Servant
Shuta Kanbe                                               Video Creator                                                       Lots of free time
Hanako Sato                                               Pianist
Takumi Minami                                           Economic Analyst
Batiste Perron                                            Graphic Designer
Masaaki Yuasa                                           Pâtissier                                                              Confident in his voice
Shoko Takahata                                         Psychologist
Mizuki Kiyama                                            Bathhouse Clerk
Kentaro Aiba                                              Singer-Songwriter                                                 Good at impressions
Eunyoung Choi                                          Hyper Media Creator
Rie Misumi                                                  Gourmet
Ryoko Tanaka                                            Pearl Craftsworker
Haruno Yoshioka                                       Sexing Baby Chicks
Kohei Sakita                                               Matagi Hunter                                                        Tough
Yang Changjik                                            Exchange student                                                 Lots of free time
Hiroyuki Saito                                             Systems Engineer
Asami Murakoshi                                       Former Art School Student
Kai Fujisawa                                               Archaeologist                                                       Well-spoken
Toma Kimura                                              Fisherman
Ikki Kawamura                                            Stand Up Comedian, Blogger                            Lots of free time
Daichi Nabeta                                            Hot Springs Sommelier
Akane Sakagaki                                         Golf Ball Diver
Rodrigo Makoto Matsumoto                     Suit Actor                                                             Can do stunts
Eri Kinoshita                                              Carrot Farmer
Takumi Matsumoto                                   Radio Personality
Hiroki Koshida                                           Cameraman
Shinnosuke Saito                                      Worked at a Bakery
Satsuki Watanabe                                     Copywriter
Hiroaki Hashimoto                                    Game Music Composer                                       Has stamina
Dorian-Niels Leclair                                  Barista
Kenji Maeba                                               Worked at a Hotel
Yumeno Hoshi                                           Mountaineer
Kohei Shindo                                             Soccer Club Captain                                            Lots of free time
Nick McKergow                                         Pro Gamer                                                              Can speak English
Yoshie Ezaki                                              Dental Hygienist
Masamichi Takemura                                Truck Driver                                                         Can do improv
Mari Motohashi                                          Technical Sound Arranger
Kanon Obata                                              Basketball Player                                                  Loud Voice
Karin Noguchi                                            Udon Shop Owner
Takashi Mizukami                                      Taxi Driver
00_Confirmed
How are things proceeding, Asakusa?
Bit by bit.
Ideally, we'd be able to include a lot
references to the real Shibahama...
Canals
Sandy Coast/Pine Forest
Gantry Cranes
Containers
Lighthouse
Waterways
Bridge
Other Side of Coast
Harbor
Very impressive.
You see, Kanamoney, once you're
directing your third production,
you start to understand what the people want.
And where are we with the story, Director?
Got it right here!
An enemy prisoner of war comes
to understand human kindness,
changes sides, and fights
alongside humanity!
Soldier smiles,
but can't talk
Can I stop you for a second?
What does the enemy look like?
And who are they?
They're in UFOs, so they've
gotta be aliens, right?
P-Probably?
The enemy fortress appears
out of Lake Shibahama,
and has the same kind of design
as the human towers. Why is that?
Actually, why were the UFOs attacking again?
Are they invading the Earth?
Figure it out!
Your directions dictate what
the entire staff is doing!
You can fret your weird head off,
but the clock is ticking!
If the storyboards take too long, that puts
extra pressure on every
other step in the process!
Understand?!
I understand!
Asakusa melted her way into hiding!
That sounds exciting!
Let's go to the Sound Club!
Open sesame!
Fully Rotated
Rrrrrumble...
It felt like we were lost in space.
She's asleep.
A kappa?!
No. Human.
You sounded like you were
firing a beam in your sleep.
Like you'd see in a space battle.
There's no sound in a vacuum, y'know.
Wheel, dough.
Well, duh.
Wait, is it Saturday?!
Is today t-tomorrow?!
Today is tomorrow.
Oh, crap!
Tomorrow from yesterday, which was Thursday.
It's still Friday.
Oh, man... so it's not tomorrow yet.
Did you seriously think a whole day
passed while you were asleep?
Well, I've never napped before.
Wait, that was a lifetime first?!
Were you doing something on Saturday?
Good morning, comrades!
Morning!
You're sure you want to come along?
Why exactly are we meeting up on bikes?!
Because we're going sound hunting!
Let's hunt some sounds!
Work on the storyboards!
And figure out who the bad guys are!
Why are you tagging along on a sound hunt?!
That's the audio director's job!
The general director's job is
to keep an eye on everything!
Talk big after you finish
your own damn job.
I would've been fine on
my own, but she insisted.
I mean...
You clearly don't mean anything.
But...
No ifs, ands, or buts.
Still...
No, not still! Moving!
I-I'm just looking for
ideas for the storyboards!
It's a hunt of my own.
What hunt?
Scenario hunting!
I wanted one last idea to put a
bow on the setup for the project.
I don't mind the company,
as long as you help out.
Sounds good!
Why am I here?
Let'sa go!
This had better be productive.
Turn on Lights
This is the place.
Looks like the remains of a generator...
With English brick bonding.
I can see the school!
I've been curious about
this place for a long time.
And this has something to do
with the Shibahama-UFO Battle?
Probably!
No roof, huh?
The idea is the water comes down and
turns a wheel, which generates power.
That's cool!
Six
Five
Seven
Four
Eight
Three
Nine
Two
Ten
One
Eleven
Twelve
Hey, it's the clock tower
that we're always looking at!
Interesting to catch a glimpse up close.
This is one of the things I'm here for.
It's kinda like a tourist spot...
Oh, wow! It's a pendulum!
I wonder what this place was?
Looks to me an awful lot like an alien
base disguised as a clock tower.
It's so big! And you can
see the back of the clock!
I'd wager the owners or some
politician thought they'd
fix the place up and turn it
into a tourist destination.
This building just gave me an idea!
Twelve
Three
Eleven
Ten
Nine
Eight
Five
It was once a luxurious home to wealthy tenants!
And inside the clock, high atop it,
a massive treasure is hidden!
Thus...
An alliance of thieves has targeted it!
They face...
The bodyguard hired by the building's owners.
So a security guard, basically.
The last scene is a duel atop the
grass field that grows on the roof...
Stop. Hold it right there.
This is one huge clock!
How about that concept? It'd make
for a great 15-minute short!
Stop talking about other projects.
Focus on finishing the one you're working on.
What now?
K
There are Ks!
K? What?
You take the "K" from "kinetic
energy" and call it a "K-cannon!"
K
It's a DEW the Imperial Army
was cooking up in secret...
A Directed-Energy Weapon!
Those are urban legends, right?
But then, it turns out, they're real!
And maybe this is the forgotten
laboratory where it was worked on!
Gonna stop you right there again.
Get back on topic with our current project.
I feel a guiding hand here...
This time, we're working something
we were destined to make!
Essentially...
In our club room, on the
other side of the coast,
the subject for an exposure
test was being stored.
Something was fired from this side...
Which lit something in the eizouken club room
that kicked those fans we have
into gear, to awaken something!
Asakusa's gone crazy!
K
I just figured out the
connection to my storyboards!
A mecha to fight those UFOs was
developed right where we stand!
Basically, this was the base
for the Shibahama military!
That sounds good to me.
See, Kanamori? This bit of sound
hunting paid fine dividends!
Crap, my target!
Everybody, gimme a hand!
K
Kanamori, get the fluffy thing from my bag.
Asakusa, set up the tripod!
Roger Wilco!
Is this it?
Mizusaki, your jacket's kinda noisy.
Really?
Almost time. Nobody move a muscle.
Good work, everyone. That went smoothly.
That was nerve-wracking!
I finally got it!
I'm surprised you didn't have it already.
K
There's an old one in the club's collection,
but the sound has degraded with time.
But even though everything else is
in ruins, this bell still rings out.
It's probably just been forgotten about.
It continues to ring for some reason?
That's magnificent!
All right,
the bell that continues to chime for
some reason has given me a new idea!
That's enough out of you!
I wanna go next!
Hey, eizouken.
The class president!
Uh, no. I'm actually the secretary.
So, did you figure out what to
do about that stuff from before?
The copyrights of works belong
to their individual creators.
We'll enter Comet A as the film club,
and then any sales and collection of
cash will be done on an individual basis.
Couldn't you just enter a contest?
A contest would be good for our reputation,
but it'd take too long to pay dividends.
An event like this gets us instant
recognition, an influx of income,
and market research, all in one.
The eizouken's agenda is production
and research, isn't it?
Management is a type of research, too.
The baseball club does that kind of thing.
They keep records of their sales,
organize the data, and then report on it.
It's only natural that popularity
would be the standard by which
club activities are measured.
You could manage all that inside
the school's jurisdiction.
It wouldn't be anything more
than a simulation, then.
Well, it's not exactly a model for society.
Schools are a world unto themselves.
Step too far outside of that world,
and you won't be protected anymore.
What're you getting at?
Behold!
We're moving beyond simple rotation!
Fans, drills...
propeller skirts, ducted fans, and chainsaws!
It's time we reconsider all
of these spinning machines!
What is this thing?
Her job.
This?
This motion is more like a gear.
Like in a clock?
What is this? Wavy grass?
No, it's wavy sound.
You layer it like this, the
same way you would an image.
I can hear it.
You knock it around, layer it,
clip it up, and reattach it...
What kind of tool is it supposed to be?
I'll think that up.
I've got it!
This equipment is said to be able
to transmit wishes and gratitude
from the surface world to the underwater one!
A device (ritual tool) that was created by using machine technology
originally designed for milling
Top is a flat surface
Cylinder is made from bamboo,
cut into quarters
Jet
Sometimes depicted as going up
and down
Range of rotation is
90 degrees, won't turn
all the way at once
And the water responds in kind by
granting the surface world its blessing.
Wing
Axel catches water,
causing the paddle to rotate
How the movement works
Axel
Stabilizer
Teeth will catch if there's
ever reverse rotation.
Lower axles also rotate.
Flow of water
Direction of piston movement
It's pushed in an undulating motion,
so the axle moves upwards
The paddles move left and right,
like a pendulum, when hit by
the flow of water
Raised up by water's pull
on the paddle, which is
connected to the axe
This device is what enables
that mutual exchange!
Output
Input
The tradition behind it is eventually forgotten,
but the technology itself evolves
into becoming the basis for
clockwork machinery, and is passed on.
And the bells?
Festival rites.
They purify people of their evil,
and call upon the water for a bountiful harvest.
The chime!
I'm curious...
Does this have anything to
do with our current project?
Did you figure out how to connect this to it?
You're really gonna need
to decide on the villains,
or I won't be able to make
much progress with the sounds.
What about the climax? Have you figured
out the identity of the bad guys?
Not yet...
And what are they after?! I thought you
were gonna put a bow on the concept?!
I forgot that they're in their own world, too.
Illustration by: