Direction CH  Animation CH  Keyframes   Direction CH  Animation CH Animation                                Filming        Final CH
45 Days Until Deadline!
I wanted to check something.
Why does the town transform
into an armed version?
Who arranged for it, and why?
It'd help to know when it was done, too.
Well...
You've got too much stuff up in the air!
Maybe you ought to pick something at random!
Because we can't get started at this rate!
I-I'll come up with something ASAP,
so if you'd just be patient...
Why are they fighting in the first place?
Episode 11       Each Other's Existence!
Keep
Your
Hands
Off
Keep Your Hands Off Eizouken!
Film
Isn't the Transcription Research Group
famous for discovering the Dead Sea Scrolls?
No, no!
It was a portion of the Nag Hammadi library.
Plus, that was forty years ago and
has nothing to do with any of us.
Shibahama UFO Wars
More importantly, we need to get the data,
or there are gonna be problems!
We're not quite at the date
stipulated in the contract yet.
But there are parts that are at a standstill!
You realize we're about the only ones
We should install
some partitions for
moments like this
who will go to the trouble of burning
physical discs anymore, right?
We've got a lot of work to do,
and it's not exactly a
cakewalk to get it all done!
It seems like a bad sign if you're accepting
more work than you know you can finish.
I wasn't expecting griping
from such a prestigious club.
Listen, you!
I hear propellers!
Film
It's a drone!
SECURITY CLUB
It says "security club" on it.
Nice eyesight.
The security club?!
Film
Something's happening!
Stop that! I didn't give the order to shoot!
Freeze!
Drop your weapons!
You're under arrest for arranging deals
using school funds without permission!
What's all this?
We've already been given permission
to reproduce media already!
Not to mention we—
SECURITY CLUB
That came from the entrance!
Don't shoot!
Notice of Expulsion
The Transcription Research Club
is hereby expelled immediately.
Moving forward, all related matters
regarding this case will be handled
under the authority of the student council.
Shibahama High School Student Council
The student council's taking it from here.
He's just been expelled with
prejudice on suspicion
of illicitly spending school funds
on an unauthorized exchange.
As of this moment, this entire matter
is now under our jurisdiction.
You guys, clear on out.
If you don't want to end up
like this, I'd be careful.
We're not like them.
Now, about compensation for
the broken door and windows...
• Seven Window Panes
40,000 Yen
• Door Repairs
20,000 Yen
The school's bound to make a move soon.
The day of Comet A
will be the day of
the screening event!
Featuring interviews, behind the scenes
features, a location tour, a chat with
the cast, and songs
Specially arranged for the local screening
Venue is across from
Chamber of Commerce!!
Shibahama Chamber of Commerce
Original Animation
Shibahama UFO Wars
Audition
Shibahama Water
Shibahama Map
Wasabi Senbei
It leads here? That's another route scouted!
Why is the vice-principal here on a Sunday?
Neue! Deutsche! Härte!
Good morning.
Good morning! Guten morgen!
Guten morgen.
Neue! Deutsche! Härte!
Cosmos...
A flower that represents peace...
What even is an enemy?
The leaves you can make money off of!
Values vary, depending on the environment.
What a tasty-looking raccoon dog we've caught.
Is that an ant queen being carried away?
You think you've got the time
to go out for a stroll?!
Mercy, please!
Mercy for the fourth-rate director who
still doesn't know her own story?!
A bear!
I'd say the tech marks him
as a human being, actually.
What's he doing here on a Sunday, though?
I must be present whenever you girls
are at the school for club activities.
Them's the rules.
And with you three, that means
I basically never get a day off.
Not to mention I'm always here late
without getting paid overtime...
Being a club adviser is a lot
rougher than I imagined.
I figured I'd play video games all day,
but had trouble deciding on which one.
See, you can't expect
someone to be able to work
with no time off or no enjoyment.
Don't work more than you have to,
and when you find the time to, you play around.
That's the trick to working.
That's it! We haven't
been playing around enough!
Time to make up for lost time!
We don't have time for more distractions!
It'll be a change of pace!
You two have work to do!
Damn it!
The best work comes from a sense of play.
So have fun, young lady.
If you fall off, you'll die!
I'm already dead, so it's fine.
You still have three more lives!
I've already died six times.
Takamune
Let's go down here!
There's a river flowing underneath the ground!
The river to hell!
Underground Tunnel
There's a sheer cliff on the other side of here!
This is less making the project fun,
and more just goofing around
It's a freaking sheer cliff! We could
actually die if we fell from here!
Look at you, repeating what I just said like
you're the first one to realize it—
There's a swing!
That thing that looks like it's meant
for trapping people by the behind?
You'd have to be nuts to get on that thing!
You could end up biting the big one!
Aw, man, I wanna swing on it!
I don't think there's a route
to get down there. How come?
All roads lead to Rome.
Maybe you need to go there first.
You'd still need a road from Rome,
and I don't see any leading to the swing.
Let's take the river, then!
Are we headed toward heaven or hell?
Either way, make sure to
pay the ferryman yourself.
Y'know you cross the river
Styx widthwise, right?
That makes the afterlife over there!
So the world we live in is heaven and hell, huh?
No wonder it's so hard to "live" in it!
What's up, Kanamori?
Well, I think I just saw a ghost.
Bunny High Altitude ver.
With Safety Harness to
Prevent Falls
Don't!
Asakusa's sucking on her bunny again.
It's getting a bit less steep around here.
Let's all make this a solar town
Wow! What is this place?
It's completely flooded!
There are fish!
Submarines
Yeah!!!!
Where's that swing, though?
On the other side, likely.
I guess we'd have to go through here...
There's too much water to pass through.
I guess we really do need a sub.
I'm pretty sure this is a road, not a river.
Whuzzat?!
EXIT
You're right!
I saw something at the other end of the tunnel!
Was it a kappa? You think?
Let's all make this a solar town
We're left with more and more questions...
Let's just say it's a sunken
city full of kappas.
Nice!
Ta-dah! The Greater Atlantis
Alliance of Archipelago States!
Kings throughout history
The greatest state
in the seaborne alliance is Mahashiba
Layout of the southern block
Inside of the centrifugal pump
monument is the actual monument
Vessel Elevator
The Greater Atlantis Alliance
of Archipelago States
~Its Golden Age and Fall~
Due to several inventions created in the civilization's
earliest period they became relatively more advanced,
which only led to further technical optimization
brought on by even greater technological innovation
over time. This explains why their culture can exist in
the same world as ours despite having developed in
such a unique way, in theory.
Upper level:
Manufacturing,
royal palace
Third layer:
Ocean water filtration tanks
Manufacturing plants
Ship owner's berth
First and second layers
are general residential housing
Whether defined by exotic
terrain or craton,
[Culture of a powerful nation in decline]
Floating island configuration
Age of Luxury
As a result, culture is split in two
In spite of making floating buildings
so that the nation could be seaborne,
they were knocked around by shifting ocean
currents until they were ultimately destroyed
Water begins to encroach, creating a need
to construct living space.
But runoff from the
land and buildings
begins to threaten
lower layers.
Age of Efficacy
Submerged configuration
it's the embodiment of lost
continental adventure!
By extending snorkel-like tubes, life on
the seabed was made possible.
But this is the real draw:
Urban area that spreads out across the bottom of the sea
Closer
Large elevator used for
distribution of goods
Faster
As nations began to be constructed at the bottom of the sea, a shift
occurred in transport infrastructure.
Massive shift in infrastructure!!
Instead of ascending to the surface
via an underwater elevator to travel at sea level,
they realized that spreading the
city outward and traveling underwater
would be more efficient in
terms of energy and time!
And after people discovered the fun
to be had in customizing them,
Frontal View
Front Hatch
The Great Age of Submarines
Docking at a port on the seabed
Transport submarine
Mooring wire
Fuji Marine
Personal Submarines
Diagram of a submarine docked in a building
Some are
ambitious!!
it led to a culture built
around submersible vehicles!
There are high-speed passenger vessels, too!!
Underwater scooters are extremely handy!!
Asakusa!
Are you okay?!
The river swept my leg away...
Like hell it did.
You just weren't paying enough attention!
Let's all make this a solar town
The sound a kappa makes...
Film
Asakusa!
Look... Look at this!
Reminder
Absolutely no funds are to be
acquired from outside of school
Vice Principal
The art club's not sure
if they'll be able to do the
backgrounds because of it.
The vice principal warned us.
The PC club might be in the same situation.
I think the vice principal's
trying to put pressure on us.
We need Kanamori!
She hasn't been answering!
She might be at home! Let's move!
3 Years Ago
Kamitanukisawa School
Expecting us to talk to random strangers...
That'll get you reported in the real world.
Oh, there's another loner.
She looks like a thug.
People like that are why I hate school.
All right, everybody! Pair up, back to back!
Uh, Teacher, I don't have a partner yet...
You two can pair up.
U-Um, I can manage on my own...
No, you can't.
Being alone is scary, but so are other people.
Okay, one!
Two!
I can't do this with someone, either!
Honestly, they're always
trying to make us socialize.
Well, fitting in with society can suck it.
I know... I can be a hermit when I grow up.
I mean, friends would be nice, but...
Hey, girl who wants friends.
Wanna make money from some leaves?
Thugbelina!
Leaves?
Leaves.
You were playing around in the grass, right?
I... uh... don't know any magic tricks,
so I wouldn't be able to...
I wasn't sure how to say no,
so I ended up going along with her.
Is this good enough?
Uh, I have some here.
Thanks.
Here.
A thousand yen?!
My mother told me never to
accept money from strangers!
I need to take the train to
sell these, so if you'll excuse me.
Train?!
I-I'll join you!
You don't have to do that.
I've never rode a train before.
Uh, well...
So why haven't you?
I'm bad with crowds.
And I wanted to be with a friend when I did.
Please stop hiding behind me.
Besides, I'm not exactly your friend, am I?
But what about in PE?
The idea that all children
can potentially be friends
is magical thinking on
the part of the educators.
Our interests simply coincided at the time,
since we had no one else.
So friendship is magical?
That said... we'll probably be
coexisting at school for the time being,
so there's bound to be a bit of give-and-take.
Coexistence?
I'll be going now.
Wait!
I'll carry this for you.
I'll be joining you, and you
won't have to carry the bag!
It's coexistence!
What's with her?
Wow!
I didn't know trains were this amazing.
What are you doing?
Um, making blueprints.
Has a propeller affixed for acceleration,
which is under evolution evaluation
Rack Railway
Able to reach an equilibrium speed
of 112km/h on a 1000% incline!
A propeller-equipped train created
in the 1930s by the German National Railway!
The Ethereal Monorail Soars!
Something sounds (good) about
a train that flies through the sky
Black Hole
Engine
Catalog Spec:
Total Length: 25.675m
Total Width: 3.362m
Overall height: 4.8m
Maximum operational weight: 52.2 tons
Maximum speed 22.6 km/h
(Maximum output: 66,000 horsepower)
In the spirit of the Asia Express
Ta-dah! The use of "ethereal" refers to
how it flies gracefully through the air!
Rail Connector Unit
Connector Unit
Spherical Car
Conductor controls the orientation
Car travels while staying horizontal
You can bring your bicycle aboard, too.
And the train itself is
a propeller-equipped model, like the
Mole
Travels along something similar to a ropeway!!
German National Railway made!
With super-strong connectors!
Connection is very strong
Train car
Hypothetically, there may even be
a hanging, armored monorail car!
Can be affixed in a variety of positions as necessary thanks to articulation
The connection to the rail can be
adjusted for a variety of angles!
Hello again.
Thank you so much!
What're they for?
We serve grilled fish on them.
The aroma is great, and they
look wonderful, too.
Thank you.
So when did you become friends with Kanamori?
Kanamori's not my friend.
Then are we...
We're not friends, we're comrades!
Comrades, huh?
Lady Kanamori, you're sick?
She is?
You need anything?
Milk.
Thank you.
Oh, could you get my phone, please?
Hey there, sicko! We're here to check up on you.
You don't have to get up!
Here's some milk.
Sunny Day
Milk
Thanks.
You seem weak as a kitten.
It seems I'm only human after all.
I can even take candid shots,
and you can't throttle me!
Oh, right, Kanamori...
Look here.
Reminder
Absolutely no funds are to be
acquired from outside of school
Vice Principal
This was posted on the door to our club room.
And the art club said—
It won't be a problem.
Top Page
Share Article  Post Article  Contact Us
[Tsubame Mizusaki] Local renewal via anime?
The super-popular high school model's
new challenge!
School festival's anime becomes the talk of town
We're in the news.
"Tsubame Mizusaki produces an anime as part of her club activities at Shibahama High School"
"Robot anime from school festival gets praise"
"Turning the acting talent she inherited from her parents towards anime"
Source: A surprising side to Tsubame Mizusaki? Entertainment News
"All eyes on Shibahama High School's festival! This robot anime created by students is amazing!"
"An anime by the famous model Tsubame Mizusaki?!"
"The next project is a set in the town of Shibahama itself!"
Source: Shibahama High School Festival a Huge Success! Shibahama Hot News
• Even the internet's talking about it! A look at the anime made by high school students!
Seems like a big deal...
High school model Tsubame Mizusaki
produces an anime set in Shibahama!
When will it premiere? And where?
• External Link Special Report: "Tsubame Mizusaki's New Venture" Teen's News
What the heck?!
The press has started promoting us now.
Why?
"The school is allowing
students to participate in a"
"local revitalization effort in order
to teach them about business,"
New Cat Mom @nyan_mam
It's so nice for a school to help out locally
Kappanosuke @Cucumbeeeeeee
Think Shiba High is now my first choice for a school
"a locally-oriented educational
program that's earning"
"Shibahama High praise from all around."
Well,
the school's position is...
About producing
pamphlets for Shibahama High School—
The eizouken's?
After watching the
anime screening?
Hello
You read an
article about the eizouken?
Really interested in the eizouken's
activities...
Filming for a
local TV program?
Hello
The school has no choice but
to let us move forward at this point.
Goodness gracious, that sure is something.
So we can finish the short?
Speaking of, is it done? The concept
for the enemy, and the story?
You bet your butt!
Es perfecto!
Ta-dah!
An enemy UFO is shot down and crash-lands.
There's a silhouette inside the cockpit....
The enemy is a kappa!
They didn't come from space, but nearby!
But through a quirk of fate,
they learn about their history
as a result of the crash-landing.
As water levels began to rise,
the remaining cities were
built higher and higher,
but those forced to live in
the water eventually found
their bodies adapting to their new way of life.
The Atlantis Alliance!
A race from below the waves!
Gills
For a while, they communicated
with their distant brethren with a
device that worked like a prayer wheel,
but in time the tradition
faded and was forgotten,
leading to ignorance that
bred fear, and then enmity...
with both sides arming themselves.
That's how land reclamation
turned into an invasion.
A war waged because of a forgotten kinship...
Conflict born from focusing
only on one's own conditions.
A battle rooted in a lack
of concern for each other.
"The humans we were so afraid of..."
"They're not different
from us kappas after all!"
He realizes what they have in common.
And at the same time, a human
enemy has a similar revelation.
Wait, new material?
W-We can manage it by altering
the footage of the kappa POW,
so it won't be as much work as it sounds like!
He hears the chime of the
harmonious prayer bell...
Things play out the same way.
And the human has the same realization:
"The enemy isn't something dreadful,
but the same as us."
The entire conflict spins
out of the deterioration
and disrepair of a system for interchange!
It's war!
Zoom  Screech  Pow
Then they both take action.
To repair the signaling device
that allows for communication
with the other side,
and restore trust in each other...
Prayer bell
is now buried
in dirt
And to end the war!
Prayer bell
is now buried
in dirt
This time the light crosses by
up close in front of the screen
The POWs don't betray their own kind,
but become mediators seeking to
reconcile with their lost kin!
And then...
Ripples
Land
Hearing the sound, all parties involved
learn the truth about each other.
They come to an understanding,
and the fighting stops.
The theme of this work...
is coexistence.
Coexistence
Values are shaped by surroundings.
It's only natural that there'd be
different ways of looking at things.
A mutually beneficial relationship
of give-and-take...
And the grand finale is a
dance party with the kappas!
Dance party with kappas and people begins!
Kappas?
But I was drawing people in the rough drafts.
They're basically the same shape as humans!
You just need to add a little bowl
to the top of their heads.
Well, I guess that shouldn't be too hard.
11:30?!
Are the two of you trying
to commit sabotage?!
Get back to work, damn it!
Film
Emergency Containment Tank
A piece with a calm, sensible tone
Stillness
For use on c001-012, even-handed and steady sounding,
with sparse arrangement
Sign • Premonition
For use on c025-033, arrangement is gradually starting to become more lively
Tension
For use with c050-070, brings to mind tensely played string instruments
Intensifying
For use with c090-126, Steadily starts to intensify,
coming on more strongly, and thrillingly
Understanding
For use on c135-c163. On the sparse side re: arrangement,
with a gentle, intimate sound
Battle Pattern 1
Shibahama comes under attack. Lots of low tones
Battle Pattern 2
UFO vs Steam Tanks. Starting to sound more heated
Battle Pattern 3
Fast-paced, the most exciting piece
Dance Scene
Music like you'd hear at an elegant ball
A bright, fun-sounding piece
Tsubame Mizusaki &
the Eizouken @ C-lobCOMETA
Shibahama High                            Following                       Followers
Kappa Soldier 1
Okay, it's done!
Impressive.
There are so many...
'Cuz I added more!
Film
Finished with time to spare!
Are we awesome or what?
What are you talking about?
The goal is producing a bunch of DVDs
this time, so we're cutting it close again.
Flower petals scattering.
Animated shot tracking back from the camera.
32 people shake hands,
each stepping back afterwards.
Something wrong, Doumeki?
I'm gonna play something.
Film
The Film Research Group
What the heck is this?
What's this music?!
Is this really the track?
I think so.
And this is the only track we've got?
It's nothing like the demo!
It doesn't match at all!
Illustration by: