Once again, we're wrapping up
at the very last second.
I'm glad we made it in time, though!
Excuse me?
Not being able to record the voice-overs
means we didn't make it in time.
True...
We'll have to do the dubbing live.
All thanks to a certain someone
and their late animation.
I can go ahead and record the performance,
but there's a lot of echo
in the auditorium...
I don't know if it'll be good
enough to use on the DVDs.
I'm still worried about how Onocchy's
reads are gonna turn out.
I'll go ahead and run it.
What do you think, Asakusa?
You haven't balanced it yet, right?
Right. As it stands, only the timing is done.
Although I was making adjustments
while it was playing...
About the music in cut 6...
Does it seem out of sync to you?
Probably because the action
on screen doesn't happen
until after the music peaks.
We could try delaying it.
You mean offsetting it even
more from the action?
Wouldn't that mess with the big hit?
Let's see.
I'm not sure why, but I think that's better!
The music is setting the tone before
the action, and leading the audience along!
There were a few spots where the music
and the action didn't have the right tone,
where I was thinking we
could use different tracks.
For cut 150 and 82...
If we use the music from cut 24,
we can create a motif linking
the different scenes.
What do you think?
Sounds like it might work. Let me try it.
Something about the music for
cut 86 doesn't sit right with me.
What if we dropped
the music for that part?
You mean to put an emphasis
on the sound effects from 79?
The animation is amazing for that part.
So by subtracting the music...
So cool!
That makes the scene really stand out!
You're some kind of music master, Asakusa!
We are so sorry.
Who would've thought production
would end up canceled
because the director and screenwriter
tried to murder a producer?
Film Director Tomo Komatsu Arrested for Attempted Murder
Komatsu's arrest
On the 19th in Nishi-Azabu, Tokyo,
a movie director was arrested for
attempting to kill a movie producer.
with a katana.
Director Tomo Komatsu (45)
and screenwriter Mazda-Ford (51)
were charged with attempted murder.
Police believe that Komatsu and an accomplice attempted to slice open
the stomach of movie producer Jubei Honda (52). Mr. Honda is in
critical condition, but Mr. Komatsu denies the allegations stating he does
not recall what happened.
Mr. Komatsu and Mr. Honda were reportedly having disagreements
over finances for their newest movie.
It was supposed to be your first time
onscreen together in sixteen years, too.
It's not that big a deal, right?
Yeah. To be honest, we kind of saw this coming.
We are so sorry!
We can actually visit our daughter's
culture festival, thanks to this.
We were onscreen together sixteen years ago,
but we've never been to her cultural festival.
We haven't exactly been the most...
present of parents for her.
Being able to improvise a kettle
stand from pegs like this...
Sometimes, I do impress myself.
Well, here's to the culture
festival being a success!
Let's eat!
Unlike last time,
we're going to need to attract an
audience for today's screening.
I definitely want lots of people to watch it!
That's part of it,
but our primary objective
today is to score preorders
for the DVD release after
the screening today.
Again with the money...
And that's why we need an audience.
First, since it's summer, we'll need to
make sure our auditorium is nice and cool.
Good idea.
But I hear the HVAC club are
lackeys of the student council.
It'll be fine. I've got
what I need to negotiate.
But more important than even that...
is the involvement of the popular
amateur model Tsubame Mizusaki,
and how much we can
put her out in front of this.
Whoa! Hang on!
That makes it sounds like the anime
would be playing second fiddle
to Tsubame Mizusaki!
What're you talking about?
We're using you along with
air-conditioning to get people
to pay attention to the anime,
not the other way around. Right?
I-I guess, but...
We're going to win over the people who
came to see you with the anime's quality.
Which we can't do if they won't show up.
And if the short is good enough,
they're bound to preorder the DVD.
That's a lot of extra responsibility..
We've got a big spotlight that'll
allow us to draw plenty of attention.
We need to use that to our
advantage as much as possible.
Whether we like it or not,
if it benefits our production situation
in the long run, we need to do it.
I'm kinda worried
my parents might find out if
I draw too much attention, though.
Oh, right, if your parents find out...
Huh? Asakusa...
You're holding your chopsticks kind of weird.
You can actually grab stuff like that?!
I think I'll be our poster girl after all.
My parents found out I didn't go home today.
You didn't tell them?
If they knew I was working
on the culture festival,
they'd want to know specifics...
And they just told me... that they're coming.
Wh-What?!
But if they find out, you won't be
able to make anime anymore, Mizusaki!
Episode 8       The Grand Shibahama Festival!
Keep
Your
Hands
Off
Keep Your Hands Off Eizouken!
Are you sure about this, Mizusaki?
I don't care if they find out anymore!
My family situation can suck it!
If they're coming, then bring 'em on!
I'll give them a real eyeful!
Besides, if I can't bring in
a crowd for this screening,
we're at a dead end anyway!
Hell yeah! You'll have our
full support as backup!
For once, we're gonna
tackle things with spirit!
Spirit, spirit, spirit, go!
We've already lost the chance
to form a line, though...
It's like everyone's putting
on a spirited show.
Our electromagnetic amoeba!
Electro-
magnetic
Amoeba
Accessibility
Research Club
Pi Research Club
~The Beauty of Pi~
Pi Is Great!
Rap Club
Rakuda
I'm the best there is! No. 1 in the biz!
Shortwave Radio Research Club!
Shortwave radio tournament coming up on the East Tower roof
Oden Club
Shaved Ice Club
Hot, hot, hot! That radish is too...
Anyone want some shaved ice?
Shingeki Theater Research Club
We will be performing in Auditorium 3!!
Presented by the Robot Study Club Featuring the Eizouken
SHIBA8 VS The Pistol Crabtle
The Great Shibahama Festival!
Including an appearance by the famous model
Tsubame Mizusaki
Join us!
Something will happen
in Shibahama...
We're the eizouken! Please check us out!
Tsubame Mizusaki has worked on an anime—
Please come by!
We've got anime!
Tsubame Mizusaki will be appearing at—
Even the people who'd come to see
you won't notice us at this rate.
Thank you for your service!
Tsubame Mizusaki
The robot club?
The prep took longer than anticipated.
Tsubame Mizusaki! We're Launching a Rocket Before the Robot Anime Screening!
Hey, what's that?
What the...
Count down along with us!
Ten! Nine!
Eight! Seven! Six! Five!
Tsubame Mizusaki! We're Launching a Rocket Before the Robot Anime Screening!
Four! Three! Two! One!
Fire!
A robot anime featuring Tsubame Mizusaki
will be screening in Auditorium No. 1!
I made an anime! Come check it out!
I'll also be greeting the audience!
Wait, isn't that...
It's really her!
Tsubame Mizusaki!
She's so cute!
Dang...
Man, celebs have it easy.
I thought there was a ban on megaphones?
Three-Star
Restaurant
It's nice and cool inside! Care to join us?
So she gets away with it because she's famous?
Let's leave this to Mizusaki
and the robot club.
We need to cover the rest of the campus.
Roger!
What about twenty-two?
Is that number your idea of a joke?
Because I'm not here for comedy.
You'd better watch your mouth.
Who do you think you are?
Wait.
How about it? Twenty-one suit you better?
Eighteen.
Twenty.
Sixteen, then.
Nineteen!
I said sixteen.
You dirty, rotten...
Auditorium 1
Fight for every degree°
We've got a deal, then.
President, why?!
It's ecologically criminal!
And if the student council
finds out, we'll be in huge trouble!
You're all guilty, too!
If these pictures get out, we're done for!
Damn it! She's a monster! A devil!
Autographs will be available
at the screening!
This is a handshake-only promotion!
Head to the auditorium if you want more!
Please don't crowd together!
Proceed into school grounds.
The use of megaphones and aerial
accoutrements is forbidden!
What were you going to do if you
hit someone with that rocket?!
Mizusaki of the eizouken, you're under
arrest as the ringleader!
This is a promotion by the robot club!
The responsibility lies with us!
Everyone, head on over to
Auditorium No. 1 and shake hands with me!
Mizusaki...
Here. Kanamori gave the order.
We're all going to protect you, so don't worry.
Thank you...
Anything for the robot anime's screening.
Where's Mizusaki?
I don't know.
You're in the robot club,
but I don't see any cardboard.
There!
Mizusaki, excellent work.
Now you just need to make
it to the auditorium.
Is this gonna work?!
Keep going ahead. I'll direct you.
Anyone in a cardboard robot is on our side.
Watch out for the security club.
Get down.
Udon
Woodworking
Club
Karaage
Ramen
Head down those stairs.
Danger
Stop!
Okay. Keep going, and then head
into the hall on your left.
I've got her!
We've apprehended a robot.
Get that one, too!
We've caught a robot we believe to be Mizusaki.
We've also caught one of the Mizusaki robots.
Same here.
We've spotted a crowd of them!
We'll move to apprehend them—
We've restrained one.
Got another one here.
Should we pursue?
How many people are even in the eizouken?!
Catch them all!
You're under arrest!
Japanese Marching Band Study Group
The robot anime will
be screening in Auditorium No. 1!
The famous Tsubame
Mizusaki will be there!!
Paper robot costumes are available
to anyone who wants one!
Make it to Auditorium No. 1
in your robot cosplay,
and you'll receive some
special Tsubame merchandise!
Presented by the Robot Study Club Featuring the Eizouken
SHIBA8 VS The Pistol Crabtle
The Great Shibahama Festival!
Including an appearance by the famous model
Tsubame Mizusaki
will be there!
Something will happen
in Shibahama...
Huh, it takes place at the school?
Yes. With a few alterations, but...
Cardboard Robot Distribution
Sounds like fun!
And to think a girl like her
is making a robot anime!
I'm in!
Tsubame Mizusaki
Th-Thanks for your interest.
Bring them all in.
This is oppression by the majority—
Get those boxes off them!
They're not coming off!
Some of them might not be students.
Don't get too rough.
He's getting away! After him!
My soul, dadada! A body of iron, dadada!
An invincible body with a steel
heart fighting to the end, dadada!
Dun dun dun dun,
machines have no tears to shed!
Ono... he's powering up!
But you can see the passion
welling up inside!
We'll deal with them later!
Go, Ono!
Passion!
Boy, that takes me back.
So cool!
Robot anime screening in Auditorium No. 1!
With Tsubame Mizusaki!
Huh, an anime screening?
Let's check it out!
Sounds good.
Zip Line
Z       I       P       L         I        NE
Here he comes!
Welcome!
Switch: Super Wing!
Easy does it!
Robot anime screening featuring Tsubame Mizusaki!
What the heck?
What's his deal?
Holy moly!
Touchdown!
I'm gonna check your show out!
Good luck!
That's a big crowd!
Mission accomplished.
Where's Asakusa?
She's still passing out
fliers near the entrance.
She should be on her way back in.
Mizusaki! We need you
standing by at stage left.
I did it... I've done it!
I did it!
You're not done yet.
The show's about to start!
Presented by the Robot Study Club Featuring the Eizouken
SHIBA8 VS The Pistol Crabtle
The Great Shibahama Festival!
Including an appearance by the famous model
Tsubame Mizusaki
will be there!
Something will happen
in Shibahama...
I remember you!
Men in black!
Get back here!
Hang on a sec.
The robot club has holed up
inside Auditorium No. 1.
Should we breach?
We can't take them in if
they're inside the venue.
Nail them as soon as they set foot outside!
Oh crap! Oh crap! Oh crap!
I just handed a flier to some men
in black and Mizusaki's parents!
They're already here.
It's almost time.
The robot study club will now
begin the screening of its anime!
This should be good!
It's Tsubame Mizusaki!
Tsubame!
There she is!
We're so sorry. We tried to stop her, but...
They did?
It was my idea. I wanted to get
Tsubame's mind off of anime.
You wanted her to be an actress, remember?
I am really excited for this.
Now!
Wait, it's not—
Please enjoy!
Hey, that's really Shibahama! Cool!
Look at them eat!
Why so much crab?
Look at that...
Vibrations have been detected
in the underground pit.
A monster resembling a crab has appeared.
I repeat, a monster resembling
a crab has appeared...
Open it up... Easy does it...
Preparing Launch
Launching
Head directly to the subterranean waterway.
The target is on a slow and steady
course through the underground.
Recoil starter!
That running...
It's Tsubame.
A cooling fan is down, and the movement
software isn't coming online!
Wh-What?! Manual control?!
You remember how Tsubame's
always been good at dancing?
She'd mimic what she saw on TV.
Yeah. She used to imitate
how her grandma moved, too.
And that bit before...
She was always analyzing and
repeating things she saw.
I always thought it was brilliant.
But at some point...
She started having more fun
recreating the movements
she saw with art, rather than with her body.
I think her real talent is her eye for detail.
And even without the help of their parents...
Kids will still grow up.
There's real ingenuity to all this.
I've been on her case about
becoming an actress, but...
Tsubame is already a fine performer.
Sponsor
Robot Study Club
Tsubame!
Tsubame Mizusaki Autograph Session
Preorder your DVD now and you'll get a bonus!
Candid Photos of Animator Tsubame Mizusaki
Want!
I gotta get that bonus!
Please line up!
An invincible body and a steel heart!
You don't get in line, you don't get the bonus!
That was amazing!
Really? Thank you so much!
Thanks for coming by!
We'll take it from here.
Head out the back and grab
us some lunch, please.
Yeah! Thanks.
We've got plenty to go around.
And if you preorder now, you can get an
autographed picture of Tsubame Mizusaki!
Go ahead and put down your name and
address on the form while you're in line.
Cash only.
Yakisoba
Four, please.
That'll be 1,600 yen.
Let me get that.
Yakisoba
Hey.
Say... have you ever been
satisfied with a performance?
I haven't.
Me neither.
I see.
I realized something working on it.
That to me, life is about
working on stuff like this.
And there's nothing I can do about that, now.
I need to take this to the others!
What did you think of my animation?
Real explosions give off a different impression.
And the way they held those chopsticks...
You could've told me sooner!
I didn't find out until this morning!
But... it was some fine acting.
Just what I'd expect from a couple
of actors. You know what to look for!
Sorry about the wait!
Mizusaki!
There were a ton of preorders for the DVDs.
And we ran out of all the
pictures we had prepared.
Despite the reception, I feel like I'm
only satisfied with 20% of what we did.
Again?
It might've been more impressive
with more long shots...
And a more detailed
background during the scene
with the wall collapsing would've
added to the sense of scale—
Are you Tsubame's friends?
N-No, ma'am...
We're her comrades!
Illustration by: Shoko Takahata