This is nothing like the demo!
Are you sure it's the right file?
Yeah, the length fits perfectly.
And the title is right, too.
I'm pretty sure this is it.
Dance Scene demo                      (4 weeks ago)
Background Music TAKE 1                                                     (2 weeks ago)
M1~12 A Hot Spring in Space.mp3    (2 weeks ago)
Memo.txt                                      (2 weeks ago)
UFO Wars Sound Menu.pdf     (6 weeks ago)
To.Film Study Association
I suddenly got this vision of a hot springs sitting
amidst the cosmos, and put this together thinking
it could fit all the scenes. What do you think?
(2 weeks ago)
Memo
From.Part Shouji
Huh? What the heck?
I never noticed...
This is from two weeks ago.
Didn't you check it?
A hot spring amidst the cosmos, huh?
A piece with a calm, sensible tone
Stillness
For use on c001-012, even-handed and
steady sounding, with sparse arrangement
Sign • Premonition
For use on c025-033, arrangement is
gradually starting to become more lively
Tension
For use with c050-070, brings to mind
tensely played string instruments
Intensifying
For use with c090-126, Steadily starts to
intensify, coming on more strongly, and thrillingly.
Understanding
For use on c135-c163. On the sparse side
re: arrangement, with a gentle, intimate sound
Battle Pattern 1
Shibahama comes under attack. Lots of
low tones.
Battle Pattern 2
UFO VS Steam Tanks. Starting to sound
more heated
Battle Pattern 3
Fast-paced, the most exciting piece
Dance Scene
Music like you'd hear at an elegant ball
A bright, fun-sounding piece
Title
Summary
Demo
The track itself isn't a bad one, but...
It doesn't fit the story at all!
It's kinda the opposite. It's got a sad vibe.
Which isn't fun at all!
We can't use this!
Is there anything else?!
This is the only track that was sent?
It is.
I wonder if the idea was to compose it
using traditional film scoring.
It doesn't match the visuals at all!
Why?! Let's call them!
I dunno, I really doubt a
rewrite would be ready in time.
Is there any other music we can use?
Well, we can't use this in the dance scene!
It was done to fit the demo,
so it won't work with anything else!
What about the demo itself?
Ugh, why'd he change it out of the blue?!
Of all the... It's so...!
Well, we can't use this. I understand.
We'll have to pass on this music.
Look for some free tracks we can—
I'm telling you, there are none!
I made sure the animation matched
the exact timing and rhythm!
Well, what do we do, then?
We've dragged a lot of other people
into announcing the day of the sale.
All of our advertising and DVD
sales are targeted for Comet A.
Everything has been moving
toward that one day.
Not to mention, having Tsubame Mizusaki at the
event selling DVDs was a big part of our draw.
And there are a lot of
people who are going to be
participating at the special
screening in Shibahama, too.
No matter how the short turns out,
our participation in Comet A
is a 1,000% foregone conclusion.
Do you have any ideas, Asakusa?
We've got one hour and 32 minutes before
our arrangement with the company we
have making the DVDs for cheap is broken.
Can we stretch that out a little?
Maybe get us until the morning?
I'll try negotiating, just in case,
but don't get your hopes up.
There's something I need your help with.
Right. Do you think it's possible?
Yes, it's an emergency.
I see.
Okay, in that case, don't worry about it.
Yeah. Right.
I hope we can work together
again some time.
They could only wait as late as midnight tonight.
Any later and the delay fee
would nearly double the price.
Since we're on a tight budget,
and it probably won't be ready,
I went ahead and canceled.
It wouldn't kill them to just wait a little.
We're in big trouble here!
This is how it works.
An overnight job would mean making
extra arrangements for their staff...
And it'll affect their workload tomorrow.
This have their own business to worry about.
They don't gain anything by indulging
our trouble for fun, or out of curiosity.
If anything, they're already at a loss,
since we canceled so suddenly.
The school has protected us,
and taken our side when they've
deemed us in need of it,
but once we're outside of their jurisdiction,
the fact that we're "just students"
doesn't hold water anymore.
That being the case,
I now need to come up with a way
for us to produce these DVDs.
I'll figure it out, so don't worry.
In the meantime,
I need the rest of you to think
up a way to finish the short.
No... but it's already...
Think...
That's it! Keep thinking!
Let's adjust the whole thing to fit this score!
We'll ditch the dance scene! And make
major adjustments to the story!
Episode 12        Shibahama UFO Wars!
Keep
Your
Hands
Off
Keep Your Hands Off Eizouken!
You want to what?! After all
this time!? Is that a joke?!
What do you mean?
You get two seconds to explain.
Can't... Neck...
Oh, right.
I'm sorry, Mizusaki.
Something's actually been kinda
bothering me about the finale.
Whether it was a good idea.
We can adjust the whole
thing to suit this music,
and then, if we make a new finale,
I think it'll turn out even
better than we we have.
Adjust to the music?
We can release the dance scene as
special extra footage somewhere.
"Adjust the whole thing."
"Change the finale."
There's no way we have time to—
We can use the material we already
have for everything except the finale!
And the finale would only
be another two cuts!
So... we should be able to
finish by... morning, I think.
And the final result will something
you'd be satisfied with?
Indeed!
Right now, we have a story where two
sides with different positions start fighting,
and then a pair of prisoners from each side
realize everything they have in common,
and how a misunderstanding is
what caused the conflict.
"There's no real reason to fight."
In order to convey that message,
the duo repair, and then activate
a tool that sends a message.
The signal goes out.
A sound that reaches everywhere.
After everyone hears it, they understand
the truth in an instant,
with everyone putting down
their weapons at once,
agreeing to respect each
other's territory, de-escalate,
Coexistence
and the relationship turns friendly.
And then there's a dance party.
Camera continues to gradually pull out,
the scene repeating,
creating momentum
Dance party with
kappas and
people begins!!
But that'd never happen!
Even in times of peace, different sides
will jockey for position and benefits!
Take any respected individual.
Disrespect      School regulations
Weight loss      Social media
Recycling      Stalking
Generational differences      Poaching (cooking) & Poaching (killing)
Trash      Abusive workplaces
Cryptocurrency      Property
Aging population      Higher taxes
Accidents      Alcohol
Cancel culture      Death from overwork
Violence      Self-sufficiency
Allowances      Bias
Sexual harassment      Power harassment
"Don't rock the boat" thinking      Ransom
Gambling      Unpaid overtime
Death of the pension system      Abuse
Internet trouble      PTA
Inequality      Decay
Costs
Education      Study
Tardiness
Bullying      Talent
Camaraderie      Child rearing
Tests      Moratoriums
Grades      Contagion
Crime      Infidelity
Kidnapping      Corporal punishment
Suicide      Equality
Endurance      The working poor
Complaints      Territory
Dependence      Cram schools
One-click      E-mail
Invasive species      Panic
Mom friends      Gender
Best friends      Effort
Renovation      Extortion
Drugs      Crowded trains
Post-Olympics recession      Landslides
Lack of consideration      Freedom
Shut-ins      Board of education
Monster parents      Over-achievers
Criminal relationships      Social castes
Race      Segregation
Cyber education      Missiles
Controversy      Senior isolation
Infrastructure      Closings
Higher education      Homeless children
Water      Nationality
Criminal recidivism      Conflict
Nukes      Marathons
Student council      Future
Vacant housing      Genetic modification
Once their interests don't align
with yours, that opinion changes!
The majority of what's going
on in the world isn't peaceful!
There's no such thing as a perfect 50/50 split!
Even when you share the same ideals,
making certain distinctions
can still be hard, true.
So what happens?
The fighting doesn't stop!
But even then, the POW human
and POW kappa don't give up!
They try again!
Even if what they think is right doesn't work,
they keep thinking, and keep
doing what they believe is right!
Hey, neither of them will
be able to back down, now!
Are they both going to die?
The path they ultimately choose is...
You've got until morning.
Roger, dodger, and wilco!
Film
I'm here to deliver that
data you were asking for.
Shibahama Shopping District's
Local Celebration Anime!
On Sale at Comet A!
I've arranged for the DVDs.
You need to be done in the next
43 minutes and 30 seconds.
Roger that!
Film
So how much are you spending today?
Gonna hit a convenience store first.
You think the Katou sisters
will be there this year?
Uh, what sisters are those?
I heard there's a new anime
from Studio Kobanzame.
For real?
They updated their blog out
of nowhere this morning.
Good morning.
As of this moment, Comet A is now open.
I'll take one of those red ones.
No, the other red.
Oh, we're out of 100 yen coins...
Oh, that'd be a huge help!
Blast Past Those Borders!
Monthly Borders
Kinda feels... like we're
kind of out of place, here.
How long did it take to make this?
Eight years.
Eight...
There she is! Tsubame Mizusaki!
Traveling to
Iceland
So cute!
Hey, this is it.
Her face is so tiny!
Thank you very much!
This says it's set in Shibahama.
That'll be 1,000 yen.
Yakisoba omelets.
Thanks muchly.
Here you are.
There I am.
The cut scene that Tsubame Mizusaki
poured her heart and soul into!
Purchase a DVD and you'll be able
to see the finished version
(with sound) online in the future!
Eizouken
Love
Large-Scale Farming Machinery
Anime
Thank you very much!
I wasn't mentally ready for this.
I'm not sure where I am, or what I'm doing here.
It doesn't feel real.
All these folks, who've lived
lives totally different from mine,
who are neither friend or foe,
come here, hand cash over,
and walk away with a box, but why?
So tired. Wanna go home.
You're really cute!
Eizouken
Anime
Thank you so much!
This is a thoroughfare! Please stay in motion!
I'm hungry for some sincere criticism.
I bet that's something that'll never go away.
All right.
Time for paper bags.
Pictures
Is that Tsubame Mizusaki?
Seems pretty obvious who she is, bag or not.
And that's fine. It's all stagecraft.
The idea of "The model who makes anime"
helps strengthen Mizusaki's identity,
@kpst_066
I saw something, but I dunno if it's her or not. #TsubameMizusaki
@mooric_07
Whoa, there's someone who kinda looks like Tsubame Mizusaki at Comet A #CometA
@gmzymt
I think she's selling something, but Tsubame Mizusaki being at Comet A freaked me out... #CometA
@2000tinachu
Oh, that's cool. #CometA
@gmzymt
Apparently Tsubame Mizusaki is making an anime while in high school. Impressive. #CometA
@mtbokkuri_t2
Saw Tsubame Mizusaki at Comet A with a paper bag on her head lol #CometA
@a2k801
Huh?! That was actually Tsubame?! I should've shaked her hand.... <- #TsubameMizusaki #CometA
@chelyama
wiped out from setting up table #CometA
@ryuusis_1710
hang on!!! tsubame's at comet a!!!! she's got a paper bag and is selling an anime for some group!!! why!?!?!?!?! #CometA
@bujisawa_0827
It's unbelievable that she's a popular amateur model and an animator. I guess God gives some people two gifts. #CometA
@cs_1992_mnm
Wow someone at Comet A looks a lot like Tsubame Mizusaki! is what I thought when I passed by, but I guess that's really her. I wonder if she made something. #CometA
@asstnt_ss
I'm almost there! I hope the book I wanted is still in stock... #CometA
@kkk375
That was Tsubame Mizusaki selling something, right?! She was super cute #CometA
@yoi_0902
Tsubame made an anime? I should've gone...! #CometA
@minami47uv
why the paper bag tho #TsubameMizusaki #CometA
but if we have people speculating on why
she would go as far as to hide her identity,
just because she's making anime...
It will amplify their interest in the project.
I'd like a copy.
Me, too.
Can I get one?
I'd like a copy!
Um, I'd like a copy.
One for me.
Thank you so much!
That'll be 1,000 yen.
I'm a big fan!
Thanks!
It's 1,000 yen a piece.
I'll take one.
Thank you.
Excuse me, can I get one?
Thanks for coming by!
That'll be 1,000 yen.
This now concludes Comet A.
I still haven't sat down
and watched my own anime.
Hey, let's watch Shibahama UFO Wars at my house!
Shibahama South Building
Turning a profit from these kinds of
events is a bit of an anachronism,
but when you factor in the awareness
that this has built for us,
I think we can call this project a success.
The reactions on social
media were pretty good, too!
Come to think of it,
Doumeki just recorded some audio from
the show floor and then left, huh?
She doesn't believe in group activities
for their own sake, after all.
All right, let's get this party started!
Shibahama
Shopping
District
Film
The Film Study Association
Look Out
Danger
That was...
Agreed. The visuals and sound, both.
Kinda hard to say for sure
without Asakusa's input, but...
Even then, it's pretty easy...
...to imagine what she's going to say.
We've got more to do tomorrow,
so let's head home.
There's still a lot of room for improvement.
Animation by:     Sumito Owara