yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
too
Go
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
iku zo
Let's go!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
ieaa ieaa
Yeah, yeah
aiteru heya wo haijakku yume no ajito tsukurimasho
Let's hijack an empty room and
turn it into the hangout of our dreams
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
are mo kore mo yaritai tatami no ue wa paradaisu
I wanna do this, I wanna do that, this room's our paradise
(hai) uerukamu (hai hai hai)
(Yeah) Welcome (Yeah yeah yeah)
ocha no ko saisai suisui chacha wo irete gomen nasai
It all went too smooth and easy,
sorry, but I'm going to put on some tea
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
hangurii seishin ii jan osenbei futon kajittara
I'm feeling super hungry, I think I'll have this cracker pillow
(hai) non non
(Yeah) No, no
nayamigoto wa minai furi oshiire ni shimaimashou
Let's pretend our troubles don't exist,
shove them into the closet
asatte no hougaku muita nara
And do something completely random
hissatsu yuru yuri dondengaeshi
Take this! Yuru Yuri Non Sequitur!
kimi to iru dake de chiisana atarimae no koto demo
When I'm with you, even the smallest, simplest things
okashikute (hai hai)
Can be so funny (Yeah yeah)
nukedasenai (hai hai)
I never want to leave (Yeah yeah)
sugoku ii yo ne kono shunkan (san hai)
I love these moments so much (Ready go)
hyaku en demo tanoshimeru yo
It's fun for less than a hundred yen
nooberu shou dai hakken
A huge discovery worth a Nobel Prize
shiawase wa sugu tonari ni aru
Happiness is always right by you
saikouchou chochochocho choo
It's the best! Best-best-best-best-best!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
kochira wa gorakubu ii tokoro
This is the Amusement Club, a great place to be
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
goo
Go
The Girl Falls Into Darkness.
That should do it for today.
We finished that pretty quickly.
Excuse me!
I have plans with my family, so I'm leaving early.
Oh, really?
We're gonna have okonomiyaki!
Don't scavenge for food on the way home.
Are you making fun of me?
Anyway, I'll be off now.
Good work.
Thanks.
What's wrong, Furutani-san?
I'm troubled.
My back hip circle test is tomorrow.
You can't do back hip circles?
I talked to Sakurako about it, but...
Really? You can't do back hip circles?
Boo!
I tried talking to Akaza-san
and Yoshikawa-san, but...
You'll be fine!
Do your best!
What are you guys doing?!
You're excluding me!
It's always the same outcome.
I beg of you!
Please teach me how to do back hip circles!
I don't mind, but I'm not sure I'm the best teacher.
Even the smallest bit of advice helps!
I can't really do back hip circles either.
Can you, president?
I have an idea!
Let's ask Toshinou-san and Funami-san for help.
Huh? What?!
Your back hip circle training starts now!
Let's get practicing!
Hey! This isn't for me!
We didn't tell Akari and the others about this.
Thank you.
Oh, so they're teaching Himawari-chan
how to do back hip circles.
We shouldn't bother them. Shall we go home?
Yeah.
The trick to doing back hip circles
is to first keep your arms close to your body,
then draw the bar towards your stomach,
and finally, kick off the ground.
Like that.
That's impressive.
Woo, Yui-senpai!
Give it a try.
Okay.
Don't sweat it.
Imagine yourself kicking up
towards the top of your head.
It's no use.
Don't give up, Himacchan.
You have my support.
Your face is going a weird color.
Let's try it again.
I'll support you this time.
O-Okay.
I did it!
Just like that.
Try doing it yourself this time.
Okay!
Keep it up!
Believe in yourself!
Couldn't you help a little?
I need to try harder.
I'd be letting my seniors down if I give up now.
You can do it, Furutani-san.
Okay!
Kick higher!
Go, go, Himacchan!
Fight, fight, Himacchan!
One more time.
We'll now begin the back hip circle tests.
Looks like she couldn't get it.
Do you think she'll be okay?
Next up, Oomuro-san.
Right!
Here I go!
Wow! That was amazing!
We knew you could do it, Sakurako-chan.
What did you think of Sakurako-chan's gorgeous back hip circle, Himawari?
Were you watching?
She'll be up soon.
Yeah.
Next up, Furutani-san.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Hey, now.
Why do you look so gloomy?
Don't tell me you can't do back hip circles.
Hey, Sakurako-chan!
Ah, was I right?
It's those, isn't it?
Your boobs are too heavy for you to do it.
Just kidding!
I did it!
All right!
That was a beautiful back hip circle!
Hey!
Thank you. I owe that to you, Sakurako.
Good for you.
I wonder if Furutani-san did all right.
Excuse me, Toshinou Kyouko.
Classes are already—
Ouch...
I ripped it off!
Kyouko, let's go to the club room.
What's wrong?
Huh? Are classes already over?
You didn't notice?
Oh. Hey, Ayano.
Do you have student council today?
Y-Yes, I do!
I see.
Work hard.
See you tomorrow.
We don't have school tomorrow.
All righty. See you two later.
See you later.
Sure.
What should I do?
Us two?
Ayano-chan, the student council—
Chitose! How long have you been there?
Huh? I just got here.
Did something happen?
I-It's nothing.
Could you go on ahead?
STUDENT COUNCIL room
I hope you help me next time too.
No way!
That really hurt!
Ah, Ayano-chan.
You're treating me to ice cream later!
Sugiura-senpai!
Thanks to you, I was able to do it!
Really?
That's great, Furutani-san.
Thank you so much!
What's going on with Ayano-chan?
Could it be...
There's something I've always wanted to tell you.
I understand already, Ayano.
We've no need for words anymore.
Toshinou Kyouko...
That must be why she's so restless!
It makes sense!
Is there anything I can do for her?
Chitose.
What's wrong? If there's anything I can do to help, I'll be right on it!
You can tell me anything.
Thank you.
Well, the truth is...
I...
need to turn myself in.
What?
Are you missing something today?
Huh?
Now that you mention it...
I wonder what could be missing?
Huh.
Her head!
How rude.
You shocked me there!
So you accidentally took her ribbon off.
This is no laughing matter!
What should I do?
Toshinou-san might be looking for that as we speak,
so let's go and return it.
But I plucked her ribbon off,
and I didn't even apologize straight away.
What if she hates me now?
Is the person you love really the kind of person who'd hate someone for something like this?
Be confident.
Thank you, Chitose.
You're right! It's gone!
Not ribbon number four!
This is the fourth one you've lost?
I didn't notice.
Me neither.
Hello.
Hey, what's up?
Toshinou Kyouko...
Um, here.
Hey! It's ribbon number four!
Why did you have it?
The truth is...
Ah, so that's what happened.
I'm really sorry.
Don't worry about it.
You didn't hurt yourself
when you tripped, did you?
No.
That's good.
Since you're here, help yourself to some snacks.
Chinatsu-chan, do we have anything else?
There are cookies in there.
Roger that.
Whoopies...
Akari!
Yesterday sure was a crazy day.
You can say that again.
I never expected it to end like that.
Me neither. I was surprised.
And Toshinou-san doesn't hate you, after all.
Oh, please, Chitose...
Don't make fun of me.
No need to be embarrassed.
Chitose, which one do you prefer?
Hm, let's see...
I think I like this one.
Why?
I thought that's what Toshinou-san would say.
What?!
Why are you bringing up Toshinou Kyouko?!
You should put on some new clothes and go out with Toshinou-san.
Are those clothes new, by any chance?
Did you buy them just for today's date?
Sheesh. Don't make me say it.
You look great in them!
They're very nice.
Toshinou Kyouko...
Ah, yes...
Hey, Chitose!
Oh, Chitose...
But this certainly is cute.
Thanks, Chitose.
No problem.
I'd like this, please.
Just this one?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm not very good at picking clothes for myself,
so I don't know what to get.
I know what you mean.
I always end up picking the same kinds of clothes.
You too?
I have an idea!
To thank you for earlier, I'll pick something that will look good on you now.
Really?
You sure?
Of course!
I've never had someone pick
clothes out for me before.
Is it hard?
I wouldn't say that.
It's just that picking out
cute clothes for you is so fun!
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Are you bored?
Not at all.
Then give me another minute.
Ayano-chan seems so lively.
Hey, look at this.
How about this?
What a wonderful dress.
But do you think it'll look good on me?
Isn't it too cute?
It'll look great!
Try it on!
O-Okay.
Are you finished changing?
Ayano-chan...
Are you finished?
Let me see!
You look great!
It's amazing, Chitose. You look so cute!
Really? Don't you think I look weird?
No, you look nice!
Ayano-chan chose this dress for me.
Sorry for getting so excited.
If you don't like it,
we can pick something else.
No, I'll get it.
Thanks, Ayano-chan!
Oh? You two are here?
Toshinou Kyouko!
Wow, Chitose seems different from usual.
Oh, yeah! You look cute.
Really? Thanks.
Ayano-chan picked this out for me.
Did she? It looks good.
Ayano, Ayano!
I bet this would look good on you.
Huh?!
Look! It even has a ribbon!
You don't have to tell me.
I already bought one.
Chitose picked the same thing
out for me just earlier.
Huh?
You mean you chose for each other?
That sounds nice.
Hey, Yui.
Pick me something you think
would look good on me.
Stupid
She likes it?!
Way to go, Yui. You've got good fashion sense.
I know, right?
Ayano and Chitose were both so cute.
Stupid
Okay, let's do our homework now.
If I had money and a big house
and fame and power,
I could buy lots of cute clothes for everybody.
Then you better study hard to become someone important.
Someday I'll make you wear
lots of sexy, cute outfits, Yui.
Yeah, yeah. I look forward to it.
I don't get it.
I want to give up.
Hey, it hasn't even been five minutes.
What don't you know?
What's on the test.
You don't even know that?!
Sheesh!
Jeez...
Welcome.
Just one?
Two more are coming later.
You can take a seat here.
Let me know once you're ready to order.
Okay.
Math Drills
for the 2nd Grader
What a smart kid.
Not you.
I'll be right there.
I'd like pancakes, please.
Coming right up.
She's getting pancakes.
Doesn't that sound good?
Order some yourself, then.
Good idea!
How can I help you?
One hamburg steak, please.
What happened to pancakes?!
You used to study hard, Kyouko.
Yeah. I wonder how I turned out like this.
Why are you acting like it's not your problem?
Thank you for waiting.
Here are your pancakes.
Enjoy.
Thanks for the food.
Well-mannered too.
Aw, shucks.
Again, not talking about you.
Thanks for waiting.
Nadeshiko-oneechan.
Wait, where's...
She probably forgot.
Well, that's nothing new.
Is that her older sister?
She's really pretty.
She might be my doppelgänger!
I'm going to die!
No way in hell, so don't worry about that.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your beef hamburg steak.
Satisfied?
Yeah.
That's...
A fellow fan?
That girl's staring at me.
And...
"I am stupid"?
Stupid
What's wrong?
Oh.
The magazine that girl's reading
has Mirakurun in it.
I wonder if she likes it.
Uh-huh...
What are you doing?!
I thought that if she's a fan,
she'll respond to the Mirakurun pose.
If you're a fan then behave properly!
Aw.
Giga, giga, giga.
You're being embarrassing! Cut it out!
Excuse me, but do you like that magazine?
What?
Oh, well, this edition has a spin-off of a
comic I like, so I just got it this one time.
Aw, so it's not Mirakurun you're into.
Kyouko!
Sorry for bothering you.
I'm a fan of the Mirakurun comic in that magazine.
I just thought you might be too.
Ah, so that's why you were looking over here.
By the way, earlier my friend was saying,
"Hey, check out that chick next to us.
She's totally hot."
You should've heard her.
I didn't say it like that!
And about you, she was saying,
"She looks pretty smart. I could so be into that!"
That's what she said.
What are you talking about?!
Are you trying to be comedians?
Oh, you can tell?
That's news to me!
Wait, you aren't? But normal people
don't wear T-shirts like that.
Oh, you can even read English?
That's amazing.
But "stupid" isn't written in English.
Do you go to Nanamori Middle School?
Studying for exams?
Yes.
No.
We're meeting to discuss our duo name.
We're studying for exams.
How much more embarrassing do you have to be?
Being a comedian wouldn't be so bad, you know.
Ah, middle school problems bring back memories.
You made an error here.
Huh?
Your work is correct up until here.
But there's a calculation error here.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
If there's anything else
you need help with, just ask.
Are you sure?
In that case, I could use some help on this.
Let me see.
Oh, do you mind if I sit here?
Not at all.
Okay. I'll help you study.
Yep. I have nothing to teach you.
Gee, thanks.
I got it!
Thanks for the help.
Class alone didn't help me
understand this very well.
No worries. It's no big deal.
Is there anything you don't understand?
What'll be on the test, I suppose.
Seriously?
You should really find out soon.
But once I know what's on it,
I'll have to study for it.
You should!
Kyouko.
Stop bothering them. Let's keep studying.
Aw.
Ah, here you are!
Thanks for waiting!
Hey, Sakucchan.
Oh? It's the seniors!
Hi.
Sorry, Hanako.
Your big sister totally forgot we were meeting.
We figured that might be it.
Sure did.
Big sister?
So, then...
These two are my older and younger sisters.
Surprised?
Yeah, very.
Temperature has no upper limit,
so why does it have a lower limit?
Unlike me, they're not too sharp.
Toshinou-senpai, that's an awesome T-shirt!
Yeah, I guess so.
If you like it, let's go out together sometime and get you one.
Really?
All right!
We'll be matching!
T-shirts with English on them are cool!
Sakurako.
You're bothering people. Be quiet.
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
seishun hajimeyou (wan tsuu san hai)
Let's get started with youth (one, two, three, go)
hitomazu hashiru zo (wan tsuu san hai)
First up, let's get running (one, two, three, go)
minna ga egao de (wan tsuu san hai)
Everyone's smiling bright (one, two, three, go)
kore ga seishun da (wan tsuu san hai)
Now this is youth (one, two, three, go)
haru sakuramochi wo tabeyou
Spring! We'll eat sakuramochi
natsu kakigoori de kimari
Summer! Gotta have shaved ice
aki yakiimo wo hoobari
Fall! Stuff your cheeks with sweet potatoes
fuyu yuki de mata kakigoori
Winter! Shaved ice again with the snow
mou iccho
One more time!
haru kyoushitsu wo machigaete
Spring! Going to the wrong classroom
natsu shukudai wo wasurete
Summer! Forgetting my homework
aki marason de biriketsu
Fall! Finishing last in the marathon
fuyu kotatsu ni chouki taizai
Winter! Staying late in the kotatsu
ichinen sanbyaku rokujuugo nichi
All year long, three-hundred sixty-five days
tokidoki sanbyaku rokujuuroku nichi
And sometimes three-hundred sixty-six days
iroiro aru kedo zenryoku zenkai
There's a lot to do, but we've gotta go all out, all in
zenshin zenrei tanoshimou yo
And enjoy youth with all our souls
yoo yoyoyoyo
Yo yo-yo-yo-yo!
enjoi enjoi jojojojojoi
Enjoy, enjoy, jo-jo-jo-jo-joy!
acchuuma seishun (oorai)
Youth blows by in a flash (all right)
mabushii yo seishun (ooesu)
Youth is bright and beautiful (oh yes)
nemuke sayonara kokoro no hitomi wo bacchiri akeyou
Wave away sleep, keep the eyes of your heart wide open
acchuuma seishun (donmai)
Youth blows by in a flash (don't mind)
mou supiido seishun (faito)
Youth runs like a beast (fight)
mabataki shiteccha oishii tokoro minogashichau yo
Blink for a second, and you'll miss the best parts
chuui
Careful!
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
YuruYuriCrossReview
Stupid
"STUPID" T-shirt
Size: Medium
Material: 100% Cotton
Price: 3,000 yen (inc. tax)
Yuru Yuri Cross Review!
Toshinou Kyouko likes these kinds of clothes, doesn't she?
YuruYuriCrossReview
Stupid
"STUPID" T-shirt
Size: Medium
Material: 100% Cotton
Price: 3,000 yen (inc. tax)
YuruYuriCrossReview
Size: Medium
Material: 100% Cotton
Price: 3,000 yen (inc. tax)
What?! They have shirts like this?!
I don't know much about fashion, but
I guess people call this fashionable.
Boy, I learned a lot today.
It's pretty cool. I bet an
actual idiot would be
hesitant to wear it.
Only those who are willing to be clowns
for other people's amusement could.
It's a sophisticated shirt.
Well, it's perfect for Kyouko-senpai,
isn't it?
I might have given it four more points
if Yui-senpai had worn it, but Yui-senpai
wouldn't even wear a shirt like this even
by accident!
She'd wear something more gorgeous
<4indentation>and princely.
<4indentation>Honestly, this isn't cool.
<4indentation>The way the wearer
<4indentation>seems to be declaring
that they aren't stupid is just pathetic.
I would've given it a 6, but it lost 2
points because the smug face Kyouko
makes when she wears it annoys me.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Size: Medium
Material: 100% Cotton
Price: 3,000 yen (inc. tax)
"STUPID" T-shirt
What?! They have shirts like this?!
I don't know much about fashion, but
I guess people call this fashionable.
Boy, I learned a lot today.
It's pretty cool. I bet an
actual idiot would be
hesitant to wear it.
Only those who are willing to be clowns
for other people's amusement could.
It's a sophisticated shirt.
Well, it's perfect for Kyouko-senpai,
isn't it?
I might have given it four more points
if Yui-senpai had worn it, but Yui-senpai
wouldn't even wear a shirt like this even
by accident!
She'd wear something more gorgeous
<4indentation>and princely.
<4indentation>Honestly, this isn't cool.
<4indentation>The way the wearer
<4indentation>seems to be declaring
that they aren't stupid is just pathetic.
I would've given it a 6, but it lost 2
points because the smug face Kyouko
makes when she wears it annoys me.
YuruYuriCrossReview
"STUPID" T-shirt
Size: Medium
Material: 100% Cotton
Price: 3,000 yen (inc. tax)
Size: Medium
Material: 100% Cotton
Price: 3,000 yen (inc. tax)
What?! They have shirts like this?!
I don't know much about fashion, but
I guess people call this fashionable.
Boy, I learned a lot today.
It's pretty cool. I bet an
actual idiot would be
hesitant to wear it.
Only those who are willing to be clowns
for other people's amusement could.
It's a sophisticated shirt.
Well, it's perfect for Kyouko-senpai,
isn't it?
I might have given it four more points
if Yui-senpai had worn it, but Yui-senpai
wouldn't even wear a shirt like this even
by accident!
She'd wear something more gorgeous
<4indentation>and princely.
<4indentation>Honestly, this isn't cool.
<4indentation>The way the wearer
<4indentation>seems to be declaring
that they aren't stupid is just pathetic.
I would've given it a 6, but it lost 2
points because the smug face Kyouko
makes when she wears it annoys me.
Stupid
YuruYuriCrossReview
"STUPID" T-shirt
Size: Medium
Material: 100% Cotton
Price: 3,000 yen (inc. tax)
What?! They have shirts like this?!
I don't know much about fashion, but
I guess people call this fashionable.
Boy, I learned a lot today.
It's pretty cool. I bet an
actual idiot would be
hesitant to wear it.
Only those who are willing to be clowns
for other people's amusement could.
It's a sophisticated shirt.
Well, it's perfect for Kyouko-senpai,
isn't it?
I might have given it four more points
if Yui-senpai had worn it, but Yui-senpai
wouldn't even wear a shirt like this even
by accident!
She'd wear something more gorgeous
<4indentation>and princely.
<4indentation>Honestly, this isn't cool.
<4indentation>The way the wearer
<4indentation>seems to be declaring
that they aren't stupid is just pathetic.
I would've given it a 6, but it lost 2
points because the smug face Kyouko
makes when she wears it annoys me.
YuruYuriCrossReview
"STUPID" T-shirt
What?! They have shirts like this?!
I don't know much about fashion, but
I guess people call this fashionable.
Boy, I learned a lot today.
It's pretty cool. I bet an
actual idiot would be
hesitant to wear it.
Only those who are willing to be clowns
for other people's amusement could.
It's a sophisticated shirt.
Well, it's perfect for Kyouko-senpai,
isn't it?
I might have given it four more points
if Yui-senpai had worn it, but Yui-senpai
wouldn't even wear a shirt like this even
by accident!
She'd wear something more gorgeous
<4indentation>and princely.
<4indentation>Honestly, this isn't cool.
<4indentation>The way the wearer
<4indentation>seems to be declaring
that they aren't stupid is just pathetic.
I would've given it a 6, but it lost 2
points because the smug face Kyouko
makes when she wears it annoys me.
YuruYuriCrossReview
"STUPID" T-shirt
What?! They have shirts like this?!
I don't know much about fashion, but
I guess people call this fashionable.
Boy, I learned a lot today.
It's pretty cool. I bet an
actual idiot would be
hesitant to wear it.
Only those who are willing to be clowns
for other people's amusement could.
It's a sophisticated shirt.
Well, it's perfect for Kyouko-senpai,
isn't it?
I might have given it four more points
if Yui-senpai had worn it, but Yui-senpai
wouldn't even wear a shirt like this even
by accident!
She'd wear something more gorgeous
<4indentation>and princely.
<4indentation>Honestly, this isn't cool.
<4indentation>The way the wearer
<4indentation>seems to be declaring
that they aren't stupid is just pathetic.
I would've given it a 6, but it lost 2
points because the smug face Kyouko
makes when she wears it annoys me.
YuruYuriCrossReview
"STUPID" T-shirt
What?! They have shirts like this?!
I don't know much about fashion, but
I guess people call this fashionable.
Boy, I learned a lot today.
It's pretty cool. I bet an
actual idiot would be
hesitant to wear it.
Only those who are willing to be clowns
for other people's amusement could.
It's a sophisticated shirt.
Well, it's perfect for Kyouko-senpai,
isn't it?
I might have given it four more points
if Yui-senpai had worn it, but Yui-senpai
wouldn't even wear a shirt like this even
by accident!
She'd wear something more gorgeous
<4indentation>and princely.
<4indentation>Honestly, this isn't cool.
<4indentation>The way the wearer
<4indentation>seems to be declaring
that they aren't stupid is just pathetic.
I would've given it a 6, but it lost 2
points because the smug face Kyouko
makes when she wears it annoys me.
What?! They have shirts like this?!
I don't know much about fashion, but
I guess people call this fashionable.
Boy, I learned a lot today.
It's pretty cool. I bet an
actual idiot would be
hesitant to wear it.
Only those who are willing to be clowns
for other people's amusement could.
It's a sophisticated shirt.
Well, it's perfect for Kyouko-senpai,
isn't it?
I might have given it four more points
if Yui-senpai had worn it, but Yui-senpai
wouldn't even wear a shirt like this even
by accident!
She'd wear something more gorgeous
<4indentation>and princely.
<4indentation>Honestly, this isn't cool.
<4indentation>The way the wearer
<4indentation>seems to be declaring
that they aren't stupid is just pathetic.
I would've given it a 6, but it lost 2
points because the smug face Kyouko
makes when she wears it annoys me.
What?! They have shirts like this?!
I don't know much about fashion, but
I guess people call this fashionable.
Boy, I learned a lot today.
It's pretty cool. I bet an
actual idiot would be
hesitant to wear it.
Only those who are willing to be clowns
for other people's amusement could.
It's a sophisticated shirt.
Well, it's perfect for Kyouko-senpai,
isn't it?
I might have given it four more points
if Yui-senpai had worn it, but Yui-senpai
wouldn't even wear a shirt like this even
by accident!
She'd wear something more gorgeous
<4indentation>and princely.
<4indentation>Honestly, this isn't cool.
<4indentation>The way the wearer
<4indentation>seems to be declaring
that they aren't stupid is just pathetic.
I would've given it a 6, but it lost 2
points because the smug face Kyouko
makes when she wears it annoys me.
"STUPID" T-shirt
What?! They have shirts like this?!
I don't know much about fashion, but
I guess people call this fashionable.
Boy, I learned a lot today.
It's pretty cool. I bet an
actual idiot would be
hesitant to wear it.
Only those who are willing to be clowns
for other people's amusement could.
It's a sophisticated shirt.
Well, it's perfect for Kyouko-senpai,
isn't it?
I might have given it four more points
if Yui-senpai had worn it, but Yui-senpai
wouldn't even wear a shirt like this even
by accident!
She'd wear something more gorgeous
<4indentation>and princely.
<4indentation>Honestly, this isn't cool.
<4indentation>The way the wearer
<4indentation>seems to be declaring
that they aren't stupid is just pathetic.
I would've given it a 6, but it lost 2
points because the smug face Kyouko
makes when she wears it annoys me.
That's great, Ayano-chan.
Huh? What's is?
Now you know another thing
that Toshinou-san likes.
What are you talking about, Chitose?!
Next episode...
"The Invisible Face is There."
Next Episode: The Invisible Face is There.
What a mysterious title.
It certainly does smell mysterious.