seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
seishun hajimeyou (wan tsuu san hai)
Let's get started with youth (one, two, three, go)
hitomazu hashiru zo (wan tsuu san hai)
First up, let's get running (one, two, three, go)
minna ga egao de (wan tsuu san hai)
Everyone's smiling bright (one, two, three, go)
kore ga seishun da (wan tsuu san hai)
Now this is youth (one, two, three, go)
haru sakuramochi wo tabeyou
Spring! We'll eat sakuramochi
natsu kakigoori de kimari
Summer! Gotta have shaved ice
aki yakiimo wo hoobari
Fall! Stuff your cheeks with sweet potatoes
fuyu yuki de mata kakigoori
Winter! Shaved ice again with the snow
mou iccho
One more time!
haru kyoushitsu wo machigaete
Spring! Going to the wrong classroom
natsu shukudai wo wasurete
Summer! Forgetting my homework
aki marason de biriketsu
Fall! Finishing last in the marathon
fuyu kotatsu ni chouki taizai
Winter! Staying late in the kotatsu
ichinen sanbyaku rokujuugo nichi
All year long, three-hundred sixty-five days
tokidoki sanbyaku rokujuuroku nichi
And sometimes three-hundred sixty-six days
iroiro aru kedo zenryoku zenkai
There's a lot to do, but we've gotta go all out, all in
zenshin zenrei tanoshimou yo
And enjoy youth with all our souls
yoo yoyoyoyo
Yo yo-yo-yo-yo!
enjoi enjoi jojojojojoi
Enjoy, enjoy, jo-jo-jo-jo-joy!
acchuuma seishun (oorai)
Youth blows by in a flash (all right)
mabushii yo seishun (ooesu)
Youth is bright and beautiful (oh yes)
nemuke sayonara kokoro no hitomi wo bacchiri akeyou
Wave away sleep, keep the eyes of your heart wide open
acchuuma seishun (donmai)
Youth blows by in a flash (don't mind)
mou supiido seishun (faito)
Youth runs like a beast (fight)
mabataki shiteccha oishii tokoro minogashichau yo
Blink for a second, and you'll miss the best parts
chuui
Careful!
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay