yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
too
Go
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
iku zo
Let's go!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
ieaa ieaa
Yeah, yeah
aiteru heya wo haijakku yume no ajito tsukurimasho
Let's hijack an empty room and
turn it into the hangout of our dreams
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
are mo kore mo yaritai tatami no ue wa paradaisu
I wanna do this, I wanna do that, this room's our paradise
(hai) uerukamu (hai hai hai)
(Yeah) Welcome (Yeah yeah yeah)
ocha no ko saisai suisui chacha wo irete gomen nasai
It all went too smooth and easy,
sorry, but I'm going to put on some tea
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
hangurii seishin ii jan osenbei futon kajittara
I'm feeling super hungry, I think I'll have this cracker pillow
(hai) non non
(Yeah) No, no
nayamigoto wa minai furi oshiire ni shimaimashou
Let's pretend our troubles don't exist,
shove them into the closet
asatte no hougaku muita nara
And do something completely random
hissatsu yuru yuri dondengaeshi
Take this! Yuru Yuri Non Sequitur!
kimi to iru dake de chiisana atarimae no koto demo
When I'm with you, even the smallest, simplest things
okashikute (hai hai)
Can be so funny (Yeah yeah)
nukedasenai (hai hai)
I never want to leave (Yeah yeah)
sugoku ii yo ne kono shunkan (san hai)
I love these moments so much (Ready go)
hyaku en demo tanoshimeru yo
It's fun for less than a hundred yen
nooberu shou dai hakken
A huge discovery worth a Nobel Prize
shiawase wa sugu tonari ni aru
Happiness is always right by you
saikouchou chochochocho choo
It's the best! Best-best-best-best-best!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
kochira wa gorakubu ii tokoro
This is the Amusement Club, a great place to be
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
goo
Go
With You, Forever
Huh? Yui-chan?
Akari.
Whose place is this?
Mari-chan's.
I came to help shovel snow.
I'll give you a hand.
You don't mind?
Nah. I was just out for a walk.
Thanks.
You can use this.
Okay.
Their yard's sure big.
I'll do my best.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I'm glad you showed up to hel—
I'm sorry, Yui-chan!
It's okay.
The snow's really heavy,
so I tried to move it with all I had.
At least it was only me you hit.
She's amazing. I'd better do my best too.
Akari!
Got you.
Th-That was a shock.
Thanks, Yui-chan.
Are you sure you're not
carrying too much at once?
I thought we'd finish quickly that way.
We still will.
You're helping me, after all.
I love you, Yui-chan.
That was cold.
Yeah.
Yui-chan!
There!
Your hands are so warm.
New Message from Chinatsu-chan
It's Chinatsu-chan.
Chinatsu-chan
Hi, Akari-chan!
What are you up to?
I'm shoveling snow with Yui-chan
at Mari-chan's house.
We've made good progress.
I'm having fun because we're working together.
Me too.
Oh? What a coincidence!
Are you shoveling snow?
I happen to have a shovel
with me, so I'll help out!
Why would you happen
to have a shovel?
You guys are so dependable.
With three of us, we'll finish in no time.
With China, you have the strength of a hundred men!
Well, I'll do my best!
Since we're all here, I'll give Kyouko a call.
Yeah, good idea.
Yui-senpai!
Oh, Mari-chan!
Um, my mom made tea for you.
It really warms you up.
Thanks, Mari-chan.
Thanks for helping out, guys.
We finished before Kyouko-senpai even got here.
Hey!
Speak of the devil.
Look! A huge snowball!
Throw that away!
Don't bring more snow into the yard!
So big!
A death mask.
Now that we're all here, let's have some fun.
Mari-chan, what do you want to do?
I want to build a snow hut!
I've never seen a real one.
Good idea.
Yay, snow huts!
Okay, let's do it!
Yeah!
It's pretty warm inside a snow hut.
It's tiny!
The rest of my body is cold, though.
Of course it is.
Okay! Let's warm up by building snowmen.
Once we're finished, I hope we can go inside and eat pork buns.
This is fun, but will all five of us fit in here?
Good question.
I guess if Mari-chan can fit in,
that'll be good enough.
Yeah!
Check this out.
It's Akari.
Sheesh! My neck isn't that long!
You really are dexterous.
Yui, want me to make you too?
No. Put that effort towards
building the snow hut instead.
I'm dead!
No, you're not.
Onee-chan, I want to climb on top.
Okay, here we go.
Hey, no fair!
I'm coming too!
Huh?
Don't you know how heavy you are?
You're so mean.
How could you bring up a young girl's weight?
Whatever. Just please fix that hole.
Akari!
Huh?
Mari-chan!
I'm dead!
I'm totally dead!
No, nobody's dead.
That was fun.
All right, Mari-chan!
This one's next!
You actually made one?!
This is taking longer than I expected.
My arms feel heavy.
Mari-chan, are you okay?
Are you cold?
Shall we go inside?
Yeah. We don't want to catch colds.
Aw!
I'm fine!
I'm going to build a snow hut!
I want to see a real snow hut!
Mari-chan.
Enough of that.
I'm freezing.
I'm going to the convenience store
to get us all pork buns.
Yay! Thanks!
Want me to go with you?
No, I'll be fine by myself.
Just wait for me.
I'm going to put Mari-chan in the bath.
You can wait in the living room.
Okay.
Yui-chan, can I use the bathroom?
I'll show you where it is.
Thanks.
Now, time to fire up the kotatsu!
Kyouko-chan, what's wrong?
Th-The kotatsu is br-br-broken.
Calm down!
So you plugged it in, and it's not getting warm?
It's so cold!
Warm me up!
O-Okay!
W-Wait a minute, Kyouko-chan.
I-I can't breathe.
Akari, you're so warm.
I was so cold that now I understand exactly how polar bears feel.
Polar bears enjoy cold places actually.
They're not like you.
I wouldn't be so sure.
What if they're just pretending to like it?
I-I'm not cold or anything.
Really?
Oh, no.
You're going to catch a cold.
Thanks.
This is relaxing.
Yeah.
This reminds me of when we were little.
Ready?
Not yet.
N-Not yet.
What should I do?
Kyouko-chan.
Over here.
Akari-chan.
She won't find us in here.
Huh? But it's dark and scary.
It's okay.
Ready?
Ready!
I'm here.
As long as we hold each other, we'll be okay.
I thought I heard voices coming from over here.
Here you are!
Found you, Akari!
You got me.
Way to go, Yui-chan.
Well, I heard you making noise.
That just leaves Kyouko.
Let's go look for her.
Yeah!
Akari-chan...
Remember that?
Hey, don't make things up.
You're denying everything?
I'm just kidding.
You were so cool back then.
Now it's everyone else who's always helping me.
You think so?
We always turn to you for help too, so we're even.
But if you're ever in trouble, you can count on me.
Kyouko-chan, you're much cooler now.
I've parted ways with my old crybaby self.
I'm so cold!
Make it stop!
What happened to having parted ways?!
But...
Well, it is cold.
I'm starting to feel sleepy.
Don't fall asleep, Akari!
Let's use some matches to warm up.
Fwoosh.
Look.
Fluffy shaved ice like cotton candy...
Uh, I'm not so sure about shaved ice right now.
But also, look. There's some delicious turkey.
Yeah.
I can see a fireplace too.
What are you two doing?
Now I see Chinatsu-chan.
Is this an illusion too?
Hey! You're both turning blue!
Is that really you, Chinatsu-chan?
We're not dreaming?
I'd better kiss you to make sure.
This pain is real!
It's definitely real!
Chinatsu-chan!
You're so warm!
Let me get in too!
You two are hopeless.
So warm...
I'm in heaven.
I'm back.
Wait, what happened here?
It's an emergency!
The cold's made them lose their minds!
Chinatsu-chan, come back!
What about the kotatsu?
The k-kotatsu is b-broken.
Huh? It shouldn't be.
This side isn't plugged in.
So warm~
I feel rejuvenated.
Nothing beats eating pork buns in a kotatsu.
Yeah.
Thanks, Chinatsu-chan.
But the snow hut...
Sorry. We'll make one another time.
I want rum raisin.
That was sudden.
I can hardly believe that came from
someone who was shaking a second ago.
We don't have any.
I'll go buy some. Do you guys want anything?
Can you get some potato chips?
You want anything, Mari-chan?
Sea urchin caramel.
Got it.
So sea urchin caramel and miso potato chips, right?
Get lightly salted ones.
I know.
Well, I'm off.
Isn't Kyouko taking too long?
The convenience store isn't far away.
Yeah.
Thanks for waiting!
The snow hut is finished!
What? Did you do it by yourself?
Your nose is running!
Snow hut?
Ta-da!
This seems ominous.
It's wearing a death mask.
Since you like sea urchin so much, Mari-chan, I call it the sea urchin hut!
That's not creative at all!
Wow...
Wow, wow!
It's a snow hut. A snow hut!
You could've told us.
Thanks.
What?
You're so cool, Kyouko-senpai.
I'm starting to change my opinion about you.
You're amazing, Kyouko-chan.
Maybe it's because I'm not used to being thanked, but I feel a chill.
That's a cold.
Good morning.
Hey, did you see the show on TV last night?
Yeah, I did.
Actually, I...
Funami-san, good morning.
Morning.
Good morning.
Toshinou Kyouko still isn't here.
She's at home with a cold.
What?! Is she all right?!
Are you sure she didn't eat
something strange off the ground?
It's just a common cold.
She said she'll get better with some rest.
I think it's because she was
playing in the snow yesterday.
I see.
But I'm still worried sick-apore Singapore.
Yeah, true.
Hand Soap
Funami-san.
Do you have a minute?
Thanks for coming.
It's okay.
I figure they already mentioned what this is about,
so how about it?
Have you given it some thought?
Hey, Kyouko.
Guess I'll bring her handouts over.
Should we buy something to take there?
Yeah, good idea.
How about flowers?
What should I do?
So far I've been dodging the issue with them.
Yui-senpai, what do you think?
Yui-senpai?
Oh, sorry.
What do you think we should bring Kyouko-senpai?
How about ice cream?
That might be good.
I do feel like eating ice cream when I'm sick.
Kyouko eats it all year round, though.
rum raisin
So good!
You seem better than I thought.
We were worried.
I still have a bit of a fever, but I should be able to go to school tomorrow.
So even you catch colds, Kyouko-senpai.
What's that supposed to mean?
Ayano was worried you might've
eaten something weird off the ground.
I didn't eat any rice crackers off the ground!
So you did.
Just kidding.
That would break all my teeth.
What kind of cracker would do that?
Actually, that might be what'll really happen.
While I had my fever, I had a prophetic dream.
Uh-huh...
So what happened?
I was passing time like I normally do,
when...
all my teeth suddenly fell out.
The inside of my mouth was empty.
I couldn't even chew rice.
I realized the importance of teeth,
and became stricken with sadness.
How truly terrifying.
Rice crackers are so scary.
Rice crackers have nothing to do with it.
But later, all my teeth grew back.
Thank goodness!
That's fine, then.
I guess it was that sense of despair you feel when you
suddenly lose something you've taken for granted.
Losing something makes you realize how important it is.
It was that kind of prophetic dream.
That's a nice way to explain it.
Hey, Yui.
Thanks for the handouts.
Sure.
Hey, listen...
Uh, well...
Ayano said she'd come by if she has time after student council.
All right!
Maybe she'll bring me pudding.
Well, then, we should get going.
Yeah.
Kyouko-chan, take care.
Make sure you wash-n'-gargle.
That's not gonna catch on.
Kyouko-chan has made a full recovery!
That's great!
You're as well as ever.
Yep!
She wouldn't stop talking during class.
By the way, yesterday I was asked to join the track and field club.
Huh?
They've been trying to recruit me for a while,
but this was the first time a teacher's asked me.
Really? That's amazing.
You are a fast runner, after all.
No, not at all.
I wish I were athletic too.
You don't come across as a fast runner,
so it wouldn't suit you.
What? Does that really matter?
So that's why you seemed off yesterday.
You could have told us.
Well, Kyouko had a fever.
So, what are you going to tell them?
I'm not sure.
What?! Don't tell me you're actually considering it!
I don't want to have less time together with you!
What?
I'd be sad too.
Wait, uh...
Why not?
What?
You should do whatever you want.
Huh? Kyouko?
I'm going home early today.
There's a Mirakurun rerun on.
Hey!
Kyouko-senpai!
Kyouko-chan!
That's not her bag!
It's a cushion!
Kyouko-chan, good morning.
Good morning.
Morning. Thanks for bringing me
my bag yesterday.
No worries. Your bag's pretty light.
Well, it is empty.
What about your study materials?
Sheesh.
Put the cushion back when we get to school.
What's gotten into you?
Aren't you taking that to the club room?
It's comfy.
You still have to do it.
Fine, I'll take it back to the club room.
But you come with—
Funami-san!
The track and field club wants to see you.
Sorry. I'll be right back.
Sorry for bothering you so early.
No, it's fine.
Can you come with us to see the teacher?
Sure.
Have you thought about joining the club?
Yeah.
The Amusement Club has always been the four of us.
I can't believe we'll lose a member now.
I...
I won't allow it!
Papa won't allow it!
Yui is my daughter!
Where is she? Where'd she go?
Huh? Kyouko?
Yui!
Where'd you get that moustache?
What happened with the track and field club?
Oh, I turned them down.
Huh?
I could never join another club now.
But I couldn't tell them about the
Amusement Club since it's not official,
so I was worried I couldn't
turn them down properly.
I'm glad I talked to Akari and Chinatsu-chan yesterday.
What are you doing?!
Hey, Kyouko! I can't breathe!
Kyouko, that's enough.
What was that for?!
That's right!
You're part of the Amusement Club!
It's not the Amusement Club
without all four of us!
Yeah, you're right.
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
Okay, let's write up some rules.
Anyone who cheats on us with another club
owes me a year's worth of rum raisin.
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
You just want to eat rum raisin.
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
Even without rules like that,
nobody's going anywhere.
seishun hajimeyou (wan tsuu san hai)
Let's get started with youth (one, two, three, go)
hitomazu hashiru zo (wan tsuu san hai)
First up, let's get running (one, two, three, go)
Yep.
minna ga egao de (wan tsuu san hai)
Everyone's smiling bright (one, two, three, go)
The Amusement Club will never die!
kore ga seishun da (wan tsuu san hai)
Now this is youth (one, two, three, go)
haru sakuramochi wo tabeyou
Spring! We'll eat sakuramochi
natsu kakigoori de kimari
Summer! Gotta have shaved ice
aki yakiimo wo hoobari
Fall! Stuff your cheeks with sweet potatoes
fuyu yuki de mata kakigoori
Winter! Shaved ice again with the snow
mou iccho
One more time!
haru kyoushitsu wo machigaete
Spring! Going to the wrong classroom
natsu shukudai wo wasurete
Summer! Forgetting my homework
aki marason de biriketsu
Fall! Finishing last in the marathon
fuyu kotatsu ni chouki taizai
Winter! Staying late in the kotatsu
ichinen sanbyaku rokujuugo nichi
All year long, three-hundred sixty-five days
tokidoki sanbyaku rokujuuroku nichi
And sometimes three-hundred sixty-six days
iroiro aru kedo zenryoku zenkai
There's a lot to do, but we've gotta go all out, all in
zenshin zenrei tanoshimou yo
And enjoy youth with all our souls
yoo yoyoyoyo
Yo yo-yo-yo-yo!
enjoi enjoi jojojojojoi
Enjoy, enjoy, jo-jo-jo-jo-joy!
acchuuma seishun (oorai)
Youth blows by in a flash (all right)
mabushii yo seishun (ooesu)
Youth is bright and beautiful (oh yes)
nemuke sayonara kokoro no hitomi wo bacchiri akeyou
Wave away sleep, keep the eyes of your heart wide open
acchuuma seishun (donmai)
Youth blows by in a flash (don't mind)
mou supiido seishun (faito)
Youth runs like a beast (fight)
mabataki shiteccha oishii tokoro minogashichau yo
Blink for a second, and you'll miss the best parts
chuui
Careful!
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
I, Kyouko-chan, have bought cream puffs for everyone.
Wow, thanks!
Did something good happen to you?
Not really.
Kyouko just did it on a whim.
By the way, Yui-senpai,
were you able to turn down the track and field club?
Yeah. Thanks to you, it was no problem.
Speaking of clubs,
there's a comic club forming at our school.
A comic club... you say?
Gulp.
Hey.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Sea Urchin Caramel
Manufacturer: Morinana Confectionery Company
Contents: 12 pieces
Energy: 38 kcal (per piece)
Ingredients: Starch syrup, sugar, condensed milk,
Ingredients: butter, eggs, soy sauce
Yuru Yuri Cross Review!
They make candy out of anything.
Though it was good.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Manufacturer: Morinana Confectionery Company
Contents: 12 pieces
Energy: 38 kcal (per piece)
Ingredients: Starch syrup, sugar, condensed milk,
Ingredients: butter, eggs, soy sauce
YuruYuriCrossReview
Manufacturer: Morinana Confectionery Company
Contents: 12 pieces
Energy: 38 kcal (per piece)
Ingredients: Starch syrup, sugar, condensed milk,
Ingredients: butter, eggs, soy sauce
They have an unusual flavor, but they
taste good.
When you eat them with friends,
they're worth an extra 2 points!
Mari-chan is really cute when she's
eating them too. That itself is
a comforting flavor.
They have a seemingly
artificial sea urchin
flavor!
Boy, these somewhat unusual candies
give me chills.
Maybe they'll make a rum raisin caramel
too. I'll try mailing them a request!
Hm, why make them sea urchin
flavored? They don't taste very good.
Mari-chan seems to love sea urchin, so
I can't say too many negative things.
Even considering Mari-chan, I can't give
these any higher than a 6!
<4indentation>Sea urchin flavored
<4indentation>caramel?
<4indentation>Honestly, the concept
confuses me, but when I ate them, I was
surprised to find they taste okay.
Mari-chan likes them. She was
disappointed they're a limited time
product.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Manufacturer: Morinana Confectionery Company
Contents: 12 pieces
Energy: 38 kcal (per piece)
Ingredients: Starch syrup, sugar, condensed milk,
Ingredients: butter, eggs, soy sauce
Sea Urchin Caramel
They have an unusual flavor, but they
taste good.
When you eat them with friends,
they're worth an extra 2 points!
Mari-chan is really cute when she's
eating them too. That itself is
a comforting flavor.
They have a seemingly
artificial sea urchin
flavor!
Boy, these somewhat unusual candies
give me chills.
Maybe they'll make a rum raisin caramel
too. I'll try mailing them a request!
Hm, why make them sea urchin
flavored? They don't taste very good.
Mari-chan seems to love sea urchin, so
I can't say too many negative things.
Even considering Mari-chan, I can't give
these any higher than a 6!
<4indentation>Sea urchin flavored
<4indentation>caramel?
<4indentation>Honestly, the concept
confuses me, but when I ate them, I was
surprised to find they taste okay.
Mari-chan likes them. She was
disappointed they're a limited time
product.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Sea Urchin Caramel
Manufacturer: Morinana Confectionery Company
Contents: 12 pieces
Energy: 38 kcal (per piece)
Ingredients: Starch syrup, sugar, condensed milk,
Ingredients: butter, eggs, soy sauce
Manufacturer: Morinana Confectionery Company
Contents: 12 pieces
Energy: 38 kcal (per piece)
Ingredients: Starch syrup, sugar, condensed milk,
Ingredients: butter, eggs, soy sauce
They have an unusual flavor, but they
taste good.
When you eat them with friends,
they're worth an extra 2 points!
Mari-chan is really cute when she's
eating them too. That itself is
a comforting flavor.
They have a seemingly
artificial sea urchin
flavor!
Boy, these somewhat unusual candies
give me chills.
Maybe they'll make a rum raisin caramel
too. I'll try mailing them a request!
Hm, why make them sea urchin
flavored? They don't taste very good.
Mari-chan seems to love sea urchin, so
I can't say too many negative things.
Even considering Mari-chan, I can't give
these any higher than a 6!
<4indentation>Sea urchin flavored
<4indentation>caramel?
<4indentation>Honestly, the concept
confuses me, but when I ate them, I was
surprised to find they taste okay.
Mari-chan likes them. She was
disappointed they're a limited time
product.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Sea Urchin Caramel
Manufacturer: Morinana Confectionery Company
Contents: 12 pieces
Energy: 38 kcal (per piece)
Ingredients: Starch syrup, sugar, condensed milk,
Ingredients: butter, eggs, soy sauce
They have an unusual flavor, but they
taste good.
When you eat them with friends,
they're worth an extra 2 points!
Mari-chan is really cute when she's
eating them too. That itself is
a comforting flavor.
They have a seemingly
artificial sea urchin
flavor!
Boy, these somewhat unusual candies
give me chills.
Maybe they'll make a rum raisin caramel
too. I'll try mailing them a request!
Hm, why make them sea urchin
flavored? They don't taste very good.
Mari-chan seems to love sea urchin, so
I can't say too many negative things.
Even considering Mari-chan, I can't give
these any higher than a 6!
<4indentation>Sea urchin flavored
<4indentation>caramel?
<4indentation>Honestly, the concept
confuses me, but when I ate them, I was
surprised to find they taste okay.
Mari-chan likes them. She was
disappointed they're a limited time
product.
Sea Urchin Caramel
Manufacturer: Morinana Confectionery Company
Contents: 12 pieces
Energy: 38 kcal (per piece)
Ingredients: Starch syrup, sugar, condensed milk,
Ingredients: butter, eggs, soy sauce
YuruYuriCrossReview
They have an unusual flavor, but they
taste good.
When you eat them with friends,
they're worth an extra 2 points!
Mari-chan is really cute when she's
eating them too. That itself is
a comforting flavor.
They have a seemingly
artificial sea urchin
flavor!
Boy, these somewhat unusual candies
give me chills.
Maybe they'll make a rum raisin caramel
too. I'll try mailing them a request!
Hm, why make them sea urchin
flavored? They don't taste very good.
Mari-chan seems to love sea urchin, so
I can't say too many negative things.
Even considering Mari-chan, I can't give
these any higher than a 6!
<4indentation>Sea urchin flavored
<4indentation>caramel?
<4indentation>Honestly, the concept
confuses me, but when I ate them, I was
surprised to find they taste okay.
Mari-chan likes them. She was
disappointed they're a limited time
product.
It's wonderful how they
always challenge themselves!
YuruYuriCrossReview
Sea Urchin Caramel
They have an unusual flavor, but they
taste good.
When you eat them with friends,
they're worth an extra 2 points!
Mari-chan is really cute when she's
eating them too. That itself is
a comforting flavor.
They have a seemingly
artificial sea urchin
flavor!
Boy, these somewhat unusual candies
give me chills.
Maybe they'll make a rum raisin caramel
too. I'll try mailing them a request!
Hm, why make them sea urchin
flavored? They don't taste very good.
Mari-chan seems to love sea urchin, so
I can't say too many negative things.
Even considering Mari-chan, I can't give
these any higher than a 6!
<4indentation>Sea urchin flavored
<4indentation>caramel?
<4indentation>Honestly, the concept
confuses me, but when I ate them, I was
surprised to find they taste okay.
Mari-chan likes them. She was
disappointed they're a limited time
product.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Sea Urchin Caramel
They have an unusual flavor, but they
taste good.
When you eat them with friends,
they're worth an extra 2 points!
Mari-chan is really cute when she's
eating them too. That itself is
a comforting flavor.
They have a seemingly
artificial sea urchin
flavor!
Boy, these somewhat unusual candies
give me chills.
Maybe they'll make a rum raisin caramel
too. I'll try mailing them a request!
Hm, why make them sea urchin
flavored? They don't taste very good.
Mari-chan seems to love sea urchin, so
I can't say too many negative things.
Even considering Mari-chan, I can't give
these any higher than a 6!
<4indentation>Sea urchin flavored
<4indentation>caramel?
<4indentation>Honestly, the concept
confuses me, but when I ate them, I was
surprised to find they taste okay.
Mari-chan likes them. She was
disappointed they're a limited time
product.
They have an unusual flavor, but they
taste good.
When you eat them with friends,
they're worth an extra 2 points!
Mari-chan is really cute when she's
eating them too. That itself is
a comforting flavor.
They have a seemingly
artificial sea urchin
flavor!
Boy, these somewhat unusual candies
give me chills.
Maybe they'll make a rum raisin caramel
too. I'll try mailing them a request!
Hm, why make them sea urchin
flavored? They don't taste very good.
Mari-chan seems to love sea urchin, so
I can't say too many negative things.
Even considering Mari-chan, I can't give
these any higher than a 6!
<4indentation>Sea urchin flavored
<4indentation>caramel?
<4indentation>Honestly, the concept
confuses me, but when I ate them, I was
surprised to find they taste okay.
Mari-chan likes them. She was
disappointed they're a limited time
product.
They have an unusual flavor, but they
taste good.
When you eat them with friends,
they're worth an extra 2 points!
Mari-chan is really cute when she's
eating them too. That itself is
a comforting flavor.
They have a seemingly
artificial sea urchin
flavor!
Boy, these somewhat unusual candies
give me chills.
Maybe they'll make a rum raisin caramel
too. I'll try mailing them a request!
Hm, why make them sea urchin
flavored? They don't taste very good.
Mari-chan seems to love sea urchin, so
I can't say too many negative things.
Even considering Mari-chan, I can't give
these any higher than a 6!
<4indentation>Sea urchin flavored
<4indentation>caramel?
<4indentation>Honestly, the concept
confuses me, but when I ate them, I was
surprised to find they taste okay.
Mari-chan likes them. She was
disappointed they're a limited time
product.
They have an unusual flavor, but they
taste good.
When you eat them with friends,
they're worth an extra 2 points!
Mari-chan is really cute when she's
eating them too. That itself is
a comforting flavor.
They have a seemingly
artificial sea urchin
flavor!
Boy, these somewhat unusual candies
give me chills.
Maybe they'll make a rum raisin caramel
too. I'll try mailing them a request!
Hm, why make them sea urchin
flavored? They don't taste very good.
Mari-chan seems to love sea urchin, so
I can't say too many negative things.
Even considering Mari-chan, I can't give
these any higher than a 6!
<4indentation>Sea urchin flavored
<4indentation>caramel?
<4indentation>Honestly, the concept
confuses me, but when I ate them, I was
surprised to find they taste okay.
Mari-chan likes them. She was
disappointed they're a limited time
product.
By the way, I hear their headquarters
isn't too far from here.
What?! Seriously?!
Next episode...
"Terrible No Matter How Much You Struggle."
I have a really bad feeling about this.
Next Episode: Terrible No Matter How Much You Struggle
Don't worry. It'll be fun!
I didn't ask for your opinion!