yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
too
Go
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
iku zo
Let's go!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
ieaa ieaa
Yeah, yeah
aiteru heya wo haijakku yume no ajito tsukurimasho
Let's hijack an empty room and
turn it into the hangout of our dreams
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
are mo kore mo yaritai tatami no ue wa paradaisu
I wanna do this, I wanna do that, this room's our paradise
(hai) uerukamu (hai hai hai)
(Yeah) Welcome (Yeah yeah yeah)
ocha no ko saisai suisui chacha wo irete gomen nasai
It all went too smooth and easy,
sorry, but I'm going to put on some tea
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
hangurii seishin ii jan osenbei futon kajittara
I'm feeling super hungry, I think I'll have this cracker pillow
(hai) non non
(Yeah) No, no
nayamigoto wa minai furi oshiire ni shimaimashou
Let's pretend our troubles don't exist,
shove them into the closet
asatte no hougaku muita nara
And do something completely random
hissatsu yuru yuri dondengaeshi
Take this! Yuru Yuri Non Sequitur!
kimi to iru dake de chiisana atarimae no koto demo
When I'm with you, even the smallest, simplest things
okashikute (hai hai)
Can be so funny (Yeah yeah)
nukedasenai (hai hai)
I never want to leave (Yeah yeah)
sugoku ii yo ne kono shunkan (san hai)
I love these moments so much (Ready go)
hyaku en demo tanoshimeru yo
It's fun for less than a hundred yen
nooberu shou dai hakken
A huge discovery worth a Nobel Prize
shiawase wa sugu tonari ni aru
Happiness is always right by you
saikouchou chochochocho choo
It's the best! Best-best-best-best-best!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
kochira wa gorakubu ii tokoro
This is the Amusement Club, a great place to be
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
goo
Go