ART room
Hey, Himawari, stop looking at me!
You're staring at me too much yourself!
I am not!
You're just a self-conscious boob monster!
today's topic
portraits of your friends
What did you call me?
Be quiet over there.
Make me look cute, okay?
You're so cute, it wouldn't look right if I didn't.
Oh, you...
This is looking good.
I'm doing pretty well too. Want to see?
Huh? Well...
You can show me when you're finished.
All right! Now to color it the best I can!
Wait, Chinatsu-san!
Nothing on my face is either of those colors!
Don't worry.
Have faith in my artistic sense.
Skin always looks better when it's silver.
Silver skin?!
Finished!
Bonk
Those breasts are ridiculous!
Don't you think that's mean?
Well, you worry that your boobs
are too big, don't you?
You should be grateful for this!
Is yours finished, Himawari?
Of course.
Look at my masterpiece!
Those breasts are ridiculous!
That's way too mean!
Please don't copy my reaction.
You worry that your breasts are underdeveloped.
You should be grateful for this!
Why, you...
Give me that!
Why should I do that?
It'll be too obvious if you
make them that different!
Give it to me so I can fix it!
Then you give me yours as well!
Hey, you two! You're making too much noise!
We're in class!
Oh, you two are both doing very well.
What?!
Both drawings are brimming with affection.
Even though you always fight,
you actually hold each other dear.
Wh-What are you talking about, Azuma-sensei?
Yes, this is no joking matter!
Come on, Sakurako.
Hurry up and fix those breasts
so they look normal.
You fix yours too!
Yoshikawa-san, you sure are incredible...
in more ways than one.
Oh, please. You're too kind, Azuma-sensei.
Here we go.
A brand new brush.
For some reason, using new notebooks and brushes make me nervous.
Oh?
This thick brush is hard to paint with.
Looking good!
What's wrong? Does your stomach hurt?
No. It's nothing.
By the way, how is that brush to paint with?
Oh, this thing?
I borrowed it.
I didn't have the right brush. Thanks.
It's the least I could do.
It feels like it's missing something.
Isn't it coming along well?
I know!
I should put a floral pattern on your skin!
I'm not sure about that!
I'm worried about what she's doing,
but I need to finish my own.
Oh, no!
I made her eyebrow super thick!
It's too thick to hide.
I know!
If I make the other one look the same,
it might balance out.
Of course that wouldn't help!
What's wrong?
Um, nothing!
Are you already finished?
Let me see.
I'm still working. It's not finished yet.
I don't mind.
W-Wait!
Give me a second!
There!
Why am I wearing a headband?
Um...
Because you always try so hard.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, it looks cute.
Gee, thanks.
You're spitting blood.
Bonk
Hey! What are you doing?!
Who cares? It's funny.
I find it embarrassing!
Well, then...
what if I fix it like this?
This tomato
is delicious!
That doesn't fix anything!
Oh, for crying out loud.
You're so careless.
Hey!
You just messed up my face, didn't you?
Um...
Show me!
Don't worry. It's still all good.
If anything, I've managed to protect your privacy.
Hey!
Everyone seems to be sneezing.
Maybe there's a cold going around.
We shouldn't let our guard down just because it's still warm out.
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
too
Go
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
iku zo
Let's go!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
ieaa ieaa
Yeah, yeah
aiteru heya wo haijakku yume no ajito tsukurimasho
Let's hijack an empty room and
turn it into the hangout of our dreams
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
are mo kore mo yaritai tatami no ue wa paradaisu
I wanna do this, I wanna do that, this room's our paradise
(hai) uerukamu (hai hai hai)
(Yeah) Welcome (Yeah yeah yeah)
ocha no ko saisai suisui chacha wo irete gomen nasai
It all went too smooth and easy,
sorry, but I'm going to put on some tea
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
hangurii seishin ii jan osenbei futon kajittara
I'm feeling super hungry, I think I'll have this cracker pillow
(hai) non non
(Yeah) No, no
nayamigoto wa minai furi oshiire ni shimaimashou
Let's pretend our troubles don't exist,
shove them into the closet
asatte no hougaku muita nara
And do something completely random
hissatsu yuru yuri dondengaeshi
Take this! Yuru Yuri Non Sequitur!
kimi to iru dake de chiisana atarimae no koto demo
When I'm with you, even the smallest, simplest things
okashikute (hai hai)
Can be so funny (Yeah yeah)
nukedasenai (hai hai)
I never want to leave (Yeah yeah)
sugoku ii yo ne kono shunkan (san hai)
I love these moments so much (Ready go)
hyaku en demo tanoshimeru yo
It's fun for less than a hundred yen
nooberu shou dai hakken
A huge discovery worth a Nobel Prize
shiawase wa sugu tonari ni aru
Happiness is always right by you
saikouchou chochochocho choo
It's the best! Best-best-best-best-best!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
kochira wa gorakubu ii tokoro
This is the Amusement Club, a great place to be
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
goo
Go
No Self-Awareness
You need to shape up.
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
Let's see...
You should be more serious and diligent all the time.
Like me, you mean.
Shut it.
Like, for example...
Nadeshiko-san.
What?!
No, no, no! As if!
Then how about like Sugiura-senpai?
Oh, right. I think I see what you mean.
You should try to be like her.
Hello.
Uh, what's the thing on your head?
And why aren't you wearing any socks?
I tried wearing tights to be more like you,
but they're so hot.
Of course they would be.
It's still summer.
Why are you copying Ayano-chan?
I advised her to shape up and
try to be more like Sugiura-senpai.
That's why I wore tights to school!
I never told you to mimic that specifically.
Not even I'd wear them at this time of year.
Well, it can't hurt to copy her in any way you can.
Maybe you'd actually start to shape up, then.
That's right!
This one is cute.
Cute and Tiny Dogs Galore!
It's fluffy.
Hey!
Kyouko-chan, Yui-chan.
Boy, it's hot.
It's not cooling down at all.
The forecast says it'll stay hot a little longer.
I like the heat, though.
Kyouko-senpai, you're always
complaining about how hot it is.
Am I?
Cute and Tiny Dogs Galore!
I want a dog.
That's quite the statement.
Lick my feet.
That's not what she meant.
Why don't you get one?
My mom told me we can't.
But I really wish I had one I could
walk, nap, and play with.
Dogs are nice, but I'm more a cat person.
Pets, huh?
I wish I had one.
But you do have one.
What? No, I don't.
You don't get it.
You're my pet?
Jeez. Don't be stupid!
Yeah.
The one who'll be Yui-senpai's pet is me.
Oh, not that I wouldn't still prefer to be your girlfriend, of course!
But being your pet is my second choice!
You're okay with that?!
In other words, if I were Chinatsu-chan's pet...
What are you talking about?
Kyouko-chan, what kind of pet would you like?
A snake would be cool.
A snake!
I saw someone on TV with snakes wrapped around them once.
Yeah.
I want to do that.
Isn't that wrapped around you wrong?!
Like this, then?
Can you breathe like that?!
This?
You need to wear something!
Done!
That's not wearing it! It's eating you!
Nice commentary.
Sheesh!
There!
You're just copying her appearance again.
There we go.
Chitose, could you bring me those forms?
Um...
Don't mind me.
Oomuro-san's like her little sister.
Sugiura-senpai seems desperate.
What?
What is it, Sugiura-senpa—
Huh?
Where'd she go?
Horses are nice too.
It'd be cool to ride to school on a horse.
It would?
You can't do that.
Horses suit Yui-senpai the most.
What?
Oh, I'd like a tiger or a lion too.
What are you, an animal tamer?
None of those are realistic.
Yui-chan, what would you like as a pet?
Tropical fish, maybe.
I don't know much about them,
but I wouldn't mind some.
That sounds nice.
I could buy a big aquarium...
...and I'd get in it!
Why would you go in it?
Well, I couldn't actually keep them, though.
Okay!
The Amusement Club should get a pet!
We'll get a dog for starters!
There's no way we could do that.
Toshinou Kyouko, where's your form?
No one would find out.
A large dog?
At least get a small one.
We still won't be able to, so it's a moot point.
Aw...
How about we have some tea?
Good idea.
We have snacks today too.
NANAMORI MIDDLE SCHOOL
I didn't know it would be so embarrassing
to have someone copy me.
I can't handle that kind of attention.
Really? Even though you're
student council vice president?
Just don't mind me!
I know.
I'll share some of my mental fortitude with you.
Here!
What'll you do if that turns her into an idiot?
What did you say?! You're just a boob monster!
See what you do.
Sugiura-senpai isn't so quick to pick fights.
Oh, right.
Um...
You shouldn't use language like that at... uh...
at...
at all, xylitol!
Oh, that pun just reminded me...
We don't have all the forms yet.
Why did that remind you?
Toshinou-san hasn't turned hers in yet.
I guess someone has to go get it, then.
Toshinou Kyouko is always so careless.
I don't have the time to be
constantly looking after her.
B-But, well, it's not like I have any reason not to.
So I guess today, I'll go and—
I know!
I'll go and get it!
Huh?
You always seem so busy,
so I'll go and get it this time.
What?!
Just sit back and relax.
I'm off!
Wait, Oomuro-san!
These are delicious.
I love these!
What are you doing?
I made a dog house.
That's amazing, Kyouko-chan!
You put way too much effort into it.
These really are the only things you're good at.
Scented
Someone get inside.
What? No way!
Get in yourself.
Aw. You're no fun.
Kyouko-chan, do you want a snack?
Yeah!
But I went through the trouble of making it.
Arf, arf!
A dog.
Shake.
What?! Why are you barking at me so much?!
Toshinou Kyouko
-senpai!
Huh? What's the matter?
It's Sakurako-chan!
Hey!
Toshinou-senpai, I came to get your form.
Wow, well done.
Here. Have some crackers as a reward.
Yay!
What's that?
Did you forget about the form again?
Our teacher mentioned it this morning.
It entered in the right ear,
and left out the right.
So it didn't even make it through your head.
Future Career Survey
But Kyouko-chan has her form
ready to hand in anytime!
It's still blank!
Fill it in already.
Aw...
Bark!
Bark, bark, bark!
Shake.
Bark!
Good girl.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Cheer up, Ayano-chan.
I have returned!
I have collected her form.
Well? Am I more like Sugiura-senpai now?
Still not quite, huh?
What else can I do to be like Sugiura-senpai?
I know! I'll eat pudding!
W-Wait, Oomuro-san!
Don't worry.
I'll split it in half like you always do.
Huh? It's empty.
Huh?
Aw...
I put a pudding in the refrigerator this morning.
Why isn't it there?
Senpai.
I thought this might happen.
Thank you! Thank you!
Now, then. What should I do next?
Sakurako, um...
I think you shaped up quite well today.
What? Really?!
Yes! So I think now...
I'd better keep it up tomorrow, then!
O-Oomuro-san, as unfortunate as it is,
I have nothing left to teach you.
Tomorrow... you should...
behave... like normal.
Thank you, Senpai!
By the way, did you learn anything today?
Um...
I need a ponytail and tights!
Nothing's changed!
Also, when I shouted "Toshinou Kyouko,"
I seemed a lot like Sugiura-senpai.
Is that so? That's nice.
Sugiura Ayano!
Toshinou Kyouko.
Toshinou Kyouko
-senpai!
Sorry. I forgot to write my name on the form.
Okay! I'll go get it right—
Unbelievable...
How careless of you to forget to write your name.
Don't be like that!
What? Hey!
G-Get away from me!
Geez!
Today was fun.
Coming!
Hey.
Geez. You came way too early.
I thought you'd be happy to see me sooner.
Yeah, yeah.
I'd say to make yourself at home,
but I see that you already have.
Wait here until Yui-senpai and the others arrive.
I'm going to buy snacks and drinks.
I'll come and help.
That's okay. You don't have to be so considerate.
You're so nice.
Get me some rum raisin!
You can be a bit more considerate than that.
Well, I'm off.
Okay!
Pow.
This sure is Chinatsu-chan's room.
What's this?
Chinatsu.
Oh, you're already here.
Yes.
That drawing...
That's Chinatsu's most recent work.
This one's cute too.
What? Y-Yeah, it sure is.
Um, are you Chinatsu-chan's sister?
Yes.
Thank you for your hospitality!
Oh, please. There's no need to kneel!
You wouldn't happen to be the cool senior
Chinatsu always talks about?
That's me.
I thought it might be.
Aw, shucks.
But you look a bit different from what I imagined.
I thought you'd be more aloof.
That was only in your imagination.
By the way, what does Chinatsu-chan say about me?
Well...
She says you're cool, dependable,
and always calm.
"She's just absolutely wonderful,"
she always says to me.
That couldn't be anyone other than me.
I knew it!
Yes, without a doubt!
I know. Would you like some tea?
I happen to have a tart.
What?! A tart...
...you say?
Here you go.
That looks yummy!
It looks rather delicious.
Thanks for the food.
Enjoy.
It's delicious.
You like it?
Yes!
Huh?
Oh, it's nothing.
As her sister, I'm happy to see that Chinatsu-chan
is blessed with wonderful seniors and friends.
I hope you'll continue to be her friend.
Of course. So do I.
But man, Yui sure is amazing.
She gets praised like crazy.
Maybe I should've tried to be a cooler senior too.
Hey, Chinatsu-chan.
Did you study hard today?
I bought a pool full of Boronamin C
for you, Chinatsu-chan.
In you go!
Kyouko-senpai, I had no idea you were so gorgeous, elegant, and dependable!
Please. You're embarrassing me.
Kyouko-senpai, you're so wonderful!
I'll try acting like that from now on.
That'll send her opinion of me through the roof.
Thanks you very much.
It was very delicious.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I'm back.
Make yourselves at home.
Pardon the intrusion.
Welcome back.
Kyouko-chan!
You all came together?
I happened to run into them.
Welcome.
Hello.
My, my, my!
You wouldn't be Akari-chan, would you?
Are you Chinatsu-chan's sister?
Nice to meet you. I'm Akaza Akari.
You're just too cute!
You look just like your sister!
So then...
you must be Kyouko-san.
Huh?
Thank you for looking after Chinatsu.
Uh, actually...
Chinatsu tells me you can be reckless,
but you're a cheerful, fun, and exhilarating senior.
Hey, Onee-chan! What are you talking about?
Oh, there's no need to be shy.
No, stop! Don't say any more!
Uh...
She was so happily telling me about you after you went camping the other day.
Onee-chan!
Thank you for everything.
I hope you'll continue spending time with her.
Um... Actually, I'm...
Yes, of course I will!
Huh?
I hope we can keep being friends,
Chinatsu-chan.
Sheesh!
Stop that! You're being annoying!
Yui-senpai, help!
Huh? What?
Oh?
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
seishun hajimeyou (wan tsuu san hai)
Let's get started with youth (one, two, three, go)
hitomazu hashiru zo (wan tsuu san hai)
First up, let's get running (one, two, three, go)
minna ga egao de (wan tsuu san hai)
Everyone's smiling bright (one, two, three, go)
kore ga seishun da (wan tsuu san hai)
Now this is youth (one, two, three, go)
haru sakuramochi wo tabeyou
Spring! We'll eat sakuramochi
natsu kakigoori de kimari
Summer! Gotta have shaved ice
aki yakiimo wo hoobari
Fall! Stuff your cheeks with sweet potatoes
fuyu yuki de mata kakigoori
Winter! Shaved ice again with the snow
mou iccho
One more time!
haru kyoushitsu wo machigaete
Spring! Going to the wrong classroom
natsu shukudai wo wasurete
Summer! Forgetting my homework
aki marason de biriketsu
Fall! Finishing last in the marathon
fuyu kotatsu ni chouki taizai
Winter! Staying late in the kotatsu
ichinen sanbyaku rokujuugo nichi
All year long, three-hundred sixty-five days
tokidoki sanbyaku rokujuuroku nichi
And sometimes three-hundred sixty-six days
iroiro aru kedo zenryoku zenkai
There's a lot to do, but we've gotta go all out, all in
zenshin zenrei tanoshimou yo
And enjoy youth with all our souls
yoo yoyoyoyo
Yo yo-yo-yo-yo!
enjoi enjoi jojojojojoi
Enjoy, enjoy, jo-jo-jo-jo-joy!
acchuuma seishun (oorai)
Youth blows by in a flash (all right)
mabushii yo seishun (ooesu)
Youth is bright and beautiful (oh yes)
nemuke sayonara kokoro no hitomi wo bacchiri akeyou
Wave away sleep, keep the eyes of your heart wide open
acchuuma seishun (donmai)
Youth blows by in a flash (don't mind)
mou supiido seishun (faito)
Youth runs like a beast (fight)
mabataki shiteccha oishii tokoro minogashichau yo
Blink for a second, and you'll miss the best parts
chuui
Careful!
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
YuruYuriCrossReview
Cardboard Dog House
Dimensions: W60 D75 H80 (cm)
Weight: 2.6kg
Material: Cardboard
Value: Priceless
Yuru Yuri Cross Review!
YuruYuriCrossReview
Cardboard Dog House
Dimensions: W60 D75 H80 (cm)
Weight: 2.6kg
Material: Cardboard
Value: Priceless
YuruYuriCrossReview
Dimensions: W60 D75 H80 (cm)
Weight: 2.6kg
Material: Cardboard
Value: Priceless
This is amazing, Kyouko-chan!
A dog could actually live in this dog
house.
You came up with the idea of keeping a
dog at the Amusement Club, but since
it's at school, we won't be able to.
That's a shame.
It's a satisfactory work,
if I do say so myself!
I'm pretty confident in
my nimble fingers. Maybe it's because
I've been drawing comics for so long.
Or is it just a natural gift? Man, it's scary
what talent I have.
It's impressive that this is handmade,
but why did you make it out of card-
board?
Cardboard products are no good if they
get wet. A dog house that you can't
keep outside is a bit...
<4indentation>It's so well-made, it's
<4indentation>hard to believe it's card-
<4indentation>board.
Kyouko really is needlessly good with
her hands. But if I praise her too much,
she'll become full of herself, so I'll give
it an eight.
Actually, she might already be full of
herself.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Dimensions: W60 D75 H80 (cm)
Weight: 2.6kg
Material: Cardboard
Value: Priceless
Cardboard Dog House
This is amazing, Kyouko-chan!
A dog could actually live in this dog
house.
You came up with the idea of keeping a
dog at the Amusement Club, but since
it's at school, we won't be able to.
That's a shame.
It's a satisfactory work,
if I do say so myself!
I'm pretty confident in
my nimble fingers. Maybe it's because
I've been drawing comics for so long.
Or is it just a natural gift? Man, it's scary
what talent I have.
It's impressive that this is handmade,
but why did you make it out of card-
board?
Cardboard products are no good if they
get wet. A dog house that you can't
keep outside is a bit...
<4indentation>It's so well-made, it's
<4indentation>hard to believe it's card-
<4indentation>board.
Kyouko really is needlessly good with
her hands. But if I praise her too much,
she'll become full of herself, so I'll give
it an eight.
Actually, she might already be full of
herself.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Cardboard Dog House
Dimensions: W60 D75 H80 (cm)
Weight: 2.6kg
Material: Cardboard
Value: Priceless
Dimensions: W60 D75 H80 (cm)
Weight: 2.6kg
Material: Cardboard
Value: Priceless
This is amazing, Kyouko-chan!
A dog could actually live in this dog
house.
You came up with the idea of keeping a
dog at the Amusement Club, but since
it's at school, we won't be able to.
That's a shame.
It's a satisfactory work,
if I do say so myself!
I'm pretty confident in
my nimble fingers. Maybe it's because
I've been drawing comics for so long.
Or is it just a natural gift? Man, it's scary
what talent I have.
It's impressive that this is handmade,
but why did you make it out of card-
board?
Cardboard products are no good if they
get wet. A dog house that you can't
keep outside is a bit...
<4indentation>It's so well-made, it's
<4indentation>hard to believe it's card-
<4indentation>board.
Kyouko really is needlessly good with
her hands. But if I praise her too much,
she'll become full of herself, so I'll give
it an eight.
Actually, she might already be full of
herself.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Cardboard Dog House
Dimensions: W60 D75 H80 (cm)
Weight: 2.6kg
Material: Cardboard
Value: Priceless
This is amazing, Kyouko-chan!
A dog could actually live in this dog
house.
You came up with the idea of keeping a
dog at the Amusement Club, but since
it's at school, we won't be able to.
That's a shame.
It's a satisfactory work,
if I do say so myself!
I'm pretty confident in
my nimble fingers. Maybe it's because
I've been drawing comics for so long.
Or is it just a natural gift? Man, it's scary
what talent I have.
It's impressive that this is handmade,
but why did you make it out of card-
board?
Cardboard products are no good if they
get wet. A dog house that you can't
keep outside is a bit...
<4indentation>It's so well-made, it's
<4indentation>hard to believe it's card-
<4indentation>board.
Kyouko really is needlessly good with
her hands. But if I praise her too much,
she'll become full of herself, so I'll give
it an eight.
Actually, she might already be full of
herself.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Cardboard Dog House
This is amazing, Kyouko-chan!
A dog could actually live in this dog
house.
You came up with the idea of keeping a
dog at the Amusement Club, but since
it's at school, we won't be able to.
That's a shame.
It's a satisfactory work,
if I do say so myself!
I'm pretty confident in
my nimble fingers. Maybe it's because
I've been drawing comics for so long.
Or is it just a natural gift? Man, it's scary
what talent I have.
It's impressive that this is handmade,
but why did you make it out of card-
board?
Cardboard products are no good if they
get wet. A dog house that you can't
keep outside is a bit...
<4indentation>It's so well-made, it's
<4indentation>hard to believe it's card-
<4indentation>board.
Kyouko really is needlessly good with
her hands. But if I praise her too much,
she'll become full of herself, so I'll give
it an eight.
Actually, she might already be full of
herself.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Cardboard Dog House
This is amazing, Kyouko-chan!
A dog could actually live in this dog
house.
You came up with the idea of keeping a
dog at the Amusement Club, but since
it's at school, we won't be able to.
That's a shame.
It's a satisfactory work,
if I do say so myself!
I'm pretty confident in
my nimble fingers. Maybe it's because
I've been drawing comics for so long.
Or is it just a natural gift? Man, it's scary
what talent I have.
It's impressive that this is handmade,
but why did you make it out of card-
board?
Cardboard products are no good if they
get wet. A dog house that you can't
keep outside is a bit...
<4indentation>It's so well-made, it's
<4indentation>hard to believe it's card-
<4indentation>board.
Kyouko really is needlessly good with
her hands. But if I praise her too much,
she'll become full of herself, so I'll give
it an eight.
Actually, she might already be full of
herself.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Cardboard Dog House
This is amazing, Kyouko-chan!
A dog could actually live in this dog
house.
You came up with the idea of keeping a
dog at the Amusement Club, but since
it's at school, we won't be able to.
That's a shame.
It's a satisfactory work,
if I do say so myself!
I'm pretty confident in
my nimble fingers. Maybe it's because
I've been drawing comics for so long.
Or is it just a natural gift? Man, it's scary
what talent I have.
It's impressive that this is handmade,
but why did you make it out of card-
board?
Cardboard products are no good if they
get wet. A dog house that you can't
keep outside is a bit...
<4indentation>It's so well-made, it's
<4indentation>hard to believe it's card-
<4indentation>board.
Kyouko really is needlessly good with
her hands. But if I praise her too much,
she'll become full of herself, so I'll give
it an eight.
Actually, she might already be full of
herself.
This is amazing, Kyouko-chan!
A dog could actually live in this dog
house.
You came up with the idea of keeping a
dog at the Amusement Club, but since
it's at school, we won't be able to.
That's a shame.
It's a satisfactory work,
if I do say so myself!
I'm pretty confident in
my nimble fingers. Maybe it's because
I've been drawing comics for so long.
Or is it just a natural gift? Man, it's scary
what talent I have.
It's impressive that this is handmade,
but why did you make it out of card-
board?
Cardboard products are no good if they
get wet. A dog house that you can't
keep outside is a bit...
<4indentation>It's so well-made, it's
<4indentation>hard to believe it's card-
<4indentation>board.
Kyouko really is needlessly good with
her hands. But if I praise her too much,
she'll become full of herself, so I'll give
it an eight.
Actually, she might already be full of
herself.
This is amazing, Kyouko-chan!
A dog could actually live in this dog
house.
You came up with the idea of keeping a
dog at the Amusement Club, but since
it's at school, we won't be able to.
That's a shame.
It's a satisfactory work,
if I do say so myself!
I'm pretty confident in
my nimble fingers. Maybe it's because
I've been drawing comics for so long.
Or is it just a natural gift? Man, it's scary
what talent I have.
It's impressive that this is handmade,
but why did you make it out of card-
board?
Cardboard products are no good if they
get wet. A dog house that you can't
keep outside is a bit...
<4indentation>It's so well-made, it's
<4indentation>hard to believe it's card-
<4indentation>board.
Kyouko really is needlessly good with
her hands. But if I praise her too much,
she'll become full of herself, so I'll give
it an eight.
Actually, she might already be full of
herself.
Cardboard Dog House
This is amazing, Kyouko-chan!
A dog could actually live in this dog
house.
You came up with the idea of keeping a
dog at the Amusement Club, but since
it's at school, we won't be able to.
That's a shame.
It's a satisfactory work,
if I do say so myself!
I'm pretty confident in
my nimble fingers. Maybe it's because
I've been drawing comics for so long.
Or is it just a natural gift? Man, it's scary
what talent I have.
It's impressive that this is handmade,
but why did you make it out of card-
board?
Cardboard products are no good if they
get wet. A dog house that you can't
keep outside is a bit...
<4indentation>It's so well-made, it's
<4indentation>hard to believe it's card-
<4indentation>board.
Kyouko really is needlessly good with
her hands. But if I praise her too much,
she'll become full of herself, so I'll give
it an eight.
Actually, she might already be full of
herself.
I think it's pretty well-made, if I do say so myself.
I admit it's impressive,
but a dog house you can't keep outside?
Chinatsu-chan, get in with me!
No!
What? So mean...
Next episode...
"The Night Will Connect Their Hearts."
Next Episode: The Night Will Connect Their Hearts.
Will I finally become one with my soul mate?