Ahem.
We will now commence with the flower viewing.
First, a word from our MC, me!
You're the MC?
Hello, everyone!
Hello.
Now on to the next act.
That was it?
Thank you, thank you.
Blooming Cherry Blossoms and a Romantic Storm
I'm Lightly Salted Akari.
And I'm Mister Sakurako.
Together, we're...
Ready, and...
Sakura Dango!
Together?
Mister?
We hope you'll at least remember our names when you leave today.
Nice, nice. This is great!
Today we're throwing a flower viewing party.
Being chosen to provide entertainment was quite the conundrum.
It sure was.
Yesterday my sister brought us sakura dumplings to snack on.
We were so caught up in writing jokes
that I mistook the buns on my head
for dumplings and ate them instead.
Oh, really?
You were supposed to retort.
Ugh, I forgot.
Um...
Oh, right. What do flower viewings
make you think of?
Tasty food and sake for me.
New Year's money and kagami mochi.
And don't forget your first
shrine visit for the year!
Don't go eating those buns!
You were supposed to say that earlier!
Just now you were supposed to say,
"those are for New Year's, not flower viewings!"
Oh, right.
What a mess.
We were better yesterday.
I forgot the whole thing after sleeping.
I suppose it was too difficult for you, Sakurako.
What was that?!
Yes, yes. Good work.
Delicious!
This is good too!
This salad's pretty nice as well.
You think so? I'm glad.
I'm so pleased you like it.
Okay, Chinatsu-chan,
I challenge you to a drinking contest.
I accept your challenge.
Ready, go!
Winner!
That was too fast.
I'll go buy us some more tea.
Want some help?
No, I'll be fine by myself.
See you later.
Come to think of it, what kind of party goods did you get?
Uh, well...
That was, you know...
We might be better off
forgetting all about those.
Yeah.
What happened to you two?
Don't be so depressed.
They might like them.
Is that them in that bag you've got?
Let's see what party goods you got!
Don't!
It'll be fine.
I'm excited.
What's in here?
Ta-da!
Sakura Afro
Perfect for
flower viewings!
Sakura Afro
Perfect for
flower viewings!
Sakura Afro
Perfect for
flower viewings!
Sakura Afro
Perfect for
flower viewings!
Sakura Afro
Perfect for
flower viewings!
Sakura Afro
Perfect for
flower viewings!
Sakura Afro
Perfect for
flower viewings!
Sakura Afro
Perfect for
flower viewings!
Sakura Afro
Perfect for
flower viewings!
We were overthinking and just lost it.
Why on earth did we buy these?
Don't worry about it. It's fine!
I'm sure we'll have fun if we put them on.
What good is there in having a third fluff on my head?
Huh? But they're nice.
Since we have them, let's try them on!
You're so fluffy!
Sheesh, Toshinou Kyouko...
Don't I look good, too?
It's nothing!
Don't mind me, Akaza-san!
I'm back.
Thank you.
Here.
I know it's spring, but you
must've been cold last night.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Thanks!
Huh? Chinatsu-chan, where did you get that?
It's cute.
It's seriously cute.
Yui-senpai!
Oh, by the way...
I made this.
What is it?
Sakurako's fortune telling, part two.
Shouldn't you have been practicing our
comedy routine instead of making that?
What's done is done.
Another fortune teller?
Wait, "district"?
Yeah, it says "district."
District? What are you talking about?
Okay, throw a rock at the board from over there.
Fine.
Good luck!
Today your luck is so-so.
Your luck is quite mediocre.
Nothing particularly good will happen.
Uh-huh...
You're up next, Chinatsu-chan.
Bad luck!
It's all over for you with luck this bad!
The world is ending! The universe will explode!
But that's not "bad luck," it's "district."
Huh?
See.
The Mobile Kanji Dictionary
English meaning: Bad Luck
Don't sweat the small stuff.
Well, whatever.
You're next, Akari-chan.
Okay!
There!
Excellent luck!
All right!
With your excellent luck, something very fortunate will happen to you.
And that something was landing on excellent luck just now!
Now you've used up all your luck for the day.
What?!
I've got the perfect thing for you, Akari-chan.
Sugiura-senpai, can you get it out?
Oh, that. Yeah, sounds like a good idea.
This is just what it was made for.
Yep!
Akaza-san, congratulations.
Star o
the D
Yay, I'm the star!
That's great, Akari.
It suits you.
I'm so happy.
Now it's my turn.
I'm going to get excellent luck and
steal the spotlight from Akari-chan.
Star of
the Day
Don't do that!
I'm sorry.
I-It's fine.
Furutani-san, it's about time we get them out.
You're right.
I'd completely forgotten.
Wow! Sake cups!
Can we use these?
Of course.
I've never used sake cups before.
Me neither.
I feel like an adult now!
Yeah! We're just like adults!
Sakurako, yours is a bowl lid.
No way!
Just kidding.
It's weird how it tastes better than usual.
Yeah. Atmosphere is important.
They're so nice and elegant.
I'm so fortunate to be surrounded
by so many grandchildren.
What are you, a grandma?
Nice.
Oh, one fell in mine too.
So this really does happen.
Yep.
Hey, lucky you!
It's not fair!
None are falling in mine!
Oh, Sakurako-chan...
That was surprising.
But at least it wasn't a spider.
Funami-san, you're as fast as ever.
I'm jealous.
Sorry, I didn't think about anyone else.
It's all right.
I didn't have time to worry
about my surroundings either.
Yui-chan!
Over here!
Thanks for waiting.
Look down there.
Oh, ducks.
What a cute little family.
There are koi over there too.
This is nice.
It's relaxing.
Just as planned.
As if.
There you are!
Sakurako-chan!
Geez... You guys all ran off.
It's your fault for dropping caterpillars on us.
The wind feels nice.
It's wonderful.
I feel like my heart is being cleansed.
Oh, your heart was dirty?
There you go again.
I feel so happy right now.
The duck got it.
What are you doing, Akari?
Hey, it stole the spotlight from you.
Typical Akari-chan.
That's for sure.
Star of
the Day
I wonder if I'll finish by morning.
Yay!
Miso
Cabbage!
Even if I do finish, I'll have to
pay for super express shipping.
I don't know what's going on,
but it sounds pretty bad.
Last week's flower viewing took too much of my time.
It was your idea.
I'm excited for the sleepover at school though.
If anything happens, we're supposed to
inform the teacher on duty immediately.
But why are we staying in our club room?
Because here... uh...
As the Amusement Club, I thought we could...
I can't remember.
I don't know what you're trying to say,
but I'll do my best to help with your pages.
Chinatsu-chan!
Could I have more tea?
You're especially thirsty today.
Chinatsu-chan!
There's something I want you to help me with.
Could you erase this for me?
Sure, no problem.
Let me know if you want any more tea.
O-Okay...
Hey.
Nishigaki-sensei!
I came to check on you.
So you're the teacher on duty?
Yeah.
It's hard getting permission to
stay overnight in your club room,
so don't cause any trouble.
I brought you these.
Thank you.
Here, Akari.
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Yay, they're lightly salted.
I love lightly salted chips!
These snacks don't explode, do they?
What are you talking about?
She has no self-awareness.
Is something the matter?
This is rough.
Should we take a break?
Okay, let's do a robot.
Huh?
It's important to change things up.
We don't have the technology or the knowledge for that.
No, no.
I'm thinking about writing a comic with a robot,
but I haven't come up with a design for it.
Oh, that's what you meant.
We can help you do the design?
What kind of robot is it?
A cool battle robot, I guess.
I wonder how we should come up with ideas.
How about we take turns
drawing one part at a time?
A collaboration.
That should reduce her influence.
Whose influence?
Okay, let's start drawing!
I'll go first.
I started with the head.
Add more on to this.
I'm counting on you.
Drawing robots is hard when it comes down to it.
How about this?
Yui-senpai, that's amazing!
They're very fitting for a robot!
The next part will be important.
Akari, you're up.
Okay.
Here.
But what should I draw?
Give it something like a nose.
Got it.
How's this?
Isn't that a nose?!
What?
Wasn't I supposed to draw a nose?
That's not like a nose!
That's exactly a nose!
What? I think it works fine.
W-Well, you're up next, Chinatsu-chan.
Okay!
The top of his head is lacking,
so why not draw something there?
Good idea.
There we go!
Hair?!
It's not a robot anymore. It's human!
What if I add this to fix it?
Kyouko-chan, that's amazing!
That's so robot-like!
Yui, your turn.
Okay.
I'll try drawing its neck.
Let's add the body next.
Akari, it's on you.
Okay.
I'm finished.
It's tiny!
I thought it would be cute.
S-Sure.
Oh, Akari-chan...
Kyouko-senpai said it's supposed to be cool, not cute.
Oh, right.
I put us back on course.
Why did you add more?!
Akari-chan's drawing is part of the neck now.
Right...
Robot parts, robot parts...
There!
Those sure do give it a robotic feel!
I'm counting on you, Yui.
I'll try not to add anything unnecessary.
I tried giving it more of a mecha feel.
Now it looks like a robot!
You're a genius!
Now let's add the arms and legs.
Akari-chan, you can do it.
Thanks. I'll do my best.
Done.
They're tiny!
You want them to look more robust?
Yeah, it's gotta look strong!
I'll draw the legs that way, then.
I made them exactly how you wanted!
Great!
How are we gonna get this back on track?
That might be difficult.
What's left?
How about giving it a weapon?
A weapon, huh?
I'll give it a try.
How's this?
It's so graphic!
I'll draw wings.
Oh, that could actually work pretty well!
You can do it, Chinatsu-chan.
Yeah!
Done!
Bug wings?!
Don't you think they look pretty good?
I... guess so.
The Amusement Club's original robot is complete!
Thanks.
Think you'll be able to use it?
Probably.
I'm so excited to see the finished product.
Akari?
Her battery ran out.
It's crazy the way she always falls asleep.
Chinatsu-chan, Chinatsu-chan.
Yes?
Could you ink this for me?
Okay.
So fast! And good!
But... who is this?
Can I go lie down too?
Yeah, sure.
Sorry for making you do so much today.
Not at all. It's fine.
Good night.
Are you okay with that?
Huh?
Wasn't there something you wanted to say?
What are you talking about?
More importantly...
We're all alone in the
middle of the night.
Don't make it sound so creepy!
What was that? An earthquake?
No, that was...
Good morning.
You could have slept a bit longer.
I woke up.
I'll help.
I'll take a break, then.
Wake me up whenever.
Sure thing.
Akari, you should change into your pajamas.
Yeah, good idea.
I can feel Akari's warmth.
Yui-chan, aren't you tired?
Will you be okay?
Yeah.
How about you?
I'm fine since I slept a little.
But wearing pajamas in our club room feels strange.
It's a little embarrassing too.
Nishigaki-sensei said it's hard to get permission to stay overnight in the club room,
so how come we could this time?
The student council got permission for us.
And lately they haven't objected to us using this room.
Come to think of it, how was
the Amusement Club formed?
Well, if I recall correctly...
What's this key for?
Let's take it to the faculty office.
No, I'm going to find out what this key unlocks!
I get the feeling I just need to!
What kind of sense of purpose is that?
Headmaster's Office
It's a match!
Tea Club
The tea club, huh?
Hey.
So this is what it's like inside.
But do we even have a tea club?
I heard it was disbanded last year.
In other words,
no one is using this club room.
Which means that starting today,
this will be our secret base.
Don't casually declare to
illegally occupy this room.
Besides, what'll you do if the teachers find out?
It'll be fine!
Somehow.
It's just a hunch?
That's basically how it went.
What did you do here
when it was just the two of you?
It wasn't much different back then.
We'd do homework, hang out,
and I'd help Kyouko with her manuscripts.
Since there were only two of us,
there were limits to what we could do.
You didn't invite any of your other friends?
We discussed that the day we formed the Amusement Club.
We decided you'd be the third member.
What?
Now that I think about it, I don't know what we'd have done if you wanted to join a different club.
What's wrong?
Sorry. I was so happy, I couldn't help myself.
I'm really glad I joined the Amusement Club.
Since Chinatsu-chan joined,
it's only been getting livelier.
I'm glad.
Yui-chan?
Sorry. I lost consciousness for a second.
You should've told me if you were tired.
You should sleep for a bit.
I'll be fine.
You'll get sick.
Yui-chan can be so stubborn sometimes.
Akari.
Want to visit the vending machines?
I'm going to get a coffee.
What? Coffee?
Do... Do you drink it black?
Why do you seem kinda excited?
What do you want?
Piccho Orange.
Want to try a sip?
Are you sure?
Thanks, Yui-chan.
It's bitter!
Looks like you're not ready for it after all.
Chinatsu-chan looks so cute in her sleep.
Yeah.
But it's a little strange when she's so quiet.
She does fly off the handle sometimes.
But that's also what makes her adorable.
Yeah, it's fun.
She can be scary sometimes, though.
Bleed line...
Screen tone fragments...
She's dreaming about her pages.
It's too bad she's asleep.
Feather brush...
Shut up.
Things are never boring with Kyouko around.
It's like every day's Sunday.
She's always pushing us around,
but even that makes good memories.
Yeah, you're right.
All right, let's get a little more work in for Kyouko.
I'll do my best.
Yes! It's done!
We finished!
That's great.
Congratulations.
I'm exhausted.
Man, the morning after finishing a manuscript is the best!
We all worked really hard on it, you know.
That's for sure.
But it was fun because we got to stay at school.
I guess this is nice every once in a while.
If you're too easy on her,
she'll get carried away,
so try not to say too much.
Kyouko.
Come on.
I'll only say this once.
You're always there for me,
Yui, Chinatsu-chan, and Akari.
You're always willing to hang out with me,
and when I'm struggling
like I was today, you help me.
The treasured moments we spend together make me so happy.
Thanks for everything.
kimi to te wo totte waraiatte
You were always by my side
donna toki mo soba ni ita ne
as we laughed hand in hand
Say something.
I practiced that, you know.
kawaru koto no nai kono kimochi ga
These never-changing feelings
Kyouko-chan!
asu wo kagayakasetekureru
will light up our future
Kyouko-senpai!
Kyouko.
I'm happy too.
Did you choose the club room just so you could say that?
You're so roundabout.
And I can't believe you practiced that.
How cute of you.
There, there.
atarimae na koto kimi to au koto
The moments we shared, how every day we meet
Kyouko-chan, your face is red.
atarimaesugite nani ka wasureteita
Sometimes we'd take them for granted and forget
tanoshii koto bakari janai kedo
There will always be bad times
kitto sonna koto ni mo sou daiji na imi ga aru
But I know everything happens for a reason
kirakira kagayaku mabushii sekai
I want to live every day to the fullest
saikou no kyou wo ikitai
in this bright and dazzling world
ichidokiri no jinsei damon ne
We've only got one life to lead
mainichi taisetsu ni shinakya
So we have to treasure every moment
kimi to te wo totte waraiatte
You were always by my side
donna toki mo soba ni ita ne
as we laughed hand in hand
kawaru koto no nai kono kimochi ga
These never-changing feelings
asu wo kagayakasetekureru
will light up our future
kimi ga kureta shiny story
Thank you for the shiny story
Huh?
You forgot to color this page in.
What? Really?
That was close.
You always scream over these things
when you notice them later.
Well, then, let's get this done with.
Wait!
Chinatsu-chan!
Wait, wait!
You all look so pale.
Is something wrong?
YuruYuriCrossReview
Manufacturer: Culb
Package weight: 60g
Energy: 345 kcal (per pack)
Main ingredients: potatoes, vegetable oil,
and salt
Lightly Salted Potato Chips
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Ready?
Yuru Yuri Cross Review!
Yay, lightly salted.
I love lightly salted chips!
Good for you, Akari.
But it's not good to eat too much of them.
Huh? It's not?
YuruYuriCrossReview
Manufacturer: Culb
Package weight: 60g
Energy: 345 kcal (per pack)
Main ingredients: potatoes, vegetable oil,
and salt
Yay, lightly salted! I love lightly salted
chips!
One time I missed the train, but then I
had lightly salted chips from my bag
and I was just so happy!
If possible, I'd like to give it a hundred
more points!
Lightly salted is great,
but I like Miso flavored
ones more!
Yui gets really mad when I eat snacks
while playing games.
"The controller will get sticky!" she says.
Using chopsticks should be fine though.
It's a tasty snack, but be careful not
to eat too much!
Especially if you're a girl in love.
The club room usually has lots of
snacks lying around though, which
might lead to a disaster if someone
is weak minded.
<4indentation>Don't you just
<4indentation>sometimes crave for
<4indentation>potato chips while
<4indentation>playing games late
<4indentation>at night?
It would be best not to eat chips at night
though. 'Cause, like... you know what
I mean.
Why must the tastier ones have more oil?
YuruYuriCrossReview
Manufacturer: Culb
Package weight: 60g
Energy: 345 kcal (per pack)
Main ingredients: potatoes, vegetable oil,
and salt
Yay, lightly salted! I love lightly salted
chips!
One time I missed the train, but then I
had lightly salted chips from my bag
and I was just so happy!
If possible, I'd like to give it a hundred
more points!
Lightly salted is great,
but I like Miso flavored
ones more!
Yui gets really mad when I eat snacks
while playing games.
"The controller will get sticky!" she says.
Using chopsticks should be fine though.
It's a tasty snack, but be careful not
to eat too much!
Especially if you're a girl in love.
The club room usually has lots of
snacks lying around though, which
might lead to a disaster if someone
is weak minded.
<4indentation>Don't you just
<4indentation>sometimes crave for
<4indentation>potato chips while
<4indentation>playing games late
<4indentation>at night?
It would be best not to eat chips at night
though. 'Cause, like... you know what
I mean.
Why must the tastier ones have more oil?
YuruYuriCrossReview
Lightly Salted Potato Chips
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Manufacturer: Culb
Package weight: 60g
Energy: 345 kcal (per pack)
Main ingredients: potatoes, vegetable oil,
and salt
Lightly Salted Potato Chips
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Yay, lightly salted! I love lightly salted
chips!
One time I missed the train, but then I
had lightly salted chips from my bag
and I was just so happy!
If possible, I'd like to give it a hundred
more points!
Lightly salted is great,
but I like Miso flavored
ones more!
Yui gets really mad when I eat snacks
while playing games.
"The controller will get sticky!" she says.
Using chopsticks should be fine though.
It's a tasty snack, but be careful not
to eat too much!
Especially if you're a girl in love.
The club room usually has lots of
snacks lying around though, which
might lead to a disaster if someone
is weak minded.
<4indentation>Don't you just
<4indentation>sometimes crave for
<4indentation>potato chips while
<4indentation>playing games late
<4indentation>at night?
It would be best not to eat chips at night
though. 'Cause, like... you know what
I mean.
Why must the tastier ones have more oil?
Well, you know, they have a lot of calories.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Lightly Salted Potato Chips
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Manufacturer: Culb
Package weight: 60g
Energy: 345 kcal (per pack)
Main ingredients: potatoes, vegetable oil,
and salt
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Yay, lightly salted! I love lightly salted
chips!
One time I missed the train, but then I
had lightly salted chips from my bag
and I was just so happy!
If possible, I'd like to give it a hundred
more points!
Lightly salted is great,
but I like Miso flavored
ones more!
Yui gets really mad when I eat snacks
while playing games.
"The controller will get sticky!" she says.
Using chopsticks should be fine though.
It's a tasty snack, but be careful not
to eat too much!
Especially if you're a girl in love.
The club room usually has lots of
snacks lying around though, which
might lead to a disaster if someone
is weak minded.
<4indentation>Don't you just
<4indentation>sometimes crave for
<4indentation>potato chips while
<4indentation>playing games late
<4indentation>at night?
It would be best not to eat chips at night
though. 'Cause, like... you know what
I mean.
Why must the tastier ones have more oil?
YuruYuriCrossReview
Lightly Salted Potato Chips
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Manufacturer: Culb
Package weight: 60g
Energy: 345 kcal (per pack)
Main ingredients: potatoes, vegetable oil,
and salt
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Lightly Salted Potato Chips
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Manufacturer: Culb
Package weight: 60g
Energy: 345 kcal (per pack)
Main ingredients: potatoes, vegetable oil,
and salt
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Yay, lightly salted! I love lightly salted
chips!
One time I missed the train, but then I
had lightly salted chips from my bag
and I was just so happy!
If possible, I'd like to give it a hundred
more points!
Lightly salted is great,
but I like Miso flavored
ones more!
Yui gets really mad when I eat snacks
while playing games.
"The controller will get sticky!" she says.
Using chopsticks should be fine though.
It's a tasty snack, but be careful not
to eat too much!
Especially if you're a girl in love.
The club room usually has lots of
snacks lying around though, which
might lead to a disaster if someone
is weak minded.
<4indentation>Don't you just
<4indentation>sometimes crave for
<4indentation>potato chips while
<4indentation>playing games late
<4indentation>at night?
It would be best not to eat chips at night
though. 'Cause, like... you know what
I mean.
Why must the tastier ones have more oil?
YuruYuriCrossReview
Yay, lightly salted! I love lightly salted
chips!
One time I missed the train, but then I
had lightly salted chips from my bag
and I was just so happy!
If possible, I'd like to give it a hundred
more points!
Lightly salted is great,
but I like Miso flavored
ones more!
Yui gets really mad when I eat snacks
while playing games.
"The controller will get sticky!" she says.
Using chopsticks should be fine though.
It's a tasty snack, but be careful not
to eat too much!
Especially if you're a girl in love.
The club room usually has lots of
snacks lying around though, which
might lead to a disaster if someone
is weak minded.
<4indentation>Don't you just
<4indentation>sometimes crave for
<4indentation>potato chips while
<4indentation>playing games late
<4indentation>at night?
It would be best not to eat chips at night
though. 'Cause, like... you know what
I mean.
Why must the tastier ones have more oil?
YuruYuriCrossReview
Lightly Salted Potato Chips
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Manufacturer: Culb
Package weight: 60g
Energy: 345 kcal (per pack)
Main ingredients: potatoes, vegetable oil,
and salt
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Yay, lightly salted! I love lightly salted
chips!
One time I missed the train, but then I
had lightly salted chips from my bag
and I was just so happy!
If possible, I'd like to give it a hundred
more points!
Lightly salted is great,
but I like Miso flavored
ones more!
Yui gets really mad when I eat snacks
while playing games.
"The controller will get sticky!" she says.
Using chopsticks should be fine though.
It's a tasty snack, but be careful not
to eat too much!
Especially if you're a girl in love.
The club room usually has lots of
snacks lying around though, which
might lead to a disaster if someone
is weak minded.
<4indentation>Don't you just
<4indentation>sometimes crave for
<4indentation>potato chips while
<4indentation>playing games late
<4indentation>at night?
It would be best not to eat chips at night
though. 'Cause, like... you know what
I mean.
Why must the tastier ones have more oil?
YuruYuriCrossReview
Lightly Salted Potato Chips
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
Yay, lightly salted! I love lightly salted
chips!
One time I missed the train, but then I
had lightly salted chips from my bag
and I was just so happy!
If possible, I'd like to give it a hundred
more points!
Lightly salted is great,
but I like Miso flavored
ones more!
Yui gets really mad when I eat snacks
while playing games.
"The controller will get sticky!" she says.
Using chopsticks should be fine though.
It's a tasty snack, but be careful not
to eat too much!
Especially if you're a girl in love.
The club room usually has lots of
snacks lying around though, which
might lead to a disaster if someone
is weak minded.
<4indentation>Don't you just
<4indentation>sometimes crave for
<4indentation>potato chips while
<4indentation>playing games late
<4indentation>at night?
It would be best not to eat chips at night
though. 'Cause, like... you know what
I mean.
Why must the tastier ones have more oil?
Yay, lightly salted! I love lightly salted
chips!
One time I missed the train, but then I
had lightly salted chips from my bag
and I was just so happy!
If possible, I'd like to give it a hundred
more points!
Lightly salted is great,
but I like Miso flavored
ones more!
Yui gets really mad when I eat snacks
while playing games.
"The controller will get sticky!" she says.
Using chopsticks should be fine though.
It's a tasty snack, but be careful not
to eat too much!
Especially if you're a girl in love.
The club room usually has lots of
snacks lying around though, which
might lead to a disaster if someone
is weak minded.
<4indentation>Don't you just
<4indentation>sometimes crave for
<4indentation>potato chips while
<4indentation>playing games late
<4indentation>at night?
It would be best not to eat chips at night
though. 'Cause, like... you know what
I mean.
Why must the tastier ones have more oil?
Yay, lightly salted! I love lightly salted
chips!
One time I missed the train, but then I
had lightly salted chips from my bag
and I was just so happy!
If possible, I'd like to give it a hundred
more points!
Lightly salted is great,
but I like Miso flavored
ones more!
Yui gets really mad when I eat snacks
while playing games.
"The controller will get sticky!" she says.
Using chopsticks should be fine though.
It's a tasty snack, but be careful not
to eat too much!
Especially if you're a girl in love.
The club room usually has lots of
snacks lying around though, which
might lead to a disaster if someone
is weak minded.
<4indentation>Don't you just
<4indentation>sometimes crave for
<4indentation>potato chips while
<4indentation>playing games late
<4indentation>at night?
It would be best not to eat chips at night
though. 'Cause, like... you know what
I mean.
Why must the tastier ones have more oil?
Pretty girls don't get fat.
Yeah, yeah.
You're lucky, Kyouko-chan.
So you actually meant that.
That brings us to a close.
Everyone...
Thanks for watching!