yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
too
Go
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
iku zo
Let's go!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
ieaa ieaa
Yeah, yeah
aiteru heya wo haijakku yume no ajito tsukurimasho
Let's hijack an empty room and
turn it into the hangout of our dreams
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
are mo kore mo yaritai tatami no ue wa paradaisu
I wanna do this, I wanna do that, this room's our paradise
(hai) uerukamu (hai hai hai)
(Yeah) Welcome (Yeah yeah yeah)
ocha no ko saisai suisui chacha wo irete gomen nasai
It all went too smooth and easy,
sorry, but I'm going to put on some tea
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
hangurii seishin ii jan osenbei futon kajittara
I'm feeling super hungry, I think I'll have this cracker pillow
(hai) non non
(Yeah) No, no
nayamigoto wa minai furi oshiire ni shimaimashou
Let's pretend our troubles don't exist,
shove them into the closet
asatte no hougaku muita nara
And do something completely random
hissatsu yuru yuri dondengaeshi
Take this! Yuru Yuri Non Sequitur!
kimi to iru dake de chiisana atarimae no koto demo
When I'm with you, even the smallest, simplest things
okashikute (hai hai)
Can be so funny (Yeah yeah)
nukedasenai (hai hai)
I never want to leave (Yeah yeah)
sugoku ii yo ne kono shunkan (san hai)
I love these moments so much (Ready go)
hyaku en demo tanoshimeru yo
It's fun for less than a hundred yen
nooberu shou dai hakken
A huge discovery worth a Nobel Prize
shiawase wa sugu tonari ni aru
Happiness is always right by you
saikouchou chochochocho choo
It's the best! Best-best-best-best-best!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
kochira wa gorakubu ii tokoro
This is the Amusement Club, a great place to be
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
goo
Go
Today's hot as well.
That's for sure.
Where's Akari?
She's on duty today.
It's the Beginning of Amusement
Hey, could you grab volume 97 for me?
Get it yourself.
You'll turn into a lazy cow.
Moo.
Fine.
Oh, while you're up, get the crackers for me.
What? You'll turn into a lazy cow.
Thanks for waiting, everyone.
Akari-chan, good timing.
Could you pass me those crackers?
What?!
I don't mind, but you're
ordering me around already?
All right! Let's play the King Game
to cool ourselves down.
How's that gonna cool us down?
The loser gets to be the King's errand girl for life.
For life?!
That's too harsh!
What's wrong with just playing it normally?
How do you play the King Game again?
Well—
Well, you see...
The person who behaves in the most kingly manner is the winner.
I had a feeling you'd make a dumb joke.
It's more fun this way, though.
Now bow before me!
You're a lord?
I sure am thirsty.
Which one of you will make me some tea?
A company president now?
Um...
You ran out of ideas quick.
Being a king is hard work.
Maybe being a queen is easier.
What?
You! Listen up, dog!
Lick my feet!
In the King Game, you draw straws
to determine who the King is,
and then the King gets to give
a command to another player.
That sounds fun!
Let's give it a try, then.
There's nothing else to do.
I have a pack of disposable chopsticks.
That's perfect, Akari-chan.
Okay. Shall we begin?
Who's the King?
I'm the King!
What should I do?
Okay, number two.
That's me.
Uh, then...
Be my friend forever.
Sure!
Wait, that was her command?
That's Akari for you.
She's too nice.
Okay, next round!
Who's the King?
It's me!
Ugh...
Now just what shall I do?
Okay, number three, give me a nice big kiss.
What?
You could learn a thing or two from Akari.
Oh wait, you're number three.
Wait! What?!
I'm not letting Yui-senpai kiss you!
But the King's orders are absolute.
Yeah, but...
Fine. In that case...
I'll settle for a kiss on my finger.
Even if it's just on the finger, how dare you!
That finger's a billion times more valuable now!
Chinatsu-chan, it's not a big deal!
Calm down!
Do you know what you've done?
You can kiss it too if you want, Chinatsu-chan.
Come on, come on.
Not a moment's hesitation!
So basically, all I have to do is draw King,
and then I can order the number Yui-senpai draws to marry me!
Uh, Chinatsu-chan, I think that's enough.
Now that that's out of the way,
let's keep this game going!
Who's the King?
Me!
You've been lucky today, Kyouko.
All right, number one,
spin around a hundred times
and pretend to be an elephant.
A hundred?!
One, two, three, four...
You can do it, Akari!
I must become King.
Five, six...
Akari! Who did this to you?
You did!
Oh, well. Let's just play with
us three until she recovers.
All right. That increases my chances of becoming King.
Who's the King?
It's me.
Um...
Okay, number two.
Yes! I'm number two!
Oh, my. What will she order me to do?
Could it be?
Chinatsu-chan, bring your lips...
to meet with mine at once.
Y-You're so bold, Yui-senpai.
The King's orders are absolute,
Chinatsu-chan.
Of course, Yui-senpai...
Wh-What's gotten into you, Chinatsu-chan?
Yui-senpai...
Um... Hey, could you get me some more tea?
Huh? That's your command?
Yeah, I definitely have to become King!
Here you go.
Thanks, Chinatsu-chan.
Okay, time for the next round!
All right.
Who's the King?
It's me!
Chinatsu-chan, huh?
Congrats.
Now I have to guess Yui-senpai's number.
I wonder what kind of order she'll issue.
It'll be better than anything you can come up with, that's for sure.
Nobody else would tell someone to turn around a hundred times and pretend to be an elephant.
I've got it!
Number one, I've got an order for you!
That'll be me.
What?
In that case, turn around a hundred times and pretend to be a bear.
What?! How can you give such a cruel order?!
Look who's talking!
One, two, three...
Four, five, six, seven...
If I can take Kyouko-senpai out of the game...
B-Bear...
Just as planned!
Now it's just me and Yui-senpai playing!
The King Game of Love is about to begin!
Hey, everyone!
Who wants some cookies?
Excuse us. We brought cookies to share with—
What?!
What in the world happened here?
Those two will be fine.
Actually...
The King Game?!
That sounds super fun!
I'll bring Sugiura-senpai and the others over!
Sakurako, wait up!
I'm sorry. I'll leave the cookies here.
Thanks.
Wait, Sakurako!
This is my chance!
Huh? For what?
Let's play one more round before everyone else gets here!
I'm feeling better now.
What?!
Toshinou Kyouko!
Did you forget to hand in your...
Huh? Where's Toshinou Kyouko?
What?! Toshinou Kyouko!
O-Oh no! Are you sick?
What did you eat off the ground this time?
I told you not to do that!
That's not what happened.
Oh, I see. So that's all it was.
Then I'm no longer anxious Angkor Wat.
Anyway, she should be waking up any time now.
The King Game, huh?
Aha, found you!
Oh.
Apparently Akari-chan and her friends
are playing the King Game!
Yeah, they just told me about it.
Let's join in!
Huh?
Why not?
We're pretty much done with
student council work for today.
I suppose that's true.
Shall we join them, then?
It's decided! All right!
Excuse the intrusion.
Bear...
Here we go.
Who's the King?
It's me!
King... Truly an appropriate title for me.
Now then, number seven!
We only have six straws.
What? But we have seven people.
And one of them is the King.
Oh, right.
Starting over, then...
Numbers two and three, kiss!
Why does this seem familiar?
I'm three.
What?
I'm two.
Huh?!
The King's orders are absolute.
Get it over with already.
What?
We couldn't possibly...
Just kiss her on the cheek already. Hurry up.
Why do we have to do such a thing?
I guess I'm okay with Sugiura-senpai kissing me on the cheek.
Here goes...
O-Okay.
Okay, stop right there!
I retract my command!
Aren't you the one who wanted this?
I'm the King! I'm changing my orders!
King, punch number three!
Let's keep playing!
Who's the King?
Oh, it's me.
That's me.
Who's the King?!
I'm the King again.
Oh, it's me.
Why, King?!
Chinatsu-chan, don't you think we've had enough?
Not yet! One more round!
Kyouko-chan makes a magnificent recovery!
Kyouko-senpai, go back to sleep!
O-Okay.
Come on, King straw!
Listen to me!
You know what's gonna happen if you betray me!
She's acting like a queen.
You'll be punished!
Oh, I'm the King again...
Done!
Now you'll find it, right?
River
Park
HERE!
Boobs
Sakurako-chan, what's this symbol?
Don't you know that, Akari-chan?
That indicates which direction is up.
Up?
You mean north.
This is how you're supposed
to draw a compass symbol.
Well, that's one way to draw it!
That's the only way to draw it.
Class is starting. Take your seats.
It's time for Cooking with Kyouko-chan.
You won't believe what's on today's menu!
A Kyouko-chan-style love harmony with vegetables and meat.
It's just meat and potato stew.
Hurry up and get ready.
Gee, way to be a buzzkill.
Welcome! We got some fresh vegetables in!
You're a vegetable vendor now?
What shall I roll for you next?
You change jobs quick.
Stop playing around and peel some potatoes.
Oh, no! They're going to strip me buck naked!
Shut up!
That's dangerous!
I don't know how to do it properly.
I've never done it before.
So like this, then?
Stop!
You tell me to do it, then you tell me to stop.
You're so fickle.
Toshinou.
What?
You're gonna have your own special class over here.
Is this all right?
Yeah.
They're perfect.
How are things over here?
Everything going well?
We'll be able to start cooking soon.
You're so good at this.
We're way behind.
My, how awful!
Help us over here.
But there's nothing much to do over there!
I learned to use a knife for nothing.
You learn quick.
Do you usually cook at home?
Not at all.
Yeah, kind of.
Nah, not at all.
Stop walking around with a knife.
How long until they'll be done?
About 15 minutes.
15 minutes?!
What are we supposed to do until then?
How about washing these dishes?
I wonder what I should do.
Hey.
My tendons are inflamed from drawing too many comics!
Fine, I'll do them.
Kyouko, go get the dishes and utensils.
Got it!
She sure moves when it's time to eat.
Got them.
We're making four servings.
I'm using the one on the bottom.
Just how much are you going to eat?!
Is it ready yet?
Is the meat and potato stew ready yet?
Wait just a little longer.
I cannot wait!
Since I cannot wait, let's arm wrestle!
Bring it on!
What happened to your inflamed tendon?
It's all healed up now.
You can't just say whatever suits you.
Fine. I'll arm wrestle you.
Ready, fight!
I cannot lose!
Oh, you're putting up a fight.
There.
If there were a spike here,
that would've been a disaster for my hand!
It would've been just as much a disaster for mine.
I've never been able to beat you.
Okay, Ayano.
What?
I can probably beat you.
I can't arm wrestle. I'm too weak.
Come on, just give it a try.
Just once, then.
Here we go!
O-Okay...
Ready, fight!
Toshinou Kyouko...
I'm sorry.
I lost again!
That's the first time I've won
an arm wrestling match.
Liar!
You're as strong as anyone!
Okay,
Chitose. Your turn!
But I'm also weak.
There.
You're just weak, Kyouko.
So you can be cute.
This is unbelievable.
How humiliating...
I'll have to play Akari and Chinatsu after school.
Oh!
Looks like it's ready.
All right!
Thanks for the food!
Meat and potato stew is delicious!
Wow, you're eating already?
We're getting in first.
Lucky you.
The meat is soft and delicious.
It makes you want rice, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Once you've finished eating,
write up your reports and turn them in.
Ingredients
pork slices \
potatoes \
carrot \
onion \
shirataki noodles \
beans \
Okay.
Thanks for the food!
"Zero wins, three losses.
3 Losses
My arm wasn't strong enough.
I had no idea I was such a weak maiden."
You don't need to report on your arm wrestling.
"My inflamed tendon may be the reason I lost."
I thought that had healed up.
River
Park
HERE!
Boobs
River
Park
HERE!
Boobs
River
Park
HERE!
This vending machine is too tall.
And why did they put it up here?
What's wrong?
Someone saw me. How embarrassing...
Oh, are you having trouble reaching it?
I'll push it for you.
I-It's all right.
I can do it myself.
Which one did you want?
That one. At the very top.
Then how about I buy it,
and then we can trade?
What? Are you sure?
Yeah. I wanted the one you got anyway.
Here.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Thanks.
Hey, wait!
Cider
Masochist
What is this?
I love this stuff.
You don't have to force yourself to drink it.
I-I'm not forcing myself!
Wow, it looks great.
I-It's delicious.
That's one crazy face.
I'm going to rest on this bench.
Bye-bye.
What's wrong?
I'll rest with you, Miss.
M-Miss?
Well, shall we sit together, then?
She called me Miss. I'm so happy.
I've always wanted someone to call me that.
I need to show her I'm a strong young lady.
Hey.
Wait, she wasn't after juice.
That's black coffee!
This little girl drinks black coffee?
I heard grade schoolers these days are mature,
but I never thought they were like this.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Miss, are you on your way somewhere?
Yeah, I'm going to my friend's house.
It's my first time going there, so I'm excited.
My sister asked me to get this for her,
so that's why I was here.
Oh.
I see!
It's for your sister.
What grade is your sister in?
Third year in high school.
She has lots of assignments,
so she's going to drink coffee and work hard.
Sounds rough.
High schoolers drink black coffee, right?
I'm going to drink my juice, too.
Oh, no!
I spilled it.
You need something to wipe that!
What? I don't have any tissues!
Now what?!
I have tissues.
Thanks. You really—
I'm glad I had tissues.
She ended up helping me.
Miss, I'll throw that away.
It's okay.
I can handle it. You can relax.
Are you okay?
I tripped.
You're bleeding!
Thanks.
You should disinfect it later.
I'm sorry for being such a handful.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Here. Now cheer up.
A candy!
I can have this?
Yay!
Not only has she been helping me,
she patted my head and gave me a candy!
There we go.
I'd better go home now.
You be careful, Miss.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
I'm pathetic.
I wasn't like a young lady at all.
Akari-chan!
Thanks for waiting!
Chinatsu-chan.
You're early again today.
Not at all.
I think I'll keep this to myself.
It is somewhere around here?
I think it's more over that way.
Oomuro
This is it.
Welcome!
Hello.
We're here.
So how was my map? Perfect, right?
Um, sure.
Well, we did manage to make it here.
Huh?
What?
You're the young lady from earlier.
You're Sakurako-chan's sister?
You two know each other?
Not really, we just met at the park earlier.
Ah, wait. That's supposed to be a secret.
Secret?
Uh, I mean, I...
Geez... It just really surprised me!
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
seishun hajimeyou (wan tsuu san hai)
Let's get started with youth (one, two, three, go)
hitomazu hashiru zo (wan tsuu san hai)
First up, let's get running (one, two, three, go)
minna ga egao de (wan tsuu san hai)
Everyone's smiling bright (one, two, three, go)
kore ga seishun da (wan tsuu san hai)
Now this is youth (one, two, three, go)
haru sakuramochi wo tabeyou
Spring! We'll eat sakuramochi
natsu kakigoori de kimari
Summer! Gotta have shaved ice
aki yakiimo wo hoobari
Fall! Stuff your cheeks with sweet potatoes
fuyu yuki de mata kakigoori
Winter! Shaved ice again with the snow
mou iccho
One more time!
haru kyoushitsu wo machigaete
Spring! Going to the wrong classroom
natsu shukudai wo wasurete
Summer! Forgetting my homework
aki marason de biriketsu
Fall! Finishing last in the marathon
fuyu kotatsu ni chouki taizai
Winter! Staying late in the kotatsu
ichinen sanbyaku rokujuugo nichi
All year long, three-hundred sixty-five days
tokidoki sanbyaku rokujuuroku nichi
And sometimes three-hundred sixty-six days
iroiro aru kedo zenryoku zenkai
There's a lot to do, but we've gotta go all out, all in
zenshin zenrei tanoshimou yo
And enjoy youth with all our souls
yoo yoyoyoyo
Yo yo-yo-yo-yo!
enjoi enjoi jojojojojoi
Enjoy, enjoy, jo-jo-jo-jo-joy!
acchuuma seishun (oorai)
Youth blows by in a flash (all right)
mabushii yo seishun (ooesu)
Youth is bright and beautiful (oh yes)
nemuke sayonara kokoro no hitomi wo bacchiri akeyou
Wave away sleep, keep the eyes of your heart wide open
acchuuma seishun (donmai)
Youth blows by in a flash (don't mind)
mou supiido seishun (faito)
Youth runs like a beast (fight)
mabataki shiteccha oishii tokoro minogashichau yo
Blink for a second, and you'll miss the best parts
chuui
Careful!
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
YuruYuriCrossReview
The Sea Urchin's Adventures - Volume 97
Publisher : Jinno Co.
Author : Iroman
Price : 514 yen + tax
Magazine : Comic Ryona
Printing Office : Yahata Print
Issues in Circulation : 230 million
Yuru Yuri Cross Review!
It's amazing that The Sea Urchin's Adventures has almost reached a hundred volumes.
Men and women of all ages love it.
YuruYuriCrossReview
The Sea Urchin's Adventures - Volume 97
Publisher : Jinno Co.
Author : Iroman
Price : 514 yen + tax
Magazine : Comic Ryona
Printing Office : Yahata Print
Issues in Circulation : 230 million
YuruYuriCrossReview
Publisher : Jinno Co.
Author : Iroman
Price : 514 yen + tax
Magazine : Comic Ryona
Printing Office : Yahata Print
Issues in Circulation : 230 million
I didn't really get some parts... but
maybe that's because I'm just a kid.
I had nightmares about the spread on
page 89.
But since Kyouko-chan recommended
it, I'll give it a 9!
Volume 97 marks the
start of The Battle of the
Black Sea arc.
From the Mediterranean to the Black
Sea, huh? You got me! The author who
came up with this story is incredible!
The anchovies he met in the iron sulfide
sea were good, too.
It's definitely a must read!
I didn't understand the story, but basi-
cally, a sea urchin goes on adventures.
It's already on its 97th volume, but the
art could use some work!
Does the world's savior really die so
easily?!
<4indentation>For that shocking turn
<4indentation>of events, I give it a 4.
<4indentation>This volume starts on
<4indentation>the heels of the excite-
<4indentation>ment left by the Legend
<4indentation>of the Savior of the
Mediterranean Sea arc concluded in the
previous volume.
I started reading at Kyouko's recom-
mendation, but I can't stand not
knowing what happens next!
The sudden and brutal scenes aren't
quite my taste, though.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Publisher : Jinno Co.
Author : Iroman
Price : 514 yen + tax
Magazine : Comic Ryona
Printing Office : Yahata Print
Issues in Circulation : 230 million
The Sea Urchin's Adventures Volume 97
I didn't really get some parts... but
maybe that's because I'm just a kid.
I had nightmares about the spread on
page 89.
But since Kyouko-chan recommended
it, I'll give it a 9!
Volume 97 marks the
start of The Battle of the
Black Sea arc.
From the Mediterranean to the Black
Sea, huh? You got me! The author who
came up with this story is incredible!
The anchovies he met in the iron sulfide
sea were good, too.
It's definitely a must read!
I didn't understand the story, but basi-
cally, a sea urchin goes on adventures.
It's already on its 97th volume, but the
art could use some work!
Does the world's savior really die so
easily?!
<4indentation>For that shocking turn
<4indentation>of events, I give it a 4.
<4indentation>This volume starts on
<4indentation>the heels of the excite-
<4indentation>ment left by the Legend
<4indentation>of the Savior of the
Mediterranean Sea arc concluded in the
previous volume.
I started reading at Kyouko's recom-
mendation, but I can't stand not
knowing what happens next!
The sudden and brutal scenes aren't
quite my taste, though.
YuruYuriCrossReview
The Sea Urchin's Adventures - Volume 97
Publisher : Jinno Co.
Author : Iroman
Price : 514 yen + tax
Magazine : Comic Ryona
Printing Office : Yahata Print
Issues in Circulation : 230 million
Publisher : Jinno Co.
Author : Iroman
Price : 514 yen + tax
Magazine : Comic Ryona
Printing Office : Yahata Print
Issues in Circulation : 230 million
I didn't really get some parts... but
maybe that's because I'm just a kid.
I had nightmares about the spread on
page 89.
But since Kyouko-chan recommended
it, I'll give it a 9!
Volume 97 marks the
start of The Battle of the
Black Sea arc.
From the Mediterranean to the Black
Sea, huh? You got me! The author who
came up with this story is incredible!
The anchovies he met in the iron sulfide
sea were good, too.
It's definitely a must read!
I didn't understand the story, but basi-
cally, a sea urchin goes on adventures.
It's already on its 97th volume, but the
art could use some work!
Does the world's savior really die so
easily?!
<4indentation>For that shocking turn
<4indentation>of events, I give it a 4.
<4indentation>This volume starts on
<4indentation>the heels of the excite-
<4indentation>ment left by the Legend
<4indentation>of the Savior of the
Mediterranean Sea arc concluded in the
previous volume.
I started reading at Kyouko's recom-
mendation, but I can't stand not
knowing what happens next!
The sudden and brutal scenes aren't
quite my taste, though.
YuruYuriCrossReview
The Sea Urchin's Adventures - Volume 97
Publisher : Jinno Co.
Author : Iroman
Price : 514 yen + tax
Magazine : Comic Ryona
Printing Office : Yahata Print
Issues in Circulation : 230 million
I didn't really get some parts... but
maybe that's because I'm just a kid.
I had nightmares about the spread on
page 89.
But since Kyouko-chan recommended
it, I'll give it a 9!
Volume 97 marks the
start of The Battle of the
Black Sea arc.
From the Mediterranean to the Black
Sea, huh? You got me! The author who
came up with this story is incredible!
The anchovies he met in the iron sulfide
sea were good, too.
It's definitely a must read!
I didn't understand the story, but basi-
cally, a sea urchin goes on adventures.
It's already on its 97th volume, but the
art could use some work!
Does the world's savior really die so
easily?!
<4indentation>For that shocking turn
<4indentation>of events, I give it a 4.
<4indentation>This volume starts on
<4indentation>the heels of the excite-
<4indentation>ment left by the Legend
<4indentation>of the Savior of the
Mediterranean Sea arc concluded in the
previous volume.
I started reading at Kyouko's recom-
mendation, but I can't stand not
knowing what happens next!
The sudden and brutal scenes aren't
quite my taste, though.
YuruYuriCrossReview
The Sea Urchin's Adventures - Volume 97
I didn't really get some parts... but
maybe that's because I'm just a kid.
I had nightmares about the spread on
page 89.
But since Kyouko-chan recommended
it, I'll give it a 9!
Volume 97 marks the
start of The Battle of the
Black Sea arc.
From the Mediterranean to the Black
Sea, huh? You got me! The author who
came up with this story is incredible!
The anchovies he met in the iron sulfide
sea were good, too.
It's definitely a must read!
I didn't understand the story, but basi-
cally, a sea urchin goes on adventures.
It's already on its 97th volume, but the
art could use some work!
Does the world's savior really die so
easily?!
<4indentation>For that shocking turn
<4indentation>of events, I give it a 4.
<4indentation>This volume starts on
<4indentation>the heels of the excite-
<4indentation>ment left by the Legend
<4indentation>of the Savior of the
Mediterranean Sea arc concluded in the
previous volume.
I started reading at Kyouko's recom-
mendation, but I can't stand not
knowing what happens next!
The sudden and brutal scenes aren't
quite my taste, though.
YuruYuriCrossReview
The Sea Urchin's Adventures - Volume 97
I didn't really get some parts... but
maybe that's because I'm just a kid.
I had nightmares about the spread on
page 89.
But since Kyouko-chan recommended
it, I'll give it a 9!
Volume 97 marks the
start of The Battle of the
Black Sea arc.
From the Mediterranean to the Black
Sea, huh? You got me! The author who
came up with this story is incredible!
The anchovies he met in the iron sulfide
sea were good, too.
It's definitely a must read!
I didn't understand the story, but basi-
cally, a sea urchin goes on adventures.
It's already on its 97th volume, but the
art could use some work!
Does the world's savior really die so
easily?!
<4indentation>For that shocking turn
<4indentation>of events, I give it a 4.
<4indentation>This volume starts on
<4indentation>the heels of the excite-
<4indentation>ment left by the Legend
<4indentation>of the Savior of the
Mediterranean Sea arc concluded in the
previous volume.
I started reading at Kyouko's recom-
mendation, but I can't stand not
knowing what happens next!
The sudden and brutal scenes aren't
quite my taste, though.
YuruYuriCrossReview
The Sea Urchin's Adventures - Volume 97
I didn't really get some parts... but
maybe that's because I'm just a kid.
I had nightmares about the spread on
page 89.
But since Kyouko-chan recommended
it, I'll give it a 9!
Volume 97 marks the
start of The Battle of the
Black Sea arc.
From the Mediterranean to the Black
Sea, huh? You got me! The author who
came up with this story is incredible!
The anchovies he met in the iron sulfide
sea were good, too.
It's definitely a must read!
I didn't understand the story, but basi-
cally, a sea urchin goes on adventures.
It's already on its 97th volume, but the
art could use some work!
Does the world's savior really die so
easily?!
<4indentation>For that shocking turn
<4indentation>of events, I give it a 4.
<4indentation>This volume starts on
<4indentation>the heels of the excite-
<4indentation>ment left by the Legend
<4indentation>of the Savior of the
Mediterranean Sea arc concluded in the
previous volume.
I started reading at Kyouko's recom-
mendation, but I can't stand not
knowing what happens next!
The sudden and brutal scenes aren't
quite my taste, though.
I didn't really get some parts... but
maybe that's because I'm just a kid.
I had nightmares about the spread on
page 89.
But since Kyouko-chan recommended
it, I'll give it a 9!
Volume 97 marks the
start of The Battle of the
Black Sea arc.
From the Mediterranean to the Black
Sea, huh? You got me! The author who
came up with this story is incredible!
The anchovies he met in the iron sulfide
sea were good, too.
It's definitely a must read!
I didn't understand the story, but basi-
cally, a sea urchin goes on adventures.
It's already on its 97th volume, but the
art could use some work!
Does the world's savior really die so
easily?!
<4indentation>For that shocking turn
<4indentation>of events, I give it a 4.
<4indentation>This volume starts on
<4indentation>the heels of the excite-
<4indentation>ment left by the Legend
<4indentation>of the Savior of the
Mediterranean Sea arc concluded in the
previous volume.
I started reading at Kyouko's recom-
mendation, but I can't stand not
knowing what happens next!
The sudden and brutal scenes aren't
quite my taste, though.
I didn't really get some parts... but
maybe that's because I'm just a kid.
I had nightmares about the spread on
page 89.
But since Kyouko-chan recommended
it, I'll give it a 9!
Volume 97 marks the
start of The Battle of the
Black Sea arc.
From the Mediterranean to the Black
Sea, huh? You got me! The author who
came up with this story is incredible!
The anchovies he met in the iron sulfide
sea were good, too.
It's definitely a must read!
I didn't understand the story, but basi-
cally, a sea urchin goes on adventures.
It's already on its 97th volume, but the
art could use some work!
Does the world's savior really die so
easily?!
<4indentation>For that shocking turn
<4indentation>of events, I give it a 4.
<4indentation>This volume starts on
<4indentation>the heels of the excite-
<4indentation>ment left by the Legend
<4indentation>of the Savior of the
Mediterranean Sea arc concluded in the
previous volume.
I started reading at Kyouko's recom-
mendation, but I can't stand not
knowing what happens next!
The sudden and brutal scenes aren't
quite my taste, though.
I didn't really get some parts... but
maybe that's because I'm just a kid.
I had nightmares about the spread on
page 89.
But since Kyouko-chan recommended
it, I'll give it a 9!
Volume 97 marks the
start of The Battle of the
Black Sea arc.
From the Mediterranean to the Black
Sea, huh? You got me! The author who
came up with this story is incredible!
The anchovies he met in the iron sulfide
sea were good, too.
It's definitely a must read!
I didn't understand the story, but basi-
cally, a sea urchin goes on adventures.
It's already on its 97th volume, but the
art could use some work!
Does the world's savior really die so
easily?!
<4indentation>For that shocking turn
<4indentation>of events, I give it a 4.
<4indentation>This volume starts on
<4indentation>the heels of the excite-
<4indentation>ment left by the Legend
<4indentation>of the Savior of the
Mediterranean Sea arc concluded in the
previous volume.
I started reading at Kyouko's recom-
mendation, but I can't stand not
knowing what happens next!
The sudden and brutal scenes aren't
quite my taste, though.
The Sea Urchin's Adventures Volume 97
The almost excessively brutal scenes really grow on you!
I don't like those parts so much.
But Mirakurun's even more entertaining!
Next episode...
"Tremble in Fear!"
Next Episode: Tremble in Fear
What? Is it going to be scary?
Rum raisin is so scary!