yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
too
Go
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
iku zo
Let's go!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
ieaa ieaa
Yeah, yeah
aiteru heya wo haijakku yume no ajito tsukurimasho
Let's hijack an empty room and
turn it into the hangout of our dreams
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
are mo kore mo yaritai tatami no ue wa paradaisu
I wanna do this, I wanna do that, this room's our paradise
(hai) uerukamu (hai hai hai)
(Yeah) Welcome (Yeah yeah yeah)
ocha no ko saisai suisui chacha wo irete gomen nasai
It all went too smooth and easy,
sorry, but I'm going to put on some tea
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
hangurii seishin ii jan osenbei futon kajittara
I'm feeling super hungry, I think I'll have this cracker pillow
(hai) non non
(Yeah) No, no
nayamigoto wa minai furi oshiire ni shimaimashou
Let's pretend our troubles don't exist,
shove them into the closet
asatte no hougaku muita nara
And do something completely random
hissatsu yuru yuri dondengaeshi
Take this! Yuru Yuri Non Sequitur!
kimi to iru dake de chiisana atarimae no koto demo
When I'm with you, even the smallest, simplest things
okashikute (hai hai)
Can be so funny (Yeah yeah)
nukedasenai (hai hai)
I never want to leave (Yeah yeah)
sugoku ii yo ne kono shunkan (san hai)
I love these moments so much (Ready go)
hyaku en demo tanoshimeru yo
It's fun for less than a hundred yen
nooberu shou dai hakken
A huge discovery worth a Nobel Prize
shiawase wa sugu tonari ni aru
Happiness is always right by you
saikouchou chochochocho choo
It's the best! Best-best-best-best-best!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
kochira wa gorakubu ii tokoro
This is the Amusement Club, a great place to be
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
goo
Go
There we go.
Now, the clothes—
I've gotta call Kyouko.
No, out of the question.
She'll make fun of me for sure!
Hi. Akari speaking.
Sorry for calling so early. Do you have a minute?
Yeah, sure.
Akari, you wouldn't happen to like spiders, would you?
Huh? What was that?
I don't imagine you would, but...
Yeah, I like tigers.
What? Really?
Yeah! Looking at them makes me feel warm and fuzzy.
They're nice and furry.
Riding on one has been my dream since I was little.
R-Really? How unusual.
It is kind of childish I guess.
Childish?
Well, whatever.
Since you like them so much,
could you come over to my place?
Yeah, sure.
Tremble in Fear
I'm heading out!
Be careful!
All right!
While nobody's home, I'll give this a wash!
That should do it!
A spider!
Yui-chan, you called me over just to scare me, didn't you?!
Huh? Don't you like them?
Don't make weird jokes like that!
That leaves one option.
Though I can't expect much from her.
You're calling me, Senpai?! I'm so glad!
Chinatsu-chan, are you free today?
Is she going to ask me out on a date?!
I'm free! I'm free! I'm so free,
I'm gonna die from boredom!
Could you come over to my place, then?
I actually—
I'm on my way! I'll be right there!
I'll come at the speed of light!
I am the Chinatsu light!
O-Okay. I'll be waiting.
Thanks for waiting for me!
Chinatsu-chan, you look especially nice today.
Huh? Why are you so disappointed?
No reason.
Anyway, Yui-senpai, is something wrong?
Well, I found a spider in my room.
You wouldn't happen to be
okay with them... would you?
I guess not.
Spiders?
I don't like them, but I can get rid of it.
What? Really?
No, no, no, no!
That's bigger than I thought. I can't do it.
That's much too large to squish with a tissue.
Nope! No way!
But if I look courageous now,
will I capture Yui-senpai's heart?
That's right. If I can't capture a simple spider,
I can't even dream of capturing Yui-senpai's heart!
With your bare hands?! Are you okay?!
I'm fine!
If I tell myself I'm doing it for you—
Oh, no!
I have a lecture this afternoon!
AKAZA
That was close! I nearly committed social suicide!
This must be the power of Akari!
Okay already! Just hurry up and save us!
Hm, how should I do this?
Okay. I guess I'll use this cup and flier.
You're so dexterous.
There.
Pest removal complete.
Thanks.
Yui, I thought you used to be okay with bugs.
That was a long time ago.
It's so cutesyui that you hate bugs.
Shut up.
Sorry for asking you all to come here.
But since you're here, why don't we hang out today?
Sure!
We better wake Akari up.
I'm kinda hungry actually.
Want to make pancakes?
The time has come for me to display my skills.
Hey! Close the door!
Yay! Pancakes!
I haven't had these in so long!
I've got fresh cream too.
Oh, fantastic!
Here you go.
Hurry up.
What? You want me to do it?!
The tops are starting to bubble.
There we go.
That looks delicious.
Come on! This isn't foaming up at all!
Don't you have a hand mixer?
I don't exactly bake often.
Fatigue is building up in my right arm.
You can do it.
Hurry up.
Would you still be my friend even if my right arm alone was super buff?
Want me to do it?
A buff Akari sounds kinda scary.
Akarin!
What is this?!
Is that a heart?
Yeah, I guess.
You can have it when it's done.
Really? I can have your heart?
What is that?
Nice muscles, right?
You can have it when it's done.
Don't want it.
The cream is ready.
That was quick!
We still have another carton.
My arm's going to fall off!
How about we decorate our
pancakes and trade them?
Good idea.
Here. A macho man shampooing his hair.
I said I don't want that!
Here, Chinatsu-chan.
It's not very good, though.
So cute!
Kyouko-chan, mine's done.
Oh, nice job!
I'm pretty proud of it.
Is that you, Akari?
It's a bear!
You're saying that because of my buns, aren't you?
Here, Akari-chan.
I can't even see the pancake!
I put a lot of effort into decorating it.
Th-Thanks.
Now, time to dig into Yui-senpai's heart!
Uh, okay.
What are you doing, Kyouko?
By adding more on top like this...
Ta-da!
That's amazing!
You're good at this kind of thing.
Any requests?
I've got one! I want a cat.
Coming right up!
Here you go!
That's not what I wanted!
I mean, it is, but not like that!
Akari-chan, why don't you try doing one?
Okay!
It's hard to pour it right.
You're good at it!
Akari, you sure love drawing yourself.
I told you, it's a bear!
It's because of my buns again, isn't it?
You sure like bears, Akari.
Rum raisin is the ultimate topping!!
My friend's daughter bought it,
but it wasn't quite how she imagined.
I took it off her hands since
I thought you could wear it.
But...
I'd never look good in something this cute.
Success!
Do your homework already.
I will!
Hey, what's wrong with you?
If she'd take her studies more seriously,
she wouldn't panic so much at test time.
She's acting weird.
Is she depressed about something?
Is it because I took some of her lunch the other day?
Or because I made fun of her
during the physical exam?
Or...
She's taking her homework so seriously!
She must finally feel motivated.
Sakurako...
Okay!
Let's play cards!
Huh? Don't you like cards?
Then how about...
Pop-up Pirate?
What?!
She brought that over?
Could there be some reason she refuses to study?
Like some sort of painful memory, perhaps.
Seriously, what's wrong with her?
Just what is she worrying about?
Sakurako...
Is there something bothering you?
Yeah, you!
No, not really.
Well, this is you we're talking about.
You wouldn't ever worry about anything.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Can you even hear me?!
Boobs.
Shut up.
I barely even whispered that.
Maybe since she reacted to that,
her boobs are what's bothering her!
This has happened before.
Don't tell me they grew again!
And when are mine going to grow?!
When will you grow, boobs?! Tell me!
She seems a little upset.
Does she hate studying that much?
Perhaps it makes her realize how stupid she is.
But if she never learns to study, she'll never improve.
What she needs is tough love.
Sakurako.
Yeah?
I have something important
to tell you. Listen closely.
What?
Well, you see,
you certainly are stupid,
but don't let that get you down.
Also, um...
It's not as though I...
d-dislike that about you.
She suddenly called me stupid and then tried to cheer me up!
Oh, sheesh!
I'm done!
I don't want to study anymore today!
What? What are you saying?
I can't focus in this environment!
You're supposed to be helping me study,
but you've been thinking about some other thing!
What?
I've been thinking about you this whole time!
Huh?!
Wh-What are you talking about?
A-Are you stupid?
Stupid, stupid!
You shouldn't call people stupid.
Isn't that what you did a minute ago?!
Fine. Hurry up and help me study!
Thank goodness.
She wants to study now.
Huh? She's in a good mood now.
What was she worrying about, anyway?
Okay, Sakurako, what's the answer to this one?
It's not boobs... is it?
What?
Oh?
This is surprisingly...
While I have it on, I guess I'll go for a walk.
Not many people come around this—
Hey, if it isn't Ayano!
T-Toshinou Kyouko?!
Wh-What are you doing here?
I'm on my way home from Yui's place.
I stopped to buy some comics too.
Huh? Those clothes were mine.
What?!
Yeah, without a doubt.
I'm the one who sewed this ribbon on.
So the friend who took it was your mom, huh?
This is too embarrassing!
I'm going to get changed!
Hey, no, wait!
Who cares? You look good in them!
Really? I don't look weird?
Not at all! You look super cute!
We should go visit that park if you're free.
All right, then.
Just for a bit.
There.
You look pretty good in that.
Toshinou Kyouko, did you buy this to wear it?
Yeah.
I planned on wearing it to an event
since it looked like one from a comic,
but it wasn't as frilly as I wanted.
This is a cosplay outfit?!
I'm glad, though!
It looks good on you.
It's Tarim Basin blazin'!
Tarim Basin... blazin'...
Blazin'...
Isn't it unfair for you to react like that?
Um...
Don't worry about it.
Keep the puns coming, Wyoming.
Now you're trying to be considerate?
Does she do them subconsciously?
By the way, what kind of comics did you buy?
Oh, right...
The new Mirakurun.
That wouldn't be...
WITCH GIRL
Yep! That's the outfit I wanted to make.
Awakened Mirakurun!
Do you read comics?
Well, I read some.
Like the four panel ones in the paper.
Oh, those?
Sometimes I read girl's comics too.
Really?!
Mirakurun's a girl's comic!
Why don't you give it a try?
You can borrow my copy.
You really like it, don't you?
What's wrong with that? You don't have to laugh.
Sorry, sorry.
Sheesh!
I'm thirsty. I'm going to get something to drink!
What would you like? I'll treat you.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Thanks. I'll have a lemon tea, then.
Got it. Red bean soup, right?
That's not even close.
I'm just kidding.
It was red bean soup, right? I know.
Lemon tea!
Huh?
I hadn't thought about it until now, but isn't this...
a d-date?
Wh-What am I going to do?
Suddenly I feel so nervous.
I wish I hadn't noticed.
Thanks for waiting.
Sorry.
There wasn't any red bean soup there,
so I got you lemon tea.
Don't make me retort again.
Cider
Masochist
We were talking just fine up until a minute ago.
It's just the two of us.
I should work up some courage today.
Um...
Hey...
Wh-What is it?
Oh, sorry. It's not important.
You go first.
Toshinou Kyouko, what do you
enjoy besides comics?
Let's see...
I just do whatever comes to mind.
Like today I made pancakes at Yui's place.
Oh? That sounds fun.
Oh, right!
Here.
What are they?
The cookies I baked at Yui's place.
You can have them!
What?
We made them together.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Hey, what were you going to say earlier?
Don't worry about that. It wasn't important.
Now I'm even more curious!
It really was nothing important.
I was just thinking about that cloud.
It kinda looks like Akari arching her body backwards.
It really wasn't important.
What do you enjoy doing, Ayano?
Taking baths, I guess.
I like thinking about things in the tub.
In the tub, huh?
You're thinking about something stupid again, aren't you?
Oh, I like collecting character merchandise too.
Really? Like from what?
Stuff like the Three Jellyfish Sisters.
Ah, the three stuck together, right?
The Three Jellyfish Sisters
Yeah, that!
I didn't know you liked that.
Well, I mean, it's too embarrassing to bring anything to school.
Really?
I wouldn't be embarrassed even wearing a Mirakurun cosplay.
Well, you should be.
Oh, no! I had to go home early today.
Thanks for hanging out with me.
Oh, sure.
Later.
Toshinou Kyouko!
Um, let's...
Never mind. It's nothing.
Let's hang out together again!
Fine, if you insist!
Take good care of those clothes.
I will. Thanks for today.
I guess sometimes...
it's important to challenge yourself.
What's wrong?
Were you asleep?
Oh, no.
I left my pillow case out!
I need to get it in before Akari sees it.
If she sees it...
What... is this?
It's not what you think, Akari!
This is a little...
more love than I can handle.
I'll be staying at Yui-chan's place from now on.
Bye.
Akari, wait! Don't leave me!
Akari!
Just thinking about it makes my heart race.
I love you, Onee-chan.
I love you.
Her smile is like magic.
Just thinking about it calmed me down so much.
But this is no time to be calm!
I'm about to lose that smile!
Sorry, Tomoko.
Huh?
I'm done for the day.
What? Do you feel sick?
I feel fine.
I need to put that pillow case away!
Please, Akari!
Please still be at Yui-chan's place!
She came home already.
Onee-chan!
Did your lecture finish already?
Y-Yeah.
L-Listen, Akari...
No!
Stay away!
Onee-chan?
I'm sorry. I'm the worst.
I should just die.
What?!
Now that you hate me and reject me,
I...
What are you talking about?
You told me to stay away!
Oh, I didn't mean it like that.
The thing is...
I made these.
My friend taught me how to make them.
Are those cookies?
I wanted to thank you for being so nice to me.
Yui-chan helped me.
I was going to wrap them up nicely,
but you came home before I could.
Sorry if they're not to your liking.
I'm sure I'll find them delicious.
After all, my dear little sister made them for me.
I love you.
Hurry up and try them!
Certainly.
But first, do you mind going upstairs for a minute?
They're delicious!
You're amazing, Akari.
These taste like something you'd buy at the store.
Really?
I'm glad.
Huh? You're only eating one bite?
It would be a waste to eat it all at once!
I'll eat it a little at a time.
Oh, you...
Sugiura
Aya-chan?
You still haven't changed out of that?
Just a little longer.
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
seishun hajimeyou (wan tsuu san hai)
Let's get started with youth (one, two, three, go)
hitomazu hashiru zo (wan tsuu san hai)
First up, let's get running (one, two, three, go)
minna ga egao de (wan tsuu san hai)
Everyone's smiling bright (one, two, three, go)
kore ga seishun da (wan tsuu san hai)
Now this is youth (one, two, three, go)
haru sakuramochi wo tabeyou
Spring! We'll eat sakuramochi
natsu kakigoori de kimari
Summer! Gotta have shaved ice
aki yakiimo wo hoobari
Fall! Stuff your cheeks with sweet potatoes
fuyu yuki de mata kakigoori
Winter! Shaved ice again with the snow
mou iccho
One more time!
haru kyoushitsu wo machigaete
Spring! Going to the wrong classroom
natsu shukudai wo wasurete
Summer! Forgetting my homework
aki marason de biriketsu
Fall! Finishing last in the marathon
fuyu kotatsu ni chouki taizai
Winter! Staying late in the kotatsu
ichinen sanbyaku rokujuugo nichi
All year long, three-hundred sixty-five days
tokidoki sanbyaku rokujuuroku nichi
And sometimes three-hundred sixty-six days
iroiro aru kedo zenryoku zenkai
There's a lot to do, but we've gotta go all out, all in
zenshin zenrei tanoshimou yo
And enjoy youth with all our souls
yoo yoyoyoyo
Yo yo-yo-yo-yo!
enjoi enjoi jojojojojoi
Enjoy, enjoy, jo-jo-jo-jo-joy!
acchuuma seishun (oorai)
Youth blows by in a flash (all right)
mabushii yo seishun (ooesu)
Youth is bright and beautiful (oh yes)
nemuke sayonara kokoro no hitomi wo bacchiri akeyou
Wave away sleep, keep the eyes of your heart wide open
acchuuma seishun (donmai)
Youth blows by in a flash (don't mind)
mou supiido seishun (faito)
Youth runs like a beast (fight)
mabataki shiteccha oishii tokoro minogashichau yo
Blink for a second, and you'll miss the best parts
chuui
Careful!
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
I'm off.
Sept
Onee-chan!
That's way too little at a time!
YuruYuriCrossReview
Akari Body Pillow
Size: 152 cm
Weight: 1.2kg
Material: 100%
Polyester Cost: Priceless
Yuru Yuri Cross Review!
What exactly is this?
YuruYuriCrossReview
Akari Body Pillow
Size: 152 cm
Weight: 1.2kg
Material: 100%
Polyester Cost: Priceless
I'm not sure, but people in this world
have all kinds of tastes.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Size: 152 cm
Weight: 1.2kg
Material: 100%
Polyester Cost: Priceless
Hurray!
I didn't know there was a huge collect-
able of me. I'm so happy!
It makes me seem like a heroine. It's
kind of embarrassing.
Ehehe.
Both the fabric and
printing are superb.
I feel like I've seen it
somewhere before.
Ugh, I can't remember where! My head
hurts!
There's a body pillow with Akari-chan
on it? And not one of Yui-senpai?
Just the thought of one put me in a
good mood, so I'll give this an 8.
Someone, please make me one!
<4indentation>I don't really want to
<4indentation> poke my nose into
<4indentation>other people's affairs.
And it's not good to
frown upon someone else's tastes.
Well, Akari looks happy about it, so I
guess it's okay.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Size: 152 cm
Weight: 1.2kg
Material: 100%
Polyester Cost: Priceless
Akari Body Pillow
Hurray!
I didn't know there was a huge collect-
able of me. I'm so happy!
It makes me seem like a heroine. It's
kind of embarrassing.
Ehehe.
Both the fabric and
printing are superb.
I feel like I've seen it
somewhere before.
Ugh, I can't remember where! My head
hurts!
There's a body pillow with Akari-chan
on it? And not one of Yui-senpai?
Just the thought of one put me in a
good mood, so I'll give this an 8.
Someone, please make me one!
<4indentation>I don't really want to
<4indentation> poke my nose into
<4indentation>other people's affairs.
And it's not good to
frown upon someone else's tastes.
Well, Akari looks happy about it, so I
guess it's okay.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Akari Body Pillow
Size: 152 cm
Weight: 1.2kg
Material: 100%
Polyester Cost: Priceless
Size: 152 cm
Weight: 1.2kg
Material: 100%
Polyester Cost: Priceless
Hurray!
I didn't know there was a huge collect-
able of me. I'm so happy!
It makes me seem like a heroine. It's
kind of embarrassing.
Ehehe.
Both the fabric and
printing are superb.
I feel like I've seen it
somewhere before.
Ugh, I can't remember where! My head
hurts!
There's a body pillow with Akari-chan
on it? And not one of Yui-senpai?
Just the thought of one put me in a
good mood, so I'll give this an 8.
Someone, please make me one!
<4indentation>I don't really want to
<4indentation> poke my nose into
<4indentation>other people's affairs.
And it's not good to
frown upon someone else's tastes.
Well, Akari looks happy about it, so I
guess it's okay.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Akari Body Pillow
Size: 152 cm
Weight: 1.2kg
Material: 100%
Polyester Cost: Priceless
Hurray!
I didn't know there was a huge collect-
able of me. I'm so happy!
It makes me seem like a heroine. It's
kind of embarrassing.
Ehehe.
Both the fabric and
printing are superb.
I feel like I've seen it
somewhere before.
Ugh, I can't remember where! My head
hurts!
There's a body pillow with Akari-chan
on it? And not one of Yui-senpai?
Just the thought of one put me in a
good mood, so I'll give this an 8.
Someone, please make me one!
<4indentation>I don't really want to
<4indentation> poke my nose into
<4indentation>other people's affairs.
And it's not good to
frown upon someone else's tastes.
Well, Akari looks happy about it, so I
guess it's okay.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Akari Body Pillow
Hurray!
I didn't know there was a huge collect-
able of me. I'm so happy!
It makes me seem like a heroine. It's
kind of embarrassing.
Ehehe.
Both the fabric and
printing are superb.
I feel like I've seen it
somewhere before.
Ugh, I can't remember where! My head
hurts!
There's a body pillow with Akari-chan
on it? And not one of Yui-senpai?
Just the thought of one put me in a
good mood, so I'll give this an 8.
Someone, please make me one!
<4indentation>I don't really want to
<4indentation> poke my nose into
<4indentation>other people's affairs.
And it's not good to
frown upon someone else's tastes.
Well, Akari looks happy about it, so I
guess it's okay.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Akari Body Pillow
Hurray!
I didn't know there was a huge collect-
able of me. I'm so happy!
It makes me seem like a heroine. It's
kind of embarrassing.
Ehehe.
Both the fabric and
printing are superb.
I feel like I've seen it
somewhere before.
Ugh, I can't remember where! My head
hurts!
There's a body pillow with Akari-chan
on it? And not one of Yui-senpai?
Just the thought of one put me in a
good mood, so I'll give this an 8.
Someone, please make me one!
<4indentation>I don't really want to
<4indentation> poke my nose into
<4indentation>other people's affairs.
And it's not good to
frown upon someone else's tastes.
Well, Akari looks happy about it, so I
guess it's okay.
YuruYuriCrossReview
Akari Body Pillow
Hurray!
I didn't know there was a huge collect-
able of me. I'm so happy!
It makes me seem like a heroine. It's
kind of embarrassing.
Ehehe.
Both the fabric and
printing are superb.
I feel like I've seen it
somewhere before.
Ugh, I can't remember where! My head
hurts!
There's a body pillow with Akari-chan
on it? And not one of Yui-senpai?
Just the thought of one put me in a
good mood, so I'll give this an 8.
Someone, please make me one!
<4indentation>I don't really want to
<4indentation> poke my nose into
<4indentation>other people's affairs.
And it's not good to
frown upon someone else's tastes.
Well, Akari looks happy about it, so I
guess it's okay.
Hurray!
I didn't know there was a huge collect-
able of me. I'm so happy!
It makes me seem like a heroine. It's
kind of embarrassing.
Ehehe.
Both the fabric and
printing are superb.
I feel like I've seen it
somewhere before.
Ugh, I can't remember where! My head
hurts!
There's a body pillow with Akari-chan
on it? And not one of Yui-senpai?
Just the thought of one put me in a
good mood, so I'll give this an 8.
Someone, please make me one!
<4indentation>I don't really want to
<4indentation> poke my nose into
<4indentation>other people's affairs.
And it's not good to
frown upon someone else's tastes.
Well, Akari looks happy about it, so I
guess it's okay.
Hurray!
I didn't know there was a huge collect-
able of me. I'm so happy!
It makes me seem like a heroine. It's
kind of embarrassing.
Ehehe.
Both the fabric and
printing are superb.
I feel like I've seen it
somewhere before.
Ugh, I can't remember where! My head
hurts!
There's a body pillow with Akari-chan
on it? And not one of Yui-senpai?
Just the thought of one put me in a
good mood, so I'll give this an 8.
Someone, please make me one!
<4indentation>I don't really want to
<4indentation> poke my nose into
<4indentation>other people's affairs.
And it's not good to
frown upon someone else's tastes.
Well, Akari looks happy about it, so I
guess it's okay.
Akari Body Pillow
Hurray!
I didn't know there was a huge collect-
able of me. I'm so happy!
It makes me seem like a heroine. It's
kind of embarrassing.
Ehehe.
Both the fabric and
printing are superb.
I feel like I've seen it
somewhere before.
Ugh, I can't remember where! My head
hurts!
There's a body pillow with Akari-chan
on it? And not one of Yui-senpai?
Just the thought of one put me in a
good mood, so I'll give this an 8.
Someone, please make me one!
<4indentation>
<4indentation>I don't really want to
<4indentation> poke my nose into
<4indentation>other people's affairs.
And it's not good to
frown upon someone else's tastes.
Well, Akari looks happy about it, so I
guess it's okay.
What strange tastes.
But if there were one of Yui-senpai...
Huh? Did you say something?
No, nothing at all!
Next episode...
"No Self-Awareness."
Some people are like that, huh?
Next Episode: No Self-Awareness
Yeah, you're right.