yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
too
Go
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
iku zo
Let's go!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
ieaa ieaa
Yeah, yeah
aiteru heya wo haijakku yume no ajito tsukurimasho
Let's hijack an empty room and
turn it into the hangout of our dreams
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
are mo kore mo yaritai tatami no ue wa paradaisu
I wanna do this, I wanna do that, this room's our paradise
(hai) uerukamu (hai hai hai)
(Yeah) Welcome (Yeah yeah yeah)
ocha no ko saisai suisui chacha wo irete gomen nasai
It all went too smooth and easy,
sorry, but I'm going to put on some tea
yuru yuri san hai yuru yuri san hai
Yuru Yuri, ready go, Yuru Yuri, ready go
hangurii seishin ii jan osenbei futon kajittara
I'm feeling super hungry, I think I'll have this cracker pillow
(hai) non non
(Yeah) No, no
nayamigoto wa minai furi oshiire ni shimaimashou
Let's pretend our troubles don't exist,
shove them into the closet
asatte no hougaku muita nara
And do something completely random
hissatsu yuru yuri dondengaeshi
Take this! Yuru Yuri Non Sequitur!
kimi to iru dake de chiisana atarimae no koto demo
When I'm with you, even the smallest, simplest things
okashikute (hai hai)
Can be so funny (Yeah yeah)
nukedasenai (hai hai)
I never want to leave (Yeah yeah)
sugoku ii yo ne kono shunkan (san hai)
I love these moments so much (Ready go)
hyaku en demo tanoshimeru yo
It's fun for less than a hundred yen
nooberu shou dai hakken
A huge discovery worth a Nobel Prize
shiawase wa sugu tonari ni aru
Happiness is always right by you
saikouchou chochochocho choo
It's the best! Best-best-best-best-best!
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
mainichi dotabata koushinchuu
Every day's a crazy parade
tuu tuu tuu tuu kamon kamon
Doo-doo-doo-doo, come on, come on
kochira wa gorakubu ii tokoro
This is the Amusement Club, a great place to be
yuru yuri yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
san hai
Ready, go
yuru yuri yuru yuri
Yuru Yuri Yuru Yuri
goo
Go
The Invisible Face is There.
I guess Akari and Chinatsu aren't here yet.
What? You're going to read?
You just spent all day in the classroom reading!
I've almost finished this.
Cut it out, idiot!
It worked, didn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, show me some attention.
Sheesh...
So now you're ignoring me on purpose?
All right, then!
If it hurts, just stop.
Sniffle, sniffle.
Yui won't play with me.
Me sob, me sob, me-sob-otamia.
Now she's going for sympathy.
Oho, what a poor girl!
Don't cry, sweet young girl!
Now this is something.
I see, I see.
You're lonely because you're all by yourself.
All right!
Kyouko-Kyouko Toshinou Kyupin!
There we go!
I used magic to make you a friend.
I'm Yui.
Hooray! It's Yui!
Yui, you're looking a little square.
Oh, you think so?
Body cutting magic!
You're hurting her!
Come on, Yui. Have a seat.
Do you know how to sit properly?
Yep, you bet!
Your lower half seems broken. Are you okay?
Don't worry about me.
By the way, I ain't got no head.
Mind doing somethin' about that?
My character's all over the place.
Whoops, sorry about that.
I'll make a wonderful head for you at once!
Done!
There. I made a wonderful head for you.
Whoa, you're as handsome as ever, Yui!
Come on, now. Don't be embarrassed!
Hey, Yui-nyan!
Guess she's bored of playing by herself.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You two took a while.
Class ran a little late.
We got a lot of English homework.
It's just a floor cushion, Akari-chan.
Sheesh. I thought it was a person.
Oh, it fell again.
What's it supposed to be anyway?
A Yui dummy.
Yui's too engrossed in her book
to pay attention to me,
so I've been playing with that.
You're so hopeless, Kyouko.
Anyway, what are we doing today?
Oh? You're going to play with us?
Yeah, right after I go to the bathroom.
But first, give me back my track suit.
Okay!
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Hot Springs
Table Tennis
Smells of Death
BUNICAN
Is this book that interesting?
Huh? Where are our cushions?
Now that you mention it, they're missing.
Oh, I used them for the dummy.
What?
I-In other words, my cushion...
has been inside Yui-senpai's track suit?!
Chinatsu-chan seems to be having fun.
There's no doubt about it!
Um...
Could I at least have my cushion back?
Ah, sorry. I couldn't help myself.
So should we do our homework?
Yeah. We do have a little extra today.
Kyouko-chan, you're a fast reader.
I'm back.
You shouldn't touch people's
books without permission.
Hey!
I said hey!
Huh?
Kyouko, wanna play?
Hello!
The culprit is the protagonist's—
Homework?
Yeah.
English is so hard.
English, huh?
Want me to teach you?
Repeat after me!
Apple!
A-Apple?
Apple?
Where did you get that?
My relatives gave me a bunch,
so I brought some.
Let's eat them together.
You have a lot!
There's more where those came from.
My bag's full of them.
Let's give a penalty to anyone
whose gums bleed eating them.
You're eating them like that?!
What are you doing?
My front teeth are stuck and won't come out.
I'll get a knife.
They're really stuck in there.
Shall I bring you a hammer?
Oh, they're out.
Here I go!
You can be pretty shaky, you know.
I'll be fine.
Kyouko-chan?!
Did you cut your hand?!
Hey!
I was expressing the apple's feelings.
Don't make us worry, you idiot!
Sheesh...
Sorry.
Geez...
Please try to behave yourself, Kyouko-senpai!
That sure surprised me,
but do you think apples might actually feel pain?
What?
You're pretty good at that.
Right? I've been practicing.
I want to give it a try too!
Let's go get knives for everyone, then.
While we're at it, let's make some tea.
I'll help too.
See you.
Did you cut some up, Kyouko-chan?
You cut yourself!
Quickly, to the nurse's...
What should we do?!
Sorry.
Kyouko-chan, stop making jokes like that!
My heart's racing.
Were you shot through the heart?
Shut up.
You'll end up cutting yourself for real.
Wait... Chinatsu-chan,
what did you do with the tea?
I'm glad it didn't get on our clothes at least.
Yeah, true.
Chinatsu-chan, you seem really disappointed.
Well, let's pull ourselves together and...
Chinatsu-chan, haven't you
ever peeled an apple before?
I haven't!
Well, here I go.
Is it peeling?
So thin!
This is hard!
I'm sure.
That's pretty amazing.
My eyes feel tired now.
Want me to finish it for you?
Oh, Yui-senpai...
This is a collaboration of love, isn't it?
Please go right ahead.
Could we use this?
For what?
World peace.
It won't work.
Done.
Look, it's a bunny.
How cute!
You're pretty good.
My sister taught me how to make them.
Let me get a closer look.
Sure!
I see. Rabbits, huh?
We've still got plenty more.
How about we take some
to the student council?
Good idea.
Let's cut some up to take.
I'll make more bunnies.
I want to make some too.
Akari-chan, teach me how.
Yeah, sure.
How about we do all of them as rabbits?
Good idea.
Let's do our best.
Kyouko-Kyouko Toshinou...
Hey. Stop summoning things.
God is telling me...
to offer him a rabbit.
Right. Just hurry up and cut them.
After cutting a V shape into the skin,
you peel half the apple from the back.
Then you add these.
And you're done!
Wow, so you use seeds as eyes.
How cute.
All right, I'll give it a try!
Don't get too excited. Take it easy.
I made one!
Chinatsu-chan, you've improved too.
Oh, Yui-senpai!
I'm done too.
That's amazing!
Wrap...
Are you going to thank your parents again?
Hello!
Toshinou Kyouko!
What are you doing here?
I acquired a bunch of apples,
so I came to share.
They look delicious!
They sure are cute.
You made these?
Oh, I made this one here.
What?!
How dexterous.
We peeled them together.
Help yourself to them.
What a great catch!
Thank you very much.
We'll certainly eat them.
By the way, Sakurako, a catch refers to fishing.
Huh?
Then what do you call what you get from hunting in the mountains?
Overhunting!
That's not very positive.
Maybe you'd say "a good catch" in hunting too.
Though you'd write it differently.
You might be right.
I'll look it up later.
You always scold me about looking things up
right away when I don't know something.
Did you say something?
See you later.
You owe us one.
Thank you!
Would you like some, President?
It seems like a waste to eat them.
Do we need to?
Well, they are apples.
We should eat them soon.
Thanks for the food, then!
No!
Hold on. Could I have that one?
Well, sure, if you really want it.
Thank you.
Sugiura-senpai, you're such a glutton.
Huh?
You shouldn't compare her to yourself.
I'll have this one, then.
So good! These rabbits are delicious!
It's strange.
They seem to taste better
when they're cut differently.
We're eating live rabbits!
I'd better take a picture.
Maybe I'll make bunnies for my sister next time.
I'm sure she'd like that.
We delivered them.
They loved them!
We finished washing the dishes.
Good work.
Could you put these on that shelf?
Okay.
I'm glad we didn't end up with any cut fingers.
But...
It's an emergency!
We need to disinfect this immediately!
Lick, lick, lick, lick.
I wish you could have treated my injury.
I think I'd be happiest if you
didn't get hurt in the first place.
Senpai!
Hey! Licking Chinatsu-chan is my job!
What?
I'd lick really gently and slurp.
Now you cut yourself?
Yui, lick it.
No way!
I'd better practice
. . . just in case . . .
It's coming down pretty heavy out there.
Should we close the curtains?
Hold it right there!
You mustn't look away from life's storms.
Stop pretending to be so insightful.
Being in nature and encountering nature...
Sometimes standing up against nature...
And other times...
We've had enough of that.
Let's go check out the rice field.
You'll die.
We can't take the boat out in this weather!
Are we trapped on this island?
What is this, a mystery novel?
Trapped on a remote island.
One by one...
we disappear.
You're the murderer?!
I disappeared in a different way!
That was close.
The power's out!
I'm scared!
This is getting more and more
like a mystery novel!
Be careful you don't die!
It's dangerous, so try not to move around.
Okay.
The first person to leave the room
is the first person to get killed.
It's a death flag!
No, it's not!
It's pitch black.
I want to go the bathroom,
but I'll have to hold it.
I hope the power comes back soon.
My eyes have adjusted to the dark.
You can kind of tell where people are now.
Like the idiot playing over there.
I can't hold it anymore!
Yui-chan, I'm using your bathroom!
Don't, Akari! Think of the death flag!
Akari!
Who did this to you?!
Th-The wall.
Ow...
Akari-chan, is your head okay?
Yeah.
It's dangerous to walk around in the dark.
Also, that's not where I hit it.
There was a flag, after all.
Yeah, yeah.
I hope the light comes on soon.
Light up, Akari.
I don't light up!
It's boring in the dark with nothing to do.
Yeah.
Hot pot in the dark!
I thought you'd say that.
I'm bored.
Be patient.
Yeah, but...
Are there any games we can play in the dark?
Like becoming dotted lines?
What kind of game is that?!
We could probably play word games
like shiritori or riddles.
Oh, that could work!
Chinatsu-chan?
What's wrong? Is she afraid of the dark?
There, there...
Ow!
What was that for?
I could ask you the same thing!
You're so mean. How could you hit a girl?
Just try to behave yourself.
Okay.
Kyouko-senpai's pulling pranks at a time like this?
Yeah, pretty much.
What should I do?
I guess there's nothing else.
I'll make funny faces.
Since it's dark, no one can see anything.
Has the weather gotten worse?
It's like a typhoon out there.
I'm glad we decided to stay over.
Chinatsu-chan, are you afraid of thunder?
You doing all right?
It's a little scary.
But since I'm with all of you,
I feel a little reassured.
Really? That's good.
And if it comes down to it,
I'll just cling to you, Yui-senpai.
Don't mind me.
Really? That's—
Akari-chan, how are you doing?
I'm fine.
I used to find it really scary when I was little,
but now I'm in middle school.
You don't need to act so tough.
Really, I'm fine!
That was loud.
That sounded close!
Oh, Akari-chan. Listen to you scream.
So the thunder does scare you.
I have Yui-senpai, so I'm fine.
It wasn't that!
Kyouko-chan had a weird face!
So mean!
How could you call my face weird?
Why would you say that?!
That's not what I meant!
I always believed I was a beautiful young girl.
Isn't that a problem itself?
Anyway, Kyouko-chan was being weird!
What are you talking about, Akari?
That's normal!
How rude!
Geez... Everyone's getting the wrong idea
because you're saying weird things, Akari.
What?!
Uh, sorry.
There, see!
Is something wrong?
Maybe it's because she hit her head earlier.
Do you know about the wolf girl?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I'm just checking to see if there's
anything weird in here.
She did it.
I didn't do anything!
Yay, cabbage rolls!
We can finally eat.
Huh?
There's no meat.
They're 100% pure.
Those are real cabbage rolls for you.
It's just cabbage, then.
Cabbage is good by itself, though.
Is this a rabbit?
We made them with apples,
so I thought it might work with sausages.
They're hard to eat when they're so cute.
Yeah.
That's not a compliment.
A shrimp?
I tried cutting the carrots decoratively.
It's needlessly elaborate!
You're way too good at this!
Kyouko-chan, that's amazing!
I want to cut something even cooler for our next hot pot.
Shouldn't it be the taste
you try to improve?
I'm just at that age where you're not satisfied doing anything normally.
You're the only one like that!
Come to think of it, Akari-chan,
did you ever go to the bathroom?
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
seishun hajimeyou (wan tsuu san hai)
Let's get started with youth (one, two, three, go)
hitomazu hashiru zo (wan tsuu san hai)
First up, let's get running (one, two, three, go)
minna ga egao de (wan tsuu san hai)
Everyone's smiling bright (one, two, three, go)
kore ga seishun da (wan tsuu san hai)
Now this is youth (one, two, three, go)
haru sakuramochi wo tabeyou
Spring! We'll eat sakuramochi
natsu kakigoori de kimari
Summer! Gotta have shaved ice
aki yakiimo wo hoobari
Fall! Stuff your cheeks with sweet potatoes
fuyu yuki de mata kakigoori
Winter! Shaved ice again with the snow
mou iccho
One more time!
haru kyoushitsu wo machigaete
Spring! Going to the wrong classroom
natsu shukudai wo wasurete
Summer! Forgetting my homework
aki marason de biriketsu
Fall! Finishing last in the marathon
fuyu kotatsu ni chouki taizai
Winter! Staying late in the kotatsu
ichinen sanbyaku rokujuugo nichi
All year long, three-hundred sixty-five days
tokidoki sanbyaku rokujuuroku nichi
And sometimes three-hundred sixty-six days
iroiro aru kedo zenryoku zenkai
There's a lot to do, but we've gotta go all out, all in
zenshin zenrei tanoshimou yo
And enjoy youth with all our souls
yoo yoyoyoyo
Yo yo-yo-yo-yo!
enjoi enjoi jojojojojoi
Enjoy, enjoy, jo-jo-jo-jo-joy!
acchuuma seishun (oorai)
Youth blows by in a flash (all right)
mabushii yo seishun (ooesu)
Youth is bright and beautiful (oh yes)
nemuke sayonara kokoro no hitomi wo bacchiri akeyou
Wave away sleep, keep the eyes of your heart wide open
acchuuma seishun (donmai)
Youth blows by in a flash (don't mind)
mou supiido seishun (faito)
Youth runs like a beast (fight)
mabataki shiteccha oishii tokoro minogashichau yo
Blink for a second, and you'll miss the best parts
chuui
Careful!
seishun oorai seishun ooesu
Youth, all right, youth, oh yes
seishun ouka harikitte iku zo
Youth, all in, come on, let's go
seishun donmai seishun faito
Youth, don't mind, youth, do it
seishun saikou ieaa ieaa ieaa ieaa
Youth, awesome, yay yay yay yay
YuruYuriCrossReview
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Hot Springs
Table Tennis
Smells of Death
BUNICAN
Railroad Gourmet Serial Murders · Hot Springs Table Tennis Smells of Death
Publisher: BuniCan Books
Author: Mochi Shigeomi
Price: 605 yen (with tax)
Printing House: Yahata Print
A Mystery Raspberry Award Winner
Yuru Yuri Cross Review!
Damn, I can't believe she spoiled that.
The descriptions of delicious food made me hungry.
YuruYuriCrossReview
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Hot Springs
Table Tennis
Smells of Death
BUNICAN
Railroad Gourmet Serial Murders · Hot Springs Table Tennis Smells of Death
Publisher: BuniCan Books
Author: Mochi Shigeomi
Price: 605 yen (with tax)
Printing House: Yahata Print
A Mystery Raspberry Award Winner
BUNICAN
YuruYuriCrossReview
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Publisher: BuniCan Books
Author: Mochi Shigeomi
Price: 605 yen (with tax)
Printing House: Yahata Print
A Mystery Raspberry Award Winner
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Hot Springs
Table Tennis
Smells of Death
It was a pretty tough read, but I man-
aged to finish.
The food in it sounded
really delicious, so it gets 8 points!
Now I'm scared of riding trains, though.
I only read it to find out
who the killer was before
Yui could, but it was
pretty interesting.
The trick he used was pretty out there,
so opinions will probably be mixed.
There weren't any hot springs table
tennis scenes, so it loses points.
I want my time back!
He invented a device that can warp
through space to overtake the train?
What's with that?
He should be winning Nobel Prizes, not
robbing trains and murdering people!
<4indentation>I haven't been scared
<4indentation>like that in a long time.
<4indentation>Ignoring the hints that
the murderer is an inventor, how is
anyone supposed to see through that
timetable trick?
The unbelievable sequence of events at
the end will leave you drained.
YuruYuriCrossReview
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Hot Springs
Table Tennis
Smells of Death
BUNICAN
Railroad Gourmet Serial Murders · Hot Springs Table Tennis Smells of Death
Publisher: BuniCan Books
Author: Mochi Shigeomi
Price: 605 yen (with tax)
Printing House: Yahata Print
A Mystery Raspberry Award Winner
Railroad Gourmet Serial Murders
It was a pretty tough read, but I man-
aged to finish.
The food in it sounded
really delicious, so it gets 8 points!
Now I'm scared of riding trains, though.
I only read it to find out
who the killer was before
Yui could, but it was
pretty interesting.
The trick he used was pretty out there,
so opinions will probably be mixed.
There weren't any hot springs table
tennis scenes, so it loses points.
I want my time back!
He invented a device that can warp
through space to overtake the train?
What's with that?
He should be winning Nobel Prizes, not
robbing trains and murdering people!
<4indentation>I haven't been scared
<4indentation>like that in a long time.
<4indentation>Ignoring the hints that
the murderer is an inventor, how is
anyone supposed to see through that
timetable trick?
The unbelievable sequence of events at
the end will leave you drained.
YuruYuriCrossReview
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Hot Springs
Table Tennis
Smells of Death
BUNICAN
Railroad Gourmet Serial Murders · Hot Springs Table Tennis Smells of Death
Publisher: BuniCan Books
Author: Mochi Shigeomi
Price: 605 yen (with tax)
Printing House: Yahata Print
A Mystery Raspberry Award Winner
Publisher: BuniCan Books
Author: Mochi Shigeomi
Price: 605 yen (with tax)
Printing House: Yahata Print
A Mystery Raspberry Award Winner
It was a pretty tough read, but I man-
aged to finish.
The food in it sounded
really delicious, so it gets 8 points!
Now I'm scared of riding trains, though.
I only read it to find out
who the killer was before
Yui could, but it was
pretty interesting.
The trick he used was pretty out there,
so opinions will probably be mixed.
There weren't any hot springs table
tennis scenes, so it loses points.
I want my time back!
He invented a device that can warp
through space to overtake the train?
What's with that?
He should be winning Nobel Prizes, not
robbing trains and murdering people!
<4indentation>I haven't been scared
<4indentation>like that in a long time.
<4indentation>Ignoring the hints that
the murderer is an inventor, how is
anyone supposed to see through that
timetable trick?
The unbelievable sequence of events at
the end will leave you drained.
YuruYuriCrossReview
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Hot Springs
Table Tennis
Smells of Death
BUNICAN
Railroad Gourmet Serial Murders · Hot Springs Table Tennis Smells of Death
Publisher: BuniCan Books
Author: Mochi Shigeomi
Price: 605 yen (with tax)
Printing House: Yahata Print
A Mystery Raspberry Award Winner
It was a pretty tough read, but I man-
aged to finish.
The food in it sounded
really delicious, so it gets 8 points!
Now I'm scared of riding trains, though.
I only read it to find out
who the killer was before
Yui could, but it was
pretty interesting.
The trick he used was pretty out there,
so opinions will probably be mixed.
There weren't any hot springs table
tennis scenes, so it loses points.
I want my time back!
He invented a device that can warp
through space to overtake the train?
What's with that?
He should be winning Nobel Prizes, not
robbing trains and murdering people!
<4indentation>I haven't been scared
<4indentation>like that in a long time.
<4indentation>Ignoring the hints that
the murderer is an inventor, how is
anyone supposed to see through that
timetable trick?
The unbelievable sequence of events at
the end will leave you drained.
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Hot Springs
Table Tennis
Smells of Death
BUNICAN
Railroad Gourmet Serial Murders · Hot Springs Table Tennis Smells of Death
YuruYuriCrossReview
It was a pretty tough read, but I man-
aged to finish.
The food in it sounded
really delicious, so it gets 8 points!
Now I'm scared of riding trains, though.
I only read it to find out
who the killer was before
Yui could, but it was
pretty interesting.
The trick he used was pretty out there,
so opinions will probably be mixed.
There weren't any hot springs table
tennis scenes, so it loses points.
I want my time back!
He invented a device that can warp
through space to overtake the train?
What's with that?
He should be winning Nobel Prizes, not
robbing trains and murdering people!
<4indentation>I haven't been scared
<4indentation>like that in a long time.
<4indentation>Ignoring the hints that
the murderer is an inventor, how is
anyone supposed to see through that
timetable trick?
The unbelievable sequence of events at
the end will leave you drained.
YuruYuriCrossReview
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Hot Springs
Table Tennis
Smells of Death
BUNICAN
Railroad Gourmet Serial Murders · Hot Springs Table Tennis Smells of Death
It was a pretty tough read, but I man-
aged to finish.
The food in it sounded
really delicious, so it gets 8 points!
Now I'm scared of riding trains, though.
I only read it to find out
who the killer was before
Yui could, but it was
pretty interesting.
The trick he used was pretty out there,
so opinions will probably be mixed.
There weren't any hot springs table
tennis scenes, so it loses points.
I want my time back!
He invented a device that can warp
through space to overtake the train?
What's with that?
He should be winning Nobel Prizes, not
robbing trains and murdering people!
<4indentation>I haven't been scared
<4indentation>like that in a long time.
<4indentation>Ignoring the hints that
the murderer is an inventor, how is
anyone supposed to see through that
timetable trick?
The unbelievable sequence of events at
the end will leave you drained.
YuruYuriCrossReview
RAILROAD GOURMET
serial murders
Hot Springs
Table Tennis
Smells of Death
BUNICAN
Railroad Gourmet Serial Murders · Hot Springs Table Tennis Smells of Death
It was a pretty tough read, but I man-
aged to finish.
The food in it sounded
really delicious, so it gets 8 points!
Now I'm scared of riding trains, though.
I only read it to find out
who the killer was before
Yui could, but it was
pretty interesting.
The trick he used was pretty out there,
so opinions will probably be mixed.
There weren't any hot springs table
tennis scenes, so it loses points.
I want my time back!
He invented a device that can warp
through space to overtake the train?
What's with that?
He should be winning Nobel Prizes, not
robbing trains and murdering people!
<4indentation>I haven't been scared
<4indentation>like that in a long time.
<4indentation>Ignoring the hints that
the murderer is an inventor, how is
anyone supposed to see through that
timetable trick?
The unbelievable sequence of events at
the end will leave you drained.
It was a pretty tough read, but I man-
aged to finish.
The food in it sounded
really delicious, so it gets 8 points!
Now I'm scared of riding trains, though.
I only read it to find out
who the killer was before
Yui could, but it was
pretty interesting.
The trick he used was pretty out there,
so opinions will probably be mixed.
There weren't any hot springs table
tennis scenes, so it loses points.
I want my time back!
He invented a device that can warp
through space to overtake the train?
What's with that?
He should be winning Nobel Prizes, not
robbing trains and murdering people!
<4indentation>I haven't been scared
<4indentation>like that in a long time.
<4indentation>Ignoring the hints that
the murderer is an inventor, how is
anyone supposed to see through that
timetable trick?
The unbelievable sequence of events at
the end will leave you drained.
It was a pretty tough read, but I man-
aged to finish.
The food in it sounded
really delicious, so it gets 8 points!
Now I'm scared of riding trains, though.
I only read it to find out
who the killer was before
Yui could, but it was
pretty interesting.
The trick he used was pretty out there,
so opinions will probably be mixed.
There weren't any hot springs table
tennis scenes, so it loses points.
I want my time back!
He invented a device that can warp
through space to overtake the train?
What's with that?
He should be winning Nobel Prizes, not
robbing trains and murdering people!
<4indentation>I haven't been scared
<4indentation>like that in a long time.
<4indentation>Ignoring the hints that
the murderer is an inventor, how is
anyone supposed to see through that
timetable trick?
The unbelievable sequence of events at
the end will leave you drained.
Railroad Gourmet Serial Murders
It was a pretty tough read, but I man-
aged to finish.
The food in it sounded
really delicious, so it gets 8 points!
Now I'm scared of riding trains, though.
I only read it to find out
who the killer was before
Yui could, but it was
pretty interesting.
The trick he used was pretty out there,
so opinions will probably be mixed.
There weren't any hot springs table
tennis scenes, so it loses points.
I want my time back!
He invented a device that can warp
through space to overtake the train?
What's with that?
He should be winning Nobel Prizes, not
robbing trains and murdering people!
<4indentation>I haven't been scared
<4indentation>like that in a long time.
<4indentation>Ignoring the hints that
the murderer is an inventor, how is
anyone supposed to see through that
timetable trick?
The unbelievable sequence of events at
the end will leave you drained.
I'm not really happy with that ending, though.
Really?
Next episode...
"It'll Be an Unforgettable Day."
Next Episode: It'll Be an Unforgettable Day
Some days are special or important.
Every day is special and important to me.