Akarin!
Here!
Sway 'n Shake starts now!
Ding!
Dong!
Wh-What's going on?!
Ding!
Dong!
We know you're in there, Akari.
Get out here.
If you don't wake up soon, we'll be late.
Kyouko?
Yui?
What do you mean by...
...late?
No way!
I'm Akari Akaza.
I'm a little clumsy, but I'm a lively girl.
Things are pretty frantic this morning, but I'm really excited!
Because I'm...
Kyouko, Yui, sorry to keep you guys waiting!
We're late.
Definitely...
I forgot that I'm a middle schooler now!
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 1
Middle School Debut!
This is so embarrassing!
This turned out just as we thought, huh?
Yeah, well, it's not like we couldn't have seen it coming.
Next time, you have to beef up your image!
But seriously, we're really gonna be late.
Oh, shoot! I'll go change right away.
Yui, you mind if we take a stroll?
Where?
Inside her house!
Come to think of it, it has been a while since we've been in Akari's house.
Yeah, I guess.
Peek!
Stop that.
Hey, Yui,
they match!
Sorry for keeping y-
Don't play around with another girl's panties!
Sorry, sorry.
Let's go to school, already!
AAAAAA
Big Sister's Room
♠
No Trespassing
A peek couldn't hurt.
Wo-
What the-
Lately, my panties have been going missing.
Like that one pair of crabby panties.
Akari, have you ever been inside your sister's room?
Well, I've never been allowed in there for as long as I can remember.
But I guess privacy's important between sisters.
Yeah, that's for the best...
I want to join the student council so that I can make this a better school for everyone.
Already acting like an honor student?
Are you stupid or something?
What was that?!
You want a piece of me?!
Next, Akaza.
Ah, right!
Um... my name is Aka-
Next time, you have to beef up your image!
That's right. I am a middle schooler now.
Shot through your hearts and I'm to blame!
Nice to meet you all.
My name is Akari Akaza~pyon!
Am I receiving hatred instead of love?
My name is Akari Akaza...
I'll be with you for our first year...
Akaza, what club will you be joining?
I'll be joining the Amusement Club!
Let's say it together!
AAAAAA
Tea Ceremony Club
Akari, congratulations on entering a new school and joining a club!
Yay! Let's celebrate!
What are we waiting for?
Cheers!
It's been a while since the three of us have been at school together.
Not since our elementary school graduation last year, right?
I'm glad I can be with you guys again.
Akari...
Take this key of love.
This is the key to our nest of love!
What are you guys planning on doing with me in the room?
It's just the key to the clubhouse.
Oh? It was only the club's key...
Now that you mention it, what exactly is the Amusement Club?
And why are we in the tea room?
Oh, right, we haven't told you yet.
This was the tea ceremony club's room,
but that club disbanded, and no one uses this room anymore.
So we're sort of like secretly using it.
We usually come here during break to laze around.
I see. Taking it easy is nice, huh?
So what do we actually do?
That's it.
We just laze around as much as we want!
What?!
That's so boring, though!
Because... I've finally become a middle schooler.
Lazing around is fine,
but isn't there something more exciting we can do?
I see... something "exciting," huh?
Exciting?
Something... exciting...
Exciting!
I-I'm sorry! Please stop!
I know!
Turning trains into jet-coasters would be exciting, right?
That's so scary, though...
It is?
Then how about a super fast ferris wheel?
How exactly would people get on?
It'd stop only for that.
That's sadistic.
But doesn't that make you want to go to an amusement park now?
I love the merry-go-round the most!
That's not for someone who wants excitement.
The same goes for the ferris wheel...
Then what should we do?
Excitement, huh?
It's a bit cliché, but...
We...
We could talk about love.
Love?
Is there someone you like, Akari?
I like the both of you!
Th-Thanks...
What about you, Kyouko?
I like myself the best.
Yeah, I kinda figured that...
What about you, Yui?
Me? Well...
There's no one in particular, I guess...
There just aren't many exciting things to do...
It's best if you don't have any expectations for middle school.
It's only the first day of school,
and you're already giving up on your dreams?!
Oh, wow! It's the latest edition of Magical Girl Mirakurun!
By the way, I read the Mirakurun fan comics you gave me, Kyouko.
They were super interesting!
Really?!
Yep! Your drawings have improved a lot!
I really have a long way to go, though.
Will your next fan comic be Mirakurun, too?
Of course!
Shine on, Miracle Run-Run Energy!
Miracle Pretty Change!
The magical girl of love and justice: Mirakurun...
...makes her appearance!
Ever since I started making fan comics,
I find writing Mirakurun stuff the most fun!
What do you know? I already have my excitement!
As long as I have Mirakurun, I'm happy!
E-Excuse me!
My name is Chinatsu Yoshikawa.
U-Um... I'd like to join your club!
Mi-
Mirakurun?!
My proud older sister;
so beautiful and kind-hearted;
so gentle.
I've always wanted to be like her.
Like her...
Just like her!
This isn't the tea ceremony club?
Yeah. It was short on members, so it disbanded.
Disbanded?!
Then there's nothing here?
You know, this is-
Hey! You're that girl in my class who made that awful introduction!
Come to think of it, you were sitting right next to me.
What kind of introduction did she give?
My name is Kyouko Toshinou.
This is the Amusement Club now!
It's not the tea ceremony club,
but I believe that you're meant to be here!
Calm down!
Sorry about that. She's excited for all the wrong reasons.
I'm Yui Funami by the way.
I'm sorry, but I really just wanted to join the tea ceremony club...
If that's the case, you don't need to worry.
If we gather enough new members, we can revive the tea ceremony club.
So why don't you stay with us until then?
The tea-making supplies are all here,
so you can practice too!
You're just saying that...
Well?
S-Sure...
Nice to meet you, Chinatsu.
Nice to meet you, too.
So why the tea ceremony club, Mirakurun- I mean, Chinatsu?
My older sister was in it, so...
It's nice for new students to have interests they want to pursue.
I wonder if it's okay for us to be lazing around.
Why?
Well, maybe we should be experiencing our youth like the other clubs are doing.
But you know-
I'm happy as long as I have Mira- Chinatsu.
Don't scare the new girl like that!
Ow... I haven't even done anything to her...
Chinatsu, if anything happens to you, tell me right away.
I'll protect you.
I will protect you.
That's not fair! I'm not gonna do anything weird!
You mean it?
Absolutely!
So let's go buy Mirakurun's transformation set!
Were you even listening to me?
Give me a minute.
Hey!
Did you know there's a cheap sweets shop nearby?
Really?!
Wanna go?
I'll treat you two in celebration of entering middle school.
Hooray!
This way's faster.
Mirakurun's Transformation Set of Love and Justice!
Just bought!
Now then, Chinatsu-
They're gone!
One week later...
Akari, let's head to the clubhouse.
Sure.
Since then, Chinatsu seems to have settled into the Amusement Club.
Thank goodness!
Akari, you go first.
Okay...
Chi-na-tsu!
Hello,
Yui!
Dang!
The tea's done.
Thank you so much, Chinatsu!
H-Here you go, Yui.
Thank you.
It's good.
Now I see why you're so eager to join the club.
It's delicious, Chinatsu!
Stop it, Kyouko!
Chinatsu! Chinatsu!
That hurts!
Cut it out.
Yui...!
There, there.
Hey, Yui! Don't steal my Chinatsu.
Chinatsu, you're so cute!
Kyouko, I'm suffocating!
Hey, Kyouko!
Chinatsu! Chinatsu!
I'm suffocating! Save me, Yui!
Kyouko! Enough already!
So you were here.
Very funny!
I came here with Chinatsu!
I've been thinking about this lately...
Haven't you kinda faded into the background?
Th-That's not true!
You started out like the main character in a school anime,
but ever since Chinatsu joined the club, I hardly even notice you anymore.
Yui, say that's not true!
That can't be true, right?!
I'm sorry...
You still haven't said anything!
Let's hold a meeting to discuss Akari's future.
The future of Akari's middle school life depends on this meeting!
You don't have to make such a big deal of this...
Being in the background sure is tough.
Allow me to show you a few examples:
During P.E., when the teacher says to form groups of two,
you'll have no partner, and will ultimately pair up with the teacher.
When you don't receive your pudding at lunch they'll say, "There's a pudding left over!"
And the girls will start playing for it right in front of you.
And then...
Okay, I get it!
Applying New Traits
We'll show them on my go.
About-face!
All your sound effects
will be "Akarin"
Booby Missiles
Invisible Girl
And when you add them all together,
you'll look like this.
You're so mean!
My stomach hurts...
Akarin!
Chinatsu, say something!
I'm not... laughing...
Liar!
The meeting for Akari's future, part two.
I'll put my faith in you guys this time.
The physical embodiment of presence is...
...Magical Girl Mirakurun!
If you have the qualities that make you look like a main character,
your existence will be overwhelming!
Develop into a Main Character
Now, then, once you think of something, put it in this box.
Show-off girl
What a terrible name...
There are fewer than I expected.
Yay! I wonder what I'll be like.
The Secrets to Being a Super-Conspicuous Main Character!!
Directed by Kyouko Toshinou
Oh, no! It's this late already?!
Always oversleeps
Geez... Why did no one wake me-
Girls rain from the sky
Oh, no!
I really need to get to school!
High adaptability
That's right! It's supposed to rain this afternoon.
What the heck is this?!
Finds a legendary sword
I only have three minutes left!
I'm gonna be scolded by the teacher!
Someone, stop the time!
It stopped.
Lucky!
Now's my chance!
Hidden powers awaken in times of crisis
What is this?! Cut!
What's wrong?
The next quality is a bit pointless, but...
No, it's not that. I just don't get all of this.
Yeah, me neither.
Cheer up, Akari.
Yeah! After all, you have plenty of good qualities.
Yui, Chinatsu...
That's right. If you ask me, you're...
...a good girl.
Yeah! A good girl.
Also, you're...
That's right! An amazingly good girl.
Yeah! You're a really good girl!
That's it? Aren't there any other qualities?
Akari, Akari.
"Your extraordinary quality is that you have no extraordinary quality."
You're just toying with me, aren't you?
If that's how it's gonna be...
I won't rely on anyone anymore!
I'll show you a new me with my own blood, sweat, and tears!
This is the first time I've seen you like this.
You're serious about this, aren't you?
You're on fire, Akari!
I'm declaring this now!
My strategy to prove my existence is...
...is...
Is?
Is?!
...is...!
Kyouko Toshinou!
Ayano?
What's with you?!
Pardon us, girls.
M-My...
My existence!
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
Akarin here!
Did you guys enjoy the Sway 'n Shake anime?
I play a major role starting in the next episode, too,
so don't miss it, okay?
The next episode's focus will be on the student council?
With so many people appearing, my existence is definitely in trouble!