Akarin!
Here!
Sway 'n Shake starts now!
Kyouko!
Come on!
Don't steal my only job!
Sorry about that.
I'm trying to understand anime more,
so how about we change it to this?
A Quick Gag
A gag?
Why a gag?
What're you doing?
Just watch.
Three, two, one...
What's with that face?
Amazing! I wanna try that, too!
Me, too!
It's easy.
First, imagine your ideal face,
then rub your cheeks.
I did it!
It really is easy!
I failed...
It's because you didn't imagine it right.
It's alright. I think it suits you fine.
I'm gonna be more beautiful than both of you!
Yeah, right! Then show us!
Show us!
Chinatsu, not you too!
Pretty good, Yui!
You look wonderful!
You're so cute!
Daijiken!
What a big event!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 06
Art Arter Artist
I wish this burning hot summer would end,
so fall could get here already...
Toshinou.
Toshinou!
A first-year's calling you.
A first-year?
I was looking for this!
Thanks for picking it up!
Excuse me. There's something I want to ask you...
How did your drawings get so good?
How?
What practice methods do you use?
There's only one important thing.
Only one?
Wh-What is it?
It's heart!
Conviction!
And willpower!
You said only one, but there's three?!
And lastly, heart!
You already said heart...
Do you understand?
See, the most important thing is to have fun.
What? Something else now?
Also...
Ouch!
You're supposed to help out today.
Is that so?
Alright, let's go.
Okay, okay.
Sorry 'bout that, first-year. See you again sometime.
Th-Thank you...
Honestly, you only teach people useless things.
I've got it!
I wonder if Yui noticed my letter yet...
My heart's pounding...
This is so embarrassing!
But I wanted her to know how I feel.
Because these feelings...
These feelings are special!
Kyouko!
Thank goodness. You waited for me.
Yui!
This letter...
I read it earlier.
I never knew you thought of me like this...
Yui... I love you!
Thanks for being my best friend all this time.
And from now on–
Thank you, Kyouko.
Let's be together forever.
I love you, too.
Yui!
Chi-Chinatsu...
S-Sorry.
I couldn't stand it, so my hand just...
No, that's fine, Chinatsu...
Well, after seeing how motivated that first-year from yesterday was,
my inner artist got all fired up.
What?
Do you get the meaning of this picture story?
What is it?
If you don't know, I will teach you, my pet.
Yui loves me with all her heart!
Which means she'll never ever be yours!
What are you talking about?
Chinatsu, you can just ignor–
I don't like that!
But in Yui's place, you can have me!
I don't want you!
Guys, calm down! Do you even know what you're saying?
This picture story is about the miracle of love between me and Yui.
This picture story...
I'll... tear it... to pieces!
By the way, that's just a copy. The original's here.
Hey! Stop right there!
I-I'm gonna make an even better picture story.
I'll leave you speechless, Kyouko!
Bring it on, Chinatsu.
What a ridiculous chain of events...
The next day
AAAAAAAAAAAA
Why Won't it Stop? Throbbing, Beating Paradox: Eternal
So, I've made my own picture story.
"Why won't it stop? Throbbing paradox"?
What a complete title...
I was thinking of Yui while I was drawing it,
so it turned out really nice!
I'm very satisfied with it, so I hope you all enjoy.
Now, I shall begin!
Yui
Once again, the prince rides through the plains on her white horse.
With the wind in her hair, she decides to bravely let go of the reins.
Scary!
Yui
Eventually, she realizes that she has come much farther than usual.
While gazing upon the unknown landscape,
a single young lady catches her eye.
Me
She was not the kind of gorgeous lady that you might see in a castle.
Indeed, she was quite a miserable-looking girl.
Geez. What's wrong?
Oh, nothing! It's just so good that I'm in shock.
W-Why?!
How could those drawings be produced by our cute Chinatsu?
To think there was such a bomb hiding within her...
Akari's eyes turned white from shock!
She hasn't said a word today.
The poor girl.
However, the girl's smile was more beautiful than any jewel.
Intermission's over...
Scary!
My image of Chinatsu is crumbling!
As if she had been struck by lightning, the prince's body lost all feeling.
When she came to, she found herself standing dauntingly before the young lady.
Their eyes met, and in that moment...
With their hearts pounding, and chests throbbing...
Their thoughts became a paradise!
In that moment, the two eternally fell in love!
Very interesting!
You're amazing! I'm definitely speechless!
Well, this is just the first half of my epic tale...
Right? That was beautiful, right, Akari?
Then I'll read the rest now.
Y-Yui?!
Chinatsu... Thank you for your wonderful picture story.
I'm overjoyed...
I'm happy, too!
I'm happy, too, Yui!
So, how was it?
Was it to your liking?
Yeah, your drawings are pretty good.
You mean it?!
Well, this is my specialty.
R-Really? That's amazing!
Yui's doing her best...
For you to be this happy...
I'll read the rest with more heart.
Let's play with clay.
Clay?
I found it while I was cleaning my room.
I thought something like this would happen, so I brought it with me!
What did you think would happen...?
But I have to continue my picture stor–
I'd like to play with clay...
Somehow, I can't resist kneading some clay.
Clay. Clay. Clay.
Yui...
Clay, clay...
If Yui says so...
Hey! Is this paper clay?
No, it's oil based.
But doesn't oil clay smell?
It sure does.
But it doesn't harden, so you can play with it as much as you want.
Now it's time for our second activity.
Making art out of clay!
Then you can look forward to the rest of my picture story tomorrow.
This really brings back memories!
I really liked it a lot.
Yay!
Look, it's a bunny!
No matter what she does, Akari's always so normal.
Oh, come on! Don't flatter me!
Now, what should I make?
How about a giraffe?
Got it.
Done!
Its neck!
Akari.
My severed head?!
Runny nose.
Drool.
Hair Bun Bazooka.
Stop messing with my head!
Sorry, sorry. I'll make something else.
My head!
Yui's making...
...dumplings.
How cute.
You're such a natural!
W-What should I make next?
How about a cat?
A cat it is!
Oil clay's so mushy; this just won't stand up...
That's amazing, Kyouko!
Is that Mirakurun?
You're really good.
No, it's Chinatsu... pretending to be Mirakurun!
With her legs spread!
Stop it! I'll never be able to marry now!
The only one I want to show that kind of pose is you, Yui.
I-It's fine if you don't...
The dumplings are multiplying...
I think I'll use the washroom.
That cat you made is really cute!
I'm pretty proud of it.
By the way, have you heard about the second-year's class trip?
Naturally, not yet.
Naturally?
Where are you going?
Kyoto and Osaka.
Sounds nice.
I want to go with you.
Yui and me will be in the same group.
We'll be sleeping in the same room, too.
You're not gonna try anything, right?
Who knows...
What do you mean by that?!
Of course we won't.
I'd like to go on a trip with just the four of us.
Yeah, maybe to a hot spring or something.
Bathing with Yui?!
I wonder if there's someplace we can go to by ourselves.
I'm sure there is.
I'll look into it.
I'm back!
Welcome back!
What'd I miss?
We were talking about taking a trip.
A trip?
We're thinking that the four of us should go to a hot spring.
Sounds fun!
Who did this?!
Who else but Kyouko?
I thought it'd look cute.
Ta-da!
I made a different pair of legs.
Scary...
I-I was so proud of it...
Sorry...
I said to cut that out!
Akari, what would you like as a souvenir from our trip?
You'll buy me one?!
Yeah.
I'll take anything.
Where're you going?
Kyoto. Osaka, too.
Now they're pastries...
What could we get as a souvenir besides pastries?
A wooden sword?
Chinatsu, would you like a wooden sword?
Yes. In fact, I'd like one very much right now.
What's wrong?
That was a surprise.
I thought they had fallen off.
How could that happen?
This looks pretty good for something I made.
It'd be a waste to break it.
Just break it already.
Alright! I'll decorate this room with it!
No, you won't!
Then, my house.
I said no!
Why at your house, anyway?
Then, Yui's house.
It'll keep you company on lonely nights, since you live alone.
Hey...
That's...!
But if it's at Yui's...
A few days later
Hey, is it okay if we come to your place tomorrow?
We need to know if you put that Chinatsu model up properly.
You have put it up, right?
I guess that's okay, but...
...tomorrow, my little cousin's coming over.
Your cousin?
So even if we can't hang out, would you still wanna come over?
We can come? I love kids!
I like them too!
Then it's settled.
Tomorrow, we're heading to Yui's place!
Yay!
She's so cute!
She has the model I made!
She looks just like you, Yui.
Mari, can you say "good afternoon"?
Good afternoon.
Yui.
You see...
...and then...
C'mere for a sec, Kyouko, Akari.
It seems like she's shocked to see the actual Mirakurun here.
Chinatsu does look like her...
Then let's strip you for Mari's sake, Chinatsu!
Excuse us for a minute.
What are you doing?
Ta-da!
It's Mirakurun!
Again, I thought something like this would happen.
Seriously, what did you think would happen?
Really? Are you really Mirakurun?
C'mon. Do what I taught you earlier.
O-Okay...
The magical girl of love and justice: Mirakurun!
Makes her lovely squat!
Hey, isn't something wrong?
Wasn't it "makes her appearance"?
Also, the pose...
I thought it'd be funny, so I made up a few things.
Mirakurun, use some magic!
Magic?!
There's no way I can do that.
This is where Kyouko should do a good follow-up...
You're doing good!
Follow-up, will you?!
Hurry, hurry!
Okay!
I'm about to use some magic!
Mirakurun Rainbow!
Oh, dear me! My wand broke!
Mari, it looks like I can't use magic anymore.
S-Scary...
H-Hey Chinatsu, be more gentle with that-
Even if you say tha–
M-Mari! Mirakurun said she'll go for a walk with you.
You'll go, right?
Hey, what's that?
Cosplay?
Oh, yeah, she's from that anime.
Everyone's looking at me...
I'm so embarrassed!
I'm so happy I get to walk with Mirakurun!
R-Really?
I'm glad you're enjoying it.
But I really want to stop...
Wait... this might bridge the gap between me and Yui!
Looking after a child... you're so wonderful.
Let's get married!
Then I'll just have to bear it.
Mirakurun, your face is scary...
No, it's not. It's not scary, Mari!
That was close!
What is it?
These...
You want some?
Use this.
Use this as a substitute, since your wand broke.
Mari...
Thank you. With this, I'll be able to use magic again.
Really?
Well, then, let's buy everyone some sweets.
We're back.
Welcome back.
How was it?
Really fun!
I think so, too.
Chinatsu, you're really good with children, aren't you?
Mari, where are you going?
Bathroom.
Good work.
Amazing. You've really become Mirakurun!
I thought you would give up half-way through.
Nope. If I really try, it's a piece of cake.
You're extraordinary, Chinatsu.
But seriously, I'm exhausted.
My civility's all used up.
Now, now, have plenty of this 100% fruit juice!
Gee, thanks.
So refreshing!
Good work, Chinatsu.
Of course.
Who would actually enjoy wearing this costume?
Mari!
Yui.
Life's pretty sour, huh?
I somehow got the feeling she was a fake.
What exactly happened?
Everyone! I made my own picture story!
AAAAAA
Akari 's Friends
Just now?
Th-That's because I put my all into it!
What's it about?
Read it, please!
Now! C'mon!
Um... Akari's special characteristic picture story is starting!
AAAAAA
Akari 's Friends
The End
I got the page order wrong!
Gimme a second and I'll fix it!
The poor girl...
Where's the first page?!
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
People call me the red protagonist, Chitose Ikeda here.
I wonder what they mean by "red."
Next time is a Christma–
I wonder if I'll have enough blood for the next episode?