Wait up!
Hey, Kyouko, stop sobbing!
But...
Yui!
Transform: Leaf Mask!
Pain, pain, fly away!
To the ends of the universe, go fly away!
Kyouko laughed.
Because you're...
Here, take my hand.
Thank-
Ow!
If you lick scrapes like these, they'll heal in no time!
Um... What about today's title call?
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 11
Our Amusement Club
Ah! So cute!
Yui, even when you were little, you were so brave and cool!
Oh, my! if you keep praising me like that, I'm gonna get all embarrassed!
She wasn't talking about you.
Is this one from when we had that fight?
I think you're right.
You guys had a fight?
No, not like that.
Some random girl picked a fight with us.
There're always brats, huh?
I think it went something like...
Whaddya you wanna play today?
I know, Captain Yui! I want to play on the swings!
I'd like to play on the slide...
Alright! Let's compromise and head for the jungle-gym!
Hold it right there.
This is my turf!
You can't just come and play here!
What are you talking about?
T-The playground's for everyone...
Not true! Right now, this is my turf!
Who decided that, and when?
What hour? What minute? What second?
How many times had the Earth spun around?
It doesn't matter. It's mine!
This is stupid.
Let's just leave her alone and play.
You there. Come here.
M-Me?
That's right. Hurry up and come here.
What is it?
If you want her safely returned, get lost!
She took Kyouko hostage!
You're a coward!
Let go of Kyouko!
Don't touch me! I bet you have cooties!
Cootie touch!
Then I'll touch you back.
I have a barrier right now so no touch-backs!
What school do you go to?
I don't recognize you.
I'm not telling.
I just came to play at my grandma's house today.
What?
Boss, this dame is from outta town.
If you don't leave here soon,
I don't know what'll happen to this girl.
Maybe I'll roll your cheeks and turn them into manju.
Or perhaps I'll turn your hair into a topknot.
What frightening things...
Boss, this broad's a scumbag!
Yui... Save me...
Tormenting my friends is unforgivable!
Eat this!
Special Move: Yui Kick!
That hurt! Now you've done it!
You coward! Fight fair-and-square!
Stop it! Bullying's not good!
Transform: Bullyin' Ain't Good!
How lame...
An opening! Cootie touch!
I-I had a barrier up that time, too!
These are cooties that penetrate barriers!
Y-You tomboy!
Two-faced!
Savage!
Pipsqueak!
I don't like this girl!
Lieutenant Akari, protect Kyouko!
Roger!
Let go of me!
You let go of me!
Yui, that's enough! Let's just go home!
No! I won't give in to this selfish girl!
But...
It's alright. I'll protect you, Kyouko!
Chi!
It's Mommy.
Your grandma's calling for you.
Come back with me.
Okay.
I'll let you off for today.
That's my line!
Sorry, Kyouko... Were you scared?
No... You were really cool.
Hogging the whole playground for herself is unforgivable!
Just as Yui says!
It looks like everyone's having a fun time.
Mommy!
I know! I'll take a picture!
This is a picture from that day.
Man, I was so young back then.
Quit acting like a middle-aged man.
But still, I can't believe Kyouko was such a crybaby back then.
You sure you didn't just make up your character?
T-That's rude...
And what about you, Akari?
You thought things like "Leaf Mask" were funny or something?
Yui, you were pretty mischievous back then, weren't you?
But your sense of justice was strong. You were so cool!
What the heck? She's only adoring Yui...
I'm gonna kiss you, ya shrimp.
Even so, I can't forgive that little brat!
Honestly!
If she were here right now, I'd totally beat her up!
Violence isn't good, though.
But I wonder how that girl's been raised.
She was so selfish back then.
I bet she's still a problem child.
Picking a fight with Yui...
Being selfish beyond help...
If she was so ill-natured back then, it's obvious she's still mean.
I didn't see anything...
Nothing...
Come to think of it, Yui,
in that picture you showed me before, your hair was pretty long.
That was around when I was in kindergarten.
Didn't you cut your hair when we entered grade school?
Why?
It was because you were a crybaby,
so I thought I'd better be more reliable.
You're so wonderful for taking care of someone!
I see...
What's with that reaction?
Nothing. Just thinking how much better you were back then.
Again with that.
Wouldn't you say I'm still good now, madam?
Who're you calling "madam"?
I really get the feeling Kyouko was better in the past.
Right?
And back then, even Akari stood out more than Kyouko.
I really think you were better back then, Kyouko!
She's dead serious...
She definitely had more innocent charm than she does now.
I wonder how she came to be like this.
What's with you guys?!
Yui, you idiot!
I love you, Chinatsu!
Also, Akarin!
What's with... that goodbye?
Not watching where you're going is dangerous, Ayano.
You're right.
Thank you, Kyouko Toshi-
I had a pop quiz today,
but I didn't do all that well.
That must've been hard on you, Akari.
But it's important that you study a bit every day.
How'd you do, Chinatsu?
I didn't do that well, either...
Are you two preparing for your lessons properly?
You can't just neglect the basics.
Okay...
But during the test, there was this girl talking, so I couldn't concentrate.
Oh, my. That's just awful.
I wonder if she was even aware of the trouble she caused.
Kyouko, the other day I bought some Rum Raisin.
It was the extra large container.
Oh, how nice.
Although, you shouldn't overeat.
You're a girl, so eating too many sweets is a no-no.
I get it, already.
What's this "off" feeling?
Fellmann's culminating theory... It's so profound.
Who the heck are you?!
Who is this person?!
Breasts Forbidden
I see. It's because she hit her head.
This?
I got it from carelessly falling down the stairs a while ago.
But, aside from this bump, there's nothing wrong,
so don't worry.
But there is...
What should we do? How are we gonna fix this?!
For now, let's go talk to someone reliable.
Is she really... Kyouko Toshinou?
Yes.
What are you telling me?
I won't accept it!
Now, now. Calm down, Ayano.
Oh, sorry about that.
Don't worry about it, my dear Ayano.
It's a lie!
A Kyouko Toshinou like this just isn't possible!
What's with "my dear Ayano"?!
It's no good! I'm getting the chills!
It'd be nice if this happened to Sakurako...
If ya have something to say, say it straight, you Boob Demon!
At any rate, this is quite the problem.
You never change, Chitose.
I think you should really go to the hospital.
I know.
Instead of going to the hospital in this situation,
hitting her again should fix her right up.
Y'think so?
Wait here a sec.
This is what we have right now.
Why are these in the student council room...?
Take the one you prefer.
What is it?
So, we're gonna watch over her for now.
I see...
But there aren't really any problems...
This Kyouko is a pretty decent person.
It's alright, Kyouko!
You'll return to normal!
Akari?
I really don't like this!
You're always the glue that holds us together!
Akari...
I don't really get it,
but I think you're just as good at keeping us together, Akari.
Since we were little, you've always been so cheerful.
It makes me want to try my best.
Please pull us along from now on.
M-Maybe it's fine like this...
That was fast!
By the way, I noticed it earlier,
but this is the tea ceremony clubhouse, right?
That's right...
I originally wanted to join that club,
but I got to meet Yui, so it turned out alright!
T-Thanks...
Since the tea ceremony club disbanded, we, the amusement club, took over this room.
Such an irresponsible thing won't do.
The misuse of a clubhouse is outrageous.
If you stop and think about it, this is bad, isn't it?
Hey, Kyouko!
Yui! Lemme copy your notes!
Again?
If you keep staying up late, you'll always sleep in class.
Then how about we exchange diaries?
I'm gonna hit you...
Getting distracted during class isn't a good idea.
And then-
It's Kyouko.
Are you two heading for class?
Yeah, pretty much...
I see. Make sure you're not late.
See you.
What's wrong, Chinatsu?
Normally she would...
Chinatsu!
S-Stop it!
Meeting at such a place...
We must be bound by the red thread of fate!
Yui! Save me!
Kyouko, I'm here, too!
Don't ignore me!
You're right...
Well... I don't really get it, but I'm glad.
Whenever I hung around with her, she'd always try to glomp me.
For me... it's kind of painful.
Akari?
If I'm not ignored, it feels like I've lost my weak existence role...
Chizuru.
You found this book before I did, right?
Here.
Chizuru!
What's up?
Big Sis...
I was so scared...
I don't really get it, but don't be afraid.
Yes? Come in.
Excuse me.
K-Kyouko Toshinou?
Ayano, may I have a moment?
S-Sure...
That Toshinou actually knocked before coming in.
She's usually around your level of audacity...
That's right, my leve-
What do you mean?!
Well, you and Toshinou act the same.
No need to compliment me.
I wasn't really complimenting-
It's about the tea ceremony clubhouse.
I apologize for misusing it all this time.
I know I've caused you trouble, but I will take care of this matter soon.
Take care of it? What do you plan on doing?!
You're the one who created the amusement club.
We must abide by the rules, right?
It's alright. Yui and the others will understand.
Well, then. Sorry for coming when you're all so busy.
Good morning.
Morning.
Are you two not going to the clubhouse today?
W-We're going.
Right?
O-Of course!
I have to get closer to Yui while I can!
Let's get going, Akari.
See you later, Himawari, Sakurako.
Thanks to Kyouko Toshinou being so mature lately,
I've been getting so much work done!
You don't have to push yourself, Ayano.
I'm not pushing myself!
I-I'm...
With Toshinou like that, I haven't been getting any nosebleeds lately.
It doesn't feel right.
That sounds healthy...
The amusement club is disbanded as of today.
No way!
Why, Kyouko?!
I gave it some thought,
and I really believe misusing a clubhouse like this isn't acceptable.
Besides, the amusement club doesn't consist of any actual activities.
Are you... serious, Kyouko?
Yes.
You understand, don't you, Yui?
From today on, this is the amusement club's room!
Could you not declare the misuse of this place?
Besides, what's the 'amusement club' anyway?
Fun stuff.
I still don't get it.
Since we're finally middle-schoolers,
don't you want to do all sorts of strange and interesting things?
This place will serve as our secret base for doing those things.
Secret base...
Let's make it, Yui. Our amusement club!
Geez. There's no helping you, Kyouko.
I don't want that.
I don't ever want that to happen!
Yui?
It's true that you always cause trouble...
You lack common sense...
You're self-centered...
But...
...that's what was fun!
Not knowing what I'd get myself into,
I'd always go along with your reckless ideas.
But that was fun!
I loved the fun times you gave me...
That's why... I want you back.
Come back!
Go back to the way you were!
Me, too!
I like the old Kyouko better!
I... To be honest, I'm not sure I like the old Kyouko.
But...
I really want you back the way you were!
Come back, Kyouko!
You guys...
Sorry, Kyouko.
This is the only way...
Kyouko Toshinou!
Today, I'll make you leave this place for sure!
It's a match!
I accept!
If you lose, I'll have you two join the amusement club, okay?
I just won't lose, then!
Akarin!
Now, everyone! Follow me!
Let's head towards the setting sun!
Let's run off into the sunset!
This amusement club's the best in Japan!
I'm this main character!
Akari, did you fall down the stairs?
Oh, this?
I carelessly fell down the stairs a little while ago!
But aside from this bump, there's nothing wrong. Don't worry.
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
I'm still your main character, Akari Akaza!
Next week is going to finish with a "last episode-like" story,
so everyone in the Amusement Club will be attending.
I knew it! The amusement club just has to be like this.
Everyone, make sure to watch my final performance right to the end!