Akarin!
Here!
Sway 'n Shake starts now!
I'm Akari Akaza.
I'm a little clumsy, but I'm a lively girl.
This spring, I became a middle schooler. A sparkling first-year!
I'm still not used to middle school life yet,
but there are plenty of new things to do, and every day is full of excitement!
A new school.
New lessons.
New friends.
I still get excited just wearing my uniform.
Every day is just so much fun.
I can make it.
I can still make it!
Yes!
Just in the nick of time!
So you weren't late for class, but you forgot your homework,
and you got more as punishment.
My, my...
Geez, I probably left it on my desk...
It's because you overslept, isn't it?
Help me with my homework!
I'll pass.
Boo!
"Cabbage"?
Your hand...
Oh, this? I thought I'd buy some on my way home.
You should try it so you stop forgetting things.
I see.
Then I'll do just that.
AAA
Akari
Hey!
Daijiken!
What a big event!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 03
Coming over!? ...I'll go, I'll go!
But forgetting things really is annoying.
I always forget where I leave things in my room.
Same here.
And once you're ready to give up, you find it.
I remember this one time I forgot something.
The other day at the movie theater...
One ticket to Magical Girl Mirakurun!
I'm sorry, Ma'am, but the anime tickets are sold downstairs.
It's like declaring that I'm an otaku to people I don't know!
That was so embarrassing!
What does that have to do with forgetting things?
Say, Yui, do you watch movies?
Once in a while.
In that case, do you want to go together next time?
There's a movie I want to see!
Sure.
Yay!
Chinatsu is so cute!
If you let down her hair...
She'd look like this!
What kind of hair style is that?
Where does all that hair come from?
Kyouko's First Delusion
Akari, what's with that hair?
You saw them, didn't you?!
Kyouko's Second Delusion
Akarin!
Akari, what is this?
Don't think too deeply about it.
She read my mind!
These snacks are delicious!
I'd like to eat you, Chinatsu.
You should just ignore her.
Boo!
Lunch break ends before you know it.
Oh, crap! I forgot about my homework!
Just don't leave it behind.
After school...
Ah, I've...
...started living alone.
Cold noodles?
You started making cold noodles?
How did you mishear me?
You're only a middle schooler! Are you okay living alone?
Your parents weren't against it?!
I'll gain life experience,
and the landlord's a relative so my parents didn't really oppose it.
Though, they didn't readily agree to it, either.
You've become so mature!
Living alone...
Holiday
It's Kyouko!
What is this?
I came to do my homework.
What?
And I'm hungry, so while I'm at it, make me some food.
Alright already! Just get in!
Woah, compared to the exterior, this is one fancy apartment.
Originally, it was a cultural hall, but it was remodeled so people could live in it.
Oh, yeah...
Here's the cabbage.
I bought one already!
What's with this laid-back environment?
There are games!
A computer!
Manga!
And fantastic lighting!
Can I bring a pillow?
Don't live here.
Now I'm hungry.
What did I just say?
Just satisfy me with some tasty food.
I don't get you...
I guess I have no choice.
Well, if the others haven't had lunch yet, let's invite them over.
Don't worry. I can eat three helpings.
I wasn't worried about that!
Akari?
Okay, just stay put.
They're close by, but they got a little lost,
so I'm going to meet them.
Okay.
An ex-cultural hall, huh?
That sounds kinda cool!
You think so?
Coming!
Mountain!
What?
Come on. You don't say, "What?".
When I say, "mountain," you say, "river."
What a pain...
Now, let's try again.
Mountain!
River!
Good afternoon.
Coming in.
Welcome, ladies.
Now, then, all together!
Hey, aren't we having lunch?
Kyouko, you've already seen everything.
No, there has to be more surprises somewhere...
What are you looking for?
Why...?
Why don't you have any lingerie?
And why don't you have any bras?
This won't sell as a variety show!
This isn't a variety show!
Then-
I'm hungry!
You just do as you please, huh?
Kyouko, you can't go around bothering Yui like that!
But Chinatsu, Kyouko's always been like this.
Food, food!
Paw.
What are you gonna make?
Something simple.
I'd like omelette rice!
Yui makes it really well.
I wanna try it!
When she was in third grade, she made it perfectly!
That's amazing!
It wasn't perfect.
I just remembered how to make it from helping my mom.
What do you think you're doing?
I want some rum raisin!
That's not meant for lunch. You're just craving it.
I'd be fine eating rum raisin for lunch...
There's no way you would be.
Boo!
We'll get ice cream some other time.
I'll make some delicious pudding for dessert.
Pudding...?
Just when I'm trying to be nice, she gets all resistant...
Did you say something?
It's nothing.
Don't make trouble for her.
Rum raisin!
Yui, the Great One.
Yeah, yeah.
Time to dig in!
Hey, dessert comes after the meal!
Yui, you act like her mother.
I forgot the miso.
I'll go buy it.
Thanks.
Buy some Kokusan rice to go along with it, too.
Okay!
She can be pretty thoughtful sometimes...
Hurry up and go!
Alright!
I think Kyouko's back.
Mountain.
Bird!
River! River! River!
Thanks for the meal.
It's so good!
Yui's home cooking...!
I want to drink your miso soup every day!
Chinatsu, Yui can't protect you... Come to my humble abo-
No, thanks.
Even though I bought the miso...
Cheer up...
Uh, I don't think it's here...
Wasn't it at that item shop from before?
That shop sells medicinal herbs?
A photo album!
May I take a look?
Go ahead.
It's from when we were little.
This brings me back!
Your hair used to be so long.
Yeah.
Yui's so... cute.
Th-Thank you...
What is it?
This picture...
Come here, Kyouko.
What is it, Yui?
I've... always wanted to try this...
Yui, we can't...
It's alright. There's nothing to be afraid of.
She said she'd be done before I could count all the cracks in the ceiling.
That's wrong!
Don't have delusions about what actually happened!
Ow, that hurts!
We were friends back then, so you believe me, right, Akari?
That's never happened, right?
Oh, right. Sorry about that.
How long have you two been friends?
Did it just happen?
How long ago was it?
Our parents got along, so it was kind of...
...natural, I guess.
Why do you ask?
Oh, nothing.
I just want to get along more with the two of you.
Chinatsu!
I'll go get some tissues!
Honestly, this girl is really...
Sorry about that, Chinatsu.
Besides, we already get along just fine.
That's right!
Let's get along, Chinatsu!
I don't feel like I can get along with you, though.
It's all dirty now.
Sorry.
Take off your clothes and I'll wash them.
I'll get you a change of clothes. You can go take a shower.
It's all sticky, right?
And your clothes will stain.
Change into... your clothes?!
I doubt the size will fit, but you should be able to wear them.
I'll wear them! They'll fit!
Welcome, Chinatsu!
What're you doing?!
I'll watch her carefully, so take your time in the shower.
Okay!
No fair! I want to be with her!
Hey! Cut it ou-
You're wearing pajamas!
You finally noticed, Yui.
We'd better be getting home soon.
It's already this late?
It's so comfortable here that I lost track of the time.
Well, that's good.
Make sure you don't forget anything.
I wanna come over more often.
Me, too!
Sure.
Come over any time!
It's my apartment, you know.
Oh, is that right?
Thanks for today, Yui.
I'll wash this right away and return it.
No need to rush.
See you later.
Okay!
We'll come by tomorrow morning.
What a silly main character.
This rum raisin's really good!
Go home!
You just keep leveling up at the same place.
That's right.
You've already leveled up a lot.
Is the next boss really that strong?
No, how do I put it...
The boss fight is easier if you level up a lot first.
I always challenge bosses when I'm just barely strong enough.
You have to use more items if you do that, and you might even lose.
But it feels awesome when you just barely win!
You think so?
Are you really sleeping over?
Yeah, I'm wearing pajamas, after all.
I called my parents earlier.
You wanna have a pancake party with everyone next time?
That might be good.
We could invite Ayano and Chitose, too.
We haven't hung out with them before.
Okay if I turn off the lights?
Roger, Wilco! Good night!
This futon has your scent on it...
Don't sniff it!
Oh, come on...
I'm hungry again...
I want some ramen!
Won't you get fat?
I'll be okay.
Aren't you going to have some?
That's the last one.
Is that so...
Here, you eat half.
But aren't you hungry?
Hey, Yui?
Sorry for sleeping over.
It's probably inconvenient for you.
It's not.
Okay, I'm happy to hear that.
You seem extroverted, but you really get lonely easily.
That's not... true.
You sure?
Is it okay if I visit more often?
It seems there's no choice...
Thanks.
What now?
I forgot to do my homework!
Help me!
It's morning...
Kyouko! We're gonna be late!
Hey, Kyouko! Wake up!
I said wake up!
I didn't bring my uniform.
I'm so sorry, you guys!
It's completely alright! This happened to me, too.
I'm happy to be commuting with you guys!
Thanks to me.
You should be reflecting!
Isn't your uniform a bit too big, Kyouko?
Today, I'm borrowing Yui's uniform!
Why're you boasting?
I borrowed her clothes. too!
Why're you competing?
I also borrowed her textbooks!
Shut up and run!
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
Looks like I'm Sway 'n Shake's backup main character, Yui Funami.
I know I'm doing the preview and all,
but there aren't many special events in a middle schooler's life.
In the next episode, there's a test, summer break, the beach, fireworks, and the same old Chitose.
See? Completely average things.