Akarin!
Here!
Sway 'n Shake starts now!
Although, this is the last part you two will have for now.
Akarin!
I caught her contagious lack of existence?!
So now it's my fault?!
Excuse us. The show will now begin...
AAAAA
Reference Room
Whaddya know? Today's April Fools' day.
So it is...
I wish the mess in this room was all an April Fools' joke.
After all, it's finally spring vacation...
That's quite true.
I know, Ayano!
I'm gonna start telling lies and you can try and figure out what they are.
What do you mean?
Just organizing things all day is boring, right?
A liar's game, huh?
Sounds interesting!
When we're done organizing, we'll compare answers.
I'll see right through any lie you tell!
Daijiken!
What a big event!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 08
April Fools'
Hey, Ayano.
The panties I'm wearing today are... pretty sexy.
I-It's hard to respond to that...
H-How mature...
Isn't it?
This one time, Toshinou sniffed your shoes!
Also, a little while ago, I saw a ghost-like thing in the washroom.
And then yesterday, the president-
Could it be that Chitose's terrible at lying?
And then, this other time-
How cute.
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
This'll be a piece of cake!
Take care of this, too, please.
Alright.
The shopping district?
Oh, that's right. I went to the shopping district yesterday.
I stopped at the lottery stand.
Here are some tissues for fifth place.
Thanks...
I really don't have any luck at all, do I?
Luck, huh?
I won a million yen in the lottery.
Oh, yeah, did you see that show on TV yesterday?
The one with all the pets?
Ah, you mean "The Fluffy Pets of Our Home"?
Yeah, that one! Wasn't that cat cute?
Oh, right, Ayano...
This is a secret, but...
Akaza keeps an ant farm in her desk.
Do you have any pets, Chitose?
I just have some goldfish.
How about you?
I used to have a parrot.
Is that so?
Pets are really nice.
They just tug at my heartstrings.
I know what you mean.
Sometimes I sing to the things I pickle.
My beloved pickled radishes!
I wonder about that...
But don't pets kinda feel like siblings?
I could see that.
Oh, yeah...
I wonder if she has any siblings...
Toshinou?
Y-Yeah...
Do you know, Chitose...?
If I remember correctly, Toshinou's an only child.
I'm an only child!
I guess that makes sense.
You wanna know everything about the one you like, huh?
I-It's not that I like her or anything!
Ayano, actually...
I'm a twin!
Enough already. I can barely remember all of her lies...
I'll just write them down.
Let's see. Sexy panties.
Kyouko Toshinou sniffed my shoes.
There's a ghost in the girls' washroom.
Oh, and there's some corned beef in the student council room that expired 10 years ago.
Ah, okay. In the student council room... corned beef... 10 years ago.
Alright. That's the last one.
Okay, now let's compare answers.
Oh, you're just brimming with confidence, aren't you?
All of your lies are written here word for word.
Then I'll reveal the truth.
When I said, "I'm gonna start telling lies," I was lying.
I mean that statement was a lie.
So you mean... all of these are true?!
A collection of Chitose's non-lies.
AAAAAAAAA
There's a ghost in the girls' washroom?!
AAAAAAAAAA
There's an ant farm in Akari Akaza 's desk?!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAA
There's corned beef from 10 years ago in the student council room?!
That one, this one... They're all true?!
I'm a twin!
No way!
Chitose... You're a frightening girl...
I'm guessing that when you said you didn't like Toshinou, you were lying?
That wasn't a lie!
It's really busy in here.
It looks like everyone's come here to do their spring vacation homework.
Hey, it's Chitose.
It looks like she's seriously into that book.
Hey!
Hi there.
It's no good. She can't hear me.
Don't bother her.
Let's do our work here.
Math problem set!
You're doing math?
What? You're not?
Kanji.
I can't copy you then...
Do it yourself!
I wonder if Chitose brought her math book.
Hey!
If you brought your math problem set, could you lend it to Yui?
I told you not to bother her.
Hey!
Chitose's scary when she's reading.
No, she's not.
Geez, what are you doing?
If you don't understand something, I'll just teach you.
Everything!
Actually, do it yourself.
I'm the type of person who does tomorrow what can be done today!
Is that something to be proud of?
Isn't it rare to see Chitose by herself?
Huh, that's true.
She's always with Ayano, right?
I wonder if they got into a fight.
And that's why she's in a bad mood...
I've gotta cheer her up somehow.
Cheer up!
I wanna make her laugh!
Notice!
Not you!
What are you doing?
Just... trying to cheer Chitose up.
Just leave her alone.
She's probably really into her book.
But still!
Normally, even if she's focused on reading,
Chitose would always reply with a smile on her face.
Well, if it isn't Lady Kyouko.
I hadn't noticed you there on account of my enjoying this book.
Why's she speaking like a samurai?
I'll try looking like a samurai!
How can I make her laugh?!
Be quiet!
Your hair's in the way.
You're being annoying!
But...
You haven't even opened your book!
Chitose's more important right now!
I must get back Chitose's smile.
I keep telling you that it's bad to cause her trouble.
Like I said, not you.
Damn it...
Yui! She scowled at me!
Chitose scowled at me!
But you are bothering her, right?
I'm sure she just wants to focus on reading.
Are you sure about that?
Oh, you two.
Ayano!
Are you doing your homework?
Chitose?!
But Chitose's right over...
Hey there, Chizuru.
Big sister.
Big sister?!
She really has one!
Um, Ikeda... Your handout?
I'm collecting the notebooks...
Ikeda's pretty cool, huh?
I get so nervous when I talk to her.
That's so true.
But it's kinda nice, isn't it?
Chizuru!
Big Sister... and Sugiura.
We have to go to student council right now.
Do you want to come with us?
We'll be finished early today, so do you wanna go home together?
Chizuru's pretty cool, huh?
Really? Maybe she's just nervous.
She's usually a kind little sister to me.
For example?
When I take a bath, she comes in to wash my back.
In the middle of night, she comes into my bed.
Big Sister, that's private...
Sorry, sorry.
You'd like to do that stuff with Toshinou, I bet.
Don't be ridiculous!
Gosh, you meanie.
Ayano, you're so cute.
Allow me to explain!
When Chizuru enters Delusion Mode,
she removes her glasses and her heart's eye sharpens,
allowing her to focus on the situation before her.
Whoa! You're drooling!
No, I'm not.
I am fine.
No, you're definitely drooling!
Heya! I see everyone's all here.
K-Kyouko Toshinou!
You're drooling.
Shut up!
It's crossed my mind that she really hates you, doesn't she?
No way.
That can't be true!
Chizuru!
Kissy, kissy!
Shut up! Go away!
See?
What do you mean, "see"?
That's right...
Chitose, about you, I...
Ayano, I'm so happy.
Again!
She looks like Merlion!
Stop making such pointless comments and help me out here!
I'm fine.
No drool is coming out.
It is! What's the point of denying it?
Don't laugh! Get some tissues!
Come on...
Her, too?!
I see...
Chitose has nosebleeds, while Chizuru drools...
Sisters, huh?
Why are you agreeing with her?!
Ayano, is there any pudding in the student council room?
I'm kinda hungry...
Now's not the time!
I don't even have the time to visit a hot spring here!
Visit a hot spring...
Besides, that's my pudding!
Stingy...
Chizuru, do you do any club activities or anything?
Nothing in particular.
Well, I just hadn't realized Chitose had a twin sister.
Me neither...
Chitose, why didn't you ever tell us?
Somehow, it never came up.
Isn't it because our classes are far from each other?
We're in class five, and she's in class one.
Why do you know which class I'm in?
Chizuru knows all about you two.
I talk about you a lot.
I see.
Well, then... Let me introduce myself. I'm Yui Funami.
Chizuru Ikeda.
Kyouko Toshinou here!
Go to hell.
No mercy...
No, she's just shy.
Right?!
C'mon, now. That's not a very good attitude.
Let's all get along.
Are you tsundere?
Well, then, Toshinou, we're gonna get going.
For your information, that pudding's mine, got it?
Alright.
Oh, right. Ayano!
W-What?
Your shoes smell like tea.
Did you spray something on them?
Green tea and catechin deodorant.
Wait! Why are you smelling people's shoes, anyway?!
I was just curious.
Honestly, what's with you-
This one time, Toshinou sniffed your shoes!
We're home.
Now, what should we make for dinner tonight?
Time to eat.
Grandma's meeting with someone, so she said she'll be late tonight.
Sorry it's just a plain dinner.
That's okay.
Good.
What nice seasoning!
So delicious.
That's yours though, isn't it?
Then have this, Chizuru.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
What is it, Chizuru?
Y-Your back.
Thanks for always doing this.
Don't mention it. I'm your little sister, after all.
Even so, thank you.
Chizuru.
Does it feel good?
I'm turning it off.
Good night.
Come here.
You're so pampered, Chizuru.
'Cause I'm your little sister.
I guess we can't help it, then.
Yep. No helping it.
Chizuru, can you try to get along with Toshinou?
Guess I can't help it.
I got to talk with Chizuru a lot today.
But I wonder why she hates you so much.
Maybe it was because you were so annoying that time at the library...
I'm telling you; she doesn't hate me.
R-Really?!
You really didn't notice it?
So that's what it was...
You're really down?
Kyouko...
What?
You want some ice cream?
Rum Raisin?
Rum Raisin.
Yes...
Go to her and apologize. I'll go with you.
Thank you...
Chizuru!
Kissy, kissy!
Shut up!
Wait up, Chizuru!
Get away from me!
Kissy, kissy!
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
I'm the vice-protagonist, Sakurako Oomuro.
I'll never hand over the role of vice-protagonist and vice-president to the likes of Himawari!
And one day, I'll beat those breasts of hers, damn it!
I forgot to do the preview...