Akarin!
Here!
No UFO!
Is the focus okay, Mr. Camera?
Then...
Sway 'n Shake starts now!
AAAAA
Student Council
The time...
...has finally come!
That's right!
I have my favorite pickled radish for lunch tod-
I'm not talking about lunch!
The test! The end of term test.
The deciding match between Kyouko and I.
Oh, yeah, it's already that time...
But isn't it okay if you lose?
Why?
Because...
I-I lost...
But Ayano,
I don't want to fight with you anymore.
K-Kyouko Toshinou...
Let's be closer from now on!
...something like that might happen.
Th-That might be nice...
You think I'd really say that?!
Don't fool yourself.
Anyway, this time, I'll need to study extra hard.
Fight, fight!
Fai Fai Beach!
The beach?
We'd like to go to the beach, wouldn't we?
Daijiken!
What a big event!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 04
Summer's Huge Harvest Festival
It sure is hot.
You look tired. Did you get any sleep?
We're in the worst part of summer.
AAAAAAAAA
Write something to decorate the tree with.
Wish papers!
It's time for the Star Festival, huh?
Kyonshi!
Spare me.
Don't leave me alone like that.
A lot of wishes are written here.
"May my family always be in good health."
"May there be peace."
These kind of wishes really warm your heart.
There are plenty of love wishes, too.
"I'll definitely get a boyfriend this year."
"May my confession go well."
"I want my senior's address."
Those kinds of things.
You're right.
Over here, too.
Let's see...
AAAAAA
I wish Rika and AAAARGH
What the hell...?
Ayano and Chitose's are here, too.
"May I get closer to her"?
"I pray for a bountiful harvest"?
How about we write some, too?
I wanna write one!
Me, too!
How about "I want to kiss Chinatsu!"
From all the time we've known each other, we should've become close enough.
But that's...
...too embarrassing.
Chi-Chinatsu...
Just this once, okay?
It might turn out like that!
I'm done!
Let me see...
AAAAAAA
I want to kiss Yui. - Chinatsu
A kiss is kinda embarrassing...
I just wanted to try saying it!
What did you write, Kyouko?
AAAAAAA
Lots of sleep... ZZZ - Kyouko
Isn't there anything else?
Nope!
What'd you write, Yui?
I'm still thinking about it.
Just write that you want to kiss Chinatsu.
Why are you even upset?
Besides, a kiss is...
Chinatsu.
Yes?
On the mouth is just too embarrassing, sorry.
Fulfilled
What was that for?!
Why don't you ask yourself that?!
Come to think of it, what did you write, Akari?
That's right! Cough 'em up!
Don't look at it!
May I stand out more.
How dedicated.
Akarin!
AAAAAAAAAA
Thanks for my fan comic selling out. - Kyouko
Let's put these up, already.
May everyone always have fun together. - Yui
Yeah, let's do it.
Mouth to mouth. - Chinatsu
I'll at least put it where it can stand out...
Come back!
Kyouko...
Looks like she had a late night again.
Studying for the test?
No, no.
You see, pretty soon-
Kyouko Toshinou!
This time, I'll be first in our grade on the end of term tes-
She's asleep!
The end of term test?
Oh, right, they were talking about that before.
I guess it's okay.
This is Kyouko Toshinou after all.
She always crams the night before and still aims for first place.
I'll definitely win this time!
Sorry to have interrupted you, girls.
Akari... You have so many warts...
Will she be okay?
So the bet was: if she loses, we have to leave, right?
Warts?
But what will you do?
About what?
Well, you said:
"If I win, I'll make you all leave this clubhouse!"
Wasn't that just an excuse to talk to Toshinou?
You don't really want to drive them out of there,
so I was wondering what you were going to do.
To be honest, I'm not sure what I should do.
But...
For now, I have to win!
Even after I win, it won't be too late to change my mind.
For sure!
I love how you can be so haphazard sometimes.
And so the test drew closer and closer.
492 points
First Place
Ayano Sugiura
I-I did it...
I won!
Chitose, first! First place!
You did it!
I'm so happy for you, Ayano!
Now, what place is Kyouko Toshinou?
Not there.
Not there!
She's not there!
So many warts...
It's Toshinou...
Kyouko Toshinou!
What's the meaning of this?
Let me see those!
This is amazing...
What's with these marks?!
Well, the test week and the deadline for my fan comic overlapped,
so I didn't end up studying at all.
I mean, I was totally burned out during the tests.
What about our contest?!
Oh, by the way,
who do you wanna get along with?
I saw it on one of the papers in front of the station.
Overwhelmed
Remember this!
I don't really know why,
but I get the feeling we can keep using the clubhouse.
The beach!
Thanks for inviting us.
Th-They say, "The more the merrier!"
Warty Warty Seven!
My, my.
We'll see you next week, then.
Toshinou and the others can come.
Isn't that good?
I-I don't really care!
Besides, I won the contest.
So it's only natural for me to invite them.
This is going to be a good day.
With them together, my nose will be bleeding like crazy.
Let's go change.
Don't pull me!
Here, let me undress you.
Please be gentle.
Already?!
Thank you!
What do you want now?!
This is so embarrassing. Don't watch!
Same here.
Thanks to my preparedness, I put my swimsuit on beforehand.
Now changing isn't embarrassing!
At ease, Angkor Wat!
"At ease, Angkor Wat."
I'm wearing my swimsuit, too!
You didn't forget a change of panties or something, right?
I wouldn't make such a stupid mistake!
Now, now.
What color are they today?
I'm not... wearing any.
How nice.
Sorry about that.
Let's have some fun!
Yui really...
...shouldn't be taken lightly.
What are you looking at?!
Himawari, they're so big!
T-That's...
Unforgivable breasts...
Take this!
You shouldn't throw starfish.
Here it comes.
There.
Kyouko.
I got it!
Be sure not to catch a cold.
The watermelon's cut.
Thanks for the food!
This feels pretty nice, huh?
Yeah! The watermelon's good, too.
Though, if Sakurako weren't here, it'd be the perfect day!
That's dirty!
Everyone having fun together is pretty nice.
It's so lively.
You wanna come to my place next time?
We can hang out with everyone.
Sounds good.
Funami, you're living alone now, right?
Yui's place is so fun!
She'll even buy you rum raisin!
That was one time only, idiot.
I wanna have a sleepover!
M-Me too.
Sure.
You'll go too, right, Ayano?
B-But...
Oh, you can have it.
It's not that!
Indirect or direct; which do you prefer?
B-Both...
Or something like that...
Thanks for all your help.
This was fun!
Alright!
I'm glad we came.
It's getting kinda cold out.
It really is.
Maybe I should try... being more honest with my feelings...
We'll get along better if I do...
I forgot my bra!
What's your problem?!
My panties, too?!
Oh, no.
I forgot my pouch.
W-Well...
It's a yukata, so I'm safe.
Awesome!
We brought some, too.
Hurry and light them! Hurry!
Ayano, let's light some.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Um...
That yukata su-su-su-
It's okay!
Your yukata suits you!
Of course it does!
I'm the student council vice president, after all!
Is that... relevant?
It's been a while since I've played with fireworks.
They're so beautiful.
Look at this!
A heart!
Mine's way better!
Wow, a star!
Such a wonderful sight!
Toshinou's the dominant one!
Mine's longer than yours.
No, mine's longer!
Ayano, Ayano!
Why don't you confess?
W-Wh-Wha-What are you saying?!
It's not as if I like her-
What is it?
I think I saw letters...
You didn't see anything.
Behind you!
Mine's longer than yours!
No, mine's longer!
Ta-da!
Get a load of this!
That's huge!
Here, light it.
It's obviously impossible!
I'm scared...
It's fine! I'm right behind you!
I can't. I'm too scared...
It's okay. I'll help you.
Run for it!
That was it?!
Okay! Again!
Hey! You're too pushy!
Ayano, let's do it again...
Oh, my, you're so persistent.
I'm fine.
In fact, this feels great!
This was so much fun!
I'm satisfied.
Thanks again for inviting us.
No problem.
It was fun for us, too.
Alright, I'll go throw this out.
Chitose.
Thanks... for today.
I'm always being saved by you.
What's with you? You're being so serious...
This was a lot of fun!
Thanks to you, Chitose.
No need to thank me.
Did your wish come true?
Fulfilled
I'm done throwing them out!
Kyouko, it's too dangerous to run!
S-Sorry.
Are you alright?
Ayano...
Where's your underwear?
Chitose!
Get a hold of yourself! Chitose!
This is bad!
Oh, God...
Even if I run out of blood, let this delusion continue forever!
Don't do it!
Fulfilled
It's a bit late now, but...
since it flew all the way to the ocean,
it'd be nice if my wish came true!
Not again!
Come back!
Unfulfilled
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
I'm your late-coming protagonist, Chinatsu Yoshikawa.
Yui's swimsuit and yukata... ~drool~
But summer's just beginning,
and next time, I'll be all alone with Yui.
Please be gentle!