Akarin!
Here!
Sway 'n Shake starts now!
AAAAA
Student Council
AAAAAAA
Placement Test: Second Year
Something on your mind?
I just don't get it...
Ayano, you're bleeding.
You scratched your forehead too hard...
Why am I always second place?
I lost again...
...to a girl like that!
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 2
You, Me and the Student Council
Kyouko Toshinou!
Ayano?
You... what's with you?
Pardon us, girls.
You never study seriously,
yet every time you take top place in our grade!
Kyouko, that's incredible!
Top grades in the school? Really?!
Well, studying for one night is usually enough for tests.
S-Studying for one night?
If someone who studies everyday heard that, they'd flip out.
Look, here's a prime example.
Studying for one night?!
Even though I pull all-nighters everyday until I practically collapse...
Thanks to that, my shoulders are stiff and my skin's a mess!
But it's amazing that you're first in your grade...
I mean, this is you we're talking about!
I guess so.
I doubt that was meant as a compliment...
Listen to me!
What are all of you doing sitting around here?
Using a clubhouse without permission is prohibited.
I, the student council's vice president, Ayano Sugiura, will not allow such use of this room.
Wait. How did you know we were in here?
That's not important.
At any rate,
you'll receive the Buckingham Penalty if you use the room without permission.
Buckingham Penalty...
C'mon, Ayano. Forcing them to leave isn't a good way of settling things.
Chitose...
I think we should...
...have a nice, peaceful contest.
Peaceful?
A contest, you say?
I look great naked!
If that's the contest, Ayano wouldn't lose, either.
Ayano, you're so violent.
Shut up!
Anyway, if I win on the next test,
all of you will have to leave this place.
W-What'll you do, Kyouko?
Refusing would be best.
The next test, right?
But you know, there are other ways to decide besides tests.
Like what?
Hey, isn't this room a little hot?
Stop fooling around with the other girls and just play with me!
You could have an:
Erotic Appeal Contest!
For the second time...
I'm fine with a contest.
But if I win,
you two will have to join the Amusement Club.
Y-You're going to accept?
What if you lose?
I'll just have to win.
Besides, if these two join, it'll be more fun!
Fine by me!
I accept your condition.
Kyouko, if you lose, you'll receive the Buckingham Penalty!
You like saying that, don't you?
Once I win, I'm definitely gonna make you cry!
There's no way I'd cry.
How is it possible?!
I can't believe it... I... lost...
This is my true power!
And with that,
you are now mine.
Treat me tenderly!
Allow me to explain:
I enter Delusion Mode only when I remove my glasses and limit my vision.
By doing so, my heart's eye sharpens, greatly deepening my focus.
Toshinou, be sure to win!
Why are you cheering for her?!
Well, what would I gain if you were to win?
Now, will you kindly vacate the premises?
What have I done?!
But, it's okay...
Without the Tea Ceremony clubhouse, you have nowhere to go...
You poor kitten who's lost her home,
I'll take you in.
A-Ayano...
Do your best, Ayano.
You're getting way too many nosebleeds.
Use these.
Ah, thanks.
Anyway, look forward to the next test.
Do your best to resist!
Thank you for the tissues, Akaza.
What was that all about?
What?
It's just that...
you have no intention of evicting them, yet you said all of that.
What are you saying?!
What was that?
Penalty... Buckingham Penalty...
The next day
It looks like Kyouko Toshinou is the only one who didn't submit a form.
I guess I have no choice but to go to her personally.
Again with you, Ayano.
Don't tell me you just want to talk to her.
I got slapped again...
C'mon. You're coming too, Chitose.
But we still have all these documents to sort.
Besides, is going alone really that embarrassing?
It's not!
But if we don't deal with these documents...
Sorry we're late!
Homeroom ran a bit long.
Sorting documents?
That's right.
We need to step out for a bit, so we were wondering if you could take over for us.
Piece of cake!
Leave it to me!
If it's for you two, I'd be glad to help.
We're counting on you.
Thank you.
Afterwards, I'll treat you to some juice.
Yay!
I won't lose!
I'm the one who'll become the next Vice President!
I won't lose, either!
I'll become Vice President... no, the President!
Regardless, I won't lose to you, Himawari!
As always, you're so cheeky, Sakurako.
Take this!
A photo?
That's right.
In this student council photo,
it looks like I was acting all friendly with you, but I was far from it!
Yeah, well, the same goes for me.
Take a look at my right hand.
What about it?
I really wanted to hit you.
I'll get you first!
I-I'm against violence...
We accepted so willingly, but there really is a lot!
Definitely...
I'd like to surprise them by sorting it all, but...
I wonder if there's anyone who could lend us a hand.
There are two people I think I could ask!
Helping you sort documents?
Yeah! You two aren't busy with your club, right?
I wonder if you could help.
I'm okay with that.
Sure. Count me in!
For real?!
You guys are life savers.
With just the two of us, who knows how it would've turned out.
I know! I'll ask the rest of our friends to help, too.
That way, it'll be finished in no time!
Hey!
Let's head to the clubhouse.
Kyouko, Yui!
What a coincidence.
It's locked...
You think they're still in there?
I'm the student council president, Kyouko Toshinou.
As if!
Let's see...
We just have to categorize these, right?
Yeah, it looks that way.
So this is the student council's room.
There's a fridge in here!
I wonder what's inside...
Sorry, you guys. You were probably busy with your club.
It's okay, really.
It says "Ayano" on this pudding cup!
Come over here, please, Funami.
Sure.
Okay, let's get this over with.
That pudding...
So good!
Kyouko Toshinou!
No one's here...
Did they leave early today?
The roof! She could be on the roof!
That's it! She's on the roof!
You're crazy.
Sakurako, your progress seems awfully slow.
Likewise. Could it be you're not progressing at all?
Why do you guys argue so much?
They're both rivals in becoming the next Vice President.
They're like this in class all the time.
And despite always fighting, we're still forced to see each other.
We've been in the same class since kindergarten. I've had enough.
The feeling is mutual!
These handouts...
What is it?
I completely forgot...
This was due yesterday, right?
Would you hand this to Ayano?
Yes. Understood.
I'll hand it to her!
Sakurako, we aren't progressing at all!
She's not on the roof, in the gym, or in the restroom!
She might be in the library...
That's it! Just you wait, Kyouko Toshinou!
Alright! They're all sorted!
That was quick.
Thank you, everyone!
You saved us.
Well, then, we're gonna head to the clubhouse now. Was that everything?
Yeah, we're fine.
Sorry for taking up your time.
Later.
Good work!
I'll leave that handout to you guys.
Okay.
We cleaned everything up nicely.
Those two'll be surprised for sure!
Although, your progress was pretty slow.
Geez! I don't want to hear tha-
Seriously, you're too careless.
Be more careful.
T-Thanks...
Hey, there. We're back.
How're things going?
Everything's sorted!
Amazing! How did you do this?
Our friends came to help.
What happened to you, Sugiura?
Your worry is... N-N-Notre Dame...
Just leave her be for now.
She couldn't find someone. That's all.
That's right.
She said to give this to you, Sugiura.
This is Kyouko Toshinou's handout!
How'd you get that?
Toshinou and the others helped us.
Just Missed Her Shock
I just missed her...
I wonder if someone's talking about me...
My pudding's gone!
Double shock!
Double Shock
A few days later...
Delicious!
It's a "thank you" for helping us the other day.
They're really good!
They're amazing! How did you make them so tasty?
You guys can make them just as good.
Cookies...
What is it, Sakurako?
Would you like some?
I'm good.
They're yummy.
Here, try one.
C'mon.
Take it. They're really good.
I said I didn't want any, didn't I?!
You morons!
How rude of her.
What's wrong?
I forgot my P.E. uniform.
I brought two with me...
Huh? Why?
Want to use it?
I'd rather not be saved by my rival,
but I'll accept your help for today.
Just this one time, got it?
Sakurako, the bust size doesn't match.
You trying to pick a fight?!
And you!
You know I have a complex about my chest size, don't you?
Don't bite me!
Whoops, I missed.
Hurry up and move.
Got it!
Sakurako?! Stop it!
Booby dribbling...?
Stop that right now!
Afternoon P.E. is really tiring...
Once I wash it, I'll give it back.
No thanks. Just give it back now.
Geez...
You trying to pick a fight?!
Shut up, already!
Um, Sakurako.
What is it?
You... can have these.
T-They were leftovers.
It's not like they have a deeper meaning.
It's specially packaged,
even though the other ones were all in one container...
I know!
You tried giving these to someone you like, but you were rejected!
A few more days later...
See you, Akari.
Make sure to eat lots of yummy food.
Sure! Bye-Bye!
Bye-Bye!
So Chinatsu's going on a trip with her family...
What should I do today?
Ayano didn't show up at all today...
Chitose,
let's go visit Ayano!
Are you cold?
Then I'll warm you up.
I-I'm fine...
If you do, you'll catch my cold...
If that'll make you better, I don't care.
Kyouko...
Thanks for coming.
Don't sweat it.
How's your cold?
It's kinda relentless,
and I have a slight fever.
I'm relieved to see you doing this well, though.
So who proposed this visit?
Was it you, Chitose?
Nope, it was me.
What are you saying?!
My, my, you always get so flustered.
Did you get sick because you studied for your contest with he-
Chitose!
O-Ouch! My stomach...
Hey, are you all right?
You should try breaking that habit of eating things you find on the ground.
I don't do that!
This isn't good.
If you don't rest, your fever will get worse.
I'll take my temperature.
But it's good that you don't have the flu or anything.
You don't get marked absent if you have the flu.
Then you should say, "I have the flu," at school!
It would be bad to lie.
Right.
I'd probably need proof from the doctor saying I have the flu...
What do you mean by "proof"?
37 degrees Celcius...
Did it go up?
It went down a bit.
That's good.
But have you been eating properly?
Should I make some rice porridge?
Yes, please.
Open the door.
Coming!
It's ready.
Only one?
No fair!
Watch it! It'll fall!
I want some rice porridge, too!
This is only for the sick person!
I'm sick, too, you know!
In fact, I've been feeling feverish.
Just eat as much as you can.
It's good.
Dang...
I feel a bit better now.
Thanks for the food, Funami.
Sure.
Hurry and get better so you can come to school with me.
I'm fine. It's just a nosebleed.
You're not fine at all!
I-I don't need you to tell me that.
I'll do it anyway.
But thanks for coming by...
I'll thank you, at least...
Again?!
Such a fruitful day...
I guess I should head home.
Sorry for staying so long when you're sick.
I don't mind, but I'm a bit worried that you'll get sick.
When you get home, rinse your mouth out or something.
Unfortunately, we can't show you what she's seeing for various reasons
C'mon, Chitose. We're going home.
Uh, just give me a second.
Glasses, glasses, where have you gone?
Oh, my, I guess I'll look-
Whoops!
This is bad!
I can't stop my delusions without my glasses on!
More importantly, stop those nosebleeds!
They're killing me softly... with their words...
Hey! Pull yourself together!
Extremely Anemic
Someone call an ambulance!
An ambulance won't help with this!
The only solution to this problem is to fix her glasses!
Shut up!
My fever went up...
Everyone's late...
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
Now, then, what'll the next Sway 'n Shake be like?
Kyouko and her beloved Rum Raisin.
Yui and her cabbage.
Chinatsu and her bathtub surprise! Those three!
I haven't forgotten anything, have I?
That's all!
I've been your main character, Kyouko Toshinou!