Akarin!
Here!
Sway 'n-
Ow...
Sorry about that...
A-Are you okay, Mr. Camera?
S-Sway 'n Sha-
Merry Christmas!
Kyouko, Christmas won't be around until next week.
That's right.
Yup, I know that.
We are talking about me, but even I'm not that restless.
That outfit totally proves that you're restless.
With that said, winter break starts next week.
The first event being Christmas, with couples meeting across the city.
How nice!
I'd really like to go on a Christmas date...
A Christmas date...
Me, too... someday.
Wh-What?
And so...
...on Christmas, why don't we go out as couples?
We'll split off into pairs and go on dates.
Why should we go along with this little event of yours?
Does it matter?
If you do it, you might get paired with Toshinou.
I agree!
It'll suck if I pair off with Himawari and have to spend my Christmas with her.
I don't want that, either!
It'd be way more fun to spend Christmas with Yoshikawa than with you.
Then I'll go with Akari.
And with that, this is where we choose couples.
Ta-da!
The couple-choosing box!
You still have that box?
Inside are pieces of paper, each with a number on it.
Two people who draw the same number will be couples for this year!
Now, let's start drawing.
However, I'm not handing over Chinatsu.
What are you saying?!
Does everyone have a number?
Then on the count of three, open it.
Chinatsu. Chinatsu! Please let it be Chinatsu!
Please let me be a couple with Yui!
Himawari. Anyone but Himawari...
Sakurako. Anyone but Sakurako...
I guess I can't help it if it happens to be Kyouko Toshinou...
Please let Ayano and Toshinou be a couple!
Their concentration is so intense...
What'll I do if mine is the only paper without a number on it?
Alright, then!
One, two...
Daijiken!
What a big event!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 07
Christmassy
What should we do?
No idea...
Did you want to be paired up with someone else?
N-No-Not at all!
This is awkward.
The first thing on today's date is...
Ta-da! This!
Just being coupled with Kyouko makes me sad,
but this of all things?!
Makes her lovely squat!
This isn't good at all...
Since I'm with you, we just have to see this!
Mirakurun watching Mirakurun...
It's the best!
You said that you've already seen this, though...
You can never watch a good thing too many times.
After I watched it, I thought something like this would happen, so I bought these right away.
We can go straight to the theater!
Hurry up!
I really wanted to have a date with Yui...
I'm sorry that... you ended up with me...
Just talk normally.
Okay!
This is actually perfect for me since I have something to give you.
Please take this.
It's because you gave me tissues that one time.
Here you go.
Thank you!
This my thanks for back then.
Thank you.
Thanks so much!
But you didn't have to give me anything for that.
You're so nice, Akaza.
Oh please...
Have you decided what to order yet?
I wanted to be with Akari...
Yeah, well, I wanted to be with Yoshikawa.
To think I have to spend time with you here...
This is my worst case scenario!
And on Christmas, too!
Like I said, it's the same for both of us.
Good grief... Well, I'm going to order, then.
Wait!
I haven't decided yet...
They have a new pasta dish!
Let's see...
What are you having, Himawari?
A Japanese style hamburger set.
That sounds delicious.
Then why don't you get that?
No way! We can't have matching orders.
Okay, fine. Just hurry up and decide, already.
I told you to wait!
I wonder what the other couples are doing...
Like Chitose and Akaza.
Those two... I can't see them doing much.
Speaking of which, what do couples do exactly?
H-Hold hands...?
Well... That's a little embarrassing...
I suppose you're right...
What's with this mood...?
Raika! Don't tell me you're Rivalun!
Don't make it look like you've been betrayed.
You just went ahead and believed it yourself.
Then of all those times when you coached me...
...and all of the nights that you made me dinner were all lies?!
You're just so trusting.
Getting close to you was a piece of cake.
Then that time you picked up my eraser...
...and that time you pulled that string off of my shoulder were all lies, too?!
You're just so trusting of people.
Then that time I asked you to buy me a fried noodle sandwich and juice was all a lie?
I've gotta use the washroom.
Wait. I'm the trusting one?!
Raika, if we co-operate, we can easily defeat him!
I guess I'll help, since I'm so trusting of people!
It's so great to be trusting!
Go, Mirakurun!
May I open this?
Sure, go ahead.
I-It's pickled radish...
I poured my heart into making these.
I had trouble deciding between this or Harihari.
I-It looks delicious!
Really?!
I'm glad you think so!
She kinda has the cute air of a grandmother...
After we're done with our coffee, would you like to go for some anmitsu?
That sounds good!
This food isn't Christmassy at all!
Then would you like to eat some cake?
Since it's Christmas, they make some with Santa on them.
Let me see!
There's a reindeer version!
Even mini whole cakes!
Hold on! This isn't what I meant!
Then what's wrong?
I mean it doesn't have that fresh excitement...
How could we get excitement, though...?
How about some dressing?
I wonder if I should get the Japanese style dressing...
Breasts aren't allowed!
What do you think you're doing?!
I'm in a bad mood!
No breasts allowed!
I don't understand you at all.
I'm so happy, Tooru!
I love you, Noriko!
Oh, Kazu!
What should I do, Toushou-gu?
Really, what should we do?
Man, isn't Mirakurun the best?
I-I guess...
Alright! Next up is the arcade!
Let's go!
Hold on!
The normal thing to do is relax at a café or something.
It's so cute!
Chinatsu, what're you doing? Let's go!
Coming!
Bringing me along and then leaving me here...
This is the worst.
Chinatsu!
Ta-da!
Is that...?
You wanted this, right?
Here, it's your present.
Crane games are my specialty!
Th-Thanks so much.
So cute!
Well, then, next stop!
We're leaving already?
There's still plenty of fun to be had!
What's the matter?
Can we... hold hands?
Only for today...
Yes!
Note: Good children shouldn't bring their pickled radish into a store!
Oh, you're right! Salty and sweet really do go well together.
I know, right?
In some restaurants, they'll even give you salted kelp on the side.
Let's see...
Delicious!
I'm so glad it's to your taste.
It is! It is!
It's perfect!
You sure know some good stores, Akaza.
Actually, I had Yui tell me about them...
Oh, Funami?
Come to think of it, I wonder what kind of time everyone else is having.
I'll bet Ayano's a bit down since she wasn't paired with Toshinou.
No, wait...
You're always by Kyouko's side,
so you have some of her with you.
Ayano...
Let me smell you more.
Go ahead...
The unexpected can happen.
Are you alright?
Thanks.
I wonder if I should give you something else.
It's fine.
If you want, just take this.
I have another one with me.
You're really prepared...
That's not how it is at all.
Because of your breasts, this is the worst Christmas ever!
Seriously, I have no idea what you're talking about.
I don't like carrots... You want this?
I guess there's no helping it...
You should at least be able to eat this much.
But...
Sakurako... eat my pepper.
Well, if I have to...
One more...
Okay, fine.
Then finish this.
Look at those two!
So cute! They're feeding each other...
Sakurako, you idiot!
What'd I do...?
Honestly... Kyouko's always coming up with events that make no sense.
Is it tough being with Kyouko Toshinou?
Yeah, it really is,
though I'm sure it looks like fun from a distance.
We're childhood friends,
and since we always lived so close to each other, I get involved with her a lot.
I think I understand...
Chitose has her delusions almost every day,
so there are times I get completely exhausted.
Well, at least you're never bored with them around.
That's true.
Chitose also watches out for me.
Same here.
Although Kyouko usually misses the mark...
I know what you mean!
"I really appreciate it, but that isn't what I wanted."
Like that?
Exactly.
Everyone should be coming back soon.
All we did was space out, huh?
I guess that's alright.
Hey!
Yui!
Ayano!
I'm back.
How can I put it? I feel relieved when I see Chitose.
I get what you mean.
We'd be hopeless without those two, wouldn't we?
I guess you're right.
What were you two talking about?
It's a secret.
Now you're making me curious...
Kyouko.
Thanks for everything.
There's no fever...
And that was the end of that wonderful Christmas.
New Year's Day
A new year.
Happy New Year.
Same to you.
Akari, you really are a good girl.
Please accept this.
Here. This, too.
No, I couldn't...
AAAAAA
New Year's gift
Don't be shy!
I insist!
Thank you very much!
Mom, look at how much money I got for New Year's!
I wonder if I should have this much happiness...
Oh, really?
Did you thank them properly?
I'll have to go thank them later as well.
You're right. Please do so.
You don't have to be so polite...
Come to think of it, where's Sis?
She went with a friend to visit the New Year's shrine.
Akari, would you mind helping me carry the food?
Sure, Dad.
Everyone's New Year's cards are so cute!
This one's from Chinatsu...
AAAAAAAA
Happy New Year (It 's a rabbit!)
Chinatsu, I'm going out!
Where're you going?
To visit the New Year's shrine with Akaza.
That's Akari's older sister?
That's right. See you!
Have a nice day.
Must be nice...
I'd like to visit the shrine with Yui...
What'd you wish for, Yui?
Obviously,
I wished for us to be lovey-dovey together!
Yui's just too wonderful!
Last year was really great.
I got to meet Yui...
I will protect you.
She kissed me on the forehead...
This is perfect!
I'll get even closer to her this year!
And in the end...
Chinatsu, come here.
Yui, I'm so happy.
Yui!
Oh, my, what am I thinking about?!
That was so embarrassing!
Chinatsu, sorry to interrupt your fun, but can you bring in the New Year's cards?
Okay!
We got so many!
This one's from Yui!
AAAAAAAAAAAA
Year of the Rabbit: Happy New Year.
Chinatsu, I look forward to spending another year with you. - Yui
Even her New Year's card is cool.
But so wonderful!
A delivery accident?
I wonder who it's from.
Oh, it's Akari's.
AAAAAAAAAAAA
Chinatsu! Happy New Year! I hope this year will be a good one too. I look forward to another year with you! - Akari
I had a little accident...
Mari, are you hungry?
Yep!
Then I'll go get some food from downstairs.
What would you like?
Sea urchin!
Sea urchin...?
What a gourmet child you are...
Is it good?
Delicious!
When I grow up, I wanna be a sea urchin!
Really? You'll get eaten.
I don't want that!
Well, if it were you, I wouldn't mind being eaten.
I love you!
Really?
Thank you, Mari.
But don't say that in front of Mirakurun's sister, okay?
Mirakurun's sister...
What's wrong?
Mari, we're leaving soon.
Sea urchin!
Come again, Mari.
Bye bye!
Yui, some New Year's cards came for you.
Okay!
Chinatsu's card's pretty scary!
I wonder if this made Akari's eyes go white...
Kyouko's...
She's alone in every one...
Amazing...
Kyouko, here's some New Year's food.
Some New Year's cards came, too.
Kyouko! New Year's money.
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
I'm the soon-to-be vice-protagonist, Himawari Furutani.
New Year's is over, and it's spring already.
Time sure does fly.
Now, it's another April Fool's showdown, Sakurako.
I will obviously be the one left standing!