Akarin!
Her-
Wait. What's this?!
Akarin!
The title call...
S-Sway 'n Shake starts-
This year's hot, too.
It sure is...
It's times like these...
...when we should tell scary stories!
It's like this, right?
Oh, sorry!
Daijiken!
What a big event!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 09
This Summer's Not Scary
Now, then, name some scary things.
Earthquakes.
Fires.
My father?
No, nothing like that...
Dirty talk!
I mean ghost stories!
When it comes to summer, this is a must!
G-Ghosts...?
Yup!
Although, I don't really know any ghost stories myself.
Ghost stories, huh?
Speaking of scary stories...
Yesterday, it sounded like there was something in my desk drawer...
Scary!
But that's not a ghost story!
This isn't something that actually happened to me,
but if you open the door and...
I was thinking that would be pretty scary.
Stop it, Yui!
My, my, what rough hands.
Why not use this hand cream?
That doesn't make sense, though...
Let's stop talking about this.
I'll be too scared to take a bath!
It's okay. I'll take a bath with you.
I'd prefer going with Yui.
I wanna say, "That's not okay at all," but...
Okay, how about we have a test of courage?
You look like the the type who'd like that.
I am!
I'm through with scary stories.
Already?
Don't you think someone like Ayano would be really scared?
So we'd be the ones scaring people?
Then count me in!
'kay!
AAAAAAAAA
The Amusement Club's Journal of Love
We'll make Ayano and Chitose our targets.
We can do it at school, right?
Yup.
I wonder how we can scare them.
From inside the TV-
I'd like to see you try.
Well, then,
if we put a lever in the toilet,
water would come raining down on Akari.
How does that sound?
I'm the target?!
Shock
It's the curse of the toilet.
It's... just this once, okay?
Actually, that kind of sounds like bullying.
I wasn't trying to be a bully...
Trying to scare people is harder than I thought.
How about a human dummy?
Leaving it in the hallway would be scary enough.
That sounds good.
Wouldn't leaving some gloves or shoes along the way be pretty scary, too?
Yeah, yeah,
it'd freak them out if you left a bag or something.
Then if you add everything together...
What's this? Lost stuff?
Man, people have been losing a lot of stuff lately.
Wait!
I wasn't expecting that...
Are you bad with haunted houses, Chinatsu?
I think I'm okay with haunted houses.
The first time I was in one, my friends left me behind...
Wait for me!
Are you alright?
Let's find the exit.
I'm sorry...
I even made the ghost worried.
Ever since then, haunted houses don't scare me.
I've scared a ghost before.
Hey, you're not supposed to do that.
I wonder if there are real ghosts in haunted houses.
There are in some of them, aren't there?
By the way, I do believe in ghosts.
Aliens and UMA, too.
What about Santa Claus?
I cannot answer that.
It's pretty neat to believe in things that you don't know are true.
It's like having dreams.
What about Santa Claus?
Again, I cannot answer that.
"Grudges are grudges."
Something like that?
It's cold!
Man, we didn't think up anything good.
By the way, when are we doing this?
Setting it all up is too much work, so let's just forget it.
She's always been like this.
So hot...
Speaking of heat, isn't this room way too hot?
There's no AC in here.
If you think it's hot, it will be. Think cool thoughts!
What are you, a grade schooler?
Today's pretty cold, isn't it, Kyouko?
If it's hot, it's hot.
That's not what you said earlier!
That reminds me... They have a portable AC in the student council room, don't they?
Then you wanna try going there?
I'm terrible with the heat.
There's a fridge there... and Ayano might have some ice cream.
Rum Raisin?!
Probably.
Yui, thank you for the wonderful information!
Shall I prepare you some tea?
S-Sure, why not...
Okay, understood!
Lady Yui, your tea is ready.
Thank yo-
What are you doing?
My deepest apologies, Lady Yui.
I, Kyouko Toshinou, shall atone for my sins by suffocating myself.
It's fine. Just go buy some ice, already.
When you add ice, it's really cold and refreshing!
Taking off your socks makes it nice and cool.
Yui, your hair is done up!
Y-Yeah, because it's so hot... Is it weird?
Not at all! It's extremely cute!
T-Thank you...
It's so hot...
Isn't there some way to cool down?
I think jumping naked into a river would be a good way.
I see!
Not "I see!"
What are you, an exhibitionist?!
Now that you mention it...
What are you doing?
Ta-da!
If you spray it on your clothes, it freezes them.
There's actually something like that?
But if you apply it directly to your skin, you may get frostbite, so be careful!
Who are you even talking to?
It's so cold!
Okay, let's forget the heat and talk about stuff in our dreams.
Stuff in our dreams?
If you had one super power, what would it be?
A super power?
Like immortality or something.
I wouldn't wanna be immortal.
Even if you don't die, your friends and family will.
It'd be lonely...
I'd like to be able to soar through the sky!
Soar...
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see ya!
Doubtful
I'd like to be able to talk with animals!
Akari, you're so adorably cute!
Mr. Mouse, make shadow clones!
Understood, Sis!
I'd like to be able to warp.
Look, Kyouko! I can warp now!
See?
Your clothes didn't warp with you, Yui!
You guys are coming up with such lame powers...
What kind would you want, Kyouko?
Mine would be amazing!
I'd be able to turn into a burglar alarm!
AAA
Bad Guy
In times of trouble...
You can just buy one of those.
Looks like there's nothing to talk about now.
We're back to thinking about the heat.
Isn't there another topic?
You can't say that!
If someone says that, there really won't be another topic. It's a cursed phrase!
That's kinda true...
For times like this, why don't I make a topic box?
AAAA
Topic Box
That box is really doing its best...
I can't take it anymore.
Heat is bad.
Chinatsu,
come here for a sec.
Your legs feels so nice and cool!
Well, if it's so hot, we might as well head over to the student council room.
That's true...
Well, wanna get going?
Yeah!
Wait a minute!
I'm enjoying myself right now!
Like I care.
But you hear them a lot at schools, don't you?
Ghost stories about the school!
You're bringing that topic up again?
But I guess ghosts don't really exist.
Well, I've never seen one.
You haven't? That's weird.
Wait! Kyouko!
See, there are ghosts.
If you open the door, an ominous ghost'll be waiting... or something.
I'm telling you there aren't any...
AAAAA
Student Council
Really?
Breasts Forbidden
Hey, wait. Who's that?!
No clue... I've never seen her before.
Is she... human?
Th-Then what are you saying she is?!
She loved the school so much...
That's why she can never leave.
K-Kyouko?
With those feelings, she lingers here, even now.
Kyouko!
Such a... such a sad...
No!
Wait! Calm down!
Let's get outta here, Yui!
Now, while Kyouko's being attacked!
Hey, hey...
Akari, thank you!
Why are you thanking me?!
We won't forget your sacrifice!
Wait!
Wait up!
Matsumoto, ya there?
I did an experiment that sorta resulted in an explosion.
It caught fire, and now it's a mess.
What do ya think? Is this look fashionable?
The principal's really hard-headed, if you ask me.
"Stop those dangerous experiments!" he said!
If you're afraid of failing, you'll never succeed!
Don't they say that "explosions are the foundation of success"?
If that's how he thinks, then that fugu I ate that second time really was amazing.
Even though he knew that the first guy got poisoned and died...
Normally, you wouldn't eat it, right?
Parachute experiments are the same.
Well, I'm like that.
Even if I explode or catch fire!
Well? What do you think of my eyes full of hope?
Right? We think the same.
President!
About these papers...
I haven't dealt with them before, so I'm not sure what to do.
"Underline the applicable items with a marker
and take it to the staff room by the due date," says Matsumoto.
You can understand her, Ms. Nishigaki?!
Thank you very much.
"I'll deal with any other documents,
so just leave them alone for now," she says.
Thank you very much.
I wonder how she knows what the president's thinking...
Ms. Nishigaki, you came over again?
I caused an explosion and got in trouble with the principal.
Now I can't use the science room for a week.
You mean... You're going to be sitting here for the next week?!
Matsumoto said it was fine.
Right?
See?
I guess it's fine.
Please try not to blow up the student council room, okay?
By the way, Matsumoto,
I'm thinking of trying to fly next!
Like this.
If I get a running start and jump off the roof,
I expect I'll be able to fly around three kilometers.
Don't you worry.
The word "death" doesn't exist in my dictionary.
If I were to fly three kilometers, that'd be amazing!
I'd get home in one jump!
Easier than a car.
Though I would stand out a bit.
School
But going from home to school would be a problem...
My House
At my house, I'd have to jump from the second floor.
A launch pad?
If you get shot out of a cannon, you can fly really far, right?
In games, anyway.
I tried making one once, but it was a complete failure.
The blast from the launch was bigger than I'd predicted.
My house was nearly destroyed.
You see? Inventing isn't all that easy.
Explosions and destruction are inevitable,
but new things can be born from it!
Isn't it wonderful?
I won't try going from my roof, though.
That's right. Matsumoto, will you be my test subject again?
I tried improving that medicine from the other day,
but when I tried drinking it myself, my voice became really high.
You can't even compare it to helium gas.
AAAA
Goddammit!
The timing was bad and the principal came to talk to me.
"What's with that voice?! Are you messing around again?!"
"I'm not messing around!"
I said that, but it didn't sound like I was.
It was pretty surreal.
The side-effects?
It's okay.
Your hair may grow a little,
but I'll cut it for you.
Let's stop, Yui.
But I really feel bad about leaving Akari behind.
Kyouko Toshinou!
Ayano, there's big trouble!
The student council room is dangerous! Very dangerous!
I guess explosions really are inevitable.
Hey! What are you doing, Teacher?
Don't worry, I wasn't hurt.
Well, I wasn't really worried about that...
More importantly, what about that girl over there?
Matsumoto got burned more than I did.
P-President!
You okay?
I see. You're doing just fine.
Um, I was thinking about this before...
You and the president get along pretty well, don't you?
It's somewhat of a forbidden relationship.
She tests my medicines that are still in development.
And she takes care of me a lot.
That really isn't good...
Also, we both frequently get caught in explosions.
So, we're Explo-pals?
What's that mean?
Well, we're kinda like pen pals.
I should recruit more Explo-pals.
Please don't recruit!
President, if you don't like it, you should just refuse.
President?
Thank you, Matsumoto.
They're some strange people.
It's her!
She's the ghost we saw.
Ghost?
You mean the president?
The president...?
The student council president?!
That's right.
The student council president, Rise Matsumoto.
President?!
I've never seen her before.
She's in this room all the time.
That's news to me.
She was there when we went to the beach, too.
You're kidding!
But I'm glad...
She's not really a ghost.
What's wrong?
S-Something cold just touched my neck!
Nice reaction!
What are you doing?!
That's Rum Raisin!
Yes, yes, I wanted this.
H-Hey! That's what I came for!
Give it back!
Geez.
I'll do that.
By the way, President,
I've always wondered...
...what kind of experiments do you and Ms. Nishigaki do?
W-What do they do...?
Where do you think Akari went off to?
It really makes you wonder, huh?
Well, it all worked out, right? I get to eat some ice cream.
What's with you?
Guys!
Somehow, she doesn't look angry.
What a relief.
Sorry about today, guys.
Why are you apologizing?
Because I didn't go to the clubhouse today.
You were there, though.
What're you talking about? I wasn't.
We were helping the teacher with some things.
Right?
Yup.
But all Sakurako could do was get in the way.
What was that? Well, your breasts always get in the way!
Intruding breasts!
T-Then...
Who was that Akari...?
Grudges are grudges.
What's wrong, Chinatsu?
We should be asking you that!
Even as a vengeful spirit, her existence is pretty weak, isn't it?
Vengeful spirit?
Weak existence?!
And you're cold, too.
Cold?!
But it's hot today!
Right?!
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
It's your returning protagonist, Akari Akaza.
The preview is better left to me.
I won't let you call me "The Protagonist (lol)" ever again!
Now, next week's episode is the second-years' school trip.
Wait. Isn't it suspicious that they suddenly chose me to do the preview?!