Mari!
Here!
Sway 'n Shake starts now!
Good job!
Good girl.
Um, that's my job...
It's the last episode, too...!
Why?
Why'd it have to come to this?
It's no use.
I couldn't think of a better way...
Perform a miracle like you always do!
If you die, who'll be my rival?!
Just... become rivals with all of those who try to crush the happiness of others.
I'll leave everyone... to you.
Mirakurun?
Mirakurun?!
Mirakurun!
Oh, and I'll leave my leftover math homework to you.
Mirakurun! Mirakurun!
Also, please buy me some juice and a yakisoba bun.
MIRAKURUN!
What are you guys watching?!
Kyouko Toshinou!
It's time to go home.
Don't stay around here all day.
Yo, Ladies.
Ms. Nishigaki and the president...
What're you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
We're preparing.
Preparing for what?
A sleepover.
A sleepover? How nice!
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 12
Everyone to the Cozy Sleepover
Th-There's no helping it. I'll go get permission.
Don't just do whatever you feel like while I'm gone.
Sure, I won't do anything.
She's acting all high and mighty...
Sorry... for taking up your time.
Don't worry about it.
Moreover, is it okay for us to be staying over, too?
Of course.
The president's staying, too.
If you'd like, you can invite the others to come as well.
Alright.
C'mon. Let's join.
Just to make sure you guys don't do anything weird,
I'm coming to keep an eye on you.
And I'm not happy about it one bit!
Ta-da!
Stuffed animal pajamas!
How cute...
Here, Akari.
Yay!
This is for you.
Here, China-chu!
Don't call me that...
Wait. Why'd you get all of these?
Aren't they quite pricey?
I won them at the arcade.
Meow! How is it? Am I cute?
Chinatsu, you're so cute!
Really cute.
I'm glad I picked black. It really works for you.
What do you mean by that?
I'm... a puppy!
Akari, gimme your paw.
Woof!
Once more.
Now your chin.
Woof!
Kneel down.
Akari...
Hey! You hafta change, too, Yui.
Yui, you're too cute!
It really suits you, Yui!
But it's embarrassing...
Yup! It does suit you quite well.
What's yours like, Kyouko?
Mine is especially cute!
A cat? Or a bunny?
Ta-da!
A tomato!
What kinda choice is that?!
Yui, try stepping on me.
Since you're a tomato... you'll burst?
Come to think of it... Do pandas roar?
I wonder...
Do you know, Kyouko?
Tomato!
Toma-To-To-
Um, Yui?
I'm glad that I got to wear this!
Me, too!
Kyouko, thanks a bunch!
Thanks.
Don't mention it...
I'm kinda embarrassed, so I wanna take this off.
You can't!
This is proof of the friendship between the four of us.
A bond between us!
We're connected through these.
I have no clue what you're talking about...
So yeah, keep wearing it, okay?
I guess there's no helping it...
There's nothing to be embarrassed about!
You're so incredibly cute!
Well, you do lose compared to me.
Shut up, Tomato!
Okay.
Chinatsu, come here!
Hey, I'm starting to get kinda hungry!
You're ignoring me?!
I guess we haven't eaten lunch yet.
Is there anything in particular you'd like?
I'd like some spaghetti!
I like carbonara!
Bathroom.
I guess we'll go with carbonara, then.
Will you help me make it?
Sure, and we can add an egg on top!
Shopping for lunch?
Yeah. You come help, too, Kyouko.
Roger that.
We hafta buy some fresh cream...
That's right.
You took off your tomato!
Yeah, it was a nuisance in the bathroom.
You said to keep it on!
Well, pajamas are for the nighttime, anyway.
You're the one who brought it up!
The first, friendly amusement club vs. student council match.
If you lose, you're expelled.
Fight with all your might, serious match time!
Yes. On that note, the match has now begun.
The showdowns will be decided... by a random draw.
AAAAAA
Do Your Best FIGHT Box
H-Hey, Kyouko Toshinou, I never heard anything about being expelled!
I was surprised, too.
What do you plan to accomplish?
Did you think I'd let you go?
It's so frustrating, but...
How nice...
Chitose!
If I weren't here, you'd really be hopeless.
You're right, so never leave my side.
Are you okay, Chizuru?!
I'm fine.
Don't kiss up to her, Boobs for Brains.
What'd you just say?!
Idiot, idiot!
What's this all about?
With all of this going on, our presence is pretty weak, huh?
"Our"?!
Kyouko! Hurry up with the showdowns!
AAA
Othello
First Match
I won't lose.
Me neither!
Now, then, for the first battle, we have Othello!
Ready... Go!
That's it.
Akari is the victor.
Yes!
You're pretty good.
I've always been good at that game.
Well, I didn't expect much from you... This is a game of wits, after all.
Don't treat me like an idiot!
That's weird, though...
What is?
When Akari put that piece there,
I didn't even notice.
I wonder... Maybe she can erase her existence at will...
AAAAAAAA
Imitating Mirakurun Characters
Second Match
Um, I'm doing this one...?
I don't want to imitate Mirakurun any more...
Yes! This'll be easy!
Magical Girl Mirakurun,
makes her lovely entrance!
She's dark...
Cunning...
Sour...
I'm R-Rivalun...
This is so embarrassing!
Himawari is the victor!
Kyouko, why? Don't I look like Mirakurun?!
That's right. You're the only Mirakurun for me.
Kyouko...
Kyouko!
China-chu!
You think I'd buy that?
AAAAA
Gesture Showdown
Third Match
Gestures, huh?
Chizuru!
Her thinking is one-sided.
As long as I keep that in mind...
Gesture Showdown. Start!
Someone eating a churro.
It's someone playing the flute.
Did I over-think this?
Then how about the next one?
This has to be...
A baseball batter!
No. Someone grabbing the pole on a train.
What's with that?!
What's with your answer?
Next!
Breasts...
Me!
That can't be right!
Alright. I'm going.
Fushimi Inari-taisha's guardian fox.
You're right!
Kiyomizu Temple Inari-taisha's guardian fox.
The stone fox that Koizumi Yakumo loved, located at the Matsue shrine.
Right again!
Do you see the difference...?
How could I?
Fourth Match
Everyone in the amusement club went already, right?
I thought something like this would happen, so I invited some special guests.
Please come in.
Why is the president here?
"Helping students in need is the duty of the student council president," she says.
But...
"If you can't beat me, you have no hope of becoming the next president, Ayano," she said.
That one I kinda made up myself.
Please don't make things up!
AAAAA
Experiment
What kind of showdown is this?!
Whoever provides the most interesting results is the winner.
Pretty simple, right?
Now, then. Let's start the experiment.
How about you get out before me?
Himawari, you should check your boobs. They're all red.
My breasts have nothing to do with this!
Himawari, Sakurako, can we go in soon?
It sure feels good, huh?
I would've liked to bathe with Yui, though...
It's too cramped for that.
All the better...
Oh, Chinatsu...
So pretty!
If you hold out your hands, it feels like you can touch them!
I'm glad I didn't bathe with her...
Somebody save me!
No way!
No!
Wasn't there two of them?
Y-You go in first.
I'll wait until after.
It'll be fine. C'mon in.
Hey! Kyouko Toshinou!
I guess it is a bit cramped.
That's why I told you...
Geez...
That's so good...
Chitose?
W-What is it?
I was just thinking... Yours are pretty big, too.
W-Where are you looking?!
Hooray!
Again...?
I guess it's about time to get out.
Yeah, I guess so...
I'll go first.
So much!
Cut that out!
Your hair's grown pretty long. Wanna cut it soon?
Thanks for the meal!
I'm full!
We'll go get the futons.
Though, you'd be fine with just a mat.
What was that?
Thanks for the help.
I forgot about Akari...
I'm going out to look for a bit.
Kyouko Toshinou!
Help clean up!
I've already prepared dessert.
Chocolates!
Those chocolates look really good.
I haven't been able to eat it since I was little.
Seriously?!
A life without chocolate... What kind of pitiful childhood did you have?
Eat up!
Have plenty!
Really?
Thank you for the sweets.
This won't fool me.
Make sure to clean up properly.
Honestly, people like you...
Ayano...
I kissed Ayano!
W-What just happened?
Big Sis...
Chizuru! What's happening?!
When she eats chocolate, a demon awakens inside of her...
A demon?
When we were little...
Give me some chocolate, too.
Grandma, you're being mean.
Chocolate's a frightening thing.
If children eat it, a scary demon will awaken inside of them.
R-Really?
It's true.
Chocolate's a scary thing.
A scary thing!
She said that to keep us from getting cavities.
She was only looking out for us.
That is how this tragedy came about.
Then she shouldn't eat chocolate!
What happened to her promise with your grandma?!
She forgot about it.
She forgot about it?!
Wasn't it important to keep?!
It doesn't matter. Once she's like this-
I'll kiss Chizuru, too!
Hey! Chizuru! Chizuru!
It's no use. A-At this rate...
Hey, Ayano! Why are you spacing out?!
My consciousness left me for a while.
Welcome back...
Funami!
Kiss!
Sorry we're late.
I had trouble finding Akari.
I was passed out by the river.
Y-Yui! Since when are you and Ikeda like this?!
This can't be!
No!
What?! What's happening here?!
Alright! I'll try to stop her.
You can't, Kyouko Toshinou! It's dangerous.
It's okay.
We can't afford to have any more sacrifices.
Kyouko...
Come, Chitose!
Toshinou!
Kyouko!
You're accepting it?!
Stay away!
How are we supposed to stop Chitose?
I guess we just have to wait until she runs out of steam.
But then, the damage will just keep spreading.
In that case, should we take the steam out of her?
How?
A nosebleed?
Won't she die?
But there's no other way.
The way to make her have a nosebleed...
That would be...?
I refuse! I completely refuse!
But you have to do it!
Are you okay with Chitose like that?!
Chitose!
Take a good look at this!
Sorry we took so long.
Well, then, good night.
Good night.
It sure was fun.
Yeah, I guess it was.
Let's do this again.
Next time, be sure to get permission first.
You're worried you won't wake up on time?
Don't worry.
I brought an alarm clock.
I set it for 7:30 in the morning,
so sleep at ease.
Kyouko Toshinou, are you still awake?
Yeah?
Um... Thanks for inviting me.
That's it! Good night!
Ayano... Wanna sleep together?
H-Hurry up and go to sleep!
Good morning...
Akari...
In order to save us...
Akari will always be in our hearts...
She's in our hearts!
That's right!
We shall never forget about you, Akari!
Akarin!
Hey, everyone!
I haven't died!
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!