Akarin!
Here!
What's this?
What's going on?
Being called here means...
Akarin!
I knew it!
What do you mean?!
For this episode, our parts end here.
Wait. We weren't even called on.
Her weak existence is steadily spreading to us.
It's my fault now?!
AAAAAAAAAAA
Nanamori Middle School - 2nd Year, Class 5 Group
Man, I didn't have breakfast this morning.
I bet it's because you slept in.
Last night, I was so excited that I couldn't sleep!
What are you, a grade-schooler?
How many snacks did you pack?
No, no. It's not like I only packed snacks.
AAAA
Safety
For when the need arises!
You won't have a chance to use that stuff in Kyoto!
What kind of mountain did you think would be there?
Then this.
I found this in a 100 yen shop!
It'll come in handy.
We can put souvenirs or even our laundry in here!
It's really useful.
I bought quite a few, so I'll give one to you.
I don't need one.
Don't say tha-
Hey...
Don't tell me you're getting motion sickness after eating all of those snacks?
That bag came in handy right away...
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 10
It's a School Trip, but I Wonder What We're Here to Learn?
AAAAAA
Welcome to Kiyomizu
Thank you for coming
You okay?
It's Chizuru!
Hey! Chizuru!
You need a bag?
No I don't!
Kiyomizudera!
Amazing!
It really makes you feel like you've arrived in Kyoto.
Hey! Kyouko Toshinou!
Using this as an excuse to get excited'll earn you the Buckingham Penalty, got it?
You should calm down, too, Ayano.
But then again, it's been so long since I've been here, so I'm excited, too!
That's right. You are from Kansai, after all.
Wow!
There are so many emas!
Wanna write some later?
Yes! I wanna!
Like I said... You shouldn't get so worked up over Kyoto!
Aren't you one who's the most worked up, Ayano?
AAAAAAAAA
Tour of the Womb Reception Desk
Tour of the Womb?
Oh, that.
You walk around in complete darkness.
I don't really understand, but it sounds fun!
Let's womb!
It's so dark!
It's darker than I could've imagined!
I'm getting kinda pumped!
It'd be bad if you missed the railing.
It's sort of like you're floating.
It's starting to turn here.
H-Hey! Who's that?! Don't touch me in weird places!
Ah, sorry. Where'd I touch you?
My butt...
Wait! That doesn't matter!
If you're going to grab something, grab my waist!
It doesn't matter where I touch you...
H-Hey, that's not my waist!
What's this?
The exit!
Boy, that was dark.
K-Kyouko Toshinou, I won't forgive you!
It was so dark. I couldn't help it.
The womb...
It's a more fearsome place than I expected.
Though, they didn't expect that kind of reaction.
This is Kiyomizu's stage, huh?
I can fly!
Don't you dare jump!
You can fly?
Yeah, right!
But you probably wouldn't die from a fall like this.
Maybe if you only did it once... Wait. You'd definitely die!
Okay, I'll take a picture.
Take it, take it!
Give me the camera.
Hey, would you take a picture for us?
Sure.
I can take it...
What are you talking about?
All of us are finally here,
so we should have everyone in the picture.
What's this?
It's said that you'll feel healthier depending on where you touch the statue.
Whoa! Then I have to touch it.
Lately, I've been having headaches...
It's okay. I don't think you're that stupid!
It's not for that!
Please do something about my constant nosebleeds.
Something really should be done about that...
What about you, Ayano?
May I become more honest with my feelings.
Ayano, you want bigger breasts or something?
That's not it!
K-Kyouko Toshinou, where are you going to touch it?
Saying it like that sounds kinky.
I'll touch it all over!
Well, I kinda thought she'd do that...
Isn't this the bottom of Kiyomizu's stage?
You're right!
It really isn't that tall. You wouldn't die from this.
But if you fall onto those things, you'd be a goner.
I see...
What are you talking about now?
But having the resolve to jump from Kiyomizu's stage is pretty admirable.
You rarely see anyone with that kind of resolve.
Like jumping into magma.
You'd die from that. You think this is a video game?
AAAAAA
Shitagiri Tea House
My legs are so tired!
The autumn colors are really beautiful.
I know, right?
I took a lot of pictures.
I see...
It seems like there's nothing but pictures of me and Ayano, doesn't it?
They look so good!
Delicious.
Sweet things taste so much better when you're tired, huh?
This Hiyashi Ame is really refreshing, too.
Hey, hey, what kind of hotel are we staying in?
AAAA
Restless
Y-You're such a child. Getting all excited over a hotel...
Again, you're the most excited.
I looked into some hotels,
and it looks like it's Japanese-style.
Yay, Japanese-style!
Rooming with you guys is gonna be fun.
I won't let you sleep tonight.
You'll be the first to hit the sack.
It looks like they have a big public bath, too.
Great Scott!
What is it?
It's alright, just... Don't stare at me like that.
Cut it out!
Gosh, Kyouko Toshinou!
Chitose, don't die from blood loss, okay?
I can't wait!
Let's go to the hotel right now!
Calm down!
AAAA
Anxious
Calm down!
How many times do I have to say it?!
We've arrived!
You already changed?
Let's go to the bath! The bath!
I'm not going yet.
All that walking's made me tired.
I'm gonna rest for a little.
You sit down, too. Just relax for a bit.
The view's so nice!
Isn't that Daimonji mountain?!
There's juice in here! I wonder if we can drink it all.
Oh! They have satellite!
They have two TVs next door!
She doesn't have any desire to calm down...
I'm telling you, Chizuru is a tsundere.
Why are you here?!
"Why?" you ask?
To meet you, of course!
Kissy, kissy!
Sorry for the trouble she's caused.
C'mon! I finally got to play with Chizuru!
Let's go to the bath.
Really?!
If I leave you alone, you'll just bother people.
Yay! Bath time!
Plus, she should mellow out after being in the hot water.
Did you say something?
Not really.
So big!
Stop sliding, idiot.
There's an open air bath, too!
This really is embarrassing.
You have a good figure, so you'll be fine.
Don't say that! It'll make me even more embarrassed!
Shouldn't you take your glasses off?
No, no. If I remove them, my life may be in danger.
Hey!
Shampoo!
Hey! Cut that out!
Ayano, wanna lather up?
Shampoo, shampoo!
Stay away!
A crab person!
Enough already, idiot!
Don't swim.
You're being too loud, Kyouko Toshinou!
Sea monster!
H-Hey! Cover yourself up, Kyouko Toshinou!
Why?
Gosh...
What's this?
A sauna.
I'm going in!
So hot...
Yui, it was so hot...
Do you even have the word "easygoing" in your dictionary?
How naive. I don't even have a dictionary to begin with!
I thought so.
Just as I was hoping, she's calmed right down.
Oh, yeah, do you wanna go buy some souvenirs?
There's some rare pickled foods I wanna get.
Sure.
Let's go, then.
What about Toshinou? Should we wake her up?
We should just leave her.
I'll go!
You were awake?
Is this sticky one alright?
AAAAA
Pickled Vegetables
But you can find those in Tokyo.
Really?!
They had this in the Edo period.
Why are they selling this in Kyoto?
Chizuru!
Don't interfere!
She's so mean, that Chizuru...
It's because you bother her, despite her hatred towards you.
No, no. It's because she's showing signs of affection.
It only seems that way from your end.
Really?
Hey, Chitose! Did you buy the pickled veggies?
Yeah, right here.
We got other stuff, too.
I see. Maybe I'll buy something, too.
But if you buy any food, you'll just end up eating it right away.
That's rude!
Am I wrong?
Well, I guess that's true...
Now, I wonder if there's anything I can buy as a memento.
Oh, what if you bought the same thing as Toshinou?
You might become a couple.
S-Stop being ridiculous!
AAAAAA
Kyoto Wooden Sword
I'll take this!
You really like wooden swords.
I'll have one of these.
Okay.
But having wooden swords as a couples' charm is a little questionable.
It's not to become a couple! I just wanted one!
Alright, I understand.
More importantly, have you bought any souvenirs for Akari and Chinatsu?
I have.
Then I'll give them this.
What is it, Ayano?
It's nothing...
Don't worry.
I-I wasn't even feeling down!
Think of how happy Akari and Chinatsu will be when I give them this wooden sword.
Just one?
Then I'll split it in half.
Would they be happy to get half a wooden sword?
Of course they would!
Just do whatever.
This looks delicious!
Thank you for the meal.
This taro's good!
Yui, give me yours.
I already ate mine.
Then give me yours, Ayano.
I-I guess I don't mind...
Then what would you like from mine?
I suppose... the radish.
Say, "Ah!~"
It's just a pain to put on your plate.
Is it good?
Ikeda, your miso soup is red.
Well, now it's my turn.
I can't wait!
Taro's so tasty!
Don't worry.
Like I said, I'm not feeling down!
Hey, Chizuru! Gimme your taro!
Who would?!
I got some leftover rice.
Who could even eat this much?!
Now, now, we're still growing.
I-I don't f-feel so good...
You were so excited and went overboard. Are you a grade-schooler or something?
I'm a high-schooler!
Even when you're like this, you're still acting childish?
Here, stomach medicine.
Pass it to me, mouth-to-mouth.
Suffer by yourself.
You meanie.
Our futons are already laid out.
So nice and soft!
Toshinou, wanna go?
Sounds fun!
What is it?
A pillow fight tournament!
Of course not!
We're on a school trip, that-
Who cares, Ayano? Don't be so strict.
Are there rules in a pillow fight?
Oh, right, I wonder...
Just attack until the person stops moving?
A deathmatch?!
Then a special rule!
If you get a nosebleed, you're eliminated!
Knowing you, Kyouko Toshinou,
you've been trying to give Chitose a nosebleed all along, haven't you?!
W-W-What are you talking about?!
C'mon, don't play dumb.
Sorry, Ayano.
She already got a nosebleed.
That was fast! Is she disqualified?
No. We haven't started yet, so she's safe!
She's such an easy opponent.
It won't be pretty if you underestimate me.
I'll show you how serious I can be.
Then, get ready... Start!
Ayano! Kiss me!
Oh, no!
No, there's not a nosebleed...
No nosebleed!
It's coming out of your eyes!
Kyouko, in order to spare Chitose's life, that strategy is forbidden.
That right! It's cowardly.
In exchange, I'll introduce a special rule of my own.
Alright, I accept. Say it!
Talking like men is forbidden. One must only speak like a proper lady.
What?!
I mean...
Excuse me?
But I wonder if that is fine.
It is no big task for myself.
Oh, really now?
Yui. Don't tell me...
Talking like ladies isn't embarrassing at all...
It has a big effect on Funami, I see.
How cowardly!
Take this now!
Oh? I will not stand for such an offensive move!
You are quite formidable.
When they're conversing like that, don't they seem like princesses?
Those two are speaking like Furutani.
Eat this! If you'd like!
I have done it! And in one hit!
You sure have...
I am terribly sorry...
Nice hit, I say!
There!
Sorry...
Two in a row!
Ah! Ayano, dear, your yukata is open.
An opening!
Super Rolling!
Y-Yui!
Now you have done it!
You are putting the blame on me?!
That is cowardly! So very cowardly!
I'm not to blame! I didn't do anything!
I am really angry!
What did you say?!
Hey, we're at a standstill,
but can't we call it quits?
What a coincidence, I was just thinking the same.
Besides, Chitose got caught in the crossfire and retired already...
So tired...
Sweating... so much...
What should we do? Wanna take another bath?
Maybe tomorrow morning.
How about we take a bath now?
Yeah...
Man, I didn't think Chizuru would be here.
Why're you here?!
Hey, now, don't act up so much.
The stars are beautiful.
They really are.
It'd be nice... if these days could continue forever.
Hey! Someone take a jab!
Right now the mood's good, so let's just stay quiet.
I agree.
May these fun times last forever.
May these fun times last
forever. - Kyouko
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
It's your protagonist for the beginning and end, Akari Akaza.
The title call and the preview are both mine!
Now, the time for Sway 'n Shake's climax is drawing near.
It's finally time for me to shine!
That'd be nice... at least.