Why Won't it Stop? Throbbing, Beating Paradox: Eternal
I shall begin!
Yui
Once again, the prince rides through the plains on her white horse.
With the wind in her hair, she decides to bravely let go of the reins.
Eventually, she realizes that she has come much farther than usual.
While gazing upon the unknown landscape,
a single young lady catches her eye.
She was not the kind of gorgeous lady that you might see in a castle.
Indeed, she was quite a miserable-looking girl.
Me
However, the girl's smile was more beautiful than any jewel.
As if she had been struck by lightning, the prince's body lost all feeling.
When she came to, she found herself standing dauntingly before the young lady.
Their eyes met, and in that moment...
With their hearts pounding, and chests throbbing...
Their thoughts became a paradise!
In that moment, the two eternally fell in love!
But standing in the way of their romance was the girl's cruel mother and almost invisible elder sister.
The prince and the young girl were separated.
Furthermore, there were four dwarfs who tempted the girl with a poisoned apple.
Don't do it, Chinatsu! You mustn't eat that!
Ah. What a terrible tragedy!
The girl ate the poisoned apple,
and fell into a deep slumber for 10,000 years.
Then appeared a dashing, handsome prince.
The prince gazed upon the beautiful, sleeping girl, and became speechless.
Unable to hold back any longer, the prince joined lips with the girl!
In that moment, the unfortunate curse cast upon the girl was broken!
Thus allowing the girl to return to her beautiful, doll-like figure.
The girl then returned back to Mother Ocean, sparkling in the morning glow.
Then, Yui and I welcomed the morning in the same room,
and drank some friendly morning coffee.
The End
And they lived happily ever after!