Akarin!
Here!
Sway 'n Shake starts now!
Nothing's happening this time!
I guess it's okay like this...
Akari...
You poor thing...
K-Kyouko Toshinou?!
Why the sudden call?
Ayano, meet me in front of the station tonight.
Hey, wait! Kyouko Toshinou?!
Walking around this late at night...
What was she thinking?!
There she is!
Ayano!
Kyouko Toshinou!
You sure got here quickly.
Ayano!
Now, let's go!
Here we are!
Daijiken!
What a big event!
Sway 'n Shake
Alright, let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Yay!
Yui!
Hey, stop that!
Alright!
A bustling today, tomorrow, huge explosion
Tentekomai no kyou, ashita, daibakuhatsu
So we don't grow any taller, what should we do?
sonde, shinchou nobinai ya dou shiyou?
At a theme park, eating too many sweets
amai mono tabesugi temapaku
Hey now, what shall we do with this shy young girl?
hoijya, kakuseyo otome de dou jyaro?
The club's performance
bukatsudou honban
Tsk, tsk! It's bad to come late
shime shime buchikoku
A job? School work? What the heck are those?
hongyou gakugyou nani sore?
There's no way those are edible!
sonna no zenzenzenzenzenzen taberenaai!
Cut it out, Kyouko!
Exam success! (Exam success!)
sakurasaki! (sakurasaki!)
Exam failure! (Exam failure!)
sakurachiri! (sakurachiri!)
Tomorrow as well, I'll sing about the good days (Let's sing!)
ashita mo ii hi to utau yo (utau yo!)
I love you! (I love you!)
kimi ga suki! (kimi ga suki!)
You're okay! (You're okay!)
kimi ga ii! (kimi ga ii!)
Tomorrow as well, I think I want to stay by your side
ashita mo itai to omou yo tonari ni
The last thing to do is doze off into sleep
saishuu shutan de inemuri
What a big event!
Daijiken!
Episode 05
When Akari and the Cicadas Cry
Coming here during the summer and the winter is the best!
So when are you going to explain yourself?
What exactly am I doing here?
We're here to find that out!
I don't think she was expecting such a philosophical answer...
Do I need to say it?
This is where you belong.
I'm so happy.
Never let me go.
What a wonderful morning!
This is the Comic Extreme Market,
or "Comiket' for short.
It's for showing off and selling stuff made by fans.
Stuff made by fans?
Yeah.
Kyouko participates in one of the circles.
It'd be tough with just me and Yui,
so we had you two come help out!
Tell me that beforehand!
It's a surprise Comiket!
You can throw that surprise off Niagara Falls!
So why me?
Why not Akaza or Yoshikawa?
Comiket is pretty harsh, so I'd feel sorry for Akari and Chinatsu.
So you're saying I'll be okay?!
I really wanted to have Chinatsu cosplay as Mirakurun!
She's actually on the verge of tears...
Cheer up, Ayano.
I'm really sorry.
Well, then, let's enter our circle!
Without a circle ticket, you'd have to wait for hours to get in!
Let's get going, then.
See you later!
Stop this, Rivalun!
I don't want to fight you anymore!
Shut it, Mirakurun!
Since we're both magical girls, we have to talk through our fists!
That's right!
For the sake of our Giga Giga Brigade, you must defeat Mirakurun!
Understood, Ganbou!
Rivalun!
He does have bones!
Did Kyouko Toshinou really write this?
She sure did.
But I thought you would've known. It's kind of unexpected that you don't.
Well, we don't share the same interests, so...
Isn't this great?
You discovered something new about Toshinou.
W-Who cares about that?
I finally got in...
Why did I have to enter normally when I'm the circle's representative?
It's your fault for forgetting you only had 3 tickets.
More importantly, are my books selling?
I have a lot of confidence in my work this time!
That's too bad...
We've only sold ten books so far.
Ten books?!
Yay!
Ayano, did you read it, too?
Not really.
Fan comics don't really spark my interest...
Are you sure you're not interested?
Please teach me... softly.
Oh, no! If I get excited here, the books'll get dirty!
I'll take Chitose to the washroom.
Oh, perfect timing!
While we're at it, let's all change.
The magical girl of love and justice, Mirakurun,
makes her lovely appearance!
How's it look? Isn't the costume awesome?
Isn't that how he sounds?
Kyouko Toshinou, what is this?!
You can totally see my midriff!
Ganbou, Rivalun, Rivalun pre-transformation.
You all look great!
Since Chinatsu isn't here, I'll do my best as Mirakurun!
Sorry, but just deal with it.
Toshinou is pretty amazing.
Didn't she make all of these costumes herself?
Kyouko's very nit-picky about these kinds of things.
Why can't you channel that enthusiasm into something more productive?
Alright! Let's sell some books!
Oh, you guys can take a break, though.
You're finally at Comiket, so why not look around?
This is my first time here, but there sure are a lot of girls.
I guess so.
Hey! It's Ganbou and Rivalun!
Look, Mommy, it's Rivalun!
Hey, she's calling you, Rivalun!
Hey!
Mommy! Rivalun waved at me!
That's wonderful!
Come on. It's bad to disrupt the Earth's invasion. Let's go.
Do your best, Rivalun!
You look just like the real thing, Funami.
This isn't me...
Lemme see these!
Big sister...
You cute little kitty.
Please be my idol.
I'll wait for your private lessons tonight.
Ch-Chitose!
Get ahold of yourself!
This is heaven.
Chitose!
Ayano, you sure you don't wanna look around?
Walking around in this outfit is too embarrassing...
Really? But it's so cute on you...
M-My Delusion-sense is tingling!
H-Hey...
What're fan comics lik-
Excuse me!
I'll take one of the newest volumes.
That'll be 500 yen.
Okay.
Um, are you Ramuko Nishikyogoku?
R-Ramuko?
Yup, that's me.
I always buy your comics!
I love them!
Really?!
I'm so glad!
I was touched when Mirakurun and Rivalun went bowling using Ganbou!
In the eighteenth volume of Mirakurun, it really seemed like that would happen.
Exactly! Right after reading that one, I immediately came up with it!
It was like something sparked within me!
Good work, everyone!
Yeah, that sure was a lot of work.
Sorry for causing so much trouble, Funami.
You got that right! Dragging people all the way to Tokyo...
Ayano, here.
This is...
My thanks for today.
Take it if you want.
I can have it?
Thank you...
Well, it wasn't completely boring.
If you beg, I might go with you again.
Now, everyone help me carry these.
What are they?
Today's spoils!
I have even more!
I bought a few myself.
Just send them through the mail.
No way!
I wanna read them as soon as I get back!
Well, I'll leave it to you guys.
You...
You think I'm ever gonna go along with you again?!
Hey, tell me the answer for this one.
No.
Stingy demon.
I'm gonna twist off that mouth of yours.
Honestly,
I'd help you if you said you couldn't do it alone.
What homework do you have left?
I have to do a book report.
So that's why you've been reading that book.
When you're done, can you tell me what it's about?
Go to hell.
Couldn't you be a little nicer?
Be quiet and finish your homework already.
I don't wanna think anymore.
My brain's fried!
Hey! Sakurako?!
Now! Tell me the answer!
Or do you not care what happens to her?
What'll happen?
I'll pinch her cheeks and severely tickle her!
Big sister,
won't you forgive Sakurako?
I'm sure she's just tired.
It's the fault of the modern education system for placing this stress on the students.
If I sacrifice myself, you'll be satisfied, right?
It's okay, then.
In return, live your life to its fullest.
I'm so sorry!
When's the next student council election supposed to be?
You can't even remember that?
I believe it's in November.
I see. So I'll be Vice President come November, huh?
Hey! I can't just pretend I didn't hear that!
Well, unlike you, I have tons of friends, so I can dominate the polls!
Unlike you, I have superior grades!
It's kinda late to be asking this, but why'd you join the student council, anyway?
Because you said you were going to join.
Well, only you would've been a representative, and I didn't feel like losing.
Plus, isn't the student council cool?
You'll be well known by helping to improve the school!
Like Akari, who changes the water in the class flower's vase everyday!
Is that really... cool?
Speaking of Akari, she's so amazing!
I scraped my knee!
Here's a bandage!
My button came off!
I'll fix it for you!
I forgot my chopsticks!
I have some!
Stuff like that.
You're relying on Akaza way too much.
I'm sure she's secretly fighting evil in the name of justice!
The Protector of Justice, Akarin, is here!
So you finally showed up, Akarin.
I'll take your place as the protagonist today!
I won't let that happen!
Finishing Move: Hair Bun Bazooka!
Looks like I stopped them.
Give me back my buns!
Without those, I'll lose my signature look!
Serves you right, Akarin.
Eat this!
Finishing Magic: Skeleton!
Akarin?
Without my trademark buns, no one will recognize me!
With you literally disappearing into thin air,
I can take the lead role!
I... I won't let you!
Ultimate Finishing Move: Akarin Attack!
I won't hand over the lead role, even if I'm only made of air.
I'm telling Yui!
And so, the peace was protected once again.
Go forth! Never falter! Akarin!
That made no sense...
Her returned hair buns become transparent as well.
Invisible Akarin is amazing!
But you're right.
I want to become someone who looks after everyone more, like Akaza.
Then take a look at my work!
Not a chance.
That was such a touching book.
Ew, gross.
You're writing down your thoughts?
Yeah.
Alright! Then I'll write mine down too.
What? You didn't read anythi-
AAAAAAAAAA
Protector of Justice: Akarin - Sakurako Oomuro
My nose is all runny.
I bet someone's talking about me a lot!
Enough with those jokes.
Here.
What's this?
"The Yui Test"?
Answer every question!
Well, we get along, but it's not like I know everything about her.
Um, her birthday, her blood type...
What's this?!
Her favorite color of panties?!
I want to know everything about her!
Chinatsu...
You really like Yui, don't you?
Yes, I love her.
She's just trying to understand Yui more.
She really is a good friend!
AAA
Misunderstood her
I want to get closer to Yui,
so can you help me, Akari?
AAA
Serious
Sure thing!
If it's something I can do, I'll be glad to help.
Then first off,
who does Yui like?
She gets along best with...
I'd say Kyouko.
No way!
Probably.
They've always been together!
That's not fair, Kyouko...
Having a monopoly over Yui for all this time...
I thought I could close the gap between me and Yui this summer...
But you just had to take her to Tokyo.
Why do I have to be stuck with Akari?
Um, did you just say something mean about me?
Witching Hour.
Hair.
Curse.
Straw.
Nail!
That's weird. I think I'm hearing something I shouldn't...
Does Yui not think anything of me?
That's not true!
Really...?
Yeah!
So what do you want to do to get closer to Yui?
Exchange diaries?
That's fine, too...
But I'd like to... kiss her.
K-Kiss?
You want to... kiss her?
Well, that's only natural, right?
It is?!
I don't know... I doubt it, but is kissing among friends normal these days?
Then Kyouko and Yui could've...
I want to do this and that with Yui...
But don't you find it embarrassing?
You're right...
I might get nervous.
Hey, Akari...
W-What is it?
Let's kiss.
Well, I might get nervous for the real thing,
so let's practice.
You just said you'd do anything, didn't you?
I did, but...
Akari!
I really can't!
Why are you running away?!
Is anybody home?! Chinatsu is-
It's no use, Akari.
We're the only ones home right now!
Someone save me!
Chinatsu! You're just fooling around, right?
Akari... I've got you now.
A visitor!
It's probably just a salesman.
See! Your mother's back!
She won't be back for another hour!
It's okay, Akari.
This is just practice!
No!
It's open.
Yui! Kyouko!
Why are you here?!
We brought some souvenirs from Tokyo,
but I guess you were in the middle of something...
Y-You've got it wrong!
Please take your time.
Sorry. Really sorry.
Like I said, you've got it all wrong!
It's not what you think!
Yui!
Always miraculous!
itsumo mirakuru!
Mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
mira- mira- mi- mi- mi- mi-
In a delusion!
mousou chuu!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Let's go!
yoisho!
Almost late because it's morning, breakfast is overwhelming
asa kara girigiri asameshi morimori
Don't fret over your hair style (Not!)
kamigata nante ki ni shinai (Nai!)
What a Godsend I have a mochi, grab then eat it
tanabotabota mochi mochi tsuki mochi tsuke
Just go on being a glutton!
kuishinbou de ikimasu yo-!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh, yay!
Suddenly being reckless, cheekily dozing off
ikinari mucha furi chakkari neta furi
I won't be crushed, even if my works don't sell (Not!)
ukenai kurai ja kujikenai (Nai!)
Showing just a bit of courage, anything is possible
choppiri tsuyogari nandemo ari ari
Truthfully it's not, but that's alright!
honto ha nai kedo daijoubu!
During times of loneliness, I can meet you without delay so,
sabishii toki ha sugu ai ni iku kara
there aren't any secrets
kakushigoto ha nashi da yo
It's boring being alone
hitori ja yappari tsumannai
Let's go with everyone! Let's go!
minna de ikou yo Let's go!
Always miraculous, believe in miracles!
itsumo mirakuru shinjite mirakuru!
Our hearts are in a cheerful full bloom!
kokoro ha harebare mankai!
Today and tomorrow take your time, take it easy!
kyou mo ashita mo goyururi yuru yuru!
Always go at your pace
itsudemo mai pe-su de ikimashou
Always miraculous, a hesitant miracle
itsumo mirakuru mayowazu mirakuru
Love is in full bloom
ai shite sakasete mankai
The miracle that allows us to meet everyday,
kimi to mainichi aeru kono kiseki
I love it! I tell you that with all my heart!
daisuki omoikkiri tsutaeru yo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
hai! hai! hai! hai!
Ooh! Yay!
So I just have to follow the script?
Okay, here goes...
Hiya~! It's the student council's protagonist, Ayano Sugiura!
If you don't watch next time, I'll be disappointed!
Was this Kyouko Toshinou's doing?!