Akarin!
H-Hey...
Yui-chan! Why?
Sorry...
Kyoko told me to wear this
and do the intro...
Kyoko-chan!
Just this once!
Sheesh!
Keep going, Yui.
Yuru Yuri's... start... start...
I can't do something this embarrassing!
You think it's embarrassing?
Lazy, Japanese Summer
So hot...
I haven't used the AC yet this summer...
But today is brutal...
I can't take it...
I give up...
No!
Not yet!
I'll bear with it until I think I might pass out.
Then, once I'm soaked in sweat...
I'll freshen up with a shower
before turning on the AC!
That way, the AC
will feel even more...
Even more...
That's it.
Shower, shower.
I feel refreshed.
Time for this year's first use of the AC.
What?
So cool.
What're you doing?
There are no batteries in the remote,
so I can't turn the AC on!
Didn't you remove
the remote's batteries
because the ones
in your clock died?
Guess I'll have to go buy some.
How did you wind up
in front of my AC?
What're you making?
Curry.
What? I just had curry yesterday.
You're just assuming you'll get some?!
It's delicious!
You put sausage in your
curry instead of meat, huh?
Sausage is cheaper
and keeps longer.
I think I might like this
more than beef curry.
Really?
Yui-san, I want to eat
your curry everyday.
Namo Quest II, coming soon!
Coming soon!
They're making a sequel.
All right!
Now that I'm full, it's time
to buy some batteries!
Why did you come here?
Fans are great, too.
What are you doing in my house?
I was on my way to the
store to buy batteries,
but I stopped by Yui's
place to eat curry.
What?
Since I was around, I
thought I'd drop by.
You went to Yui-senpai's house?
You should have invited me.
Wait, you'd have to have walked right past
the store to get here
from Yui-senpai's home...
Now, now...
I'm off to buy batteries!
Senpai, why did you come here?
So cool.
Kyoko-chan, thanks for waiting.
This warabi mochi is tasty!
You really know how to make
someone feel at home, Akari.
You think so?
Akari, how much of your
homework have you got done?
A little more than half, I think?
What about you, Kyoko-chan?
You sure you want the answer?
That's not good.
You have to do it.
Well, the thing is...
I forgot my homework at
school, so I can't do it.
Why don't you just go get it?
I'm gonna air out
the room, okay?
Sure.
It might get a little warm in here...
What?
A cicada!
Kyoko-chan, do something.
I can't touch cicadas.
Okay!
Leave it to me!
What? Wait!
Anything but that!
Help!
Well done, Akari!
Hold still!
Take care!
What a walk.
It's so hot out.
I'll have to shower
again when I get home.
Okay!
Remote!
Batteries!
All right, set up!
Requires AAA                     AA
What?
You needed AAA batteries so
tomorrow we're going to the pool?
It's so hot.
And so humid, too.
I can't believe I missed the train...
Akari, hurry!
What?
Wait!
Wait, everyone!
Kyoko-chan!
I was looking forward to
swimming with everyone...
Let's see...
The next train is at...
That's a long wait.
I guess it can't be helped...
What should I do while I wait?
It's from Chinatsu-chan.
Get over here already!
We're waiting!
They look like they're having fun.
If the wind hadn't blown
away my pool coupon,
I would've made it on time...
The wind is so naughty sometimes.
I should send a reply.
Huh? Not quite...
Maybe this?
Yay! That's a good one!
Let's see... "I'll catch up later."
"Wait for me."
There!
I'm so thirsty...
Let's see...
Super Bitter
I'm too young for that.
I'll just get a Fanti Orange.
What?
Super Bitter
Why?
Whoever manages this vending machine,
you put this in the wrong place!
What am I gonna do?
Maybe I'll have Yui-chan drink it...
Yui-chan's lucky.
Drinking black coffee?
She's so mature...
Maybe some day, I'll be able to...
This always wakes me up.
I hope I'll say that while
studying for exams someday.
Fanti Orange is delicious.
A mosquito!
Kyoko-chan, a mosquito!
Oh, she's not here!
Help me!
I guess it left...
That mosquito scared me.
Maybe I'll close the windows
so it can't come back in.
But it'll get hot if I close them...
Jumping around like that
made me sweaty.
I feel even hotter since I'm
wearing my swimsuit under this...
If I'd known this would happen,
I'd have worn underwear instead...
But I bet it'll feel even better
when I'm finally in the pool.
It'll feel so cool.
I'm so excited.
It's Kyoko-chan.
Kyoko-chan, you're so funny.
What should I do?
Yeah.
It doesn't have enough impact...
How about this?
Not quite...
I guess this will do.
"I won't lose to you!"
Don't suck my blood!
My blood doesn't even taste good!
Well, you can suck my blood,
but don't make me itchy!
Oh, I have some bug spray!
I'm glad I borrowed
some from my sister.
Now I'm invincible.
I'm hungry...
I overslept, so I didn't
have much to eat.
Hooray, chocolate.
Maybe I'll have some potato chips.
Lightly Salted Potato Chips
Lightly salted.
I love lightly salted chips!
They're so good.
I made some for everyone,
so have some later.
It's Yui-chan.
That looks delicious.
Yui-chan made lunch for everyone.
Yui-chan's such a good cook.
I can't wait to have some!
But I didn't bring anything...
Um, let's see...
I know!
I ate a few, but
I'll bring these snacks.
And this coffee!
Everyone's waiting for you, Akaza-san!
It's Himawari-chan.
Everyone's already at the pool!
If I had super powers, I'd
warp and catch up with them.
Warp! Warp!
Just kidding.
I wanna go on the water slide.
I always go with my sister...
...because she says it's scary to go down alone.
It'll be my first time
going by myself.
I'm so nervous.
If I get scared, I'll have
someone go with me.
Don't they have a lazy river, too?
I wanna just float away.
It's Kyoko-chan!
Ikeda-senpai's nose is bleeding!
Is she okay? Is she okay?
Someone has tissues, right?
It's not stopping!
Incoming Message
Huh? What?
Kyoko-chan!
I don't need the play-by-play!
Someone help her!
Yeah, I'm okay. I'm resting.
Thanks, Mom.
Bye.
I feel all right, though...
I've just got a slight fever...
I'll just sleep.
What level did I get to yesterday?
I wanna get everyone in my
party up three levels.
I need to get the best equipment
at the weapon shop, too.
An enemy has appeared!
Gunner Yui
Kyoko, finish him!
Got it!
Swordsman Kyoko
There!
Yuri?
Non-lethal Blow
Don't worry, I used the back of my sword.
Just kill it!
He's attacking! Be careful!
White Mage Akari
Huh? What?
Akarin!
Huh? What's going on?
Black Mage Chinatsu
I'll finish it!
Black thunder!
Yuri!
You got him! There's only one left!
Akari used Revive.
Stop, everyone! I feel
bad for our enemies!
What're you doing?
Akarin!
Kyokorin!
Darn it, Kyoko...
My fever's gone down...
Oh. It's just Kyoko.
How's your cold?
My fever's gone down.
Wait, how did you know?
Our moms were talking
on the phone this morning.
I thought you might be lonely since
you're sick and all alone...
Want some udon?
Sure...but take that mask off.
Once in a blue moon,
you're actually considerate, Kyoko.
Say what you want, but I've got pajamas!
You're sleeping over?
You might get sick, too.
You shouldn't stay tonight.
What? Who cares?
I know you were lonely...
No, I wasn't...
So, when do you want the udon?
Now?
Maybe a little later...
Fine. Now.
It's good.
How many stars?
Two, I guess.
Minus one because you're noisy.
You're so harsh.
Kyoko...
There's some rum raisin
in the fridge...
Thanks.
If there's anything you want, just ask.
You're so thoughtful.
Mind if I keep playing
that game from the other day?
I'll turn the volume down.
No, don't worry about me.
They're still low level, though.
I got it!
You just rest!
Their levels really are low...
She'll have to wander
around this area
for about an hour and gain experience...
You're going to fight the boss already?
At this level, I should
be able to scrape by!
I died!
Give me that!
You're an energetic sick person.
Himawari!
Play with me!
Himawari, you're here, right?
Sakurako-sama is willing
to play with you!
Hey!
I hope your boobs explode, you booby monster!
She's not answering.
I guess she really isn't home...
Sakurako onee-chan?
Oh, Kaede...
My sister's out shopping.
She should be back soon.
What?
Do you hate boobs, Sakurako onee-chan?
No... Not really...
Oh, right. You still don't—
What?
I mean, I "still don't" what?
Your big sister doesn't
have boobs, either...
so you'll probably stay the same.
But when I grow up, I'll
share my boobs with you.
So cheer up.
Thanks.
You're a good girl.
Sakurako.
Himawari, you're late!
Your boobs weigh ya down!
Cut 'em off!
What?
So where are we going?
Good question!
You didn't even plan that far ahead...
I was bored!
It's Akari-chan.
Okay, let's follow her!
What?
She's buying something.
Black coffee!
Akari-chan likes that?
It's so bitter...
Don't force yourself.
Yay!
Oh, a pigeon.
Here you go. Eat up.
What're you doing?
Sorry, I couldn't help it...
Akaza-san is still sleeping...
This is bad!
Some pervert might do something to her!
I'll save her!
You better apologize to her tomorrow!
Okay.
I'm tired.
I'm sleeping over.
I want Wagyu steak for dinner.
You live next door. Go home!
Sushi's fine too!
Go home!
Onee-chan...
I made some tea.
Thank you, Kaede.
You're such a good girl, Kaede.
Not like my little sister...
I brought milk for you,
Sakurako onee-chan.
What?
I thought it might make
your boobs bigger.
You want your boobs to
get bigger, don't you?
What a nice little sister...
Thank you.
Why?
I don't taste good!
I'm your mind-over-matter protagonist, Funami Yui.
This preview protagonist series is
getting tough, since we're
running out of ideas.
Next, we'll be going to Tokyo
for the first time in a year.
I never know what
souvenirs to get in Tokyo.