Yuru Yuri 2 Episode 1 "The
Protagonist Returns"
Akarin!
Hey~
Yuru Yuri's starting again.
The Protagonist Returns
I'm Akaza Akari.
I'm the sort of super-normal middle
schooler you might find anywhere.
Despite that, I find every
day very fulfilling.
Because...
Good morning, everyone.
Akari!
Akari-chan!
Good morning!
Because everyone loves me!
Akari, your buns
look cool again today.
Can I touch them?
Kyoko, you just touched
them the other day!
It's my turn today!
That's not fair!
I still haven't touched them, yet!
The cute little kittens are
fighting over me again, today.
I'm such a naughty girl.
Akari, come sleep over
at my place sometime.
Yui-senpai, no!
Akari-chan's staying with me!
Not fair!
I want to watch Mirakurun alone with Akari!
Now, now. I'll sleep over
at each of your houses.
Really?
So...
No fighting!
Akari, you're so wonderful!
Akari-chan, you're so wonderful!
Shall we go to school?
Wait, Akari-chan!
I want to hold your hand...
Stop! I'll be holding her hand!
No, I will!
Come on, now. I don't have three hands.
So,
Kyoko-chan, you get my thumb.
Yui-chan, you get my pointer finger.
Chinatsu-chan, you get my middle finger.
Now you can all hold my hand.
I'm so happy!
But seems it'd be hard to walk, though.
By the way, this is what you
call Fleming's left hand rule.
Akari, you know everything!
Akari-chan, you know everything!
Just ask me if there's
anything you don't know.
Okay, then!
Why is the sky blue?
Because you're all so cute!
Akari, you're so wonderful!
Akari-chan, you're so wonderful!
I'll see you two later.
See you after school.
Chinatsu-chan's lucky
Akari's in her class.
We're finally alone, Akari-chan...
Something smells sour!
Oh, it's these pickles.
Oh, good. I thought your
feet might be stinky.
There's a person who sometimes
gives me pickles.
I'm sure someone wonderful is
watching over me from somewhere.
I secretly gave her my pickles,
homemade and full of love.
Now she will know how I feel.
Ikeda-senpai, your pickles
are always amazing.
I wish I could pickle some with you.
You can pickle me.
It's too much!
I didn't know there
was a fountain there.
It's so great to watch a red
fountain with Akari-chan!
Good morning, everyone...
Akari-chan!
What do you think you're doing?
I do not want your
stifling behavior ruining
my wonderfully fresh morning with Akaza-san.
What'd you say?
Sakurako-chan, Himawari-chan,
good morning.
You both seem lively today.
Akari-chan! You can give me a
good morning kiss, if you want!
You can kiss me, too!
What will I do with you kittens?
That will have to do.
It's not like I'm happy or anything...
You can do that every day!
Akaza Akari!
What was that?
Sugiura-senpai is so shy...
Oh, right. I baked some cookies.
They're shaped like my face!
They were left over.
Thank you.
Thanks for the food.
They're delicious!
It's just like you to start eating
from your trademark buns!
I want to see you do that again.
Your "Akarin."
Akarin~
But if I do that,
you won't be able to see
my cute face anymore.
I see.
Oh, you're hopeless.
What? You're really gonna do it?
Just today!
Akarin~
Akarin!
Akari-chan, you're so talented!
Akari-san, you're so talented!
I'm a naughty girl at school, too.
My time doesn't end after school, either.
That's right.
I am the brightest star
of the Amusement Club.
Akari's here!
You're late, Akari-chan.
I thought you weren't coming.
Sorry, sorry.
What are we doing today?
Today, we're doing...
We Love Akari-chan
Tada!
What's this?
The three of us made it.
With all our love...
Will you eat it?
Of course I will!
It's delicious.
Akari-chan, you're so awesome!
You've made a mess of
your cute face, Akari.
Thank you, Yui-chan.
I was going to do that!
Akari-chan, your cheek is so sweet.
You naughty little kitten!
I made something good, too!
This is the Akari and Mirakurun
doujinshi I wrote!
Here.
Thank you, Kyoko-chan!
Um...
Akari, I love you!
Kyoko-chan...
I love you, too!
I love you too, Akari...
Everyone...
Akaza Akari!
I love you, too!
Hold it right there!
I also love you, Akaza-san!
Those pickles... Ikeda-senpai!
I love you, too!
So do I!
I love you, too.
Chizuru-senpai!
I love you even more
than I love explosions!
Nishigaki-sensei, you too?
Akari!
Akari-chan!
We'll always be together!
Akari. Hey, Akari.
It's no use. She's fast asleep.
And after Yui-senpai went through
all the trouble to make lunch for us.
Who cares?
Leth's juth let her thleep.
Kyoko-senpai!
Don't talk with your mouth full.
It's bad manners.
Who cares? Let's just let her sleep.
I mean, look. She looks so happy...
Well, now that you mention it...
Anyway, thanks for the food.
No, you don't!
Leave some for Akari.
We'll always be together.
It's so nice and beautiful.
It's a shame it's so
close to home, though.
We're just a bunch of middle
schoolers, so we can't go far.
I'm glad our parents let us come.
Yes!
I've been looking forward
to today for a long time.
I was so jealous when you went
away on your school trip,
I couldn't stand it.
Did you want to take a
bath with me that badly?
No!
But...
If it were with Yui-senpai...
This is relaxing.
Why don't we have some of these?
Oh, I'll have one, too.
These are delicious.
You're right.
Hey!
These are good.
They really are.
I mean, no!
This isn't any different
from being at the club room.
Let's do something more hot springs-ish!
What's hot springs-ish?
Maybe table tennis?
Let's go with that.
Think before you speak.
Hurry up and serve.
Concentrate!
No.
Jeeze, Akari-chan.
Sorry.
Take this!
Killer smash!
It's stuck and won't come out.
Her hair ate it!
I got it!
I'll serve next.
Okay. Bring it on.
Here I go!
When you serve, you're supposed
to make the ball bounce once
on your side of the court,
then your opponent's...
Is that right?
Let's try that again, then.
Why do you have two?
So I can hit the ball whether
you aim left or right!
Here we go.
There.
Not... bad!
Aren't you going to use your left hand?
There!
I'm so sweaty.
I'm thirsty.
Fine, then. I'll buy you
guys something to drink.
Really? I want a Pukari.
All right.
But just buying it for
you would be too boring.
What?
Let's push Pukari and red
bean soup at the same time!
What? Pukari! I hope I get Pukari!
It's so hot...
Red bean soup won't quench my thirst...
Cheer up, Akari.
No one could've known most
vending machines prioritize
the left-most product
when two buttons are
pushed at the same time.
Obviously you knew, didn't you?
Oh, sorry.
Chinatsu-chan, what do you want?
What? Um, Boronamin C, please.
Okay.
This is going well!
I'd buy anything for you,
my cute little Chinatsu-chan.
Yui-senpai.
That's right, we're at
the hot springs today.
It's the perfect opportunity
to get closer to Yui-senpai!
Yui-senpai, I've always...
After exercising, you should
drink red bean soup
to replenish your blood sugar.
Doubles
Here I go.
There!
Akari.
Sorry!
Stop that.
All right!
It's about to get harder!
What? You can hit two balls at once?
I'm pretty good when I'm serious.
Here we go!
Yui-san, would you like
to wash each other?
I've already finished.
It's no big deal!
Don't go easy on me.
Ow! I'm sorry!
I'll do it myself!
You said not to go easy.
I can go even harder.
It's cold!
It feels so good.
It really does.
Miss, your skin is so smooth.
Kyoko-senpai?
Stop that, you idiot.
It's like cleaning a clam!
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, isn't that cute?
You got my joke?
Hot springs are so nice.
Hot springs, hot springs.
I'm in hot water-springs.
Is that one of Sugiura-senpai's jokes?
Yeah.
No Angkor worries!
You'll have to pay a fine Irvine!
I'm surprised you remember those.
Whiny, whiny, Mesopo-whiny-a!
Why don't you laugh at my jokes?
I don't know!
Don't fight, you...
Huh?
How many balls did your hair eat?
What?
I ate too much.
Yui-senpai, are you
going to sleep already?
No, I'm just resting.
Akari-chan really is asleep.
Yeah, she always goes to bed at nine.
At nine?
Oh, no! I forgot!
Mirakurun 2
Mirakurun's movie is on TV today.
You already have the
blu-rays and DVDs.
I bet you're recording it, too.
You don't understand.
Watching it air on TV is so much fun.
Really?
Thanks for the food!
Miso
Cabbage
Hooray, today's lunch is miso cabbage.
Kurumi-chan, I bought some strawberry
milk and yakisoba bread.
Good work, Raika-chan.
Since I'm a growing girl, just
lunch isn't enough for me.
Your lunch looks delicious.
I'll give you some miso as a reward.
Hooray, I love miso!
That scream...
Could it be Team Giga Giga?
Could it be Ganbo-sama?
Kurumi-chan, something has come up...
Same here!
My skirt is getting shorter and shorter!
The gap between my socks
and my skirt is so wide,
I'll never be able to get married!
Giga giga giga!
I will fill this world
with embarrassment!
I'll make you wear clothes
as embarrassing as mine!
Stop!
Witch Girl Mirakurun has arrived!
Kids who don't play nice will get hurt!
I knew you would come.
Leave this to me.
Mirakurun, I'll wrap you up
in a tornado of embarrassment!
This is what I look like
under my sunglasses!
No! Your eyes are too cute!
How embarrassing!
Well? Well?
You've done it now!
Finishing move, Mirakurun Hammer!
Ganbo-sama!
You'll pay for this, Mirakurun!
My skirt's length is back to normal!
Thank you, Mirakurun!
Serving out justice is a piece of cake.
I'm happy...
I'm so happy...
You're crying?
Hey, let's get into the hot spring again.
I'm too tired.
Hey! Don't sleep!
Shut up.
Go by yourself.
Fine.
I will.
Chinatsu-chan.
It's not because I thought you might
be lonely by yourself or anything.
I'll wrap you up in a tornado
of embarrassment!
Mirakurun Hammer!
My skull caved in.
Behave yourself!
What are you doing?
Yui, I thought you were tired.
Not really. Does it matter?
I bet you were lonely
'cause Akari's asleep.
Shut up, you idiot.
May this fun last forever.
Where did everyone go?
Your protagonist Akaza
Akari has returned.
I'm so happy to see all of you again!
I'll stand out even more this
time, so don't look away.
All together, now.
Akarin!