Yuru Yuri Episode 6 "'Breaking
News' Yuru Yuri Sold Out"
Mirakurun!
Hey!
"Witch Girl Mirakurun" is starting!
What?
Shut up!
Akarin
Whoa! Mirakurun
cast a spell on me!
Go buy some yakisoba bread!
Okay!
There!
Raika-chan, go!
Okay!
Isn't dodgeball fun, Raika-chan?
K-Kurumi-chan...
You're great at sports.
I'm not nearly as good as you...
It's okay! Let's give it everything we've got!
Here's the ball...
This time, I'm gonna throw it hard!
There!
Huh?
The ball disappeared...
That's weird.
We don't have extras...
Sensei, the balls disappeared.
We can't play dodgeball now.
What's going on?
I can't believe all
the balls are gone...
This must be the work
of Team Giga Giga!
Feast your eyes, Rivalrun!
This is...
This is the rebellion of
the balls who have been
kicked, thrown, and
oppressed by humans!
What is the meaning of this, Ganbo-sama?
Without balls, they cannot
play ball sports.
Humans, who live to play
ball sports, will panic.
I see.
Team Giga Giga will take advantage
of the confusion and take over the world!
Today will be a great victory
for Team Giga Giga!
So it is Team Giga Giga!
They won't get away with this!
Shine, miraculous—
It's a pain to animate
my transformation,
so we cut it!
Witch of love and justice,
Mirakurun, has arrived!
I'll beat the crap out of bad
kids who do naughty things!
What are you doing here?
How did you find our secret base?
I just saw it while walking down the street!
I can't believe your luck!
But you're too late.
The world's balls have already
become your enemies!
Go, balls!
Defeat Mirakurun!
Balls, stop!
Feel the balls' hatred
for humans, Mirakurun!
Ganbo-sama, don't you
think this is a bit much?
You think so?
Enough, stop!
We did it!
We've finally defeated Mirakurun...
This is just a doll!
It's my Mirakurun Magic Decoy.
You can't have unlimited powers!
Mirakurun Super Hammer!
How terrible...
All the balls are hurt...
You're the one who hurt them!
I can hear the voices of the balls.
You just wanted to rest
a while, didn't you?
But then Team Giga Giga took advantage of you...
Are you even listening?!
You're the one who did this!
But it's okay now!
Don't just chuck 'em!
Mirakurun Five-Day Work Week Flash!
Thank you, Mirakurun!
We'll be sure to let the balls
take breaks from now on!
She looks so proud of herself.
Don't think you can let your guard down...
Huh?
Humans will suffer, as they will be unable...
to play ball sports while the balls are resting.
Someday you will make
the same mistake!
But...
If only you had something to
replace the balls with.
What?
First Witch Girl Mirakurun
Bowling Tournament!!
Our first bowling tournament!
Mirakurun!
Today will be your last!
I will stop you!
Justice never loses!
Here I go!
There!
Yes!
Not bad.
Wait, Rivalrun!
Don't tell me you...
There!
Are they just letting the balls rest
so they can take their anger out on me?
Rivalrun, I'm talking about you!
Um...
What is this?
My doujin circle's latest work — a Mirakurun anime!
[Breaking News] Yuru Yuri Sold Out
It's that time of year again!
The Comic Extreme Market!
It's been a year since
the last summer market.
This is pretty amazing, Akari-chan...
Yeah...
I knew Kyoko-chan's hobby
was making fan works,
but it's the first time
she's taken me here.
It's nothing to be afraid of.
Well, Ayano was nervous at first, too.
Sugiura-senpai has come
here before, too?
Yeah. Chitose also joined us
last year, so it was
just us second years.
It was terrible.
Did something happen?
Okay, so get this.
Right before we left for Tokyo,
Kyoko dragged Ayano along
without even mentioning Comuket.
You're terrible, Kyoko-senpai...
That's what you call the
excitement of summer.
We didn't want to bother Ayano again,
so we decided not to
invite her this time.
Night Before Comuket
Come at me any time, Toshino Kyoko!
I'm Banglaready for you!
I already looked up the Comuket dates,
so you won't surprise me
like you did last time!
So you replaced them
with me and Chinatsu-chan?
No one could replace you, Chinatsu-chan!
I don't really care about that...
Wait, what about me?
I had you two come along
to power up our amusement club!
Power up?
I wanted you two to experience
this battlefield and become my soldiers...
Stop trying to lure them
into helping you with making your doujin stuff!
And don't count on my help, either!
I've had enough of drawing
frame after frame for eternity.
But you're amazing, Kyoko-chan.
You can make anime by yourself.
Well, yeah.
Directing, script, production,
art, and voices!
I did it all myself! Just like this!
Chinatsu-chan, I'm going to kiss you!
How was that?
It sounded just like the real thing!
Why can't you put your talents
to use doing something normal...
Hello, Ramuko-san.
Oh, you came again!
I've got a new volume.
Check it out, check it out!
Whoa! It's a Mirakurun anime!
I wanted to make something like a spin-off
of Dark Mirakurun's
appearance in chapter 18.
Isn't that the story from
your previous doujinshi
in which Mirakurun and
Rivalrun bowl with Ganbo?
Yeah, that's the one.
I'll write you again.
I look forward to it.
Ramuko-san, it's
great to see you again!
Run-Run Kingdom's Yasucchi-san!
How are you?
Great, great!
This feels like some strange new world...
I don't care to know more about it...
I'm already used to it.
I'm used to it, too.
You're amazing, Chitose...
Wait, Chitose?
Ikeda-senpai?
Hey, everyone.
It's Chitose!
What are you doing here?
After Toshino-san brought me last year,
I found myself interested in this stuff.
So I came here myself.
Oh, right...
You fit right in even though it was
your first time attending.
I need to stock up on ideas
for even more wonderful fantasies.
I see...
Just make sure you don't take off your glasses.
Well then, see you later!
I knew this would happen.
Akari, Chinatsu-chan,
I hope you grow up to be just like her!
Day of Comuket
I wonder when Toshino Kyoko
is going to call...
I Love Rum Raisin League — Sold Out!
Sorry
Cosplay time!
I've been waiting for this...
The time when I finally get to see
Chinachu cosplay Mirakurun at
Comuket, the holy land of cosplay!
What're you rambling about, Kyoko-senpai?
And don't call me Chinachu.
You're pretty energetic for it being so hot.
Hey! Why do you two look so bored?
Well, I've cosplayed
Mirakurun so many times
that it's kinda lost its novelty.
I'm used to it now.
I'm wearing the same cosplay
as last summer, too.
What happened to the
amusement club's promise
to cosplay together someday?
We never promised that.
Thanks for waiting, everyone.
It's kind of hard to
walk in this cosplay.
So they are removable...
It's the real Mirakurun!
Look, Mom!
Look, look!
You're right.
She looks just like her.
No, she's the real thing!
Someone's calling you, Mirakurun.
But Yui-senpai...
Mirakurun!
Oh, right!
This is my chance to show
Yui-senpai my good side!
Witch of love and justice Mirakurun...
...mad deprived!
Huh?
I got the line wrong...
Eri-chan!
I think Mirakurun must be tired
from fighting Team Giga Giga.
Come on, let's go!
Yui-senpai!
I messed up!
It's Kyoko-senpai's fault for
teaching me the wrong line!
It's my fault?
Don't worry about it, Chinatsu-chan.
I'm sure you'll get it right next time.
Yui-senpai...
Leave it to me!
Come on, children!
I don't care how many of you there are!
Okay...
Huh?
Mirakurun Goods Sold Out!
No more. I'm exhausted.
Me too...
Kyoko-chan and Yui-chan still seem
like they're up for more, though...
I still haven't seen everyone yet,
so I'm gonna go walk around again.
You two must be tired.
I'll get us something to drink,
so you guys rest.
As members of the amusement club
we have to get used to Comuket.
What's so amusing about this?
I only said yes because
Kyoko-senpai asked if
I wanted to go on a
trip with Yui-senpai.
Akari-chan, my back itches.
Scratch it?
I can't like this.
I guess it can't be helped, then...
I can use this!
That feels good.
Chinatsu-chan, that's not
very Mirakurun-like.
I don't care.
Once Kyoko-senpai and Yui-senpai
come back, I'm getting changed.
I want to take this off soon.
Life is bitter, Mom.
Yes, dear.
That's odd.
I'm sure Comuket was today.
Hello?
Hey, Ayano.
Toshino Kyoko...
What could you possibly
want at this hour?
I'm at the station on my
way back from Comuket,
but I bought too many books.
Could you help me carry them?
What did you just say?
I'm at the station.
I bought too much at Comuket.
Could you help me carry my books?
Ayano? Hey, are you there?
Hey...
There there, Ayano-chan.
Summer vacation's ending.
It went by so fast after Comuket.
Don't come over
just to laze around...
People who haven't been doing their
homework are in a panic right now.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
I finished mine in July.
I'm finished, too.
I see. Good for you.
The end of summer vacation...
It's always over before
you really do anything.
I know what you mean.
Even if you make plans,
you end up being lazy...
For times like these, I've made this!
The Conversation Topic Box!
Conversation Topic Box
Where did that come from?
Let's get started.
Akari! Here, take a card!
Really?
How exciting.
Speak using "zamasu"
Akari, you use "zamasu" when you talk!
That's not a conversation topic!
You're next, Chinatsu-chan.
Huh?
Oh, okay.
Let's see...
"Club Activities"?
Hey, you actually put some
normal topics in here.
Did you want to join
anything besides
the amusement club?
Not particularly.
The track team invited
me to join them, though.
Really?
Yui's the fastest in our class.
Yui-senpai, that's amazing!
It's not that amazing...
She's not talking to you.
We didn't want to join
any other club, either.
Yeah.
What happened to reviving the tea club?
Kyoko was in the brass
band our first year.
I didn't know that!
I quit after a month.
She got an F in music.
I just don't get it!
It
All right! I'm next!
There!
Good Luck
Why are you so smug?
The one we've been waiting for is here!
They are?
Lady Luck!
Who?
Yes!
What're you so happy about?
It's always hard to deal with that fortune.
Not nearly as hard as you.
You're next, Yui.
Okay, fine...
Are you hungry?
What is this?
I want pancakes.
Pancake Mix
Huh?
I'll get something good this time...
There!
Act Like A Dog
She barked.
Akari-chan, you're so good.
I wasn't barking!
Talk Sexy
"Talk sexy"...
Wait, sexy?
Chinatsu-chan has to be sexy!
I'm not doing this!
Then I'll do it with you!
What sort of game is this?
You're terrible...
Why would you force me
to say something
so embarrassing?
How sexy...
I wanted you
to say "Kyoko-senpai, you
can squeeze my boobs,"
or something.
But I'll cut you some slack.
Do you have any shame?
You don't have any
decent topics in here.
You guys are just drawing
all the weird ones.
This one seems reasonable.
It's "blood type".
Blood type?
Amazingly, we're all different types.
Oh no!
If something happens,
we won't be able to
give each other blood!
But type O's can give to anyone.
It's because Yui-senpai's heart
is wider than the ocean.
Pretty sure that's not the reason...
Oh, but AB's are the opposite.
They can receive from anyone.
Really?
You mean there's a
chance Yui-senpai's
blood could flow through me?
Don't worry, Chinatsu-chan.
If anything happens, you can have my—
No, thank you.
Transfusions now only occur between
people of the same blood type.
I don't like talking about blood types!
Look closely. This is your handwriting.
Type B's get such a bad rap!
People shouldn't
assume I'm self centered
just because I'm a B!
It's never nice to assume,
but they'd be right, in this case.
Don't flatter me!
I'm not.
I love you!
I don't lo—
...What?
I'm stuffed.
We talked a lot today.
Yeah. There were some weird
topics, but it was pretty fun.
Wasn't it?
Let's do this again soon.
This wasn't enough?
Oh, and Akari.
What is it, Kyoko-chan?
Why are you talking in
that strange accent?
Aren't you the one who wrote this?
Well, we're going home.
We had fun today.
See you tomorrow!
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Tomorrow!
Well, then...
Why aren't you leaving?
Homework...
What?
I was so busy with Comuket,
I still haven't finished.
Help me!
Let me copy your—
Go home.
It's your protagonist with a
bloody nose, Ikeda Chitose.
Thanks to all my new books,
my fantasizing powers have leveled up,
so get ready, Ayano-chan!
The next episode is all about sisters—
Oh, no. My fantasies
have already started...