Yuru Yuri 2 Episode 3 "Chocolate and
Tears and Girls and Girls and Isobe Fries"
Akarin!
Hey!
Another UFO?
Bun bazooka!
I did it!
Let's take it from the top!
Yuru Yuri's start...
I'm so tired!
I bet you were up late last night.
Once I started reading
The Glass Mask, I couldn't stop.
You're hopeless.
Oh, right.
I'm gonna sleep through first period,
so let me copy your notes later!
No.
What?
Why not?
Himawari, you're so mean!
How does that make me mean?
Because it is mean.
Isn't it normal for people
to take their own notes?
Fine, you booby monster!
You think name calling will
make me show you my notes?
Monster, monster, booby monster, go!
This is actually kinda fun!
You don't say.
"Chocolate and Tears and Girls
and Girls and Isobe Fries"
Isobe fried fish cakes!
Sakurako, shut up.
But I like them.
Isobe fries are so good.
Hey, Himawari, my lunch.
Yes, yes. I'll go get it.
These are mine!
Hey...
It's seaweed rice today.
Oh my God!
What's wrong?
Forgot chopsticks...
That's barely a sentence...
I have some disposable ones.
Here.
Akari-chan, thank you!
You're so much better than Himawari!
How mean to only bring chopsticks for yourself!
Did I hear you say you don't
want your Isobe fries, Sakurako?
Then allow me...
I'm sorry!
What do you want to do today?
What did we do yesterday?
We played five-character shiritori.
What should we do?
Let's all speak English!
That sounds fun!
Starting now, only English!
Start!
D-Delicious!
Oh, delicious!
Delicious, delicious!
Yes, delicious!
Isobe fries delicious!
All you're saying is "delicious."
Can you do any better?
Of course I can!
This is rice.
I know that!
I do just fine in class...
But it's hard to actually speak it.
I thought I was gonna choke!
What should we do next?
Let's say cheesy things.
Cheesy?
Chinatsu-chan, your eyes are beautiful.
They're like stars twinkling
in the night sky.
Oh, that sort of thing.
Penne arrabiata.
That's not really the same.
What sort of game is this?
Oh, Himawari!
Your Isobe fries are truly
fine and delicious looking...
Gimme!
I can't really think of any new games.
We've already done everything.
Triumphant Look
Then it's time for this!
What's that?
I made it during class.
Roll it.
Embarrassing Story
An embarrassing story?
Okay, you gotta tell us one.
I see.
Once, when I slept over
at Yui-senpai's house...
You wish you stood out more?
It's okay, Kyoko-chan.
If you work hard, you'll
be like me in no time.
...is what Akari-chan said in her sleep.
That's an embarrassing story about me!
You're next, Akari-chan.
Pun!
A pun...
Y-You can tune a piano...
...but you can't tuna fish!
This is so embarrassing!
Now you have another
embarrassing story you can tell!
That's not a good thing!
Himawari, you're next.
Win!
...Win?
What does that mean?
Himawari won, huh?
Here you go.
Chocolate?
How unexpectedly normal, coming from you.
To be honest, I dunno how
old that chocolate is.
Hey! Why would you give this to someone?
If I had eaten this and gotten sick...
Is that what it means to win?
I'm next.
A story about seasons?
Isn't it almost Valentine's Day?
A question?
That's not a story.
Who's planning to give
someone chocolate?
Chinatsu-chan, you're giving
Yui-chan chocolate, aren't you?
Is it that obvious?
How embarrassing!
What about you, Akari-chan?
I'm going to buy lots and
give some to everyone.
What about you, Himawari-chan?
Huh? I don't have any plans.
What about you, Sakurako-chan?
I buy some every year,
but I always end up eating it myself.
How very like you.
Are you calling me a fatty?
Thanks for the food.
Me too.
That was quick!
I still haven't finished
my Isobe fries!
You're just slow.
Fifth period is P.E.
Then let's get to the gym a
little early and play.
Hey, wait.
Don't you know what will happen
if you leave without me?
What?
Chop! Chop! Chopstick!
Just hurry up and eat.
A scarf?
Yeah! I thought you might
know how to knit one.
Well, I do...
Really?
I want to give Yui-senpai a scarf
and chocolate for Valentine's Day!
Could you teach me how to make one?
Sure.
Hooray! Are you free this weekend?
Yes.
Himawari!
I got an extra assignment
because I forgot my homework.
It's due next Monday.
Could you help me with it this weekend?
Unfortunately, I just agreed
to help Yoshikawa-san this weekend.
What? Really?
Sorry, can I borrow
Himawari-chan for a bit?
I don't need Himawari.
You can take her.
That's no way to talk about someone.
Could you help me shop for yarn
on the way home from school today?
Yes, of course.
Sakurako-chan, you're all by yourself?
Where's Himawari-chan?
She went shopping for
yarn with Chinatsu-chan.
I see.
You must be lonely without Himawari-chan.
No, I'm not lonely.
Really?
I was just gonna have her help
me with my assignment.
What am I gonna do?
Do you want me to help you?
Really?
Yeah, sure.
Okay, then let's go to my house!
Himawari, I'm thirsty...
Oh, sorry. It's a habit.
Don't worry about it.
I don't get this!
Boobs!
Oh, sorry! It's a habit!
Huh? It's fine.
Do you need me to explain anything?
Yeah, this part...
Oh, you do this like this...
Like this...
And you get this.
Sakurako, you always make
this kind of mistake here.
First, you need to stop doing that.
Also, I've made a list of
the words you always get wrong.
You should review these.
Of course. Himawari's
good at teaching me...
Like that. Do you get it?
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
Listen to me...
The Next Day
Himawari! You're my personal tutor!
Where did that come from?
You should be happy I chose you.
So, next Saturday...
Unfortunately, I have plans
with Yoshikawa-san next Saturday as well.
Again?
It takes quite a while to make a scarf.
I'll be meeting with Yoshikawa-san
after school for some time.
After school, too?
Now, now, Sakurako-chan.
Himawari-chan will come
back in a few days.
Cheer up...
I'm cheerful!
Really? Well, that's good...
So, when I try to add more yarn,
it gets all messed up if I just tie it normally.
You should add yarn at
the start of a new layer.
Is that right?
I'll have to untie it and do it again.
I hope I'll finish in time...
You will.
You're learning quickly, Yoshikawa-san.
Really?
Okay, I can do this!
Sakurako-chan, isn't this
boiled pumpkin good?
I hate pumpkin.
Being a picky eater stunts your growth.
Shut up!
You don't like peppers, Himawari!
Sakurako-chan, I don't like celery.
It's okay.
I'm going to the bathroom.
What's wrong with her?
Valentine's Sale
It's a Valentine's sale!
Mind if we stop in?
Sure.
Welcome.
Hey.
What?
Am I gonna get something from you this year, too?
I guess.
Then I want this.
That's not how this holiday works.
Really?
Hey.
What?
If you're giving me
something, I want this.
I told you, it's not the same
if you make a request...
That doesn't even have anything
to do with Valentine's Day.
This one... Or maybe this one...
Actually, give me this one!
You're really fired up.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm going to eat it myself.
Really?
Yes!
Um...
This one's nice.
Maybe I'll get this.
Excuse me, could I have this one?
Certainly.
Sold Out
What? That was the last one?
Then I guess I'll get
this one or this one...
This one, please!
What?
This one for me!
Certainly.
Sold Out
You're kidding!
Let's see...
Um, this is...
Sheesh!
Shoot! How come Himawari's having all the fun?
I can have fun, too!
Okay, go!
If you only use your special attacks,
you'll have trouble when you get to the boss.
Shut up!
I'll make you dinner, so
stop eating so many snacks.
Shut up, shut up!
Ow!
No fun, no fun, no fun!
Why do I feel so sick?
Chinatsu-chan... I mean, Himawari!
It's fine if you wanna teach
Chinatsu-chan to knit a scarf,
but it's still your responsibility
to help me with my homework!
Argh!
I hate scarves!
Class 2-5
Why don't you just give it to her?
What?
What are you talking about?
Chitose, you've got the wrong idea!
Really?
That's right!
Here's your chocolate.
Thanks. I have some for you, too!
It's just a bar of chocolate.
Huh? Is that chocolate?
Is that for me?
What?
Hey, don't be so greedy.
Oh, yes!
Ayano-chan accidentally bought too much,
so she has some left over.
Right?
Huh?
If you've got extras, I'll take them!
Welcome, welcome!
I suppose I have no choice!
If you want it that badly, you
can have it, Toshino Kyoko!
Thanks.
Hey Yui, give me half of the
chocolate I just gave you.
I thought you might say that.
I don't want it!
Just take it.
See you later.
Aren't you glad you gave
it to her, Ayano-chan?
I told you, that's not it!
Anyway, here.
Huh?
This is to thank you for
everything you do for me.
Ayano-chan, you're so nice...
But make sure you eat
it at home by yourself!
Huh? Why?
Yui-senpai!
Chinatsu-chan.
I made you some Valentine's
Day chocolates and this scarf!
Please accept them!
Is this a scarf?
What are you talking about?
Of course it's a scarf.
Did you make this chocolate, too?
I did!
Open it!
Okay...
Chinatsu-chan, where's my chocolate?
I thought you might say that,
so I brought you my test chocolates.
Here.
Hooray!
They're pretty good!
What do you mean, "pretty good"?
Well, I wasn't trying very
hard when I made those...
The chocolate is okay...
I put a lot of effort into making
your chocolate, Yui-senpai.
How does this happen
when she tries harder?
Himawari-chan!
Yoshikawa-san.
I gave Yui-senpai the scarf!
She was really happy!
Really? That's great.
Thank you so much!
It was nothing.
I've had enough.
Sakurako?
I've had enough!
Why? Why?
Why are you spending all of your
time with Chinatsu-chan?
Have you forgotten it's your
job to check my homework?
Why are you angry?
Why are you crying?
I don't know!
I don't know why, but I feel so sick!
Lately, when I see you and
Chinatsu-chan together,
I want to hit you!
Hit me?
I don't know what you're...
Could she be...
Are you jealous?
I'm not talking about food!
You can have this.
Huh?
I made this scarf while
teaching Yoshikawa-san.
Now that I'm done with
it, you can have it.
The chocolate's a bonus.
Can we start walking home and
doing homework together again?
I suppose I have no choice.
That's my servant! I'll work you hard!
Who are you calling your servant?
Hey, Himawari.
What?
Check my homework today.
Already?
It's been building up since you were gone.
Have you ever thought
about doing it yourself?
I tried, but I can't do it.
It's way faster when you
show me how to do it.
Faster?
Well, fine.
Hooray!
You're opening that here?
I'm hungry.
Sheesh.
Oh, I didn't give you any chocolate...
Should I give you
something on White Day?
You don't need to give me anything.
Really? Lucky me!
Your mouth is covered in chocolate.
Here you go.
That's right. You've already given me something.
Um...
This scarf makes my neck itch.
Ayano-chan, thanks for the chocolate.
Nee-san, the bath's ready.
Chizuru!
Chizuru.
The demon is back...
Well, whatever...
I gave out lots of chocolate,
but I didn't receive any.
Your lunchtime protagonist is the
Isobe-fried Omuro Sakurako!
What should I give
Himawari on White Day?
You're supposed to give people
something you'd like to receive, right?
I know!
I'll give her lots of fish cakes!