Yuru Yuri Episode 7 "Sisters'
Circumstances That This Those Which"
Akarin!
Hey!
Yuru Yuri...
Cameraman, what're you looking at?
What?
There's nothing there...
No, wait—!
Episode 7
Sisterly Relations and Such
Sakurako's Younger Sister
Hanako (8)
Sakurako's Older Sister
Nadeshiko (18)
Sakurako.
It's your turn to cook dinner.
We'll be studying in here,
so take as much time as you can shopping.
By which you mean I'm bothering you.
Right?
We can't focus when you're around.
You too, Hanako?
Don't you have homework, Sakurako?
What?
You don't even know?
Dinner, huh?
I want Camembert pizza.
What? I wish you'd actually cook something.
She's right.
We must eat a balanced diet.
What about curry?
Curry would be okay...
But not instant curry!
Fine.
Then it's decided. Hurry up and go.
But you know, being called a pest
doesn't make me want to do you any favors.
If you want me to go shopping,
can't you ask nicely?
It's your turn to cook...
It's okay, Hanako.
If you insist...
What?
Please go somewhere else.
That doesn't make me feel any better!
Thanks for the food.
I'm glad you liked it.
I love your cooking.
Really? I enjoy cooking for you, too.
Are you busy today?
No, not really.
I see...
Want to go out together?
Can we?
Where would you like to go?
Um, uh...
I'd be happy to go anywhere with you!
Yeah? Well, we can go anywhere you want.
Oh, then let's go buy bras for you.
Why?
They've grown again, haven't they?
Huh?
Yesterday I saw you struggling to get dressed.
That was just...
Sakurako onee-chan told
me to check every night.
We're having curry
for dinner. Make it.
What?
I don't think I'll be back until night.
Be careful crossing the street.
Thanks. I'll see you later.
My sister is going to
Sugiura-san's place today.
Good for you.
Forget about Toshino What's-Her-Face
and enjoy your date...
Don't look at Toshino-san.
Today, look only at me, Ayano-chan.
Chitose...
Nee-san's bed...
She takes such beautiful notes...
But there's blood from her
nose here and there...
Ayano.
What do you want, Toshino Kyoko?
All I wish for is
Ayano-chan's happiness...
That's all...
Poor Chitose!
If not for that girl, she and Sugiura-san
would be even happier...
Yes. If Toshino Whatever
would just go away...
Chitose, I'm sorry I
never noticed before.
Even though you're always
so considerate of me...
It's okay, Ayano-chan.
I supported you and Toshino-san,
but was really just ignoring my true feelings.
Chitose...
Let's stay together forever!
Okay.
Over here, Chitose!
Wait for me, Ayano-chan!
We skipped school for this.
You're surprisingly naughty, Ayano-chan.
What?
I think it's cute.
Surprise attacks aren't fair.
Did I surprise you?
Sheesh, you want to do it here?
Nee-san, be happy...
She was so excited when
we started middle school...
I became friends with a wonderful girl.
Her name's Sugiura Ayano-chan.
I think she's a bit shy.
She was sitting by herself at her desk,
but seemed really happy
when I talked to her.
She has such a cute smile!
She seemed really happy then.
I guess I'll clean while she's
out visiting Sugiura-san.
It's no use!
I can't stop thinking about
my sister and Sugiura-san!
I'm supposed to be cleaning,
but I've drooled on everything!
What should I do?
I know!
I'll just think about Toshino Whoever!
That should do it.
Now I'm annoyed,
but it's better than
filling the room with drool!
Chizuru-chu-chu!
I'm so angry!
I have to finish quickly
so I can take these down!
Prepare yourself!
We finally finished.
Today's homework was difficult.
I'm glad we did this.
Let's do our homework
together again some time.
What are you talking about, Ayano-chan?
Next time you should invite
Toshino-san instead of me.
What?
I don't get this.
Sheesh, Toshino Kyoko...
You're supposed to substitute
this in here and...
Sorry.
It's okay.
Ayano, can I substitute in my love?
Toshino Kyoko, can you solve my cubic curve?
It never seems to go straight...
It's okay.
It'll be over before you can
finish counting the prime numbers.
Right?
What the...?
I'm home.
Thanks for watching the house, Chizuru...
What's this?
She cleaned the room...
Thanks, Chizuru.
You're my one and only sister.
But why is the room covered
in photos of Toshino-san?
Chizuru-chu-chu!
This is the best!
You leveled up?
Yeah.
Gonna level some more?
The next boss is strong,
so probably another five levels or so.
I don't really like adventuring.
They call people like onee-chan reliable.
I hope I can be like
her someday, but...
Isn't this an adventure game?
No Boobs Allowed
It went up...
That can't be right.
One more time...
I've really gained weight...
Why?
I haven't been binging on food...
If anything, I've been trying
to eat a balanced diet...
Thanks for the food.
You're finished already?
I'm not really hungry.
I'll have some more if I get hungry.
Okay...
You gained weight?
Yes...
You're a fatty.
So? How much did you gain?
Shut up!
Just hold my feet.
What?
I'll get you a steak for lunch.
I can't do any more...
What? You only did ten.
You need to do it like this!
I know, but...
Your body's too heavy?
You gotta do that thing they do in manga.
When people draw out their true power...
You're quite skilled to
make me take off my buns.
Wouldn't she just disappear?
Just take off your boobs like that.
I'm sorry.
I don't get where this is going.
I borrowed this from my sister.
Thank you.
How am I supposed to use this?
Well, my sister...
She uses it like that.
So she's not really using it...
Maybe like this...
Or this...
Or perhaps this?
I don't know, Sakurako...
You're just lying around!
Enough already!
Just go run around outside!
But it's so hot outside...
If you sweat a bunch,
you might lose weight.
What?
So... hot...
Why do I have to do this, too?
I'm working up a good sweat.
Sheesh! I'm already skinny,
so now I'm gonna
be even skinnier!
I don't care if you're fat!
Fat
Go be a fatty by yourself!
Fatty
I'm turning on the AC!
I wonder what part of me is gaining weight.
Your boobs.
Aside from my chest.
Nothing's really changed.
Liar! I gained weight.
It must be somewhere.
I don't know.
Sakurako...
Please answer me seriously!
You're bowing?
Himawari, you're that
worried about this?
Fine, then...
What?
If you say, "Help me,
oh beautiful Sakurako-sama,"
then I might answer.
Dinner's ready.
Okay.
You're not going to eat?
I'm on a diet.
Anyway, try some of
the boiled pumpkin.
I'm sure it's delicious.
Okay...
I'm so hungry, I can't sleep.
Maybe I'll snack on some cookies...
No, I mustn't!
I'll have skipped dinner for nothing!
I have to refrain
so I lose that extra weight.
Three Days Later
What?
She's still dieting?
My sister hasn't been eating.
She'll get sick.
I'm fine.
I've been drinking vegetable juice.
Sakurako onee-chan?
What?
How can you keep going on about this diet?
Kaede's worried sick about you!
Onee-chan...
I'm sorry...
I told you the other day
you look the same.
I meant that!
It's the truth!
But...
Your hips, legs, and
arms haven't changed!
I agree. Onee-chan, you're skinny.
But I gained some weight...
Maybe your breasts got bigger again.
What?
You've started wearing
bigger bras...
I'll try measuring myself.
They have gotten bigger.
My waist hasn't changed.
That's great.
But I feel conflicted now...
I don't think you
need to worry.
You have a nice, slim body.
You think so? Thank you.
Akanen.
Hey. Gachi Yuri's starting.
Yoshikawa Tomoko (19)
Chinatsu's Older Sister
The sun feels great.
Yeah, it's so warm.
Are you having fun at school, Chinatsu?
Yes! I love one
of my upperclassmen.
Wow!
She must be a lovely person.
Yeah!
By the way, Chinatsu...
Aren't you friends with
a girl named Akaza-san?
Akari-chan?
Yes. What's she like?
A good girl, I guess.
I see.
If you say so, then she must be a good girl.
I'm sure her sister cherishes her, too.
What?
N-Nothing.
I'm just a little
jealous of her...
Her wonderful sister
sends her off to school,
her wonderful sister
helps her study,
reads with her,
her wonderful sister
listens to music with her,
plays games with her,
her wonderful sister
has afternoon tea with her,
washes her back,
her wonderful sister sleeps with
her in the same bed until morning...
Living with such
a wonderful sister
must make every day
wonderful.
That's what I think.
Isn't Akari-chan's sister your friend?
Onee-chan, do you...
...wish you were her little sister?
Phew.
By the way, what is
Akari-chan's sister like?
She's such a wonderful person...
She's always smiling, she's very nice,
and she always brightens the room.
I see...
She sounds like Akari-chan.
I'm so proud to call her my friend.
There.
See you later, onee-chan.
I'm off to the library.
See you later.
Akaza Akane (19)
Akari's Older Sister
Well then...
I finished cleaning and did the laundry.
Dad and Mom are out on a date.
Since it's Sunday,
I need to have some fun.
Onee-chan's Room
What should I read?
I haven't read this book yet.
Up we go.
That should do it.
Akari's Room
I almost forgot.
There. I've got to have this.
I Love You, Little Sister!
"I love you, onee-chan."
There's no substitute for her actual uniform.
It smells nice.
Akari...
I'm home!
I forgot something.
Oh my. You're such a silly girl, Akari.
Cake!
Onee-chan, no fair!
There's some for you.
Really? I love you, onee-chan.
I'm the protagonist
watching you
from morning until
night, Akaza Akane.
Akari's friends play a big
role in the next episode.
Akari's so cute hiding
in their shadows!
I'll always be watching you.