Akarin!
Hey! Yuru Yuri's starting!
Protagonist
This is the episode you've
been waiting for...
My one man show!
After 23 episodes, the staff
has finally realized
that I'm the protagonist!
That's great, Akari.
Yeah, than—
Kyoko, the new students
start tomorrow.
Help clean!
We might even get new club members!
Let's welcome them
with a clean room!
Hooray! We'll finally be upperclassmen!
I just get the feeling
this is a waste...
Senpai, should I clean this closet?
We've never cleaned
it before, have we?
I think there's tea
ceremony equipment in it.
It's like we're using
the Tea Club's room.
Chinatsu-chan, didn't you
come to join the Tea Club?
All right. I guess we should
clean it more often.
Huh? What's that?
What?
Kyoko-chan!
What's this?
That's...
It's got to be...
A time machine!
A real one?!
It must be the theater
club's prop or something.
Hey, wait!
I'll go check everyone's futures!
No, I wanna make
sure Yui-senpai and I
get happily married!
Calm down, you two!
Startup
Kyoko-chan, Chinatsu-chan, don't fight.
Hey, listen...
There's only one person
at school who'd
make this sorta thing, right?
Explosions are necessary
for invention!
Liftoff
A-Akari!
Akari-chan!
Akari!
Huh?
What?
No! Someone help me!
Akarin~
Akari!
Akari-chan!
Not even a dotted outline!
She's really disappeared!
Yuru Yuri
The Akari Who Leapt Through Time
Niraka~
Akarin~
What's this? A dream?
Maybe they left
while I was unconscious...
Mirakurun
That's weird. What's going on?
Even my stuff was missing.
I'm hungry...
See you tomorrow.
Akari, don't oversleep!
We'll come get you.
Okay. I can't wait to
be a middle schooler!
What?!
See you later.
Okay! I'll be waiting.
Does this mean I really
traveled through time?
No!
Startup
Huh? No!
Growl
I'm hungry...
I know! Maybe Kyoko-chan...
There we go!
Lightly salted!
I love lightly salted chips!
Potato Chips
Lightly Salted
I've calmed down a bit.
But what am I gonna do now?
How will I fix
the time machine?
There's only one person
at school who'd
make this sorta thing, right?
That's it! Nishigaki-sensei!
I'll have her fix it tomorrow!
This is the latest volume of
"Witch Girl Mirakurun"!
In the future, I think I
read volume 11 yesterday...
I've really traveled
one year into the past...
One year ago...
Kyoko-chan, Yui-chan,
thanks for waiting!
Oh, no! I'm so embarrassed!
Go for an even stronger gag next time!
I take the express
to everyone's heart!
Nice to meet you! I'm Akaza Akari!
My terrible middle
school debut...
After that, Chinatsu-chan
joined the club,
and I've gotten less and
less screen time.
Now, I have no presence...
I know!
If I stop myself from
making those mistakes,
I'll have more
screen time and presence!
I'll start by making
sure my past self
wears her uniform tomorrow!
I'll wake up early and fix my mistakes!
I overslept!
Please let me be on time!
Please!
Plea—
Kyoko-chan, Yui-chan,
thanks for waiting!
Go for an even stronger gag next time!
If we don't hurry, we'll be late.
Okay.
It's okay!
I still have a chance to fix my mistakes!
Oh, Akari.
Onee-chan!
I forgot something...
Oh?
Huh? Akari... What?
That must've been hard.
I'm glad you believe such
an unbelievable story.
I'd believe anything you told me.
Onee-chan...
So what will you do next?
I need to stop myself
from giving a weird
introduction at school.
Also, I need to fix the time machine...
Thanks for the food.
Onee-chan?
You're one year older...
You've grown...
Really?
About 2 millimeters.
What?
Entrance Ceremony
This concludes the principal's speech.
I'll write a message...
Warning: You're about to make
a mistake that will change your life.
You must introduce yourself normally!
There!
What? That was quick...
The principal wouldn't shut up.
He took no longer than usual.
Sakurako-chan, Himawari-chan...
Chinatsu-chan...
Oh my. Someone wrote on this desk.
That's unfortunate.
Hey, Himawari-chan!
What're you doing to that girl's desk?
Wouldn't it be sad to start your first
day at a new school
with a vandalized desk?
Huh?
Someone wrote on your desk...
Thanks.
No way!
I wanna join the tennis club and
play at Wimbledon someday!
What should I do?
I'll have to do something drastic!
Introduce yourself properly!
I keep missing...
There.
Her hair ate it!
I'd like to join the student council
to make this school an even
better place for everyone.
No, no.
Acting like a goody-two-shoes?
What an idiot.
What did you say?
You wanna fight?
There!
Next, Akaza-san.
Yes.
How unusual for you to
introduce yourself properly.
I got a warning note!
A warning from God?
I-I still...
I still have a chance!
We just hang out and
do whatever we want!
Soon, Chinatsu-chan will
get here with her club form...
If I tell her the Tea
Club's been disbanded,
she should leave...
Sorry, Chinatsu-chan.
Once we're friends,
I'm sure I'll invite you
to join the Amusement Club...
She's here!
Uh, um!
What?
Su...
Oh? I haven't seen you before.
You must be a new student.
What are you doing here?
Uh, um... Well...
You must be lost.
There's no helping it.
The gates are this way.
Hey!
She came that way...
Why isn't anything
working out?
In any case, I need to
have Nishigaki-sensei
fix the time machine...
I'll find another way...
Matsumoto-senpai!
Oh, Matsumoto.
You want to speak with me?
You really came from the
future in this thing?
I'm not lying!
Didn't you make this?
It's not mine.
What?
If I can't fix this,
I'm stuck here...
Okay, okay.
It might take some time,
but I'll take a look.
Really? Thank you, Sensei!
I messed up my introduction,
but I got to play with Kyoko-chan
and Yui-chan at school again,
so I had lots of fun.
That's great.
It's nine. I'd better go to bed.
Goodnight, Onee-chan.
Goodnight, Akari.
Welcome home, Akari.
Thanks for the food.
Looks like you messed up.
Yeah...
What will you do now?
In a week, I'll have one last chance...
It'll take some time
to fix the time machine, so...
I see...
Sorry, but would it be okay
if I stayed in your room for a while?
What?
O-Of course! That would be fine!
Look, see?
I just bought new sheets,
and I even have some cute pajamas!
Getting to sleep with my beloved Akari
makes me two times...
No, one hundred times happier!
O-Onee-chan?
Oh yeah, I wonder how many years
it's been since I was last in here.
Akari!
The bath! The bath is ready!
Huh? Hooray!
I'm so glad since I didn't
get to take one yesterday.
Go warm yourself up.
Okay.
I'm turning off the light.
Akari...
You seem desperate to do so,
but is it really so important
to fix your past mistakes?
Huh? Yeah...
Everyone says I have no presence...
Really? I don't think that's true.
But I wanna do something about it.
I think I came to the past
because God is giving me a chance.
I see.
But are you sure?
If you change the past,
a year's worth of your
memories could change.
What?
You might like your new memories,
but your old memories will disappear.
But...
But my next chance is my last one!
I want to change myself!
I love you no matter who you are.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Onee-chan...
I remember everyone's
Smiling faces and close my eyes
Sleeping in a warm and fuzzy bed
I don't know why, but I cried
Our fun conversations
Doing nothing special
Today passes us by
But I want to convey
these important feelings
I want to tell you
I love all of you
I want to keep laughing
with everyone forever
So let's meet up again tomorrow
Until then, just for now, goodnight
I love all of you
I'll see you all tomorrow
Until then, just for now, goodnight
We'll always be together...
One Week Later
I'm sorry. I tried taking it apart,
but I still don't understand it.
You're kidding!
You weren't able to fix it?
I didn't understand it, but I fixed it.
What?
It was out of batteries.
This is my last chance...
Allow me to announce my strategy
for having more presence
than anyone else!
Toshino Kyoko!
M...
My...
My presence!
If Sugiura-senpai hadn't interrupted,
it would've worked.
I need to keep them
away from the room...
Toshino Kyoko!
You won't get away today!
Now, now, Ayano-chan.
They're here!
This is my last chance!
My last chance!
Your old memories will disappear...
Disappear... disappear...
Disapp...
Toshino Kyoko!
I can't do it. I can't change
my memories with my friends...
I can't!
You ended up not changing the past.
Are you okay with that?
Yeah!
I'll win back my presence
in the future!
We won't tell anyone
you visited the past,
so the future won't change.
Do your best.
Thank you, Nishigaki-sensei.
Thank you, Matsumoto-senpai.
Akari...
Onee-chan...
I was so happy to have two of you,
but my future self must
be dying without you.
And I was so happy to
share a bed with you...
I couldn't sleep.
I need sleep...
Onee-chan?
See you in the future!
In the future!
Akarin!
Akarin~
I can finally return
to the future.
I wonder how everyone's doing...
I'm back, everyone.
Akari.
You're back.
Akari-chan, what'd
you bring us?
Were you even
worried about me?!
You have no presence,
so we forgot.
You're kidding me!
That'd be my luck...
Akarin~
Niraka~
I'm back, everyone.
Disappeared suddenly on 4/4!
Features: No Specific Features
Hair in Buns
Please Contact
Toshino Kyoko
Missing! Akaza Akari (13)
What's this?
A-Akari...
Huh?
Akari!
Where have you been?
You've been gone a week!
Where were you?!
We were so worried about you!
I'm so glad you're back.
Sorry for making you worry.
I went to the past for a bit...
I should've set it
for a week earlier.
We told them you'd be
back soon and not to worry.
You were all so
worried about me...
I'm so happy.
This thing really
was a time machine?
Yeah. It stopped working
after I arrived in the past,
but Nishigaki-sensei fixed it.
Huh? Nishigaki-chan did?
Boom
(c) Toshino Kyoko
Fin
The end, the end.
I felt inspired after
watching a movie yesterday,
so I drew this.
What'd you think?
No.
Kyoko-chan, we don't even get to
end this episode as being my dream?!
If this was our last episode,
then next week is the
Yuru Yuri Almost All Stars Finale!
The anime ends for now
with the next episode,
but Yuru Yuri will never end!
I am your eternal
protagonist, Akaza Akari!