Aka...
It's the final episode,
and you cut the title call
and my name?!
Episode 12
Good Bye Protagonist, Until We Meet Again
Wait, it's just a toy?
I gotcha, Yui!
Yeah, yeah. Happy, now?
Well...
I was hoping for
a reaction more like...
Your expectations are too high.
I'm sure Chinatsu-chan would...
Yui-senpai!
And Akari...
I was so surprised!
Those sound normal.
Why am I the only one
stuck in the ceiling?
Hello.
Yui-senpai, the snake is so scary!
What?
You knew it was a toy, didn't you?
It's unfair to just hug Yui!
Hug me, too!
What?
Just once! Just do it one time!
She's hopeless.
I'm not going home until you do!
Chinatsu-chan, hug
her for a little bit.
Come on, Chinatsu-chan!
If you insist...
Come on, just onc—
Seriously?
I'm going to hug you, Kyoko-senpai.
Please grit your teeth.
What's with the stance?
That's not what I—
Jeez, Kyoko-senpai, you really
love playing childish pranks.
So, how did Yui-senpai react?
She was so surprised, she
jumped through the ceiling.
No, I didn't.
Sorry I'm late.
She's crying!
W-Wait, Akari!
It's a toy! Just a toy!
It's just one of Kyoko-senpai's pranks!
So don't cry!
Huh? It's just a toy?
Thank goodness!
I thought Mr. Snake was
in lots of pain because I stepped on it.
I'm glad it wasn't a real snake.
She's so righteous she has a halo!
Akari-chan, you're blinding!
These bring back memories.
I found 'em in my room and
took 'em with me.
I had these, too.
I used to stick them
to myself like this.
Do these have a proper name?
Huh? "Snaps," isn't it?
No, they're called "Popping Eyes."
A new record.
Next time, it'll reach the ceiling.
Kyoko-senpai, this one
won't pop. Is it torn?
Huh? Let me see.
There, there, there, there!
Stop that!
What're you doing?
Is her hair connected to
the fourth dimension?
Ouch...
I finally got it off.
Huh? What?
Akari, here...
My forehead!
But it's kinda cute, Akari-chan.
Yeah, it's kinda cute.
I don't know how
I'm supposed to feel.
Maybe it'll be gone by tomorrow?
Sakurako-chan and Himawari-chan
will laugh at me.
It's okay. No one will notice.
What?
Yui, here I go.
Don't throw it too hard.
I know.
There!
Got it.
Yui-senpai!
I'll catch one, too!
Don't hold back!
Huh? Okay.
There!
Look, it's so slimy and gooey.
I've never touched it before.
Neither have I.
Here.
Chinatsu-chan, Yui,
just try touching it!
What? She ignored me?
Hooray, it's so gooey!
We still have fun playing with these.
Did you bring anything else?
Yeah. Some string, kendama,
tops, chips, and pogs.
What're you coming
to school for, exactly?
I also have a bamboo copter...
H-How dare you surprise me!
You're the most scared
out of everyone.
Nanamori Private Middle School
2012 Cultural Festival
The Student Council and
Amusement Club Present: Snow White
Once upon a time,
there was a very beautiful
princess named Snow White.
She was loved by everyone.
I found some edible flowers.
There!
Gross!
Don't eat the poor flowers...
Kaede, you're such a good girl.
Starting today, you can
be our little sister.
Yeah, we'll trade you for Sakurako.
Tell me, mirror...
Who is the fairest of them all?
Who, me?
I see. I knew it.
I'd thought that might be the case!
There's no need to flatter me!
I'm kidding, mirror. I know, I know.
It's her, isn't it? Her.
I can't hear the mirror's voice at all.
The angry queen instructed
the forest's hunter
to kill off Snow White.
Thanks for helping out, Chizuru.
Leave it to me.
Hunter, no!
Sniffle.
Huh?
However, the kind hunter was
unable to kill Snow White.
Instead, she allowed her to
escape into the forest and hide,
pretending to be dead
It is no use.
I cannot kill Snow White.
No, you were definitely
trying to kill me!
Those weren't guns a hunter uses,
and you sound disappointed!
Wait, Chizurun!
Get away from me!
Alone in the forest, what
will happen to Snow White?
It's my turn to go on,
so Nishigaki-sensei, please
take over the narration.
Got it.
Testing, testing.
The story's turning sour...
Heigh-ho, heigh-ho, we are...
Heigh-ho, heigh-ho, elves!
Seven elves lived in the woods.
Their names were: Tsundere Elf.
Who're you calling a tsundere?
Glasses Elf.
What a literal name.
Retorting Elf.
What? Do I really do it that much?
Evil Elf.
Hey, who wrote this script?
Boob Elf.
Don't get ahead of yourself, dammit!
I didn't write the script!
Stupid Elf.
She said stupid! I wonder
who she's talking about.
The Remarkably Unremarkable Elf.
That's terrible!
Why is my name so long?
Would it be better
if it were shorter?
You're living up to your
name, Retorting Elf.
One day, after the elves
had finished their work,
they returned to their
cottage to find...
Welcome home.
Who're you?!
I'm Snow White.
Huh? Which part's my last name,
and which part's my first?
Dunno.
That's my pudding!
Huh? Oh, sorry.
Here, you can have the last bite!
Say, "ah~"
Th-This... Th-This is
an i-indirect k-kiss...
Come on. Say, "ah!"
I s-suppose I have no choice.
Delicious!
What in the world are you doing?!
What? Why are you mad?
I'm not mad at all!
You just can't take a hint!
Huh?
Don't fight, you two.
Don't worry. They're not fighting.
Sakurako's stupidity gives
Hima-nee a lot of grief, too.
What are we doing...
Are you okay?
"If you don't want
it indirectly,
I'll feed it to you
directly, Ayano!"
"It's sweeter than pudding..."
Just like that...
Keep it together!
Don't take off your glasses
and fantasize now!
I have no regrets...
Glasses Elf!
Don't die!
So anyway, that's why I'll be
staying here from now on.
Because why?
Hooray, we have a new friend!
Nice to meet you, Snow White!
And so, without
further discussion,
Snow White came to
live with the elves.
It's okay, Akari.
No matter how much you're
cut from each frame,
I'll be watching over
you from every angle.
You're always so well
prepared, Akane-chan.
It's wonderful.
Is dinner ready?
Is it ready yet?
Why don't you two do some work?
Snow White, Sakurako-chan,
help with the chores.
Huh?
Why do you two look so surprised?
And so the kind elves and Snow White
lived happily together.
But in the castle...
Mirror, now that Snow White is dead,
surely I am the fairest of them all, yes?
What? Snow White is still alive?
Fine, then. I will kill her myself.
After that, I'll start
a new experiment.
Gross!
What a beautiful girl.
How would you like a freshly picked
tomato for your beauty and health?
Thank you!
This freshly picked tomato is delicious!
That wasn't a fresh tomato.
It was a tomato from
the defective section
of the supermarket that I poisoned!
Snow White is done for!
Having eaten the poisoned
tomato given to her
by the disguised queen,
Snow White really died.
Tomato?
Defective section?
Snow White, why did you have to die?!
I told you not to take
food from strangers!
Why... why...
Wh-What amazing acting.
I wonder if that's really acting.
Kyoko-sen... I mean, Snow White.
Leave everything to me
and rest in peace...
Huh? Isn't one of us missing?
The Remarkably
Unremarkable Elf, wasn't it?
I'm right here, okay?!
It's one of the other
elves that isn't here!
Snow White will depart
for heaven from this church.
Huh? Church?
I thought it was a graveyard...
I'm a prince from the
neighboring kingdom.
I got lost and ended up he—
What the heck?!
Staying up late every night
really paid off, Chinatsu.
What a beautiful drawing.
Nothing less from my little sister.
So this is the Snow White
I've heard so much about.
How beautiful.
I cannot believe she is dead...
Stop laughing.
Snow White ate a poisoned
tomato and died.
She ate it all by herself? Unfair!
It was poisoned.
Snow White,
I wish we could've met
while you were alive.
At least let me
give you a parting kiss.
What?!
Wait, what're you doing, Prince?!
Well, that should be enough.
I'll hit you.
No!
Snow White is alive!
Good grief.
You're so mean, Chinatsu-chan.
Like a zombie,
Snow White has risen again.
This calls for something drastic.
Yes. I don't actually want to do this,
but you leave me no choice. Yes.
Your expression isn't
convincing me of that.
Backdrop change!
I thought this might happen,
so I made an Anti-Snow White Robot!
Well? Are you surprised?
That's amazing!
A robot? That's ridiculous.
Huh? I don't think that face
was on the original backdrop.
Quiet! Sakurako, quiet!
It looked this way! It's terrifying!
What? But it's so cute.
President, please stop this craziness!
Even I know what the
president just said.
So, Ayano-chan, shall we give up?
You give up too easily!
In that case, fire! Boob missiles!
I can't do that!
Go, backdrop robot!
You must defeat Snow White!
Why are you running with us, Queen?
I made it in a hurry,
so it can't tell the difference
between enemies and allies.
Please don't make robots like that!
Honestly.
A-Akari-chan?
Mr. Robot!
Please don't do this anymore!
It's too dangerous, Akari!
Run!
It's okay!
I'm sure even Mr. Robot
will understand if he opens his heart!
Please, Mr. Robot!
She lost.
I think she fainted.
It... It stopped?
Did Akaza-san get through to it?
No, it's out of batteries.
It seems AA batteries weren't enough.
It was running on batteries?
Sensei, maybe you should
make it a hybrid next time.
Mr. Robot! You understood how I felt!
Huh?
Akari taught us the
pointlessness of fighting...
It seems I've lost, Snow White.
Let's all live in
peace from now on.
Yeah!
Thanks, Akari...
You'll live on forever
in our hearts.
I'm not dea—
You're brilliant, Akari!
Encore! Encore! Encore!
Behind you, behind you!
Huh?