Yuru Yuri 2 Episode 10
Akarin!
Hey!
What's going on?
D-Don't tell me it's happening again.
Akarin!
Akarin~
You first years keep an eye
on things while we're gone!
Is everyone okay?
Akarin~
Niraka!
Yui-senpai!
Be good while we're gone.
We will!
I'm the only one who didn't reappe—
Nanamori Middle School Class 2-5
Just how many snacks did you bring?
I didn't just bring snacks.
Just in case!
You won't have a chance to
use those things in Kyoto!
What?
Toshino Kyoko, calm down!
Don't get so worked up over a school trip!
We'll be sharing a hotel
room with them.
Won't that be fun?
I-I'm not looking forward to it at all!
Really?
T-That's right.
I wanna go on a trip, too!
Episode 10
School Trip R
Where'd that come from?
I'm jealous of the
upperclassmen's trip.
I wanna go somewhere,
too! I wanna go!
You're such a child.
Who would you go with, anyway?
I have no choice.
I guess I'll go with you.
Why do you act so condescending?
Well? Where are we going?
I don't have any money,
so we're going as far as we can walk.
Is that really a trip?
I hope you don't get tired
and give up halfway.
Don't treat me like a kid!
I'm an adult!
Stupid, stupid!
Haven't we walked far enough?
Have you discovered anything new?
Yes.
There are a bunch of people
named Hasegawa around here.
There are probably
lots of Shibatas, too.
No one cares about that.
Anyway, I'm feeling a little hungry.
Shall we stop somewhere?
What's that? A rock?
A rice ball.
You used to like bonito.
Do you still like it?
Did you make this for me?
N-No. If you don't want it, give it back.
Oh, no. Thank you.
It's so salty.
What's that?!
But I made it for you!
Did you taste this before serving it?
You should try it.
What?
You're just too picky
when it comes to tas—
How's it taste?
There's just enough salt
to restore what's lost
during an intense workout.
Fitness food for a true athlete.
Its flavor would make a
TV gourmet reporter exclaim,
"It's a festival of salt!"
How stubborn are you?
Himawari, you like bonito, right?
You can have mine, too.
I'll choke you with that rice ball!
The forest is getting a little thick.
There aren't any bears
around here, are there?
Could you not say things like that?
What are we supposed
to do if a bear appears?
Play dead?
I've heard playing dead
is actually dangerous.
I heard on TV that they'll stay away
if you let them know
there are humans around.
For example, by whistling.
Whistling? Leave that to me.
You're not whistling.
That's it. A bell.
This should work, too.
Good job, Himawari.
You're always prepared.
We'll take that bear down
with our bare hands.
You're still not whistling.
We haven't beaten any bears, either.
Himawari.
Huh?
I've been wondering for a while...
Wh-What is it?
Where're we?
What?
You don't remember how we got here?
This is nothing to laugh about!
I thought you'd
remember how to get home!
I don't.
Don't be proud of it.
A third time?
We need to find a way home.
Butler!
Maybe if we call a butler,
a limousine will—
Shut up and think.
Okay.
Sakurako is thinking
harder than usual.
Maybe she has a plan!
Sakurako, have you got an idea?
There's a caterpillar on your foot.
What?
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
You told me to shut up.
There's a park over there.
Oh my. You're right.
What are we going to do?
We've no idea where we are,
and we're lost.
That's it! A phone!
We'll be fine if we call home
and have someone pick us up!
Sakurako, we can call...
Unbelievable.
She plays until she drops. Literally.
Little Red Riding Hood
Read it, read it!
Okay.
The wolf following Little Red
Riding Hood saw her playing...
She hasn't matured a day
since we were kids.
I knew nothing good
would happen today.
I suppose I haven't
matured either,
if I followed her
knowing that.
W-what's that?!
Could it be?
A bear?!
Huh? Himawari-chan, Sakurako-chan,
what're you doing?
Akaza-san...
What are you doing here?
I take walks in this area.
These woods? You walk this far?
Far?
We're in the woods behind the school.
Drum
River
Forest
School
Wake up already!
What's that?
That's called the Otowa-no-Taki.
Sure is crowded.
I guess we can skip it.
You're right.
We're right under the
Kiyomizu stage, aren't we?
Path
Oh, you're right.
It's not that high, after all.
This wouldn't kill you.
But if you fell and got impaled
by those, it's over.
Oh, I see.
Why are you talking about that?
The tea is ready.
That's right. Yui-senpai isn't here...
T-There's no need to be sad.
She might be gone,
but it's only for a few days...
This is a very big deal to me!
Yui-senpai!
If I don't see her face at
least once a day, I wilt!
W-Would a photo do?
Want me to take out
some photos of Yui-chan?
I have a few photos myself...
A few?!
But I still don't have enough,
so please give me the ones you have.
You don't have enough?
No?
It's fine.
When did she take those?
Sometimes, she's incredible.
Lately, I've been feeling uncertain.
Huh?
When I look at Yui-senpai's
beautiful face,
I get so nervous, I feel
like my heart will burst.
I-I see...
I tried writing Yui-senpai a letter.
C-Can I read it?
What the—?!
Why did you draw your own stationery?
Isn't homemade stationery
more heartfelt and warm?
W-Warm?
Maybe I'm just not attractive.
That's not true.
Sometimes you're scary, but...
What was that?
Nothing!
I think you're cute.
You're so devoted
to your crush.
It's wonderful.
Really?
What else?
Chinatsu-chan, you smell nice.
I'm using a new shampoo.
Your hair is so fluffy, too.
Thank you, Akari-chan.
I think I'm feeling a little better.
I'm just telling you the truth.
Akari-chan, you're so nice.
When it comes to Yui-senpai,
I get so wound up that
sometimes I lose sight of everything else.
I'd be so happy if you'd
be my friend forever.
Of course.
You're my very special friend.
Really? Thank you.
I'll do whatever you want today.
What?
Okay...
Ask me for anything.
Akari
I'd like some more tea, then.
What? You can ask for more than that.
Like "let me sleep on your lap,"
or "massage me."
What? Uh... um...
T-Then I'll sleep on your lap...
Akari
How's that?
I don't know...
You're not satisfied, are you?
I'll give you a massage.
What? You don't need to do that.
I'm afraid she'll break something...
C'mon, I'm good at giving massages.
My sister even calls me a professional.
R-Really? In that case...
Here I go.
Chinatsu-chan, stop!
She's massaging my ticklish spot!
Akari-chan, doesn't that feel good?
Stop!
You look as satisfied as my sister.
Stop! Please, not there!
Sh-She'll kill me!
Next, I'll massage your lower back.
That's enough, Chinatsu-chan.
There's no need to be shy.
I'll give you the full body treatment.
Hooray...
How was that?
Yeah... You really are a professional...
I know, right?
Maybe I'll give Yui-senpai
a massage sometime.
I don't think you should do that.
What else? Do you want anything else?
Your ears! How about
I clean your ears?
What? I've already had enough!
There's no need to hold back!
No, it's really okay.
There you go again.
My sister said I'm good at that, too.
She said I'm as rough as
a road construction crew.
Yui-chan, Kyoko-chan, come back soon!
The building you see behind me
is the hotel we'll
be staying at tonight.
It has a large outdoor bath
that's perfect for stargazing.
From your room, you can
see the Daimonji fire.
Unlimited drinks!
The television even has BS.
You know an awful lot about it.
Huh? I wonder why.
We're here!
Huh?
Didn't we come here for
a school trip before?
What? Our elementary
school trip was to Nara.
That's a completely different place.
Oh, right.
Let's hit the outdoor bath!
I'm not following that segue.
Hello.
Coming. Oh, Hima-ko.
Is Sakurako here?
She just left. She'll
probably be back soon.
Sorry to bother you.
It's fine. Make yourself at home.
Are you thirsty?
We have tea, milk, and orange juice.
Uh, I'll have some tea, then.
Orange 100%
Sorry, we didn't have any tea.
Is orange juice okay?
Yes.
Incoming Call
Someone's calling me.
Mind if I answer?
Sure, go right ahead.
What's with that
weird ringtone?
Hello? Yeah.
What? Really?
You forgot your foundation?
Do you remember where
you last used it?
Behind the sink.
Got it. I'll look for it.
I'll bring it to school tomorrow.
Okay.
Is it a school friend?
No, I'm glad you slept over.
We got to talk a lot.
We finally got to be
alone together, too.
Don't say that. It's embarrassing.
We slept in the same bed.
You're the one who was embarrassed.
Don't say "soft" like that.
Just what is their relationship?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Huh? Did I walk into
the wrong house?
My sister's on the phone, huh?
Sakurako, does your sister
have a girlfriend?
I smell oranges.
Himawari, you drank my
orange juice, didn't you?
Never mind.
I was looking forward to drinking that!
I didn't know!
Fine, then. I'll have milk.
To make up for the juice,
do my homework before going.
I'll show you how to do it.
Let's get to work.
I've got my stuff.
They're gonna do homework.
Why are you sitting next to me?
Sit over there.
I didn't sit next to you
because I wanted to.
I can't read your textbook
if I don't sit here.
I'll turn it around for you.
Then it would be hard
for you to read.
Geez, you're selfish.
Who is?
We'll do this, then.
My neck hurts.
Actually, I wouldn't mind
letting you sit next to me.
If you insist.
Here, this one's next.
When this happens,
move the adverb...
That hits the spot!
Listen to me.
I'm listening. What's
that about adjectives?
See? You're not listening.
Marriage Registration
We can't read the characters.
Tell us what it says.
Write your name here.
Thanks.
Mom, where'd you get this?
It's a marriage registration form.
I found it when I was cleaning,
so I gave it to them.
The wife's name goes here.
The husband's here.
I wanna be the wife!
Play rock, paper, scissors for it.
Winner will be the wife.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
I don't wanna be the husband!
Oh no...
Poor Hima-chan.
I know.
You can write your name
in the wife's spot.
But...
Wife
It's okay, just go like this.
Now we're both the wife.
Sa-chan, thank you.
What do we write here?
You write your address
here, and your job here.
I can't read the rest.
Job?
Maybe put what you
wanna be when you grow up?
Okay.
Lord
Candy Maker
When we get married,
I'll make you sweets every day.
Really?
Yeah.
Sakurako, what are you
gonna do for Hima-chan?
Let's see...
I'll eat candy every day.
I'll make really good stuff.
I love you!
You used to be such good friends.
We were never friends!
I'd never wanna be friends with her!
I could say the same!
What was that,
you booby demon?
I always help you
with your homework!
How dare you call me that?!
So what!
You're the one who
drank my orange juice!
Who's the one always
eating my lunch?
Who?
It's you.
I don't wanna do this anymore.
We'll never finish at this rate.
If I don't wanna,
I don't wanna.
What a shame.
I'd even brought some homemade
sweets to share with you.
What? Let's eat them!
You can eat them once you've
finished your homework.
What?
What did you make, anyway?
Madeleines.
Hooray, madeleines!
They haven't changed at all.
It's not surprising,
since you two filled out
that marriage registration.
What marriage registration?
They don't remember
We're back!
We've brought you gifts from Kyoto.
It's like we never left.
You're right.
I trust you two managed
while we were gone?
Here. This is for you.
What?
We're home, you two.
No!
Yui-senpai! I've missed you so much!
Akari, did you lose weight?
We bought you a gift.
You're giving us a wooden sword?
That sword...
Huh?
I'm your protagonist who's
finally arrived, Furutani Himawari.
I've been waiting ages for
my turn to do the preview.
Our next episode will kind of be our final,
so it may be a little serious.
Don't worry, though.
Sakurako will be her usual self.