What's this?
I drew a picture of Yui-senpai in a
lovely club meeting scenario!
Lovely, huh?
Yui, what're we gonna do?
We'll have to use it.
There's no time.
Come on, let's go. Ready, and...
Akarin!
Hey!
Akari-chan, what's wrong?
I bet her eyes are rolling back in shock...
Episode 9
A Day Something May or May Not Happen
Our final exams study group
meeting will now begin!
I brought tons of snacks!
I brought cards, too!
I also brought...
What did you come here to do?
Huh? We're not gonna take breaks?
You can't afford to take breaks!
This is boring!
If there's anything we don't
understand, we'll help each other.
Should we figure out
who's best at each subject?
Oh, yes.
I'm good at Japanese and science.
I'm good at everything but
geography and social studies...
I'm good at English and math.
And I'm okay at social studies,
so I can probably cover that.
And you, Sakurako-chan?
Arts and crafts...
That really doesn't help us at all.
Sakurako!
You mustn't slack off.
I'll study later.
Akari-chan, here. Say, "ah."
Thank you.
Akari-chan, did you buy this ribbon?
Yeah. I haven't used it, though.
Akaza-san, about this problem...
Which one?
Oh, this? This is alkaline, so...
Oh, I see.
So that's the answer.
I see. So that's how it works.
If there's anything else you
don't understand, just ask.
What's this?
You didn't notice?
Akari-chan, you're so funny!
Sakurako-chan, don't do that!
Sakurako-chan, you're sorta
like Kyoko-senpai.
Really? Maybe it's my intelligence...
Or the way you both
say things like that...
Doesn't Toshino-senpai cram
the night before a test and
score the highest in her grade?
If I'm like her, maybe
that'll work for me.
What're you talking about?
It'd be amazing if you could.
Maybe she has a memorization technique.
Why don't we ask her?
A memorization technique?
We were wondering if there's
a trick to cramming.
Okay, I'll tell you, as a special service.
Thank you, Kyoko-chan.
All right!
First, open your textbook
and place it on the floor.
Put your head on your
textbook and do a headstand.
Then pray.
What do we do next?
Well, that's a lie...
What? A lie?
A lie?
That should've been obvious.
What did they want?
Sounded like everyone was studying together.
I see...
That looks good!
They're hot, so be careful.
So good!
Take some to Akari and the
others on your way home.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Gulp...
Bread Yui made for you...
is what this was...
Did you eat it?
What I have here is an ordinary
paper bag. No tricks or gimmicks...
Where's the bread?
It's magic! All the bread inside
ended up in my stomach!
Chinatsu-chan, calm down! Calm down!
No! How could you?
Yui-senpai's homemade bread!
Her bread is gone! Why did you eat it?
Because I got hungry...
And the bread was right there, so...
Sniffle, sniffle...
I understand!
I knew you would!
Don't bond over this!
Please don't become friends!
So, what happened to my bread?
I told you. I ate it.
My sister gave me a pound cake,
so I brought it to share with everyone...
But today we're having green tea,
and those don't go together.
I guess I'll save it for tomorrow.
But if I leave it here,
Kyoko-senpai might eat it...
I'll hide it in here.
So then Ayano...
Hey, Chinatsu-chan!
Huh? She's not here yet.
Let's see, what should we do today?
Maybe you should try
doing your homework.
What?
What am I gonna do?
Why did I hide?
What should I do?
I was so surprised, I hid in the closet.
I'm so silly.
You hid in the closet?
What kind of crime did you commit?
Chinatsu-chan, I'll go apologize
to the police with you, okay?
You're weird...
I'm so scared, I can't go out!
I guess we can do homework.
Yui, let's compare our work.
You don't have anything
to share, do you?
I'll start trying tomorrow.
Chinatsu-chan's late.
You're right. Maybe a
teacher had to talk to her.
I'm here. I'm right here, Yui-senpai.
I'm so sorry for making you sad...
I want some tea. Where's Chinatsu-chan?
I've got bigger problems right now!
Make your own tea, for once...
Now, now. Chinatsu-chan will make
us some delicious tea later.
Yes, I'll make you some delicious tea!
It's getting hot.
I was going to hide in here until
everyone left, but I don't think I can...
And then I tripped.
What were you doing?
Senpai, you're always so clumsy.
You think so?
Yes.
If I just exit naturally like that,
they might not notice!
That would never work.
In that case...
Chinatsu-chan? What're you...?
Please be quiet!
They seem to have left.
I didn't think they
would come this far...
What about acting like
there's something going on?
No, no! They'll think I'm crazy!
If only I could leave unnoticed...
Huh?
Chinatsu-chan, when did you get here?
C'mon. I've been
here the whole time.
What? I thought Akari was the
only one with no presence.
Kyoko-chan, what do you mean by that?
Akarin.
Akarin~
Chinarin.
Chinarin~
No!
What should I do?
What should I do? What should I do?
I know!
Maybe I should just bolt out of
the room looking really intense!
It'll distract them from wondering why
I was in the closet in the first place!
What's wrong, Chinatsu-chan?
You're acting really intense...
Oh, I'm so silly.
I thought it was my turn to feed
the ducks in the courtyard,
but then I remembered
we don't have ducks.
Chinatsu-chan, you're so scatterbrained.
Like that!
It's the only way!
Let's go, Chinatsu! Show them
your maidenly determination!
It's an emergency!
Nope. Can't do it.
Yui-chan, what's today's snack?
I baked a pound cake...
But that doesn't go well with green tea.
That's okay. Since you made it,
I'm sure they'll taste fine together.
There you go again,
saying silly things...
Akari, could you get plates and forks?
Okay.
Thanks for the food.
Chinatsu-chan never showed up.
She must've left to do something.
Burp.
No Boobs Allowed
You seem tired.
I always go to bed at nine.
Oh, right. It's already ten.
Chinatsu-chan, when do you go to sleep?
After eleven.
If there's a TV show I want
to watch, I'll stay up even later.
I see. You're so grown up...
Grown up?
You don't have to force
yourself to stay awake.
I'll go to bed later.
No.
You came here to sleep over.
I want to talk and play more.
Really? Then what should we do?
Let's see...
Actually...
My sister rented this.
Scary stories?
Oh, sorry. Chinatsu-chan, you
don't like scary stuff, right?
Well, whatever...
Can you see it?
At first glance, it seems
to be a perfectly ordinary
cover of a manga's fifth volume.
Look at the bottom of your screen.
Underneath the band is
a large woman's face...
I'm scared.
The ghost of a woman who
demands to be seen...
Perhaps that's what this is.
Wasn't that scary, China...
It was so scary!
Y-Yeah...
Do you feel awake now?
I'm not as tired as before.
Okay, then! Wanna play cards?
Yeah!
I got a pair.
I guess I'll go to bed.
I thought of that DVD and now I can't sleep...
Akari-chan...
Don't scare me like that!
The wind? That's the wind, right?
I shouldn't have watched that!
Fu fu fu fu fu fu~
You're scaring me! Stop!
I'll go right to sleep.
It won't be scary in the morning.
But what if...
What if someone's floating right
in front of me, staring at me?
What if someone's hiding under Akari-chan's desk,
or someone's standing in the corner...
I have to think of something
else to distract myself!
Something else, something else...
Hey, Chinatsu-chan!
Yui-senpai!
You're so cute. You couldn't sleep
because you're afraid of ghosts.
But...
Instead of ghosts, you
should think about me.
That's amazing. All that
fear vanished in a second.
Yui-senpai's the best remedy.
Now I can sleep in...
I'm sorry I scared you.
I just came to get my DVD.
Goodnight.
Bathroom...
I'm not scared, I'm not scared...
I-I'm scared!
I'm not scared, I'm not scared, I'm not scared...
I'm so scared, I can't sleep!
Ikeda-senpai, hello.
Oh, Akaza-san.
Are you cleaning?
I'm helping out as a cleanup volunteer.
Are you out on an errand?
I'm on my way back from
the convenience store.
I see.
Oh, I know.
Would you like some ice cream?
What? Are you sure?
Yes. Let's eat together.
Thank you.
I wanted something cold to eat.
Thanks for the food.
Sugiura-senpai, I bet this
would look good on you.
This one's nice, too.
How about this for you, Yoshikawa-san?
It's so cute.
Maybe I'll buy it.
What a coincidence, running
into each other here.
You're right.
She's not... with you today?
Pardon?
Um...
Oh! You mean Yui-senpai?
What? Uh, y-yeah.
Oh, come on...!
I wish we could always be together,
but she was busy today.
I see...
Um, I wonder what kind of
clothes Toshino Kyoko likes?
Do you know?
I dunno.
Sugiura-senpai, why are you suddenly
asking about Kyoko-senpai?
No reason...
Anyway, Sugiura-senpai, do you know
what kind of clothes Yui-senpai likes?
What? I'm sorry. I have no idea.
I see. That's too bad...
Oh, this is cute, too.
I bet that would look
good on Toshino Kyoko.
No, it would look better on Yui-senpai.
Tomita Bookstore
Guess who?
Toshino-senpai!
Hey.
Boob-chan, what are you buying?
Could you not call me Boob-chan?
Hima-chan, then.
She gave me a nickname...
Recipe books and study guides.
Toshino-senpai, what
are you looking for?
Any new volumes of
my favorite manga.
I see.
Toshino-senpai's ribbon...
I thought it was a ribbon,
but it's cat ears?
What should I do?
Should I say something?
But if she's wearing that to look nice...
I want to know.
I want to know, but I can't ask!
And now that I look more
closely... What's that?
What is that?
What animal is that?
Whose ears are those?
That joke's done.
Senpai...
I don't know what to say...
This publisher's study guides are easy
to memorize, so I recommend them.
Middle School Social Studies Study Guide
M-Memorize?
Oh, you're right.
It brings everything together
so it's easy to understand.
I know, right?
For English, I recommend this...
She's a bit strange, but I have to
respect how mature she actually is.
She's nothing like Sakurako.
Onions and tofu and grilled meat...
Raw Meat
Is that a joke?
What are you making?
I was thinking of mapo tofu.
You can make that at home?
Of course. What are you...
Huh?
What?
She wasn't joking?
You made bread before, too!
Funami-senpai, are you a chef?
Your family never had mapo tofu for dinner?
I thought it was an instant dinner.
Oh...
I'm supposed to cook today.
Is there anything easy I can make?
What about salisbury steak?
That's a good idea! You
just buy 'em and fry 'em.
What? You're not gonna make them?
Forget what I said!
Something simple, something simple...
What about udon?
All she has to do is boil that.
All I have to do is add hot water!
Are you just lazy?
Wow, Judas' ears!
I love Judas' ears!
Yeah, they're good.
But they look a bit weird.
I've never seen 'em so black.
I wonder where they're from.
Do you think they're cute?
She seriously thinks they're...
Don't panic, Akaza-san!
Gently... Put it back gently.
I did it.
Don't let your guard down!
Use your mouth to stick it back together!
O-Okay!
Sorry!
Akaza-san, don't worry about it.
Those girls didn't mean any harm...
Ikeda-senpai...
The ants will enjoy my ice cream, won't they?
Y-yeah...
Do you want half?
Yes.
I was your student council
protagonist, Sugiura Ayano...
Why am I using past tense?
The first years have been
stealing the limelight, but...
The second years are the
focus of the school trip!
It's not like I'm happy because
I'll get to be with Toshino Kyoko!