Yuru Yuri 2 Episode 2
"Yuru Yuri Everyday"
Akarin!
Hey!
Yuru Yuri's starting!
I'm so glad to see all of you again.
I look forward to...
Yuru Yuri Everyday
I can't take it anymore...
I can't lake it anymore.
Sorry, forget I said that.
Just focus.
You're going to get called
on in math class.
Yeah, I will! The teacher
always picks me!
But I'm never picked to win the lottery.
Yeah.
What would you do if you
won 300 million yen?
And you can't say you'd save it.
I'd go on a trip with everyone
and eat delicious food.
Yui, I love you.
Thanks.
But you know, now that
I really think about it,
there's nothing I want that badly.
I have things I want.
Like what?
I want to build an arcade under my house!
Toshino's House
On the national rankings,
you'd see "Toshino's House!"
It'd be so cool!
I could see that.
I know, right?
But I've never won
any lotteries.
Have you made any progress
on your homework?
Nope.
Hey, Yui.
Do you... love me?
I do.
Really?
All right, then let me see your homewo—
No.
Why not?
I like you, so I don't want
to hinder your learning.
Darn it! Love is rough.
Just do it.
Okay.
10 Minutes Later
It never ends!
Lunch is gonna be over in five minutes.
There's no time!
If I beat you at rock-paper-scissors,
will you show me your homework?
Oh, fine. You're out of time, anyway.
All right!
Here we go.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I don't think that pose was necessary.
Just forget about it...
Rock, paper, scissors!
By the way...
You can't focus on anything, can you?
We haven't changed at all, have we?
I guess not.
You, especially, haven't matured one bit.
But...
It's better that way.
Why?
Because you'll always look after me.
You need to grow up a little.
Are you embarrassed?
Shut up.
Our friendship is rock solid.
Yeah, yeah.
Let me see your homewo—
No.
Let me see it!
I'm out.
I lost again.
Akari-chan, you're terrible at Old Maid.
Akari, you're so easy to read.
When someone starts to take a
card that's not the Old Maid...
...you look like you're gonna cry.
And when someone's about to
take the Old Maid...
...you look really happy.
Is it that obvious?
This one!
The Old Maid!?
I don't believe it!
Yui, you're good!
You didn't lose once today.
Really?
What makes someone good
at Old Maid? Is it luck?
Yui-senpai doesn't let her
emotions show on her face.
Her poker face is so cool!
I see...
Poker face...
Old Maid...
Old Face!
You're proud of that?
Mandarin oranges!
And don't give me any weird nicknames.
Speaking of which, none
of us have nicknames.
Then I'm Super Sexy Commando Kyoko.
Super Sexy Commando Kyoko,
pass me an orange.
Roger.
Not that sort of nickname!
For example...
Someone named Sachiko
might be Sacchan or Sachi.
You come up with something, then.
Really?
Kyoko-chan, you're...
Kyoppi!
Kyoppi?
Yui-chan, you're...
Yuppi, I guess.
Yu...
Kyoppi and Yuppi.
Sounds like a comedy team.
Thank you!
We're Kyoppi and Yuppi.
Okay! Today we'll be performing a
short skit with these mandarin oranges!
Sounds interesting.
Daruma otoshi!
Googly eyes.
Akari.
Boob missiles!
Chinachu.
Empty husks.
That's not a joke.
Go throw these out.
You do it.
Thank you very much.
Kyoppi's the only one who said anything.
But we get paid the same amount.
Yuppi is so cute.
What?
What's my nickname?
Huh?
Um...
China, I guess?
China!
Hey, everyone! Thanks for
coming out to see me today!
China! China! China!
It sounds like an idol's name. So cute!
Hey, give me a nickname.
Aka... Aka...
Aka Baby!
Um... Could you choose
something else?
I can't think of anything.
The Red One!
Pink Breath!
The Ebony Queen!
You're just saying the
color of our hair.
But I think focusing on
colors would be good.
Amusement Club Red! Yellow! Black! Pink!
What are we, the Power Rangers?
Our enemy is the Student Council!
Yellow hasn't been eating curry lately.
Student Council Purple!
White! Blue! Light Brown!
Hey, that last one...
Oh, man. Not only
will it be live action,
but we can load it
with special effects!
No, we can't.
We can't do either of those things.
Hey, have any of you
had nicknames before?
I have.
Kyo-chan, Ke-chan, Toshinon, Toshibo.
China-chan and Chinacchi, I guess.
You two have nicknames? Lucky ducks!
I've never had a nickname.
You have one already, Akari!
Akarin
Akarin!
I don't like that one!
You're so selfish.
Starting today, you're Selfishman.
No!
What about names of fruit?
I'm Lemon-chan!
Lemon
Peach
Peach!
Apple
Apple!
That's sort of cute.
Black...
A black fruit?
(Rotten) Banana.
I heard that.
Ah well...
None of us are very
good at naming things.
It's devastating.
I thought China was cute...
Forget the nicknames.
Let's play Concentration.
I won't lose this time!
I might be able to win!
Old Face, pass me some tissues.
Forget that nickname, too.
We're organizing the
class roster today, aren't we?
We'd better work hard.
Student Council
No!
Sakurako, no!
Sounds like Omuro-san and
Furutani-san are already here.
You can't escape now.
But... But this is so sudden...
More... Deeper...
Wait! Don't go so deep...
It's so... tight...
Sakurako...
It's... It's coming!
It came out!
What? Huh?
Oh my.
What are you two...
Senpai, watch out!
Look down!
Huh?
It went back to hiding.
I see.
You were using the broom
to guide a snake, that had crawled
beneath the fridge,
so you could capture it.
What is a snake doing
here at this time of year?
Shouldn't they be hibernating?
Maybe it snuck
in here because it's warm.
By the way...
Furutani-san, what are
you doing on the table?
I don't like snakes...
Omuro-san, you don't mind snakes?
Nope! I don't like to touch them, though.
There must be something wrong with you
if you don't mind snakes.
They're way better than cockroaches.
No way! If I had a choice,
I'd choose cockroaches any day!
No, that's crazy.
That's why your boobs are so big!
That has nothing to do with this!
Just do something about that snake.
Don't you think Toshino-san
would be good at this?
I got the snake!
Shall I go get her?
Of course not!
If she finds out I'm afraid of snakes...
Ikeda-senpai, you're not scared?
I'm fine.
Then can you catch it—
Sorry, I'm busy.
Snakes aren't scary.
Don't worry. I'm here.
Kyoko.
This is the best.
You all disgust me!
I, Sakurako-sama,
shall capture the snake for you!
Who're you impersonating?
Hey!
Come on out, snake!
Sakurako, you're so strong.
Come out! Come...
I knew that would happen.
Then you do it!
Fine then, I'll just
grab you with my hand!
Isn't that dangerous?
I'll be fine as long
as it doesn't bite me.
Taking
Refuge
Still Fantasizing
Why... you... little...
Heads up.
You should've said that earlier!
Now I'm angry!
Prepare yourself, snake!
She's angry at the wrong person.
Snake hunt in progress.
Meanwhile, please enjoy
Chitose's fantasy.
Got it!
Good work, Omuro-san.
Amazing.
It'd be a waste to just let it go.
I'll go show Akari-chan!
What? Wait...
Does Akaza-san even like snakes?
No, I think she just
wants to show her...
Akari-chan!
Look, a snake!
Sakurako-chan!
You shouldn't have come in...
What are you doing?
Um...
The snake! Sakurako-chan, the snake!
Omuro-san's still not back.
She must've gotten herself into trouble.
Correct
New Influenza Epidemic
This year's influenza
is spreading rapidly.
Make sure you take care
not to get infected.
It's really getting around.
My character song?
Hey.
It sounds like it's been going
around my sister's school, too.
We have to protect ourselves
against getting sick.
What are we supposed to do?
Don't go outside until spring!
Nice idea!
Don't be ridiculous.
Eat a balanced diet?
Balanced nutrition.
Yui, how are you doing with that?
Since I live alone, my diet
might be a little off balance.
What?
Senpai, you have to fix that!
What if you catch a cold?
Yeah, I'll be careful.
Kyoko, I bet you eat tons of rice.
You probably get extra helpings.
How rude!
Are you saying I gained two kilos?
You do eat a lot.
I guess you should also
make sure to get plenty of sleep.
Akari, do you get enough sleep?
I go to bed at nine every night,
so I get plenty of sleep.
You always go to bed so early.
I get a fair amount of sleep.
Sounds like you're all sleeping enough.
Though Kyoko seems the
type who'd stay up late.
I'm sure you think I do.
But the truth is...
The truth is...?
That's exactly right.
We knew that...
I do try to go to sleep.
I say I'll read manga
until I get tired...
...but before I know it,
I've read every volume.
And it's morning.
I notice because the
birds start tweeting.
That's how?
I'm surprised you can make it
through school without sleep.
I know, right?
Are you kidding me?
You sleep through all your classes.
You knew?
I'm always surprised when I
wake up and school's over.
If you sleep that much, it's no
wonder you can't sleep at night.
But Yui-chan, I'm surprised
you don't stay up all night.
Really?
She seems like the type
who'd play games all night.
I play games in the morning.
In the morning?
I get up early to play games.
It helps me wake up.
It clears my head, too.
I see.
That sounds pretty nice.
What were we talking about?
Preventing colds.
Right...
I guess washing your hands and
gargling are also a must.
Hand-gargle.
Why would you shorten that?
Hand-gargling's important.
Let's all hand-gargle!
That'll never catch on.
Who are you even talking to?
Anyway, Kyoko doesn't seem like
the type who'd catch a cold.
You're right.
Hey.
Cold prevention is important!
Let's form a Cold Prevention
Team here and now!
You're awfully spirited,
considering how cold it is.
I can't play if I'm sick.
I'd be bored!
So that's it.
First, make sure you're
getting enough nutrients!
Second, get enough sleep!
You should fix your sleep schedule.
I'll try!
Also, dehydration isn't good,
so use a humidifier.
They say it's good to wear a mask, too.
Fantastic idea, Squad Member Chinatsu!
Finally, there's hand-gargling! Got it?
I told you, that'll never catch on.
I'll be careful.
Me, too.
Good! Sounds like you all understand!
Now that that's settled, Captain
Kyoko's going to sleep.
They say you'll catch a cold
if you sleep under a kotatsu.
You're right!
Then where should I sleep?
Go sleep at home.
Aww! Don't say that, Yui-tan.
Moving around might wake you up.
That's it!
Is everyone okay with milk tea?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Air hula hoop.
Allow me to explain!
Moving as though you are
actually using a hula hoop
will help you shape up your waist!
Probably!
It's delicious.
Furthermore, it even prevents colds!
No, it doesn't.
After School
What?
Kyoko-chan's sick?
Yeah, so she took the day off.
Kyoko-senpai's sick...
But she was so passionate about
cold prevention yesterday...
Let's all go visit her!
I'm sure she's feeling
down since she got sick.
You're right.
Let's go.
Sorry, everyone.
Kyoko-chan, are you okay?
I'm not doing so well...
You seem to be in pain.
How did you get sick?
You were so into cold prevention.
Well, after I came home yesterday...
I thought it would stop
me from catching a cold,
so I rubbed myself with
a towel for about an hour.
Forget your cold.
You need a cure for stupidity.
Indeed...
Also, hand-gargling.
You're still saying that?
The wild protagonist,
Toshino Kyoko, is here.
I kind of liked "hand-gargling."
Are there any doctors
watching this show?
Starting tomorrow, let's all say it!
It won't cost you a cent.