Yuri Yuri Episode 4 "Achoo"
Akarin!
Hey.
Yuru Yuri's starting.
What's this?
Sorry, it's me, Nishigaki.
Toshino asked me to make this.
Kyoko-chan!
Mecharin.
What is this thing?
Mecharin... Mecha... Mecha...
Cameraman?
Mecharin.
Achoo
Here.
Thanks.
What's up with that super-cute sneeze?
Shut up. I have allergies.
There's 10 times more pollen in
the air compared to last year.
I'm in Hell...
Chitose, are you okay?
I'm fine.
If I had allergies, I bet I'd have
lots of trouble with runny
noses and nose bleeds.
That's nothing to laugh about.
What about you, Funami-san?
My eyes just get a little itchy.
I've heard allergies can develop suddenly.
Is there any way to prevent them?
What do you think?
Not a chance!
I've heard yogurt can prevent allergies.
I wonder if we get yogurt this month...
No?!
It's like they're telling us to get allergies!
Buy some yourself.
I'm already out of tissues!
No, no! I'm a girl!
But it might be better
than letting my nose run...
Sugiura-san.
It's from Kyoko.
Runny Nose
Toshino Kyoko!
Yeah.
Thanks.
Toshino Kyoko, thank you for earlier.
No worries. It was nothing.
Funami-san, thanks for the tissues.
Don't worry about it.
I bet Nishigaki-chan has some medicine.
What?
Science Preparation Room
Nishigaki-chan, do you have
any allergy medicine?
She must have allergies, too.
Even though explosions don't bother her.
Why don't you borrow a gas mask?
No, thanks.
She thought about it.
Yeah, she did.
Nishigaki-chan.
Why did you put this on me?
There's no no Norway I need this!
Just try wearing it during lunch.
It might help a little.
You too, Chitose?
Fine.
I'm going to the bathroom.
She's going to the bathroom with that on?
I really gotta go...
Ayano-chan, you're cute no
matter what you're wearing.
Student Council
Hey, guys.
I think we should take the
time to do some cleaning today.
What do you think?
Good idea.
I was just thinking it's
getting a little messy.
You're the one making it messy!
Then I'll go get some cleaning supplies.
I'll go with you.
We'll start by cleaning the windows.
Sounds good.
Come on, Sakurako...
Huh?
Window Cleaner
Freeze!
Why are you pointing that at me?
Oh, my mistake.
I thought you were a booby monster.
Oh my, Sakurako...
Window Cleaner
If you don't stop now...
I'll shoot.
She's serious...
It's dirtier than I thought.
What's this?
There's all kinds of stuff in here.
We used those during
the cultural festival.
I see.
What's it doing here?
We must've forgotten to
take it to the storage shed.
Can we have a mock culture festival?
Start cleaning already.
For the Deceased
Maid of the dead.
Why would you say that?
At least take that
triangle off your head.
I couldn't find one of those frilly headbands.
Use this, then.
What is it?
Well, I guess that's close enough.
You think?
I'm finished cleaning the windows.
Now we just have to sweep, right?
Yes, we already dusted the desks.
I'm hungry.
Clean something, you lazy maid.
They say you shouldn't
judge a book by its cover.
Just because I make a cute maid
doesn't mean I have to clean.
It's too bad you aren't a mute maid.
Sheesh! It's my fault
for dressing like this!
There!
Tada! I changed my job from
maid to Omuro Sakurako!
Now you can't tell me to clean.
Do you really hate cleaning that much?
Here's a rag. Wipe that.
What?
Himawari, you idiot.
You're an evil stepmother.
I'm a modern day Cinderella.
I actually like cleaning.
It makes me feel better.
Yeah, a clean room helps me focus better.
I'm sure it'll help us make progress
in our student council duties,
so why not try a
little harder, Omuro-san?
I guess I have no choice...
Oh, I know.
When I'm done, can I have some
pudding as a reward, Sugiura-senpai?
Today's pudding is a
special treat: fruit pudding.
Fruit Pudding
It costs twice as much as much
as the pudding I usually eat.
Well, um...
Here, Omuro-san. Have some candy.
Hooray!
So, can I have some pudding?
The candy wasn't good enough?
I need to do something to distract
Omuro-san from the pudding.
Omuro-san, why don't we
play some shiritori?
That sounds fun! Let's play.
I'll make her forget about
pudding with shiritori.
Don't hold it against me.
I can't... let that pudding go...
I'll start.
Stamp.
Pudding.
Hooray, pudding!
No!
Ayano-chan splurged on today's pudding.
I have to save her.
Pardon me, Omuro-san.
That pudding is special to Ayano-chan.
Chitose, you know how I feel.
That's why you're my best, best friend!
That pudding...
is an important,
heartfelt gift that Ayano-chan
splurged on and bought for Toshino-san!
You're wrong, friend!
Really? Guess it can't be helped, then.
I'll have to hold back this time.
Sorry.
Who do you think you are?
This is getting ridiculous!
That looks delicious!
I didn't buy this for you or anything!
Don't get the wrong idea!
You can have this, then.
I just bought it and
was about to eat it.
Isn't that great, Ayano-chan?
Toshino Kyoko's... ice cream...
I have no choice.
I accept!
Senpai, why do you stare
at that ice cream every day?
N-no reason!
Ice cream! Can I have it?
Absolutely not!
Matsumoto, good morning.
School's already over?
Such a matter is trivial
when compared to the wide open sky.
Sugiura?
Good morning.
Sensei, school's already over.
What can I do for you?
Our clock stopped working.
We thought you might be able to fix it.
I suppose I must.
I, Nishigaki Nana, will turn
this into a wonderful clock.
What do you think?
I added a radio control feature.
Why would you do that?
Yay! Lemme try!
Okay, Furutani.
Try saying "What time is it?"
What?
What time is it?
Huh? It's moving by itself...
Huh? What?
It is currently 15:50.
It's a new type of clock that flies over
to whoever wants to know the time.
That's not radio controlled!
Why even have this controller?
Fine, fine.
Here's a cute dog clock.
Cute?
It will bark the current time for you.
16:08! 16:08!
Shut up!
I'd prefer something simpler.
We just need it to work.
What? But that's so boring.
We need something with more of a bang to it!
Hey! That's dangerous!
You should be careful what
you wish for, Omuro-san.
I see, a self destruct mechanism...
You shouldn't make things explode, Sensei!
Is that a joke?
No! And we're not looking
for a joke clock, either!
Okay, I fixed it.
It's back to normal.
Thank you.
You certainly are amazing, Sensei.
I know, right?
When did you become
interested in this kind of stuff?
Let's see...
I was still in elementary school.
Both of my parents were working
and I had no siblings,
so I was always alone.
The only one who would play with
me was a puppy robot named "Choco."
Choco, shake.
Good dog.
We'll be together forever.
I love you, Choco.
Wherever I went, I took Choco with me.
When I was lonely, Choco
would listen to me.
Choco was my friend.
But one day...
Choco?
Choco!
Shake!
Shake, Choco!
His time must've been up...
Shake...
Choco.
Choco!
Wake up, Choco...
Choco...
Why?
He was fine until a minute ago...
His batteries should still be charged...
Choco never moved again.
Choco...
I'll study hard...
Someday, I'll fix you...
So...
Wait for me until then.
Sensei.
Well, that's a lie.
Give me back my tears!
Let's have some ice cream.
Hey!
You can't have that ice cream!
What actually happened, you ask?
See? The lightbulb turned on.
Let's all try it.
Okay.
Amazing!
If it's this bright
with just a battery...
It'll be even brighter if
I connect it to the socket!
Don't try this at home!
Are you okay?
That's when I was first
drawn to explosions.
What kind of story was that?
My rum raisin...
This is awful! It's pouring!
Aww, I didn't bring an umbrella.
They said it would be sunny.
Akari, your teru teru
bozu aren't working.
What teru teru bozu?
These aren't teru teru bozu!
Really?
Huh?
Are you positive those
aren't teru teru bozu?
Maybe you don't believe they are...
But maybe they think
they're teru teru bozu!
But...
Sorry. I'm sorry!
I didn't take the time
to understand you two.
So long as you understand.
Kyoko-senpai, please stop
playing with Akari-chan.
What are we going to do?
We can't get to the club room like
this, much less go home.
It might stop soon.
Why don't we wait in a classroom?
Class 1-2
I'm bored.
All right! I thought
this might happen...
A board game!
I made it during class.
Yay! Let's play!
One, two, three.
Say 'I love you, Kyoko-chan.'
Yui landed on it...
I was hoping Chinatsu-chan
would land there.
No, thank you!
Oh, good. I don't have to say it, then.
Of course you do! It's the rules!
I love you, Kyoko.
Okay, next.
You're supposed to get flustered!
Say 'I love you, Kyoko-chan.'
One, two, three...
I landed on the same square as Yui-chan.
I love you, Kyoko-chan.
This isn't fun at all.
Did you just have a mean thought?
Senpai, you're next.
There!
Say 'Kyoko-chan, I love you.'
I have to say it?
Come on, just do it.
This game still needs work...
I forgot to turn in my notebook.
I'm going to the faculty office.
I wanted to talk to
you two about something.
Chinatsu-chan gave me a handmade
scarf on Valentine's Day...
I was wondering if I should
give her something back.
Yui! You don't have to
do anything for me.
Chinatsu-chan will be so happy.
Yeah. What should I get her?
Rum raisin would be good!
You shut up for a minute.
Akari, do you know if
Chinatsu-chan wants anything?
Give me every photo of Yui-senpai!
Also her underwear and her life!
I can't think of anything.
I see.
I think she'd be happy to
receive anything from you.
Isn't "anything" is hard to narrow down?
In these situations, you should
give what you'd want to get!
For my birthday last year, one
of my friends gave me...
You can have this!
It's something I want,
so I'm sure you'll like it, too!
But when I opened the present...
I don't think the recipient will
necessarily like what you want.
Really? I bet she wanted
to wear those gloves.
I bet.
So, what did you do with the gloves?
I'm using them as pot holders.
You can hold things with those?
Yui-chan, what do you
want most right now?
An umbrella, I guess.
It still hasn't let up...
The faculty office had
some loaner umbrellas.
They only had two, though.
Oh yeah!
I forgot they had those!
Thanks, Chinatsu-chan!
You're amazing, Chinatsu-chan.
You know Yui so well.
Thanks, Chinatsu-chan.
Let's share an umbrella.
What?
Thank you, rain!
Kyoko-chan, can you move
over a little more?
We should stand in line!
In line?
If we do that, our
shoulders won't get wet.
You're right! That's
amazing, Kyoko-chan!
You're a genius!
Are you all okay?
You're all soaking wet!
She used the fact that she was off screen
to avoid getting splashed...
Akari, you're terrifying.
I am your silent protagonist,
Matsumoto Rise.
I like to talk, but everyone
says I am quiet...
How strange.
I will talk more than
ever in the next episode.