Yuru Yuri 2 Episode 8
"Chinatsu Unrivaled"
Akarin!
Hey!
Yuru Yuri's start...
Huh? What's wrong?
Stop! That's not food!
Those are gifts for our fans!
No!
That looks hard.
Winter Comuket's deadline is
the day after tomorrow.
I know! What if we all help you?
Really?
I suppose we have no choice.
Hooray!
If we must.
Hand me a sheet.
Chinatsu-san, why don't
you make some tea?
What?
Chinatsu Unrivaled
I'm going to start inking the pages.
Akari, you erase the pencil
lines once the ink dries.
Yui will fill in the black parts.
Okay.
I made some tea.
So what should I do?
Chinatsu-san, why don't
you sing for us?
What?
Yui-chan, you're amazing!
How'd you get so good?
I'm always helping her...
You will never return...
Our broken, matching mugs...
In the picture on the windowsill...
You and I smile...
Not knowing the future that awaited us...
So depressing!
Why would she sing this song?
But I don't want Chinatsu-chan
touching the pages...
I wonder how long they take to dry.
This might help!
Yui, this one's ready for filling.
Okay.
Achoo!
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
That's good.
What am I going to do?
I finished singing, Kyoko-senpai.
Huh? I-I'd like to hear another song.
What?
Senpai, are you sure
you just don't want
me touching your drawings?
N-No, that's not...
This kind of work is boring,
so why don't you do something fun?
Fine, then.
What else can I do
besides erase pencil marks?
Add tones, I guess.
Can you do it?
Probably, if you show me how.
Okay!
You place the tone like this...
Okay.
Then take a knife and do this.
I see.
If you press too hard,
you'll cut the page too,
so be careful.
Will do!
I feel like a manga artist.
What should I do about this?
Should I go for a glossy look?
Yeah, that's it.
Will we finish in time?
With everyone helping me,
I think we'll make it.
We'll help you tomorrow, too.
Seriously? Hooray!
You owe us some WcDonald's.
I want a cheeseburger.
I want a Big Wac.
Kyoko-chan, what about here?
Oh, put a gradient there.
Like this.
Chinatsu-chan! Stay still!
You're the one who told
me to do something fun!
Right, sorry!
I'll help you, too.
I'll do some filling.
What?
Chinatsu-chan, make some tea!
I really want to drink more
of your tea, Chinatsu-chan.
Oh, you...!
I'll go make some now.
Nice one, Yui.
Here you are.
Thanks.
Now then, I'll just...
Chinatsu-chan, more tea!
My stomach's about to burst.
You drank ten cups.
But thanks to Yui,
we should finish today
without any problems...
I'm done cleaning the cups.
Thank you.
Well, we should get going.
I'm going to the bathroom...
Me, too. I need to wash my hands.
Me, too.
Wait here, okay Chinatsu-chan?
Yeah, sure.
We're back.
Chinatsu-chan, let's go home.
What's wrong?
Nothing, I...
I'm sorry!
I went outside the lines a little!
A little?
I'll do better next time.
Don't you dare!
Excuse us!
Let's have a Christmas party at a karaoke place!
You're always so random, Toshino Kyoko.
Why don't we?
You might get to sing a
duet with Toshino-san.
What?
I'm all for it!
Then it's decided!
Merry Christmas!
This is amazing.
It looks delicious.
It's like a family restaurant.
Karaoke places serve lots
of kinds of food these days.
Song List
I'd Follow You to the Depths of Hell
Witch Girl Mirakurun
My first ***
Mirakurun Song
Moe is Love!
Fly Mandam
Endless Love
Love Warrior Manicure
Just how many songs
have you selected?
We're supposed to take turns choosing them.
Everyone was so interested in the food,
I thought they didn't wanna sing.
If they didn't wanna sing,
why would they come to karaoke?
Good point!
I'd never thought of that!
What were you thinking, then?
Yeah!
That was great, Toshino-san!
She's so good...
Thank you, thank you.
Was that an anime song?
That's right.
From the anime
"I'd Follow You to the Depths of Hell."
I've never heard of it.
What kind of twisted show is that?
It's a heartfelt romantic comedy.
Oh? Really?
It's about the protagonist and
a girl who's her childhood friend...
Her childhood friend is really cute.
Every morning she waits for the
protagonist at her shoe locker...
She makes a lunch box for her every day
but never gives it to her.
She's always regulates who she hangs out with
and is always watching
over her from the shadows.
That's not cute. That's stalking.
I bet she goes yandere in the end.
This is my song.
It's a fun Christmas song, so
sing along if you know it.
On a night when the stars shine bright...
I don't know this one.
You can hear the bells ringing...
Me neither.
What?
Tonight he is coming to see you...
Santa Claus is coming.
You're next, Sugiura-senpai!
What? Uh...
I'm sorry, I haven't decided yet.
Okay!
I'll sing!
Yui-senpai.
What?
This song is a duet.
Will you sing it with me?
Sure.
Hooray!
Man and Woman's Game
This is it!
Oh...
Sorry, I only know the hook.
What?
I know this song.
I'll sing it with you!
What?
You had a little too much
to drink tonight...
Why are you trying to get me drunk?
Your cute face...
What kind of smile will you flash me today?
I don't know this part.
Himawari, come here!
What?
What do you want?
Here!
What? Now?
I dunno the words.
You're hopeless.
If we grew closer
our days would be even better.
I know this part.
May my feelings reach you...
I thought you were done singing?
This part's fun to sing!
You're always so selfish.
Believe in my love and I'll
send these feelings to you...
I'm out of juice.
What do you guys want?
I'll get refills.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I'll go with you, Kyoko-chan.
It's okay, it's okay.
You spoke to me on the
beach as the sun set...
Chitose's so cute when she sings.
You're right. It's kind of soothing.
Yes?
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
How'd you knock just now?
Never mind, I figured it out.
Here you are.
Thanks.
She mixed them...
But it's not too bad...
I can't say anything.
Yui hasn't noticed.
Tsun-Tsun Ballad
This song just came out!
It's already available?
I love this song!
What a gentle yet heartbreaking song.
Ayano-chan, you sure do like ballads.
Can't you see? I can't help but
follow you with my eyes...
Hey!
How do you feel about me?
I want to be with you,
but I can't tell you...
Hey!
I say some harsh things, but
please don't hate me...
One, two, three...
This is supposed to be a ballad!
Yui-senpai, let's try again!
Do you know this song?
Yearning in Abashiri
Yeah, I know that one.
I'll select it, so sing it with me.
Okay.
"Yearning in Abashiri" is 624...
Yearning in Abashiri
I put this song in!
Get out of the way.
Sakurako, this is a duet.
Who cares?
There's no rule saying I
can't sing a duet by myself.
Your small-mindedness is
why your boobs are so big.
What did you say?
You will never return...
Our broken, matching mugs...
She's already singing it...
Miracle lucky love you...
May we be together forever...
Thank you for waiting.
That's mine!
You ordered more?
I love you...
Fried rice is so good!
We han het hrough the
hard himes hogether...
Shut up!
I inhaled some rice...
Sugiura-senpai, you haven't
sung anything yet.
I still haven't made up my mind,
so you girls go ahead and sing...
Time for Just the Two of Us
Ayano-chan, do you know this one?
We could do a duet.
But...
It's got two parts so it's hard
to sing without two people.
Give me a call...
I'll help you anytime...
That's true love...
Ayano's pretty good, too.
Of course I am! This is nothing!
Sing a duet with me.
I suppose I have no choice.
Okay! I'll select that song
Yui-senpai knows again!
I'll make her sing it with me
before anyone knows what's happening!
Our glasses are empty again.
This time, I'll get more.
Wait, get some for me, too!
I'll finish this!
It must be pretty carbonated.
Oolong tea for me.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
I can't let you knock like Kyoko.
What?
Yui, don't mix my drink.
You're one to talk!
Yui-senpai!
But...
I know this one!
Can I sing it with you?
Do what you want...
You will never return...
Our broken, matching mugs...
Thank you for waiting.
Here is your Russian takoyaki.
What? Russian?
I secretly ordered them earlier.
There you go again...
But it sounds fun.
Does one of them taste different?
Apparently it's full of mustard.
What? I don't want that.
That's why they're Russian.
The person who gets the mustard one
has to do something funny!
What?
I'm not good at that stuff...
It's okay! I'll start.
We'll eat them one at a time.
I hope it's not me...
It was spicy...
Good. I can eat without fear.
Is it good, Chinatsu-chan?
Yes! It's delicious!
Good.
But, why did she
invite me to see a movie all of a sudden?
This is the first time we've
hung out together, isn't it?
What? Y-You're right!
I felt bad we didn't get
to sing the duet you
wanted at the Christmas party.
It's totally fine.
Plus, you gave me those
chocolates and that scarf.
Oh, right.
I hadn't paid you
back for those, either.
Sorry it's taken so long.
Not at all! I wanted
to give you those.
I'm glad you came. Thanks.
I'm so glad I gave her that scarf!
I wish I could thank my past self!
I'll never forget how
Himawari-chan helped me!
If I don't enjoy this date,
I'll regret it forever!
Give it everything you have, Chinatsu!
What should we see?
Well, since we're on a date,
why don't we pick a
romantic movie?
This is a date?
It may be a date,
but we're both girls.
That might not make a romantic
film the best choice...
Action and crime films
are out of the question.
I wonder if Yui-senpai
likes anime?
Footsteps
Let's see this one!
That's a horror film.
I thought you didn't like scary movies?
I-I got over it!
Chinatsu-chan, I thought you got over
your fear of horror movies.
You're so mean.
But it's okay since
you're here, I guess.
I'll curse you to death!
It's perfect.
I've actually been too scared to ever see a horror movie,
Your movie is on screen 2.
but this is your chance to show
her your girlish charms, China!
Thank you.
Let's go, Chinatsu-chan.
Okay!
China's Romantic Horror Plan starts now!
Ow... Ow, my arm hurts. It hurts!
Chinatsu-chan, it's okay. Calm down.
Don't be scared, okay?
It was so scary, senpai! It was
so scary, I almost cried!
Yeah, it was scary...
For the wrong reason.
Oh no!
I was so scared, my plan to grab
onto Yui-senpai went to waste.
Chinatsu-chan, you were holding
my arm really tight.
Huh? I was?
Yeah...
It made my heart race.
She said holding on to her made her heart race!
I don't really remember what happened,
but doesn't that mean my
plan was a success?
I have a hand-shaped bruise...
I think I managed to get
closer to Yui-senpai.
This is going pretty well!
Oh, Toru.
Now that I've calmed down,
I have to wonder what an actual date is like.
Holding hands like that...
A real date...
But then, what's this?
Maybe it really is weird for
two girls to be together...
I'm going to buy this.
O-Okay.
No, what's with this negative attitude?
No one loves Yui-senpai more than me,
so I should have more confidence.
We should go home soon.
Did you have fun today?
Yes! So much fun!
Thanks for taking me to see a movie.
Did you have fun?
Yeah, I did.
The movie was scary, though...
I thought it was scary, too!
The day went by so quickly.
If only it could've
lasted a little longer...
Let's hang out together again sometime.
Really?
Chinatsu-chan, let's hurry.
We might miss the train!
Why was I being so hesitant?
Today has been wonderful.
Senpai...
Senpai, I love you!
Chinatsu-chan, the train!
Uh... Could you let go of my hand, now?
Oh Senpai, I love you, too!
Listen to me.
Yui-senpai...
Yui-senpai!
I'm your aggressive protagonist,
Yoshikawa Chinatsu.
Who're you calling aggressive?
I had so much fun on my
date with Yui-senpai!
If I had pursued her a bit
more aggressively at the end...
J-just kidding!