You're Old Now
A letter?
Kaizaki-sama
Must be Hishiro-san.
"Kaizaki-sama"? Really?
The 1,000 from yesterday?
Dunno why she did this.
She could have just handed it over to—
Thank you
for your help!
Hishiro Chizuru
Hishiro-san.
Good morning.
Uh, hi.
Um...
What the heck is this?
The 1,000 yen I borrowed yesterday.
Thank you so much.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Wh-What have you done to Hideyo?
It's quite... a curve ball.
I thought returning it normally
would be too serious and boring,
so I looked around the Internet for ideas
and found this amusing folding technique.
"This is it," I thought.
Well, it's hilarious!
When I opened this by the shoe lockers,
I damn near bust a gut.
Oh, my.
I did not consider the consequences.
My strategy was flawed.
I shall be more careful.
"Do not fold Hideyo."
Anyway, thanks for returning it.
It's not what you think.
I just find it cute that a high schooler
is awkwardly but earnestly trying to change.
It's like watching a kid sister grow up.
Mornin', Arata.
Morning... Wait, no honorific, huh?
Arata's easy to say!
Feel free to call me Kazu-kun.
Nah, Oga's fine. Easy to say.
Either way,
none of them will remember me
a year from now.
Wh-Why are your scores getting worse?!
We're truly ashamed.
Arata's scores don't surprise me,
but I thought An-chan
would at least pass one.
Hey, why don't my scores surprise you?
Because you always gossip
when we try to study!
Uh... point...
Got your hands full, Oga?
Help, Kariu!
They're the worst!
They keep derailing the conversation!
Like how?
Like asking if you and I are go—
What the hell are you trying to say?
Huh? I'm telling her about how you asked
if me and her were going out.
And why would you tell her that?
Are you stupid?!
W-Wow, stupid?
I just thought you two should
get an earful from her, too.
You're the one she'd be mad at, not us.
Huh? Why?
He's hopeless.
Huh?!
Oga-san.
Sensei asked both class reps
to come to the staff room.
R-Really?
Sorry, I didn't hear her.
So you really are dumb.
Dumber than I'd imagined, too.
Ouch!
I was better when I was actually in school!
Actually, I can do better than this.
Then do it!
Shut up!
I just... haven't put my mind to it yet.
Would that make a difference?
Right? Makes you sick, doesn't it?
I wouldn't go that far.
Oh, really?
Oga!
I am trying, you know!
Then try a bit harder.
Yeah! So will I!
Ah, youth.
But with math, they say that you should put
something down even if you have no idea.
Shall we go, Hishiro-san?
Okay, Oga-san.
That's too formal!
Just call me Kazu-kun!
Huh?
My given name's Kazuomi.
Then...
Kazu-kun.
Wow! You're the first person
to ever call me that!
I am?
Everyone says Oga is easier!
Hurray!
They might have a point.
I dunno, maybe try smiling a little more?
I've got to try harder to make friends.
Please wait, Kazu-kun.
You've got it wrong, Kariu.
She was trying for a friendly smile.
She didn't mean—
Nobody's that bad at smiling!
She's clearly making fun of me!
Yeah, I totally know how
you feel, but I mean it.
Arata-kun, are you friends with Hishiro-san?
Nah, we just talk sometimes.
And you're still covering for her?
You're so nice.
Oh, nah...
Come to think of it,
the other day at lunch, you loaned her...
Don't forget to write your name
on the record sheet.
National Fitness Test Averages
When did I last exercise?
Crap.
Girls start with the 50m dash.
Guys start with the handball toss.
Amatsu-sensei, could you not stand so close?
If we shout over each other,
nobody will hear us.
Usa-sensei, your voice is stupid loud,
so I'm sure it'll be fine.
If you've got a problem, move yourself.
Class 4's homeroom teacher, Usa-sensei,
was Amatsu-sensei's senior in college.
Oh? They're pretty close, huh?
Huh? How so?
Oga, you really suck at this stuff.
Let's go in order of roll number.
Starting with Asaji.
Here!
Set a record!
Huh? I... I'll try.
45 meters!
Okay. Thanks.
What's the average for third-year boys?
28 meters?!
Way too high a record
to start with, Asaji-kun!
Well, the dude is well built.
Kids these days are in great shape.
Wish I was, too.
Next, Inukai!
Here.
Good luck!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Where are you aiming, Aki?
I saw a guy not paying attention,
so I figured I'd teach him that
looking away can be dangerous.
Maybe use your words instead?
What's with that guy? He's terrifying!
Do it right, Inukai!
Next, Oga!
Yo!
Inukai-kun threw that really hard, too.
So far, both guys have been
far above average.
Is this national average even accurate?
Two meters!
You never change, Oga.
Maybe take a break from studying
and work out?
Don't be mean, Sensei!
What can I do?
I wasn't born athletic!
Next, Kaizaki!
Oh, what's this?
Looks like you aren't so good at sports.
Oh, shut up!
Let's see how you do! Go throw!
I was always pretty decent at this stuff.
I grew up in the country!
I'll show these wimpy city kids...!
What's wrong, Kaizaki?
One meter!
M-My shoulder won't rotate!
What the...
When did I get this stiff?
You okay?
I... I will be.
Adults need to warm up first,
or they'll hurt themselves.
Y-You okay, Kaizaki-kun?
I'm the health rep.
Want me to take you
to the nurse's office?
Leave him be, Nobu.
He'll be fine if he puts some spit on it.
Aki, I don't think that works
for shoulder injuries.
Don't worry about me. I'll be fine.
Really? But if you need anything, just ask.
Are you a girl?
Pathetic...
1st Throw Records
Oga: 2m
Kaizaki: 1m
Arata-kun, not only are you stupid,
you also suck at sports?
Shut up. I'm not like you.
You're too young to be as bad as you are.
We're the same age!
Don't be ridiculous!
What is it, Yoake?
Oh, nothing.
On your marks!
Lane 4, 7.38 seconds.
Lane 3, 8.22 seconds!
You're fast, Rena-chan!
Thanks.
Huh...
Kariu's fast!
She's really athletic, yeah.
Unlike you?
You're gonna make me cry.
But watch the next girl.
Which one?
Closest to us.
On your marks!
Lane 4, 6.78 seconds.
So fast!
right?
Tamarai-san's crazy athletic.
She's the volleyball team captain.
And Kariu's the vice captain.
I'm on the volleyball team!
Bet that's rough for her.
Huh?
Rena!
How'd you do?
I knew it! You're really fast!
But really slow compared to you.
Oh, come on.
You don't have to compare yourself to others!
I can't help being competitive.
I always want to be first.
Oh... I'm sorry.
Don't apologize! That's even more irritating!
"Irritating"?
Don't say stuff like that!
Get your boobs off me!
Looks like Kariu-san
and Tamarai-san get along okay.
Why wouldn't they?
They even eat lunch together.
Didn't Kariu say that the other day?
Oh, right.
Rivals aren't always enemies, huh?
Even so...
...two girls cuddling sure is nice!
It's a sight for sore eyes!
This is what having legal high school girls—
Hey!
You were just leering at Tama, weren't you?
O-O-Ow!
Aki!
I'm sorry, Kaizaki-kun.
He just gets awfully worked up
where Tama-chan's concerned...
I'm really sorry.
"Tama-chan"?
Tamarai-san.
Those two and Tamarai-san
have known each other since kindergarten.
Oh...
And Tamarai-san and Inukai-kun
are going out, or something?
Dunno.
It was dumb to even ask you.
Um...
You, the redhead who ran 7.38 seconds.
Huh?
What? You were talking to me?
Use my name!
Why would you remember my time?
Spite?!
Spite? How so?
It's a pretty good time.
As for your name, I'm sorry.
I don't know it, so I couldn't use it.
You're kidding.
We were on the class rep
committee all of last year.
I was the Class 1 rep...
This girl!
Sorry, but I just don't remember it.
Would you tell me your name?
What the...?
What's with this mocking, victorious smirk?!
Am I not even worth remembering?
Kariu.
Kariu Rena.
It's my pleasure, Hishiro Chizuru-san.
I'll remember.
And thank you.
It's almost my turn.
I spoke to you because I need you
to take over stopwatch duty.
Oh.
But why me?
You were standing nearby.
Is this girl for real?
On your marks!
I never imagined she wouldn't
even remember my name.
And here I thought we were rivals.
I'm a fool.
Okay, we're doing 50m sprints next.
Move out!
Yoake-san.
Can I see your chart?
Go ahead.
What the? It's like you deliberately
scored the average.
I'm surprised you can even manage that.
This is my second year as a student.
I'm not out of shape, like you are.
Well, getting that rusty body
back in shape is part of ReLIFE.
But you'd better remember that your body
isn't young before you hurt yourself.
I know the youth around you
gets you all fired up.
But you're old now.
Shut up! Twenty-seven isn't that old!
Unless I say it myself!
But you don't want others to say so?
You're at a delicate age, huh?
And you were actually leering
at those girls, right?
Inukai went after you for it.
We won't stop love,
but please... no crimes.
I wouldn't!
If I don't warm up,
it'll be a repeat of the ball mess.
I might even get a cramp...
And, in the worst-case scenario,
snap my Achilles tendon.
For real.
Ready!
I don't see anyone in front...
I'm in the lead?
Cool, I can still run—
Kaizaki!
I... I remember this...
At kindergarten or grade school
sports festivals,
there are dads
who get all fired up to run
but lose their balance
and fall flat on their faces.
Like I just did.
Are you okay, Kaizaki-kun?
A-Asaji-kun...
I'm fine...
Damn, that's gory! You're not fine!
I'll take you to the
nurse's office. Get on.
Uh, but...
I'm really okay...
You clearly aren't okay! Come on!
Usa-sensei, we'll be in the nurse's office.
A-Asaji-kun! Put me down!
Don't worry, I'm strong enough!
That's not the problem!
Princess-carried by a dude
ten years younger...
Just throw me away!
Huh? What's up with the boys?
Dunno.
Looks like Arata-kun
tripped and hurt himself.
That's so lame!
Mornin'.
Good morning, Kaizaki-san.
You walk to school?
Yes, from the station.
Me, too.
Are you always alone?
You never come with anyone?
Is that bad? Weird?
Nobody said it was.
I mean, I'm alone, too.
Well, you just transferred here.
That hasn't healed yet?
Uh, yeah...
It's been a while, but it hasn't...
Is that the natural healing power
of a high school student?
M-Maybe so?
My knee still throbs, too.
I wouldn't know.
I haven't fallen down since grade school.
Right.
Huh? Kaizaki and Hishiro...
What the hell?! She can smile just fine!
So what was that before?
Mornin', Kariu.
Mor...
Good morning,
Kariu-san.
I get it.
She pretends to be serious.
I didn't think she was the type.
But she acts nice around the boys.
The other day, we had a physical fitness test.
I'd explained to him before that he only looked
young, and inside, he was still twenty-seven.
Perhaps it wasn't easy to adjust,
even though he knew in his head,
so he hurt himself badly.
He seemed quite unhappy to have kids
ten years younger feeling sorry for him,
but it's helped him find his place in the class.
Oga Kazuomi
Kariu Rena
It's pretty clear now which
classmates he gets along with.
It's been a month since he started school.
It's not easy to form a community
that fast with high school kids.
One month since the experiment began.
April 25th
Nothing special happened today, again.
Still isn't fitting in with the class.
Still getting used to the high school experience.
I'll keep watch, patiently.
Nothing special happened today.
April 26th
Nothing worth reporting happened today, either.
Nothing worth reporting
happened today, either.
April 27th
No change today, either
Quite a gap between
samples no. 001 and 002.
He seemed quite unhappy to have kids
ten years younger feeling sorry for him,
but it's helped him find his place in the class.
He's had his share of mishaps,
but his ReLIFE appears to be progressing well.
He's smiling more than he did as a NEET.
Still...
And I think Kaizaki-san's
aware of it, as well...
The immediate concern is...
Kariu Rena
NEXT EPISODE
I can't believe I lost to Honoka
in all the fitness tests.
But you're smart! I wish I could say
the same for myself.
Yeah, you're pretty dumb.
You meanie!
Want me to tutor you?
Fall
No thanks.
You're too Spartan.