May 7th
After spending the rest of Golden Week studying
with Oga Kazuomi and Onoya An (Support Division),
Kaizaki Arata passed his fourth round of make-up tests.
These make-ups are from a school far better
than his actual ability, so this is impressive.
As I've written above,
ReLIFE is fraught with trouble.
But each time Kaizaki Arata
demonstrates remorse,
and attempts to improve...
As I've written above, ReLIFE is fraught with trouble.
But each time Kaizaki Arata demonstrates remorse,
and attempts to improve...
We've heard some disturbing rumors.
Specifically, that you're getting
unnecessarily close to the subjects.
Have you forgotten you are only Support?
I know it's your first,
and you want to rush things.
But that's no excuse for driving the subject
into a corner with unwarranted advice.
You can't get emotionally involved.
You'll undermine the ReLIFE process.
Right...
Have a good long think about your role here.
Decide who Yoake Ryo
should be to subject no. 001.
Test Subject 001 -> 002
Calling
Hello?
What's the matter? Is there a problem?
ReLIFE Experiment Report
I see.
Naturally, we are already aware of that.
But that's not a problem I can solve.
The goal of ReLIFE is to give you experience.
To let you grow through
your own thoughts and actions.
If I get too involved,
it will have no value as an experiment.
There's no need to rush things.
Hang in there.
Yes.
Well, then, goodbye.
The subject called.
Asking for advice is, technically, a change.
But I can't say for sure if it's a good sign.
I'll maintain my distance and observe...
Yeah, yeah, I'm about to send the report...
Suitability evaluation?
Subject... 002...
Welcome!
Kaizaki Arata. Twenty-seven.
Sociable and helpful,
but unable to get steady work.
Half shut-in.
Prime candidate for subject no. 002.
He's serious.
A little gloomy looking, but...
But I guess that's not unusual
late-night convenience store service.
Welcome.
Want me to warm that up?
Nah, it's my breakfast.
That'll be 627 yen.
Do you have a point card?
Nah, I'm good.
Exact change.
Thank you!
Sir!
Have you dropped your wallet?
Whoa, thank you!
You're a life-saver!
Don't mention it.
Please take care.
I thought I put it somewhere
hard for him to spot.
He sure saw it fast.
Watches his surroundings.
Takes action.
Not bad.
A completely different type
from subject no. 001.
Senpai!
Onoya? You came?
What are you doing here?
Eval on Kaizaki Arata.
Why you, Senpai?
I want to be his support!
Are you trying to snatch him from me?
That accusation hurts.
It was orders from above.
"Check out your junior's candidate."
Oh, is that all?
What'd you think of him?
Seems like a good guy, huh?
Are we gonna start him in the third year?
Looks like he'll have no problems
socially, so that'd work fine.
And how are you doing with subject no. 001?
I'm doing my job.
Just the way the bosses want me to.
Not that!
I'm asking if the experiment
will succeed or not...
Well, who knows?
We're talking about a human being here.
You never know what'll happen.
What can you do to get results?
How far can you push things?
It's hard to find the right distance.
ReLIFE Experiment Report
Handler: Yoake Ryo
Subject:
There was so much potential.
How could this happen?
Our branch's first subject,
and this is the result?
I'm ashamed to show my face
around the other branches.
ReLIFE Experiment Reports
A whole year without any change...
Did you not do enough
to support the subject?
ReLIFE Experiment Report
Handler: Yoake Ryo
Subject:
Senpai...
I've observed you for a year
and reported on it.
But it seems like we'll be unable
to set you up with any work.
I apologize.
My support wasn't good enough.
What should I have done?
They told me I was too involved.
So I stepped back.
Then they told me I didn't do enough.
A few minutes ago,
we received word that they've picked
Kaizaki Arata-san as subject no. 002.
And his support...
Change of support for the start of
the Kanto Branch's subject no. 002 experiment.
Support: Yoake Ryo
...was Yoake Ryo.
It was you.
They said to start prepping at once.
You don't have time to mope!
Subject no. 002, Kaizaki Arata.
Onoya must be pissed at me.
She really wanted to support
this test subject,
and I wound up snatching him anyway.
But it's my job.
Gotta deal with it.
Whoa, wai—
How did my life turn out like this?
Good evening.
Nice to meet you, Kaizaki Arata-san.
I'm Yoake Ryo,
from the ReLIFE Laboratory.
Will you become a student for a year and
see this as a chance to change your life?
Or will you get cold feet, back out,
and keep living as a NEET?
The choice is yours, Kaizaki-san.
It was rough on you, right?
Pretending you had a real job
in front of your friends.
If you're ready to accept,
please sign the contract.
Here's to a good ReLIFE.
This man...
I wonder...
What kind of ReLIFE will he show me?
Coming!
You've got a lot of nerve making
your senpai work like this, Onoya.
Sorry!
You were at the lab and coming here anyway,
so I figured you could bring it
while you were at it.
It was too heavy and too far
to bring "while I was at it."
Well, come on in.
I'll make some coffee as a thank you.
Support Division
Onoya An
Aoba High
Uniform, Textbooks
A sailor suit!
This takes me back!
My actual high school
also had sailor uniforms.
Never thought I'd wear one again at my age.
I know, right,
old bag.
If I'm an old bag,
that makes you a geezer.
I'm really looking forward to this!
I never imagined that starting April,
I'd be in the same school
and same class as you!
That's hilarious!
How was Kaizaki-san?
Huh?
Subject no. 002, Kaizaki Arata-san!
You met with him today, right?
He signed the contract.
Think you'll work well with him?
That's our job as support.
Damn right, Senpai!
Man, you really get on my nerves.
Huh? Why?
Well, you don't need to worry
about Kaizaki-san.
We already made sure
his personality wouldn't be a problem.
Yeah.
But...
I think people like that
have problems that run deep.
The trauma of thinking you
might have been the reason
that you lost someone you cared about
doesn't go away easily.
"Was there more I could have done?"
"Perhaps I shouldn't have
done anything at all?"
Now that he has no way
of knowing for sure,
Kaizaki-san has lost confidence
in his social skills.
Normally, he'd go way out
on a limb for someone, but...
But isn't that what
makes him perfect for ReLIFE?
ReLIFE will help Kaizaki-san
get his confidence back.
It'll be fine.
You guys can do it together.
I sure hope so.
Onoya, you're really flattering me today.
Huh? Am I?
It's creepy.
What? I'm just cheering you on!
See? Creepy.
You're so mean!
Hello, Kaizaki-san!
What do you need this late?
Sorry...
I need to talk to you about something.
Medicine to turn you back...?
I let everyone know I wouldn't
see 'em for a year, but...
But I can't just call in to quit my job.
Just cut them loose.
I could never...!
What's wrong with you?
Okay, got it.
I'll request the medicine.
It'll be a day or two, though.
Okay, that's fine.
Goodbye, then.
Research and Development
Hello!
Amagase-san, I have a medicine request.
You're here a lot lately.
Doing all right, Yoake?
One present and one past
for subject no. 002.
Medicine Request
And one of each for you?
I'll meet the subject
to hand over the medicine,
so I'd like to look my age.
Why bother?
Just go as you are.
No, no!
I don't want him to see me like this
until I surprise him
on the first day of school!
I can't wait to see the look on his face!
Well, that's the official reason.
I just think if he knows the support
will be in class with him,
he won't stress about it enough.
You've thought it through.
That is my job.
I'll drop by tomorrow to pick them up.
Thank you!
Sure thing.
You look wiped.
Yeah... that was stressful.
Stressful?
It was just a part-time job.
But the boss was nice.
Helped me out a lot.
I feel guilty quitting.
Thanks for going along with this.
Now I can go back to school
without any regrets.
You're just gonna take it here?
Takes a while for it to kick in, right?
You're gung-ho about this.
I-I'd better be!
I even quit my job.
I don't have any other options.
I'm just gonna hunker down
and let the year go by.
That's all.
Not exactly gung-ho.
Got it.
It's in the documents I gave you,
but you'll get really sleepy shortly
after taking that, so be careful.
I'd advise you not to drive anywhere.
I don't have a car!
But, uh...
I have plans after this...
You're so thoughtless.
Isn't it your fault for not
explaining it to me properly?!
Fair enough!
Fair enough?!
You should really read the documents.
But each time Kaizaki Arata
demonstrates remorse,
and attempts to improve...
...and that forward-thinking
nature is infectious.
He's starting to change things around him.
What effect will that have
on Kaizaki Arata's ReLIFE?
It makes me want to keep watching
and living a student's life with them.
NEXT EPISODE
Yoake-san, what do you usually do?
What do you mean?
I mean, what do you do when
you're not supporting me?
I keep thinking about you, of course!
Rift
Huh?
Is that what you want me to say?
Hell, no!