How many did you fail?
Seven. Will I have to
take make-ups again?
After failing that many, you must be
crazy to hope for no make-ups.
How'd you do, An-chan?
Seems like you did okay?
I passed everything this time!
Whoa! Awesome!
Hard to believe you got a two
on math last time!
Sorry I passed without you, Arata-kun.
You traitor...
If you failed more than three,
you get make-ups.
If that's you, come see me after school.
Have fun!
Rift
Staff Room
Are you okay, Kaizaki-kun?
That isn't the word I'd use.
At all.
Class 3-3 Roll no.4 Kaizaki Arata
1st Mid-Term Report Card
Were you sick or something?
Nope. That's how I did
in the pink of health.
Were you entering answers
in the wrong fields?
Did you study the wrong things?
Sensei, please face reality.
I made no mistakes, and this is the result.
I'm sorry.
Well, last time you didn't give up
and took the make-ups until you passed.
So I think you'll be fine.
Hang in there!
Yeah...
I could have gotten sick of it,
given up, and run away.
Maybe... I am starting to change.
Though I might have run
if I'd been alone.
Excuse me!
There you are, Honoka.
Here I am...
Kaizaki-kun, this is our captain.
Oh, you're the coach of the volleyball team?
Yeah.
Hey there, Kaizaki-kun.
I hear you're always
helping Rena out.
No, she's the one helping me.
So, you failed five, Honoka?
Gimme a break here.
Sorry.
If the captain's too busy taking make-ups
to play, it'll set a bad example!
Make sure you pass these next week!
Uh, I'll try!
Oh, she's the same as me?
The tournament in June is the
last time you third-years will play.
Without you, we might well
get eliminated in round one!
Please, do your best to pass.
Don't worry. It's a team sport.
Even if I'm not there, they'll—
Honoka!
Trusting your teammates is good.
But they can't replace you.
Maybe that puts pressure on you,
but you're just that good,
and we all know it.
Have more confidence.
Don't be so willing to hand over
your spot to someone else.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Troubled, Amatsu-sensei?
As good as she is,
she just lacks appetite.
Or maybe confidence?
Power that's too great
destroys its surroundings.
Huh?
Anyway, I wish the boys' volleyball team
had that kind of problem.
Yeah, you guys suck.
I hope you at least make it
past the first round this year.
Don't badmouth them!
They're doing the best they can!
Tamarai-san, you didn't have to
take make-ups last time, right?
There were only three subjects last time.
But the mid-terms and finals have so many...
Ah, I see...
I'm here on a sports scholarship.
So I'm not the best at studying.
Don't they cut scholarship athletes
a little slack on that?
Exempt you from make-ups,
or something?
Nope.
It's a prep school.
Sports aren't really a big thing here.
Then why choose Aoba?
Couldn't you have gone to
a school with a better team?
Sorry. None of my business, huh?
N-Nah, it's okay.
Sorry, I just spaced out.
I picked Aoba because Aki-chan
and Nobu-chan were going here,
and I thought, "I'll go with them!"
Aki-chan? Nobu-chan?
Oh, Inukai-kun and Asaji-kun.
Oh, your childhood friends?
Huh? Oh, wow!
I've never talked to you before.
I'm surprised you knew.
Kariu and Oga talk about you a lot.
You and Kariu are pretty close?
Yeah!
Thanks to Rena, high school volleyball
has been super fun!
I can't thank her enough!
Oh, I'm headed to practice now.
Okay.
Oh, right. There's something
I've been wanting to ask you.
Does Onoya-san have, like,
a crush on Oga-kun or what?
Pretty sure she doesn't.
Really?
Yep. I'm sure.
Ah, youth...
Hishiro-san. You're still here?
Kaizaki-san...
Were you called to the staff room again?
So how have you been?
How... you ask?
You've been eating lunch
with Kariu and Tamarai-san.
That's great.
You're making more friends.
Yes.
Thanks to you.
Ah! She looks happy.
Kariu-san and Tamarai-san
are both really nice,
and get along so well,
it kinda makes me jealous.
Hishiro-san?
Sorry. My consciousness left me.
That sounds bad.
You seem like you've gotten used to school
and are enjoying yourself.
Do I?
I'm barely hanging on.
With all these make-ups,
I've done nothing but take tests.
Oh, that's right.
Um... uh...
She's always with you...
the four-eyed braid girl...
Oh, An?
That's right, An-san.
Does An-san...
...have a crush on Kazu-kun?
Huh?
I don't think she does.
Is that so?
See, Kariu?
You can't beat Tamarai-san at sports
or Hishiro-san at studying,
so you drove yourself into a corner,
but they both love you.
Headed home, Hishiro-san?
Yes.
Wanna walk with me to the station?
Yes, sir.
Am I your captain now?
Aye-aye, sir!
Why'd you suddenly yell?
I thought you wanted me to.
Stop it! The deadpan jokes are killing me!
Sorry.
Kariu-senpai.
We don't need to put the net away, right?
Yeah, I'll still be using it.
Honoka, are you staying for more?
Not today.
I've gotta get home and study.
Yeah.
Oh. That's right, Rena!
Apparently Onoya-san doesn't
have a crush on Oga-kun.
Huh?!
I asked Kaizaki-kun.
What? You asked that idiot?!
I never...!
There, there.
See ya!
Idiot.
She should be focused
on her studying, not me.
..the last time you third-years will play.
This team can only play together
for three more weeks.
I've gotta pass those make-ups fast!
Was there an umbrella in the clubroom?
Wasn't Tamarai-senpai late today?
Oh, apparently she ends up having to take
make-ups every time there are tests.
And that's okay?
As good as she is, she probably
doesn't need to practice.
You can say that again!
Maybe.
Stop trying so hard!
You keep getting better, and I can't—
Whatever! You're still going
to the tournament!
Must be nice to have talent.
Must be nice.
Most people wouldn't be allowed to play
if they kept failing like that.
But she's a starter and the captain.
Well, she's just that good.
I bet it pisses Kariu-senpai off.
Yeah, for sure!
Just 'cause she's talented.
Kariu-senpai...
Rena?
Honoka practices after you all go home,
every single day.
She loves volleyball more than anything.
She has trouble keeping her grades up,
but she works her ass off at that, too.
Yeah, her raw talent is amazing,
and I'm jealous.
But because I know that's not all she is,
and because I know the work
she puts in, I respect her.
And that's why I work so hard.
Before you start bitching,
maybe try harder than her?
She's got more talent than you, so why
would you let her beat you in effort?
Excuse me!
Sorry!
Bye!
H-Hey!
Why wouldn't that make them
stay for more practice?
Hard to get fired up all alone...
Thanks to Rena, high school volleyball
has been super fun!
Thank you, Rena.
Hey there, Tama-chan.
Ah, Sumire-chan!
Thanks for having me.
Studying for make-ups?
Good, good.
I wanna get them over with
so I can focus on practice.
We can't play together much longer.
Well, if he's useful,
use him all you like!
What are you doing? Stop that!
Okay. Good luck!
Right!
Should I call Nobu?
He's better then me at—
No, don't.
You're more at my level,
which is perfect.
Am I?
And I figure Nobu-chan
will be in bed already.
Zzz...
Yeah, he's like an old man.
The tournament is on
June 15th and 16th, right?
Yup.
I'll be there.
Nobu, too.
Huh? But we're not a strong team,
not like in junior high.
I know.
That's not why I wanna go.
Honestly, I couldn't be bothered
to watch in junior high.
But now...
...you're having fun.
You seem so alive playing with them.
Nobu and I both wanna see that.
We'll be there.
Okay!
I'll play my best!
Cool.
But first, make-ups.
Right.
Hello.
Congratulations on your make-ups!
It ain't a good thing!
Oh? But because you got
summoned to the staff room,
you could leave at
the same time as Hishiro-san
and have an after-school date!
We just walked to the station together!
What's your plan this time?
Huh? I haven't got any plan.
I'll just have to push through it
with Oga's help.
I was trying to study on my own just now.
Well, well. Keep up the—
If you're in trouble, remember I'm here!
Ask me anytime!
An?
Is An with you, Yoake-san?
Yes... we're at work.
I sit next to him!
Shut up and go away.
Okay, Kaizaki-san, see you tomorrow!
Huh? I still wanna talk—
Goodbye now!
Ah, wait, wait... ah!
What the... do they like each other, or not?
What did he call about, anyway?
Okay.
Let's do this.
Mid-term Make-ups
I've finished grading your tests.
Tamarai-san.
You passed.
Thank goodness!
Kaizaki-kun...
...see you next week.
Yeah...
Bye bye, Kaizaki-kun!
Crap!
I'm off to practice!
See you tomorrow!
Wait, Tama-chan...
You're awfully pale.
You've been at our place
every night this week.
Did you get enough sleep?
I'm fine, Sumire-chan.
Don't push yourself.
Okay. Thanks!
Excuse me!
"Tama-chan"?
"Sumire-chan"?
How'd the make-ups go?
Did you fail?
Don't look so happy.
I did.
Hey.
How'd Tama do?
T-Tamarai-san?
She passed and went to practice.
Okay. Thanks.
How can you be so arrogant, you brat?!
Good for Tama-chan!
She looked so pale this morning.
I'm relieved!
Nice spike!
It's no use. Every hit is weak.
And my mind's not in it, either.
Maybe I should go home early...
Tamarai-senpai!
Tamarai-senpai! Are you okay?
Sorry...
Everything went black for a—
I'm okay now.
Kariu-senpai!
Kariu! What's wrong?
She tried to avoid a rolling ball, and—
Call the nurse! Now!
Right!
Rena! Are you okay? Can you stand?
Rena!
Nurse's Office
It's sprained.
The bone seems fine,
but make sure you go
to a hospital tomorrow.
How long to recover?
Well...
Most likely two or three weeks.
But that's—
Kariu-san.
Is there anyone at home right now?
Yes.
Then let's have them come get you.
I'll go call them.
Rena...
Rena.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
People get injured in practice
all the time.
I tried to avoid the ball
and lost my balance.
That's on me.
But it was my fault
the ball was even there!
If I hadn't—
I know that!
But you would have dodged it just fine.
It's my fault.
B-But...
If it's only two weeks,
you'll make the tournament.
I hope you get better soon.
It's our last—
No.
If it's three weeks, I won't make it.
Even if it heals in two,
I can't play in a tournament
without practice.
I can't.
You can, Rena! You'll make up
for two weeks in no time!
I said I can't!
I'm no genius!
I work and I work,
and I'm barely good enough!
But I guess you wouldn't understand!
If I'm not there,
it won't affect the team at all!
As long as you're there,
we'll win! I don't matter!
Why...?
Why?
Tama?
What are you doing here?
Are you done with practice?
We were headed over. We thought
you might be wrapping up.
Tama-chan?
Aki!
NEXT EPISODE
Nobu, you can come with me
to watch Tama play, right?
Of course! We'd better practice!
One, two...
"Hooray! Hooray! Tama-chan!"
Come on, Aki.
"Do your best, Tama-chan!"
Revenge
You listening to me, Aki?
What's the matter?
Learn to take a hint, Nobu.