New Wagashi Revives Town
Spring Comes to Kamogawa
New Anti-NEET Strategy
Labor Ministry
Emergency Funding
The Labor Ministry has
allocated special funding
Nah.
I'm about done for the day, too.
to combat the rise in NEETs and shut-ins.
I guess.
This will help support their
return to normal society, and...
Yeah.
Drinks? Now?
Okay.
Sounds good.
It's been a while, huh?
Oh, yeah, sorry.
Yeah, sure.
By the station, right?
I'm leaving work now.
See you in fifteen.
Yeah.
Okay, see you there.
Kaizaki Arata (27), Unemployed
Kaizaki Arata-san.
Yes!
You quit your first job after three months?
What happened?
Well, it just wasn't the
right direction for me.
I felt I could live up to
my potential elsewhere.
You knew that in just three months?
The ability to make such decisions and
take initiative is also my strong point.
Arata?
Anything going on where you work?
My sister's getting married.
I'm hanging in there, I guess.
Hanging in where?
Mom
Hello?
Well, how'd the interview go?
No good.
Huh? Why?!
Don't ask me. It just didn't work out.
I hate to kick you when you're down...
Oh, goody.
We ain't sendin' you any money
from next month.
What? Why?!
Where'd this come from?
Son, you're twenty-seven.
High time you stood on your own feet.
That's all. Bye.
Whoa, wai—
How did my life turn out like this?
Good evening.
Nice to meet you, Kaizaki Arata-san.
Two-year gap before college.
Finished grad school with a job lined up.
But you quit that job in only three months.
While you work part-time to make ends meet,
you're twenty-seven and have no steady job.
No—
Am I right?
Um...
Who're you?
I beg your pardon.
Where are my manners?
I'm Yoake Ryo,
from the ReLIFE Laboratory.
Something smells fishy.
How rude. That's my real name.
I'll cut right to the chase.
You've been selected as
a test subject for ReLIFE.
Huh?
We'd like your help with an experiment.
ReLIFE?
The experiment will last for one year.
We'll pay for all living expenses
during that time.
Huh?
And, depending on how things go,
we might hook you up with a job afterward.
Seriously?!
Yes.
E-Experiment?
What exactly will I be doing?
Oh, I'm thrilled!
Do I have your attention now?
What's this?
Something's off.
I look a little younge—
ReLIFE Laboratory...
A drug we developed...
You've been selected...
Take this, and you'll look like you're in...
Like you're in high school again!
For a year starting this spring...
...we want you to be a student,
and go back to high school!
Why'd I take it?!
Who in their right mind would?
It's way too fishy!
No way...
Hello?
Oh, good morning!
I see you took the pill already.
I was drunk.
I don't even remember taking it.
That's a deadbeat for you.
Dead—
Well, enough standing around.
Please, come in.
It's my place!
So, that pretty much covers
the school you'll be attending.
Like I said yesterday,
we'll pay for all living expenses.
Really? All of it?
Of course.
High schooler, huh...
Bit late for that, isn't it?
And going to school every day
for a year sounds like a pain.
You're thinking high school
sounds like a pain, aren't you?
Will you become a student for a year and
see this as a chance to change your life?
Or will you get cold feet, back out,
and keep living as a NEET?
The choice is yours, Kaizaki-san.
I'm not a NEET.
It was rough on you, right?
Pretending you had a real job
in front of your friends.
Stab
Stab!
If you're ready to accept,
please sign the contract.
None of this seems real at all.
But I've come too far to turn back!
I can live off this for a year,
and if all goes well,
I'll get a job after that!
Fine, you're on!
I'll do this ReLIFE thing!
Great. Here's to a good ReLIFE.
Thank you.
Oh, good morning!
I don't belong here...
Hey! Good morning!
Good morning!
First year would be one thing,
but I'm starting out in third?
No. Stop freaking out.
They're kids. Ten years younger.
Good. Secured a seat in the back.
Um...
That's my seat.
The names are posted on the blackboard.
We've been assigned seats
according to our roll numbers.
O-Oh, is that so?
Thank you.
Sorry for troubling you.
Already embarrassed myself!
And I accidentally used formal speech!
Here.
Fourth seat, window row.
Yo, Yoake!
We're in the same class again!
Yeah. Let's have another good year.
Yoake?
Nice to see a familiar face!
What?!
H-Hey!
Okay, take your seats!
Amatsu Kokoro
I'm Amatsu, your homeroom teacher.
P.E.'s my subject.
I'm a bit nervous because I've never
been in charge of third years before,
but let's make it a good year.
So young.
She might even be younger than me.
Well, it's the first day.
Introductions are in order.
Asaji-kun.
Yes.
And Yoake-kun.
Whoever wins rock-paper-scissors starts.
One, two...
Rock, paper, scissors!
Oh, I won.
I'm Yoake Ryo.
I was in Class 3 in second year, too.
Huh?
I'm not in any clubs.
Pleased to meet you.
"In second year, too"?
He was a student here last year, too?
What does that mean?
Is he not really a grown-up?
Is he actually a high schooler?
No, no, no.
That girl...
I'm Hishiro Chizuru.
I was in Class 2-3.
I'm not in any clubs.
Pleased to meet you.
Talk about unfriendly.
That's Hishiro-san?
Last year's top student?
Yep, yep.
Oh.
I remember her type.
Good little scholars.
A year surrounded by these
bright, young things.
Should I really be here?
This is fraud! Trespassing!
Kaizaki-kun.
Kaizaki-kun, you're next!
Right!
I'm Kaizaki Arata.
I just transferred in this year.
So I haven't joined a club.
I'm nervous because I'm in a new
environment, but I hope to have
a great year with you all.
A transfer student?
Why is he so formal?
Introductions are a piece of cake.
I'm Kariu Rena.
Excuse me. I have a bit of a cold.
I'm on the volleyball team.
Nice to meet you.
Guess I should start with remembering
the names of the people sitting near me.
Kariu. The cougher.
I'm Oga Kazuomi. Part of
the Going Straight Home Club.
Glad to meet you all.
Oga the showy.
Showga?
I'm Onoya An.
I transferred in this year, too.
I already got lost on the way here
and was late for school.
But it's great to be here.
Guess I'm not the only transfer student.
As fellow transfer students,
let's help each other out, Kaizaki-kun.
Uh, yeah, sounds good.
Transfer buddy, Onoya.
Buddy?
Wait...
I...
High School
Girls
I can legally be friends
with high school girls?
Legal
Crap, I'm getting excited!
Well, now that we're done
with the introductions...
Japanese
Math
English
Let's get the tests started!
Tests? I wasn't told about this!
Clear your desks.
I don't want to see
anything but stationery.
But, hey, I went to grad school.
I'm a grown-up.
Maybe I'll actually do all right.
I forgot my pencil box!
Students always have one in their bag.
When do adults forget that habit?
What are you doing, Kaizaki-kun?
Put that bag away.
Um, I...
Well, uh...
Kaizaki-kun, let me
take a look at your bag.
Huh? Oh, go ahead.
Oh, I get it.
She thinks I'm trying to cheat.
But there's nothing in there.
Kaizaki-kun...
What is this?
A pack of cigarettes. What about it?
"What about it"?!
What's with them? It's just cigarettes...
N-N-N-N-No, this is just...
Right! I just brought it out of habit!
"Out of habit"?
Let's start the test.
Kaizaki-kun.
You. Staff room. After school.
Right.
A delinquent?
Didn't see that coming!
He's kinda scary...
Worst first day ever...
Shamed in front of everyone...
Hello?
You okay?
Pass these back.
Right.
Here.
Wait, take one for yourself!
Him again?
Sorry.
What is wrong with him?
Okay! Begin!
Okay, I've gotta use these tests
to reclaim my good name...
No pencil box!
I can't tell the teacher now!
What do I do?!
Kariu-san?
Thanks.
Okay, break time.
Um, Kariu-san.
Thanks.
I was in real trouble there.
No biggie. Feel free to keep 'em
till the tests are over...
You okay?
Fine.
Maybe you should have stayed home.
And miss the first day? Don't be stupid.
Stu—
And...
I can't miss these tests, no matter what.
Kariu really hates losing.
Who asked you?
These tests decide who gets to be class rep.
Kariu held that position
for all of last year.
She always had the top score in our class.
Wow.
But this year,
she's in the same class as Hishiro-san,
the top scorer in our grade.
So she's all fired up now
and couldn't call in sick.
Quit running your mouths!
Sorry!
Why me, too?
Shut up!
Bye, Sensei!
See you tomorrow!
Finished...
In every sense of the word...
I couldn't answer anything...
Did I ever understand that stuff?
I'm not so sure anymore.
I should go home...
Go home, chug some beers,
and sleep.
You'd better not be running.
Staff Room
I forgot...
Aoba High Apology Letter
For crying out loud!
You are way too young to be smoking!
These things'll kill you!
When you grow up,
you'll definitely regret it.
Grown-up
Uh-huh...
Don't give me that!
Sorry!
Do you really get it?
If you make a habit out of smoking,
you'll get addicted!
It's especially easy to
get hooked at your age!
You won't be able to quit!
Amatsu-sensei, how old are you?
Wh-Where'd that come from?
I'll be twenty-five this year.
Yup, she's younger.
Wow, you're young.
So?
If you're looking down on me 'cause I'm young,
I'll knock your lights out.
I-I didn't mean it like that!
Kids like you must think
twenty-five is super old.
28 this year
Did someone tell you that?
Rude!
But no, I actually think it's impressive.
You're so young,
but you have a proper job.
You're a proper teacher.
I truly respect that.
Thanks.
Truth is, often people don't take me
seriously because of my age.
So having you say that is pretty nice.
Thanks.
Kaizaki-kun.
Thank you, Kaizaki-kun.
But...
You're still not worming
your way out of this!
Here, write an apology letter.
I want it tomorrow.
O-Okay.
Pathetic...
Yeah, pathetic.
You!
Your first day was a disaster.
And whose fault was that?!
Your own, don't you think?
Which is the real you?
The high schooler or the grown-up?
Gee, I wonder.
Which do you think?
Gross! Like girls who ask
how old you think they are!
I'm a grown-up.
It's my job to observe and
report about your year here.
The rules say the handler
must turn back the clock
and support the subject as a fellow student.
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, I just wanted to see that
look of shock on your face!
You sadist!
Then what was that about
being in Class 2-3?
Why were you a student last year?
Training.
Training?
Can't have the supporter struggle to
come to grips with student life.
Point.
So, how does it feel,
being in high school after so long?
Total train wreck.
Sure looked like it.
Why make it third year?
Everyone's got friends,
and they're starting to
freak out about college entrance exams.
It's the toughest year.
Why are you surprised?
I'm pretty sure I told you that ReLIFE is
a program to rehabilitate NEETs.
Why wouldn't it be tough?
F...
Fair enough.
Thanks for understanding!
Try not to depend on me too much.
No point in being a high schooler
if you just hang out with another adult.
Got it.
I just want to fund this year of my life
and get that job afterward.
If I can blend in and stay in the background
all year, that's fine with me.
Is that so?
Whether you enjoy it or play it safe,
I think it's best you experience
your ReLIFE however you want.
Oh, right.
I won't speak to you formally at school,
so please get used to it.
Feel free to use casual speech yourself.
O-Okay.
But I guess you always have.
You have no manners.
Well, then.
See you tomorrow, Arata!
My first name?!
You can call me Ryo, too!
Over my dead body!
Yeah.
A job.
A one-year contract to start.
Looks like it could work out, yeah.
Say hi to Dad for me.
ReLIFE Experiment Report
April 8th. First day of school.
Had not checked the schedule,
and was very unprepared.
While it is impossible to ascertain
how he'll spend the upcoming year...
Unlike Subject No. 001,
the failed sample from last year...
Subject No. 002, Kaizaki Arata,
will surely live a fulfilling ReLIFE.
NEXT EPISODE
What kind of music
do you listen to, Yoake-san?
Well, I find it hard to
get into modern music.
Same here. All I do is listen to
old tracks on MDs.
What are MDs?
Communication Skills: Zero
Wait, you don't know?
MDs! MiniDiscs!