The truth is...
Honestly, I wasn't going to
play volleyball in high school.
Sports have always been
the only thing I was good at.
I'd get better records in track or swimming
than kids on the teams.
I'd end up qualifying for meets.
I earned a lot of resentment.
I just liked moving my body.
But the harder I tried,
the more I hurt people.
Even on the volleyball team
I joined in junior high,
if I scored,
everyone acted like that was expected.
I was always left out.
Kaizaki-kun, you asked me the other day
why I didn't go to a school
with a better volleyball team.
I just got sick of it in junior high,
so I turned down offers from
all powerhouse teams.
But I still wanted to play something,
so I came to check out the
volleyball team, hoping against hope.
And that's where I met Rena.
Everyone's Selfish Desires
Okay, trial first-years, that's enough.
We're still going tomorrow,
so come hang out, if you like.
Thank you!
Thank goodness.
This is a prep school that doesn't
care about sports too much.
Nobody knows who I am.
If I play well, I'll find good teammates
to play volleyball with.
Hey.
Got a sec?
You're Tamarai-san from
Toyofuji Junior High, right?
What the hell were you doing today?
Mocking us?
You don't need to work
any harder at Aoba, huh?
No, that's not...!
Hit it.
For real.
Just do it.
If you hold back, I'll be pissed.
What's with this girl?
A-Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I actually hit it with
everything I had! Sorry!
I knew it!
I knew you were holding back!
I'm Kariu Rena.
You'll join the team, right,
Tamarai Honoka-san?
For the next three years,
I'm gonna practice real hard
and get good enough to match you.
Got it?
Don't you dare hold back again.
It was my first time having
a rival. I was overjoyed.
If it weren't for Rena, I wouldn't have gotten
to spend three wonderful years here.
I'm really grateful to her.
That's why I want to play
our last match together.
But Rena said she couldn't.
Not just that. I'm scared we
won't even be friends anymore.
I want to talk to her...
But she might push me away again.
I'm afraid the next time I speak
to her really will be the last.
I'm scared.
You're good friends.
You should treasure that.
I transferred a lot as a kid.
Hello, I'm Hishiro Chizuru!
Nice to meet you!
I'd make friends, and then transfer again.
Hello. I'm Hishiro Chizuru.
Nice to meet you.
I could feel my heart growing numb.
Was there any point to me being there?
I grew convinced that
no one would even remember me.
I'm Hishiro Chizuru.
Nice to meet you.
I gave up on knowing people.
And this mess is the result.
"This mess"?
If you keep avoiding her,
you'll drift further apart,
and you really won't know
how to talk to them.
Value the friends you have.
Don't give up like I did.
The bond between you two makes me...
Makes me...
The bond between you makes me very jealous.
The times you're spending now,
and the friends you have,
are irreplaceable.
Make the most of them,
or you'll regret it someday.
Thank you, Hishiron. Kaizaki-kun.
I'll go talk to Rena.
I can't leave things like this.
Thanks! You've given me strength!
You haven't smiled like that in a while.
Is that right?
You were quite ugly the other day.
Don't say that!
Ah, sorry we kept you this long.
Okay. Let's go.
Crap!
Hide!
Hey, don't push...!
Nah, I got it...
What are you doing?
Wait, Rena! Please!
Your ankle seems better.
Good.
I really want to play in
the tournament with you.
I don't want things to end like this.
It's my fault you got hurt,
so maybe I'm being selfish.
But please. Come back to the team.
Let's play together again.
I already told Amatsu-sensei.
I'm gonna retire.
But, you c—
I'm done with the team!
I don't care!
Just let it drop!
Kariu-san!
I'm going to watch the tournament.
I want to see what you two always
looked so happy talking about.
Tamarai-san.
I dunno if I should say this,
but Kariu was crying the other day.
The day after she got hurt, I think.
Back then, I had no idea why she was crying.
But I think I get it now.
If she really didn't care
about you or the club,
I don't think she'd cry.
She's so stubborn!
So, um, I dunno how to say it...
My point is, what she said just now
isn't how she really feels.
Thanks, Oga-kun.
I think so, too.
Rena really is stubborn.
I'm gonna trust her and wait.
Sorry I couldn't
be of more help.
I was only able to talk
to Tamarai-san because
you were there. Thank you.
Tamarai-san said she'd
trust Kariu-san and wait.
I'll do the same.
Again, why use that sticker there?!
Yeah?
Ah, hello, Kaizaki-san?
I was wondering about
your schedule this weekend.
Do you have any plans?
Going to watch volleyball
with Hishiro-san.
A date?!
Oh, come on!
You know everything already!
This isn't for fun.
I beg your pardon.
Of course I know.
Let's hope Kariu-san shows.
Thank you, Kaizaki-san.
Huh? Where'd that come from?
I just felt like saying thanks.
You're not making any sense. Creepy.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow. Bye!
"Thanks"?
I didn't do anything. Weirdo.
Wait, tomorrow?
He's coming?!
Honoka!
Is Rena...?
Oh. I called her place, but...
Let's have a good match!
I knew she wouldn't show.
But the tournament goes on tomorrow, too!
The tournament does, but...
This is an elimination tournament.
If they lose, they don't play
ever again, let alone tomorrow.
Does anybody know where Kariu lives?
You don't know?
Um... sorry.
I'm done waiting.
I'll drag her here if I have to.
Kaizaki-san.
Do you know where she lives?
Sorry. I don't.
Kariu-san's address.
Yikes! It's bad enough
that he knows her address,
but to send it with this timing
is really creepy!
Uh, I'll ask Sensei.
Let's go.
Right.
Oga, keep us updated on the match.
G-Got it.
That's unusual.
Not like you to step in and help.
You're always yelling at me
for getting too involved.
Are you that happy things are changing?
Yeah.
Kariu
Yeah?
It's...
Um, delivery.
Coming!
She might not open if she knows it's us.
I see.
Lying comes as naturally to you as breathing.
Your character is suspect.
Did you really have to go that far?
Yo!
Hello.
We've come too far
to let you get away, Kariu.
Why are you here?
We all believed you would come
and waited, but you didn't.
So we came to drag you there.
I never asked you to believe in me.
I didn't want to go, so I didn't.
That's all.
Don't show up like this.
You're dressed like you're going.
I wear this at home!
Your team tracksuit?
Yes!
With your uniform underneath?
You wanted to go, didn't you?
To play one last match with Tamarai-san.
It's none of your business.
You've got a lot of nerve.
Hishiro, you're too dense
to understand how I feel, so stop trying!
Kariu!
If I don't understand how a friend feels,
am I not allowed to worry about them?
If I don't experience what you do,
am I not allowed to
worry about you, my friend?
Please, let that iron guard
down for a minute.
It's only hurting you.
I know, when you've hit rock bottom,
people trying to cheer you up
can be really annoying.
"What would you know?"
"Just leave me alone."
But what if someone you're pushing away
is really worried about you?
That'd be a shame.
Hishiro may be awkward,
but she was genuinely worried.
I didn't ask her to be.
Quit patronizing me.
Kariu!
Ow!
Hishiro-san?
Wh-What's gotten into you?
Knock it off already, you stubborn fool.
What do you want, Kariu-san?
To stay at home forever?
To throw away three years
of practice like this?
To cut ties with your best friend?
To spend the rest of the school year all alone?
I did that. I don't recommend it.
This moment, right here?
You can't come back to it.
I want you to go to that match
and laugh with Tamarai-san again.
I want the three of us to
eat lunch together again.
I'm not trying to patronize you.
Just trying to fulfill my selfish desire.
So...
...let me know your selfish desire.
Do you really want
things to stay this way?
What do you actually want?
I want...
...to play.
I wanna play!
It's the last...
We all worked so hard,
and this is the last...
But I haven't practiced for two weeks.
I can't stand next to Honoka.
My teammates won't want me there.
I can't just jump into a match
the moment my ankle's healed!
So I made up my mind to quit
and left the team.
I couldn't back down from that
and said some horrible things, so why
are you all being so nice to me?
You won't let me give up!
Why?
Because everybody likes you.
Tamarai-san said she wants
to play with you, too.
But since she caused your sprain,
she couldn't bring herself
to ask you to grant her selfish desire.
There's no problem at all.
I mean, you both want to play
your last game together,
and we all want you to.
All of our selfish desires align.
Let's go.
Will you run if I don't drag you?
Hello?
They lost the first set!
Momentum's against them!
Your team...
They're on the back foot.
Rena!
Come on, get going.
Good luck.
Kariu-san.
Rena!
Sorry I'm late.
And for everything else.
I really...
We couldn't play well without you!
We've all been waiting. Thanks for coming!
Let's win!
So we can all play together longer!
Come on, Honoka!
Stop crying already!
You, too!
Why did I sit between them?
Sorry.
I kept thinking I had to
keep it together, but I couldn't.
But when you came, I really wanted
to win, and rushed things.
Would you have won without me?
No way!
You should've seen the look
on my face when you weren't here!
She looked dead.
Hey!
Even if we had won like that,
I wouldn't have been happy.
It wouldn't have been fun.
Yeah, same here.
We lost, but that match was super fun.
Honoka, were you going to Aoba College?
Yeah.
Then we aren't done yet.
Let's play volleyball again in college!
Yeah...
Yeah!
Sorry I was so mean the day I got hurt.
Thanks for not giving up on me.
No, I'm sorry for causing your sprain.
Thanks for coming back.
It's all thanks to you, Hishiro!
Thanks.
Thanks, Hishiron!
Hishiro's doing that creepy smile again!
How mean, Rena!
It is creepy, though.
That hurts.
But it's a super weird smile!
All's well that ends well, huh?
Yep.
We'd never seen Tama-chan look
so alive during a match, either!
I'm so glad!
Thanks.
What's that look for?
N-Nothing.
Hey! Tama-chan!
The next match is starting!
Oh, crap!
We've gotta keep score!
Come on, Rena.
Later, guys!
NEXT EPISODE
Is that a new hair tie, Rena?
Oh, I forgot I borrowed it from Hishiro.
I'd better return it.
Come to think of it, Hishiron's always
wearing the same ones, huh?
Say, Honoka. How about we...
A Trip to the Past
...gift Hishiro...
...some new hair ties?