The silver pin,
given to the boy and girl in each class
with the top test scores.
Tuition exemption. Commute allowance.
Free lunch at the school cafeteria.
I never cared about those perks, though.
It proved you were top of the class.
That you were class rep.
That's the kind of status
the pin conferred upon you,
and I was proud of myself when I wore it.
Kariu, committee meeting time!
Yeah!
And...
...for me...
Going to the cafeteria now?
O-Oga!
Y-Yeah, but I'm waiting for Honoka.
You?
Oh, class rep work.
Yeah.
And I'm starving, too!
Sensei really runs us ragged!
Right, Hishiro-san?
Kazu-kun.
Ryo's notebook was lying
on the floor in the hallway.
Huh?
Who's Ryo?
Are you okay, Kazu-kun?
Sorry, it got a bit heavy.
This is why I told you
to let me carry half.
Sorry.
Give that here.
I'll take half.
Oh, "Ryo" is Yoake-kun.
You friends with him?
He was just in the same class last year.
So... first name?
What was with that victorious smirk?!
She was trying for a friendly smile.
What part of that was "friendly"?!
She was sneering at me!
What's up?
Are you mad about something?
Nah.
Argh, I can't stand it!
I can't get that face out of my head!
Why's she flashing that gross face at me?!
I don't get it!
Rena, you're definitely pissed off.
I feel sorry for your fried rice.
White Milk
Non-homogenized
You lack calcium.
Want some milk?
Ew.
How do you drink milk with rice?
Huh? It's normal!
All through grade school...
They didn't give us an option back then!
I'm gonna drink a ton of milk
and grow taller for volleyball.
All that nutrition...
...is going somewhere else entirely.
Honoka wound up beating me
on every part of the fitness test.
I knew it! You're really fast!
As for your name, I'm sorry.
I don't know it, so I couldn't use it.
Honoka... and Hishiro.
I'm the only one who sees us as rivals.
They just keep outdoing me easily,
without even caring.
Rena?
Are you okay?
Sorry!
I hate that I'm no match for her,
but I love Honoka regardless.
She's a good friend.
But...
But that girl...
Kazu-kun...
I don't think I can ever
come to terms with her!
Why's she eating alone in the cafeteria?!
Trying to make herself look lonely?!
Waiting for some dude to hit on her?!
Rena...
We're truly ashamed.
How long is this gonna go on?
It's only our third try!
Yeah!
Counting the real one, it's your fourth!
I dunno how you can take tests
for a month straight!
Don't you even want to be free?!
I do!
Extremely.
At this rate, we'll need to hold
study sessions through Golden Week...
Huh?
Don't give me that!
I'm sick of this!
I'm starting to lose confidence
in my teaching.
Does Hishiro-san eat lunch alone?
He's right. She's eating alone.
Come to think of it...
I'm trying to take the first step
toward not being a friendless loner.
I know!
Let's invite her here to eat with us!
And we can have her help tutor you two!
How lucky is that?
Two silver pins teaching you!
Thanks.
I'll go ask.
Yeah.
Oga, wait!
Huh?
What?
Oh, you wanna go?
Right. You two are on friendly terms.
Uh, no, that's not it...
We'd better not ask her.
Huh? Why not?
It's perfect!
She's alone, and we could use the help!
Yeah, I know that, but...
Then why not?
Well...
Oh...
I see now.
I get it!
You're jealous!
You don't want any other guys
getting close to Hishiro-san.
Huh?!
It'll be fine! Don't worry about me.
That ain't it, dumbass!
If you want to talk to me about love,
come back in another ten years!
Anyway,
An and I just have to
buckle down and pass, right?
Put Hishiro-san on hold for now.
Yikes. He ain't buying that at all.
I don't get it, but whatever.
If you insist.
Yeah. We'll do our best to pass.
Might be none of my business,
but I don't wanna see her and Kariu fight.
I want to change.
Am I really unapproachable?
But maybe I hurt Hishiro-san's chances a bit.
Just when Oga thought to invite her over.
Now she's gonna stay alone.
Wait, why is this my problem?
Let the kids be!
Hishiro-san, don't you have
any friends to eat lunch with?
I don't.
Thought not...
Why are you even asking?
Didn't I tell you I had no friends already?
Are you mocking me?
Crap.
A sticker...
Why choose that one now?!
Is she emotionally unstable?!
But don't worry.
It feels like I might make a friend soon.
Oh?
I think I've been getting along
with Kariu-san lately.
What gave you that idea?!
Did something happen between them
when I wasn't looking?
No, no. Kariu looked ready to kill at lunch.
This is totally Hishiro-san
misreading things.
How bad is she at observing
those around her?
Not to mention,
she sucks at remembering names.
Maybe she doesn't care about other people?
Kids these days are so unsocial.
But damn... she really is totally alone.
Right...
I know someone else...
Kaizaki Arata
...who eats lunch alone.
I can't do that.
Why not?
You're all alone, too, anyway.
As a pair of loners,
the two of you should get along.
Considering you're trying to be nice,
you sure have a rude way of putting it.
What do you mean, I'm all alone anyway?
I choose not to mingle for work reasons.
I can't exactly stalk you
if I'm with Hishiro-san.
You were in the same class
as her last year,
and you sit next to her.
You can at least eat—
I can't.
You cold-hearted sadist.
If it's that important,
why not invite her yourself?
Well...
I'm asking 'cause I can't.
What's this? It sounds like you really care.
What happened to staying in
the background all year?
Well...
I think it's a good thing, you know.
You're paying attention to those around you.
You don't just notice...
you take action to help.
I think it's one of your strengths.
But don't you wonder?
Is getting rid of all the thorns
in someone's path
really what's best for them?
While they're still young enough
to be allowed to trip and fall,
it's important for them
to learn the pain of it
and how to pick themselves up again.
Every now and then...
...you say something deep.
It's kind of annoying.
So you think my attempts to help
wouldn't benefit them?
You don't recommend it?
No, sorry. I just said what crossed my mind.
You can live your ReLIFE
any way you see fit, Kaizaki-san.
Somewhere along the line, my life...
...my thoughts...
...began to revolve around them.
I mean, isn't it a shame?
I just want them all to enjoy
the time they're having at school.
Maybe I'm thinking like an old man
prone to lectures...
But seeing your friends every day
like it's nothing...
...is something you lose
when you grow up.
Fight with all your might.
With those young kids, give your
mind and heart a solid workout.
Let your heart, which had dried up
and gotten stiff, beat once more.
May 1st
May, huh?
I've been at this ReLIFE thing
a whole month.
Not sure if it went by in a flash
or lasted forever.
Arata!
I've got a committee meeting, so here.
A handout for your make-up retest.
With you gone, I figured
we wouldn't be studying today.
Didn't you say you'd do your best?
I did. Sorry.
You know there's a study room at
the end of the second floor, right?
Be sure to solve that before you leave.
Okay...
Kazu-kun.
Let's go to the committee meeting.
Oh, sorry, Hishiro-san.
I'm coming.
Okay.
Oh... Kariu-san.
Our eyes met again.
Honoka!
Let's go to practice.
C'mon, Hishiro-san!
U-Uh, yeah.
Does she smile at Oga
the way she smiles at Kaizaki?
We're out of balls. Better pick 'em up.
Yeah!
Oh, there she is.
See? I told you they'd still be at it.
Let's go home, Tama.
Huh?
Is it that late?
Sorry, I totally lost track of time!
Go change.
But the balls...
It's fine. I'm not leaving yet, anyway.
You need to catch your train, right?
Thanks.
Aki-chan, Nobu-chan, wait right here!
I'll go get changed in a jiffy!
Sorry, Kariu-san.
Tama-chan always makes you
stay late with her, huh?
But, thanks to you,
she seems to be enjoying
practice a lot more than she used to.
Nah. I'm the one making her stay.
You're doing more for her!
Waiting this late to go home with her.
If we let Tama-chan ride a train alone,
who knows where she'd end up?
Our parents insist we have to
look after her and bring her
home safe and sound.
Th-Thanks.
No prob.
Thanks for waiting. Let's go.
All right.
Okay.
Okay, sorry, Rena.
When you're done,
lock up the clubroom and gym
and return the key to the staff room.
Got it.
Bye!
Must be nice.
Spending every day with
nice childhood friends.
Kariu-san?
Oh, we got the same scores!
Let's work hard together as
the class reps for first term.
Y-Yeah...
I was the Class 1 rep
the first term of my first year.
But I didn't come first the next two terms.
I hated that,
so I made sure I had
the silver pin for all of last year.
Kariu!
Committee time!
Yeah!
For an entire year,
I never let go of the silver pin, but...!
Why?
Why always me?
Why can't I do anything right?
No...
I can't stand being like this!
Stop it!
It still hurts sometimes...
Is this what it means to age?
There are still students around?
Excuse me.
I'm here to return the gym key.
Hishiro?
Goodbye.
This...
...is Hishiro's bag.
The silver pin...
Proof that you're number one.
Proof that you worked hard.
But for me,
it wasn't just the status.
For me...
...it was...
...proof that I deserved to be with Oga!
She got everything without looking
like she put in any effort at all!
She deserves some trouble!
It'll be fine...
I won't get caught...
I'll just walk casually out of school
and ditch it at the station bathroom.
Huh?
You're leaving now, Kariu?
Kaizaki...
Why are you still here?
Oh, studying.
I was using the study room.
The teacher said to lock up
and bring the key by the
staff room when I was done.
How about you? Just finished practice?
What's the matter?
I, uh...
I just returned the gym key, too.
Oh, okay.
Stay away!
Oh, right...
I don't know where to put the keys.
I can't stop to chat here!
Sorry, but can you come with and show me?
If I waste too much time,
Hishiro will leave the staff room!
S-Sorry.
I've gotta get home.
Sorry, but could you ask a teacher?
All right. Take care.
Kariu!
Why do you have two bags?
Huh?
No reason.
I mean, for my practice clothes...
No.
That's not it.
I recognize that bag.
The green one.
Isn't that...
Hishiro-san's?
Kariu?
Hey, Kariu! Wait!
I said wait!
No! Let go!
Kariu!
Goodbye.
Staff Room
Huh? Where's my bag?
Wait...
What was that noise?
Fall
NEXT EPISODE
I wasn't bad at sports,
and despite taking two years to get into
college, I wasn't bad at studying, either.
I went to grad school
and managed to land a job all right.
Overlap
I thought I had a fulfilling
adult life waiting for me.