A fireworks festival.
Going out with friends!
I'll invite Kariu to
the fireworks festival...
...and confess!
So, uh...
What's up?
I'm...
...gonna tell Oga how I feel today.
Oga said he might go to college elsewhere.
And here I was taking it for granted
that we'd be together in college, too.
But if we end up separated,
I'll regret not saying anything.
So help make sure we're alone together!
If you know you'll be separated...
...then falling in love...
Understood.
...or confessing your feelings...
Leave it to me!
...kind of seems pointless.
Hishiro-san! Over here!
Sorry, everyone!
There is nothing worse
a person can do than be late!
This failure can never be forgiven.
Nobody would ever say that to
someone three minutes late.
You okay, Hishiro?
Yes...
I've never been to a festival.
I completely underestimated the crowd.
I can't apologize enough!
Her first festival!
Confession
Frankfurters
Corn on the cob
Soba
Cold
Well, everyone's here.
And Hishiro-san's calmed down. Let's go!
Arata-kun!
I'd love some takoyaki!
So buy some.
Meanie!
You can afford takoyaki!
Aki-chan! Let's catch some goldfish again!
You're on.
Don't catch too many!
Remember last year? That poor stall owner.
Man, it's hot.
Yeah.
You okay, Hishiro-san?
How far'd you run?
Your feet hurt?
My feet are fine.
But the crowd's a bit much,
and I'm a little dizzy.
I'll be fine.
Need an arm?
See? Like them.
Keeps you from tripping, yeah?
You don't mind?
I offered, didn't I?
Then I will accept your offer.
Look, we need to be subtle.
I know, I know.
Gotta leave those two alone naturally—
What?
Is Yoake-san really making
a move on a high school girl?!
No, no, out of the question.
Ryo...
Yoake-san might not be...
But could Hishiro-san be...?
Huh? Where is everyone?
Did we get separated?
Huh?
Enjoy your alone time!
Good luck!
Already?!
Sure, I asked for it,
but this came out of nowhere!
I'm not ready yet!
What are you doing, Tama?
Hurry up, or I'll catch them all.
Aw, no fair! I won't lose, though!
You! From last year!
Sorry!
Distance to target: 1 meter.
It went well, huh?
If gravitation force is g,
and my throw is at 180 degrees,
More importantly, do something about An!
I need a force of...
She's being super clingy.
Will that math help?
Hmm... it would be a problem
if we had a subject
and an employee hanging out,
ignoring the students.
But everyone's here today, so it's fine!
You're lax!
Oh, I see.
You aren't bothered by Onoya.
You don't like me being with Hishiro-san.
10 cm diameter.
That's not it!
You should have said!
Pi is 3.14...
Will those calculations really help?
Sorry, I didn't even notice.
Quiet, please.
Like I said...
It's the last summer of high school.
It's a precious time that won't come again.
But I guess for you,
this is your first and last summer!
You... god damn sadist!
So what am I supposed to do about it?
Can't wait for the fireworks!
Say, Kariu.
I, uh... love you.
Out of the blue?!
With all these people around?!
Not good timing?
Not exactly, no.
But that's not the point...
What?!
Nobody told me this would happen!
I didn't think he'd do that!
I didn't think you'd do this!
Are you... serious?
What? You don't trust me?
N-Not that! I just can't believe it!
That's the same thing, isn't it?
No.
I didn't mean it like that.
Man, I came up with so many ideas.
It wasn't supposed to go like this!
Kariu!
Oh, sorry.
When you asked me to these
fireworks, I was so happy.
Oga...
I remembered you talking about
going to college elsewhere.
So I made up my mind to tell you today.
I've been in love with you
since our first year, too.
Will you go out with me?
Come on! I summon all my courage to
tell you, and that's how you react?!
I mean, who wouldn't be surprised?
I was gonna ask you out,
but you asked me instead!
Right back at you!
Ow...
Sorry.
I... how should I put this?
I've never really talked about
these things with friends.
I think I'm not good
at picking up on things.
I had no idea you felt that way.
I didn't notice how I felt, either.
Not until Arata gave me a push.
I thought that without you,
everything would be so boring.
The idea of someone else touching you...
was just not okay.
I only realized this recently.
But I think...
...I've loved you for a long time, too.
Oh, man! That was really embarrassing!
Don't get embarrassed on a delay!
You're making me blush!
Are these fireworks starting soon?
I think so.
Um...
Kariu-san.
Do you mind...
...if we hold hands?
I... I don't mind.
Oh, Asaji-kun!
You brought a sheet!
Sit down!
A mosquito just bit me.
Here, medicine. Need some bug repellent?
What? Asaji-kun, are you our mom?
Huh? Where are Kaizaki-san and Hishiro-san?
Oh, yeah... who knows?
Oh... but the fireworks are starting!
Tama, you need bug spray?
Yep!
Huh? Where'd Yoake-kun and...
But I guess for you, this is
your first and last summer!
They set me up, too?!
Attention. Fireworks will begin soon.
Man, we're really boxed in here.
Please enjoy the beautiful fireworks
against the clear summer sky.
Hishiro-san, wanna just watch from here?
Sure.
Ryo...
Is he a friend of yours, Kaizaki-san?
I've seen you talk at school, too.
Sure, I guess.
I guess we're friends.
I see.
Kaizaki-san, you make friends
with everybody very easily.
In April, you'd just enrolled,
but you were already surrounded by friends.
I remember seeing that and clearly thinking,
"I've got to try harder."
Hishiro-san, you're here with everyone, too.
Seeing the fireworks.
Except we got separated.
You're surrounded by friends,
too, Hishiro-san.
You've tried plenty hard.
Thank you.
The credit is mostly yours.
I'm really glad I met you.
Gorgeous!
Beautiful.
Yeah.
But I'm so focused on my left hand,
I can barely watch the fireworks!
But I'm so focused on my right hand,
I'm really glad I met you.
What did she mean by that?
No, no, she meant nothing more.
If she felt like it, Hishiro-san
would totally say that to anyone!
It doesn't mean anything.
Thanks.
For thinking of me that way.
That alone...
...makes me think this ReLIFE
was worth living.
Though you'll forget me.
They're lovely.
But there's something a little sad
about them, too.
There is?
They're so flashy, pretty, and exciting,
but as they fade, you feel sort of lonely.
You're an illusion that's meant to fade away.
When the experiment ends,
so will this life.
They'll forget me.
Including Hishiro-san.
They'll all forget me.
They're so flashy, pretty, and exciting,
but as they fade, you feel sort of lonely.
Hishiro-san, you're here with everyone.
Surrounded by friends.
You've tried plenty hard.
I'm glad I met you.
If you know you'll be separated...
it kind of seems pointless.
A confession?
Ryo was in my class last year.
He told me to call him that.
It's not often that you start a conversation.
Yes. Kariu-san and Tamarai-san
gave them to me.
It's not often that you start a conversation.
It's all thanks to you, Hishiro!
I did that. I don't recommend it.
They're all irreplaceable.
You can't turn back.
Don't give up like I did.
Let's get revenge.
Fight on!
Together.
You're in my class?
I'm changing.
You have more friends.
I forgive you. After all, we're friends.
Can I have...
A friendly smile.
...your phone?
Out in the real world...
That's my seat.
Congratulations!
You've been selected as the
ReLIFE Laboratory Kanto Branch's
test subject no. 001!
Nice to meet you, Hishiro Chizuru-san.
After the ReLIFE period ends,
classmates, teachers, and anyone
you dealt with will forget about you.
The more fun I have,
the more it'll hurt when we part ways.
I know that all too well.
I know this is a bad idea.
Kaizaki-san, you're like the fireworks.
What?
Nothing, never mind.
Hishiro-san, look!
Kaizaki-san...
That face is really creepy.
Huh?
That was so much fun! Oga-kun, thank you!
No, thank you.
See ya!
Okay, I'll walk Onoya-san home!
Take care of Hishiro-san, Arata!
You live in the same direction, right?
That's true. Kaizaki-san, do you mind?
Okay.
Kazu-kun, look after Kariu-san.
Y-Yeah.
You don't like me being with Hishiro-san.
That's not true.
I just never see them together.
It was surprising, that's all.
H-Hishiro-san?!
You okay?
Y-Yes. Sorry.
The crowd got to me again.
Let's rest here a while.
Okay.
I'm really glad for Kariu-san.
And Kazu-kun.
Yeah.
The truth is, Kariu-san was also
going to ask Kazu-kun out today.
Because Kazu-kun might be
going to a different college.
She said if that happened,
she'd regret not saying anything.
Oh, wow. Kariu, too.
When I heard that,
I thought that falling in love
when you knew you'd have to part
seemed pointless.
But when I saw them together, I was
happy for them from the bottom of my heart.
Maybe worrying about future partings so much
that you miss out on happiness
in the present is a waste.
Everyone you dealt with
will forget about you.
Maybe so.
Someday, we'll part. Maybe be forgotten.
But we're living in the moment.
So...
Hishiro-san, make lots of friends,
fall madly in love,
and enjoy every moment to the fullest.
Yes. I'll try.
All I can do is cheer her on.
She'll forget all about me.
If all her memories are about me,
then she'll have no memories
of this year left.
I'll vanish one day.
I can't rob her of the life
she's fighting so hard to have.
I was just wondering
if there's anyone you like.
Someone you're always with.
You don't want anyone taking her away.
You wanna hold hands.
You wanna kiss her.
Kaizaki-san?
That's not it.
You just find it cute that a high schooler's
awkwardly but earnestly trying to change, right?
Like watching a kid sister grow up?
Kaizaki-san?
Come to your senses!
Get it together!
Hishiro-san's life will go on,
and I...
...won't be there.
Let's go!
Okay.
Sorry.
I thought I'd recovered.
I didn't imagine I'd trip.
Thank goodness.
I'm glad I caught you.
You okay? Not gonna trip again?
I'm fine.
You sure?
If you're that worried,
then let me take your arm.
Ryo offered me his.
Go ahead!
Thank you.
Someday we'll have to part.
And I'll be forgotten.
But...
I won't ever forget you.
Yes. I won't forget you, either.
Kaizaki-san, you suck!
Even though Senpai
showed you how to link arms!
Wait, that was your idea, though.
ReLIFE Experiment Report
Anyway, I've got a good report
to write today.
I knew it!
Kaizaki-san's the man I thought he was!
Yep. He managed to get Kariu-san
and Oga-kun together.
Well, yeah, but he also...
Never mind.
If she's with Kaizaki-san,
Hishiro-san, too...
Well, that's up to you. Since you'll be
taking over as her support next term!
Right! I'll do my best!
Kaizaki Arata causes change
in those around him.
This is a direct result of his own actions,
his drive to get involved
with the people near him.
That, more than anything,
proves his ReLIFE is going well.
Hishiro-san, what's that?
I used the camera for the first time.
It came out blurry.
When did you take that?
Fireworks may vanish, but memories remain.
Arata! Save me!
"Save me"?
What am I, some sort of demon?!
Ah, Hishiro! I won't lose this time!
Kaizaki-san... you're quite popular.
What?! Is that what this looks like?!
A one-year, limited edition of youth.
I may be an illusion that'll be forgotten...
...but I'll treasure every moment, and enjoy...
...my ReLIFE!