Hishiron! Let's get lunch.
What about Kariu-san?
C-Come on, Hishiron!
It's lunch break.
How haven't you noticed yet?
Rena's absent today.
She is? Then it's just the two of us today.
Yep!
Revenge
Hishiron, ramen again?
There's other good stuff
on the menu here.
Like the fried rice and the rice omelets...
Tamarai-san, you look a little ugly today.
Your eyes look weird.
Did you walk into something?
Stop, Hishiron! Don't be mean!
"Ugly"? "Weird"?
It's that obvious I was crying, huh? Ugh...
If you didn't bump into anything,
was it bees?
Uh, yeah!
Guess I was stung in my sleep!
I see. Get well soon.
Say, Hishiron...
Have you ever hurt someone or clashed
with them because you're too smart?
Made people give up,
or tell you to do everything by yourself?
Anything like that?
I don't really understand.
Sorry, weird question.
Forget it.
Excuse me.
Rena!
How's your ankle?
You went to the hospital, right?
Here.
Nice spike!
One more!
Right!
Tamarai-senpai!
Get the nurse!
It's a sprain.
It'll take two weeks to heal.
I can exercise after that,
but with caution.
Whew.
Then you can make the tournament!
You can come by practice until it heals.
Just to show your face.
They'll all be relieved.
About that...
I think I'd drag the team down if I played
in a match after taking two weeks off.
And I don't know if
I'll be able to move right.
I think I'm just gonna retire.
Let the others know for me.
Bye.
Wait, Rena!
You should try the rice omelet next time!
Kariu-san...
I've gotta use the bathroom.
Okay.
R...
No, Aki, stop.
What were you gonna do?
Drag her in front of Tama
and make her apologize.
You can't!
You heard what Tama-chan said.
She wants to stay friends with Kariu-san,
so she'll figure this out herself.
Watch over her.
I've been doing that all day.
Show more patience.
She was finally smiling at practice.
Now it's making her cry again.
It's hard for me to watch.
Kariu, are you not going to practice?
I'm gonna study a bit today.
Then since I'm not working today, maybe I
should do my homework before I go home.
Arata, you're staying, right?
For make-up prep?
Sorry, I've got somewhere to be today.
Dude, what?
At this rate, you'll fail next week, too!
Shut up.
Bye.
I'm being a nosy old man and
leaving you two alone together.
Be grateful and enjoy your youth.
How long is he gonna stay?!
I was just waiting for everyone to leave...
I don't want to be seen
dragging my foot like this!
Okay! Guess I'd better be go—
Okay! All done!
You finished, too?
Then let's go home together!
His timing is the worst!
You go on ahead, Oga.
Why? Aren't you done, too?
Just go.
You're not making any sense.
Just go!
Don't try to make sense of it!
Take a hint already!
What? Man, you're extra grumpy today.
Don't talk like I'm always grumpy!
Come on. Stop sulking, and let's go!
Hey! Stop that, you wimpy...
Kariu!
Sorry, are—
Don't look!
Ow...
Just leave me alone!
Why, you...
Didn't you hear me?
Why are you still here?!
Just leave already!
I can't just leave a crying
girl alone and go home.
I'm too wimpy to carry you,
but I can lend you a shoulder,
and get you down the stairs.
The last thing you need is a fall.
If I were a boy,
I'd hate girls like me.
Stupidly proud, short-tempered,
and utterly incomprehensible.
I was so mean to Honoka.
She might never speak to me again.
But I can't be honest
about my feelings.
I'm really starting to hate myself.
Man, I just don't know.
About what?
There's just so much happening
that the subject doesn't see.
Even though one of the goals of ReLIFE
is to reinvigorate emotions
that have withered with age
by getting him involved
with adolescent kids.
Will he actually get involved?
Well, I'm sure Kaizaki-san will notice
something's wrong soon.
But what then?
friends acting weird help
I knew it. Something's wrong.
Weird...
What's been going on lately?
I thought Hishiro-san and Kariu
had finally became friends,
but now even Tamarai-san's
eating lunch alone.
Kariu hasn't been going to practice.
Things don't seem right
between her and Oga, too.
What's with this awkward atmosphere?
What's going on?
What's with this company?
Something's off.
Do my seniors hate each other?
Kaizaki-kun...
You're absolutely right,
and I'm glad you feel that way.
But I want you to stay out of it.
Hishiro Chizuru
It's Hishiro-san.
Let's see..."I need your advice."
"I'm outside your place."
"Can we talk?"
Huh?
No way! Why?!
Scary! Too scary!
Wait, wait!
Hello.
What brings you here?
Like I said, I need your help.
Since it would be a little wordy for LIME,
I figured in person was better.
You could have just called.
I've never had a long
phone call with a friend.
It never even occurred to me.
Well, uh, come on in.
Okay, thank you.
You live alone?
Well, yeah.
Oh, sit anywhere.
Sure.
Oh, yeah.
She's in high school.
Generally when you go to a friend's house,
their family's around.
Wait, is Hishiro-san freaking out
because it's just me here?
What now? Should I give her
an excuse to leave?
No, she's Oga-level dense.
I doubt she cares at all.
Wait, I'm the one freaking out!
U-Uh, here.
Thanks.
Go ahead.
Oh, sorry.
Don't jump her!
How can I, with you guys watching?!
Tee hee!
So, what's up?
It's about Kariu-san and Tamarai-san.
It's weird.
They were so close, and now
they won't speak to each other.
I was wondering if you knew what happened.
Sorry. It's bugging me, too, but I dunno.
I see...
But I'm surprised you've been so perceptive.
It wasn't long ago that you'd have
asked them directly.
But you realized you couldn't,
so you came to see me.
That's true.
Why did I go the long way around?
Oh, I think it's because
it isn't my problem.
I'm emotionally dumb,
so I make a lot of mistakes.
If it's just me, that's fine.
But with Kariu-san and Tamarai-san,
I can't afford to be stupid and mess up.
You don't need to be so hard on yourself.
Last year, there was bullying in my class.
It was not pleasant to see.
I had this weird sense of duty,
like it was my job to stop it.
So I told them to stop this nonsense.
The bullying just got worse.
And the victim told me...
"Don't do anything.
All I have to do is put up with it,
and it won't get any worse."
You're absolutely right.
But in any society,
you just need to grin and bear it.
Even if it isn't fair.
I'm fine.
So, Kaizaki-kun... grow up.
I think she was doing her best
to maintain the balance in her little world.
But I stepped in, heeding only my emotions,
and made things worse.
I really regretted it.
I just don't know how to act while
considering other people's feelings.
After that, I did what she said.
I said nothing
and pretended I saw nothing.
What happened to her?
She changed schools after the year ended.
Oh.
Something similar happened to me last year.
At my last... school,
a senpai was... bullied.
I got all fired up and tried to help.
I lashed out at the people bullying her.
But like you said,
Senpai was maintaining her own balance.
And I upset that.
And your senpai?
What happened to her?
And your senpai...
...what happened...
...to her?
Kaizaki-san?
What's wrong?
You don't look good.
Are you okay?
Kaizaki-san?
Kaizaki-kun?
I'm sorry.
If...
...I'd only been more grown-up...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Kaizaki-san.
I don't know why you're apologizing.
Ow!
S-Sorry, I didn't mean to do that!
Don't call the police!
I won't call the police.
Good. You're back to normal.
About Kariu-san and Tamarai-san...
Is it best that I do nothing?
But I just don't like it.
They were so close.
I don't like seeing them apart.
Yeah. I agree.
It's hard to watch. I wanna do something.
But...
I'm scared.
Scared of taking that step.
What if I destroy everything again?
I wasn't supposed to be their peer in school.
I don't have the right to upset their lives.
Then let's get revenge together.
I want to defeat the me
that's dragging this failure around.
I don't want to forget my failure.
But if I carry it with me as a bad memory,
and keep running away,
I'll never change.
I think there are things
you learn to do through failing.
Kaizaki-san.
Will you get revenge with me?
Fight on!
Bye!
We're headed home. Are you good to clean up?
Y-Yeah! Thanks! You go on home.
Bye!
Don't push yourself too hard!
Hishiron?
Tamarai-san.
Can we talk?
Tama-chan never showed up.
Think she went home already?
Without telling us? No way.
Huh? She's not here.
Did she really go home?
And leave this mess behind?
Maybe she's in the clubroom?
I see.
Kariu-san's sprain is...
I'm sorry, Hishiron.
We're all eating separately.
That's sort of beside the point.
I want to play this last tournament with her.
But I caused her injury,
so I don't know what to say.
I can't bring myself to talk to her.
Aki? Where are you going?
That redhead was still at school, right?
I'm gonna make her
listen to how Tama feels.
I'm allowed to do that much, right?
Hey, let go! What the hell?!
Inukai-kun!
You're hurting her!
Inukai-kun! Listen!
This guy! He's taking me to Honoka...
Stop it!
From here on, keep it down.
Even your footsteps.
If you must talk, whisper.
Okay. We'll do what you say.
Shut up and listen.
The truth is...
Honestly,
I wasn't going to play volleyball
in high school.
NEXT EPISODE
Hishiro-san, what was that
"fight on" thing all about?
I learned about it when
I studied up on sports teams.
It's a teamwork ritual where
everyone joins hands and...
Oh...
Join me, if you like.
Everyone's Selfish Desires
Fight on!
On... Oh.