Staff Room
Goodbye.
Huh? Where's my bag?
Wait...
What was that noise?
Overlap
You're awake?
This is the nurse's office.
You two were found
collapsed by the stairs.
What happened?
Did you miss your step?
Yeah.
I guess I sorta slipped.
Kaizaki-kun, you shielded
Kariu-san from the fall.
Nicely done.
Good boy.
* Actually 27
Boy?
Inukai-sensei, Inukai-sensei,
please come to the staff room.
Oh, sorry.
I'll be back in a minute.
Can you stay with her?
Sure thing.
Oh, right.
Your classmate, Hishiro-san, let us know.
She carried your stuff here, too.
Thank her later, okay?
Hishiro-san...
I knew it... that was Hishiro-san's.
Why did Kariu have it?
What was she trying to do?
She's got top sales again.
We'll lose face if we let
a woman trounce us like this.
Why won't she just quit?
Hasn't she worked it out yet?
With all we've done? She knows.
Knock it off. The new guy's here.
Oh.
She's in charge of his training, right?
Don't rat us out, Kaizaki.
I apologize.
We'll make absolutely sure
nothing like this happens again.
Please, let us make it up to you.
You know this mess wasn't your fault!
We went over the order several times
while you were showing me the ropes!
Someone must've...
I know.
Doesn't it make you mad?
Knocking others down to gain an advantage
is a fruitless endeavor.
It means they've given up
on winning any other way.
At first,
we all competed fair and square.
It was really fun.
But then,
somehow we went from rivals to enemies.
Seeing hard workers turn out
like that doesn't make me mad.
Just...
...very sad.
Were you trying to bully her?
A hard worker like you?
Oh. Are you awake, Kariu?
Hey, no sudden movements.
Apparently, Hishiro-san found us
and let the teachers know.
I'm pretty sure she took that
green bag home with her.
That bag...
It was Hishiro-san's, right?
Why did you have it?
Don't run.
Answer me, Kariu.
You steal anything?
No!
No...
I just wanted to trouble her a bit...
I was gonna hide it somewhere.
Why?
Have you given up?
Do you think harassing her is
the only way you'll beat her?
So...
Are you gonna tell her I tried to
harass her because I was jealous?
You're close to her.
That's why you knew it was her bag,
and that's why you're mad at me.
I bet I could hurt you more if I told Oga.
I'm kidding.
I won't do that.
But... that is what I think.
Trying to knock others down a peg
just means lowering yourself.
Don't go trampling all the hard work
and trust you've built up.
It insults the effort you put in.
The only way that would make you happy
is if you were a loser
who'd given up on trying.
But I don't think that describes you.
The Kariu I know hates losing,
is curt but kind,
and is a hard worker with a strong heart.
Because I know how hard you've worked,
I'm not really mad. Just very, very sad.
Don't act like some filthy adult.
You're still young!
Don't give up on try—
What would you know?!
What the hell are you lecturing me for?
We're the same age!
I did try!
But I couldn't win.
Not only that, they don't
even see me as a rival!
Honoka for sports, Hishiro for studies...
I'm trying desperately to beat them!
So why do they act like
I'm no threat at all?!
Why am I the only one with problems?!
I try and try and try and...
No matter how hard I try,
I get nothing in return.
It's all pointless.
That's not true.
You're just too busy comparing
yourself to others to see.
Those comparisons aren't the only measure.
Don't say it's all pointless.
You've worked hard and made yourself better.
That's what you got in return.
So don't...
...put yourself down like this.
Oh...
I guess...
...all my hard work...
...wasn't pointless.
Nurse's Office
Feeling better?
Huh? About what?
Always gotta act tough, huh?
You said no matter how hard you tried...
Stop talking about that!
But Hishiro-san's trying, too.
She was in the staff room this late...
I bet she had questions
for the teachers.
There are things even she doesn't find easy.
She's really awkward, after all.
I think you've got the
wrong idea about her, too.
You've never really talked to her.
Oh, right!
Next time you get a chance,
ask her to smile for you.
Smile?
It's really something.
I just lectured her like an old man!
Don't give up on trying.
Talk about pot calling the kettle black.
I'm one to talk,
considering I gave up.
Wh-What's up, Hishiro-san?
I was waiting for you.
There's something bothering me.
Thinking about it didn't get me anywhere,
so I waited to ask you.
Why did Kariu-san have my bag?
I've thought about it a lot,
but all I can think of is that
she stole it, so I'm confused.
Uh...
Kariu-san and my eyes
have been meeting often lately,
and every time, I've made sure to smile.
So I thought we were friendly.
Th-Think!
What the hell should I tell this
malice-free tone-deaf communicator?!
Sh-She thought it was dangerous
to leave the bag lying in the hall.
So she thought she'd take care of it for you.
Oh...
That's a relief.
Now that I know the reason,
I feel a lot better.
I knew she couldn't have tried to steal it.
But I couldn't think of anything else.
I'm ashamed of myself.
Is getting rid of all the thorns in
someone's path really what's best for them?
Sorry.
That was a lie.
Kariu took your bag to
cause problems for you.
Why would she...
She wanted the silver pin,
so she was jealous and frustrated.
Kariu-san wants this?
Holy crap.
She's even denser than Oga.
Then if I give her this,
can we be friends?
No way.
I don't understand.
Does Kariu-san hate me?
Yeah, I guess you wouldn't get it.
Hishiro-san,
for someone so smart,
you can be really dense.
You haven't noticed that
everyone's mad at you, have you?
I don't understand what I say
that makes people so mad.
I don't understand how they feel.
I know that's because
I haven't properly socialized.
I've tried to learn.
I've tried to study up on it,
but I just don't know what's right.
That's a tough one.
There is no right answer for getting along.
Different people require different answers.
Different people...
require different answers?
Sorry, I didn't mean to overload you.
I'm going to wait for Kariu-san.
I can't leave this be.
I want to be her friend for real.
But I don't know how.
If I don't know the right answer...
I'll just ask her.
Like you're asking a teacher?
One more question.
When I saw your hands wrapped
protectively around her,
why did I feel a pang?
No, never mind.
It's ineffective to deal
with many problems at once.
One at a time.
Please go home.
I think I have to take care of this myself.
G-Got it.
See you later, then.
As if!
Like I can possibly just leave!
Will she be okay?
I dunno, will she?
Why are you here?!
You should be used to this by now.
Wherever you go, I go with you.
Creepy!
Keep your voice down!
And don't be mean.
You're supposed to be
watching me, not Hishiro.
The influence your choices
have on those around you
is also a target of my observations.
Kariu-san.
I've been waiting for you.
An ambush?
Oh. that's right.
She knows I had her bag.
So this is an interrogation.
Kariu-san.
Do you want this silver pin that badly?
Right for the jugular!
I heard you tried to run off with my bag.
Kaizaki-san told me.
That jerk!
She ratted me out for ratting Kariu out!
When I asked why you would do that,
he said your motive was this silver pin.
So I asked if we could
be friends if I gave you this,
and he said no way.
Yeah, no way.
Kariu-san.
Do you hate me?
Not really...
I...
Then why did you take my bag?
Why would you do that
to someone you don't hate?
She straight up asked.
I dunno how she can keep asking this stuff.
Doesn't it hurt her?
Well, it is Hishiro-san.
No, I...
Don't run.
Answer, Kariu.
I'm not...
...running anymore!
I hate you.
No matter how hard I try, I can't win.
You took what I wanted.
You stood where I wanted to.
And ever since you won, you've always,
always flashed that mocking smile,
so of course I hate you!
I've never mocked you.
You do! Every time our eyes meet!
I don't.
You do!
Why would I ever do that?
Don't ask me!
How can you deny it?!
That constant stream of sneers...
Every time our eyes meet,
every time we speak!
Next time you get a chance,
ask her to smile for you.
Wait...
Hishiro...
Smile for me.
Where did that come from?
Hold on. I'm trying to think
of a reason I'd mock—
Just do it!
A normal smile, like you'd do
if your eyes met someone's!
Like this?
You just freaked out.
Huh?
Er... wait... let me get this straight.
Huh? Huh?
Hishiro thinks that's a smile?!
She was trying for a friendly smile.
I thought Kaizaki was lying.
Smile again.
Stop.
Again.
Oh my god, you suck!
How is that a smile?!
Have you even looked in a mirror?!
Do you have any idea
how it makes people feel?!
I thought you were
mocking me this whole time!
I have been smiling in the hope
that we could be friends.
Wow, this girl...
How awkward can you be?
My strong point is I'm smart.
If I don't understand something,
I look into it on my own,
and if I still don't get it, I ask until I do.
My weak point is that
I'm not interested in other people.
She said it!
Because of that, I don't know
how to interact with anyone,
and I must have caused
lots of problems for people.
But right now, I'm trying to change myself.
Kariu-san, that's who I am.
But would you be my friend?
It's my pleasure, Hishiro Chizuru-san.
That day,
she wasn't intentionally
ignoring the handshake.
Okay, Hishiro Chizuru-san.
But in return, recognize me as your rival!
I won't lose next time!
I'll definitely take that silver pin from you!
If you want it, you can have it next test...
Don't you dare! I want it, but not like that!
If you hold back, we're not friends!
Not Friends
And...
I'm really sorry about all this.
I won't do it again.
Sorry.
I forgive you.
After all, we're friends.
Whoa, so you can actually smile.
But I smile all the time.
Yeah, right!
You told Hishiro about me.
But thanks.
What'd you take a picture for?
A test subject grinning
because a high school girl LIMEd him.
For my report.
Delete it!
Why are we drinking at my place, anyway?
What is all this?!
What's the big deal?
You helped them become friends.
Let's celebrate!
We've got school tomorrow.
For an ex-NEET, you sure are serious.
Not NEET! I was a part-timer!
Yoake-san...
Was what I told Kariu
really the right thing to say?
Resignation
In reality, I couldn't grow up,
and became a NEET.
And those awful bullies probably
still have their jobs.
I know the real truth is uglier.
Maybe it wasn't the ugly truth.
But it wasn't a lie.
It's what you really meant,
so isn't that enough?
When she's out in the
real world and stumbles,
she'll remember someone
yelling at her, if not who.
I think what happened today
will stay with her.
Oh.
Though, really, it was
the pot calling the kettle black!
Yelling at her for comparing
herself to others!
Says the man so worried about appearances,
he pretended he still had a job!
Shut up! I thought the same thing!
So? Are you liking ReLIFE?
Is it letting you take a long,
hard look at yourself?
The way you see through everything
is seriously driving me nuts!
Rena, see any empty seats?
Say, Honoka...
Thanks for the food.
I-I don't mind eating lunch with you.
I'm fine like this.
I like being alone.
Isn't that the problem?!
Don't you want to change?!
That's right.
Then, please.
Thank you.
D-Don't thank me!
We're friends!
This is normal!
NEXT EPISODE
Hishiro, you need to first
practice how to smile.
Grin.
Not like that.
But I thought I was doing it right.
Show me how it's done, Kariu-san.
Huh? Oh, all right.
This Isn't the First Time
H-Heh.
How stiff.
I don't wanna hear that from you!