ReLIFE Experiment Contract
ReLIFE Laboratory is an organization
that is developing a program
to rehabilitate people who have dropped out
of society: your so-called NEETs.
For a year starting this spring,
we want you to be a student,
and go back to high school!
I've come too far to turn back!
Fine, you're on!
I'll do this ReLIFE thing!
Communication Skills: Zero
I can't handle waking up this early.
Based on yesterday's tests,
the 3-3 class reps for the first term are:
Oga-kun for the boys,
and Hishiro-san for the girls.
Great to be working with you all!
I look forward to working with you all.
I failed all of them!
I don't believe Oga.
He's actually smart.
With these two leading you,
I hope you have a fun first term.
But he's so showy.
Kariu-san?
What's up with her? She looks furious.
But this year, she's in the same class as
Hishiro-san, the top scorer in our grade.
So she's all fired up now
and couldn't call in sick.
Oh, she must be mad
she didn't top the class.
Pleasure working with ya, Hishiro-san.
Likewise.
That's it for homeroom.
Drop by the staff room later
to pick up your silver pins.
Okay.
Sensei!
Too bad, huh, Kariu?
Why're you rubbing salt into her wound?
Get a clue, Oga!
But, well, you did have a cold.
Hope you can take her on
at full strength next time.
Whatever. It was all my fault,
including my failure to take care of myself.
I don't wanna use the cold as an excuse.
I just wasn't as good as her.
That's all.
You're so indifferent. Not cute.
Knock it off already, Oga.
Yeah, yeah, I'm not cute!
I bet you're glad you don't
have to work with me anymore!
Nah...
I don't think that.
What's with the persecution complex?
Just drop it already.
What the heck?
I was trying to cheer you up!
By talking down to me? Ugh.
Oh? Could it be?
Why are you so pissed?
Shut up!
Oh, I almost forgot. About the tests...
As always, if you failed even one,
you're going to take make-ups.
And you'll keep taking them
until you score higher than 50.
Study hard so you pass the first time.
F-Fifty or more on all of them?!
Endless make-ups!
What? You failed one, Kaizaki?
Not "one." All of them.
Wow, people like that actually exist?
By the way, which was the worst?
Math. I got a four.
Well, excuse me for getting a four!
Not everyone's as smart as you!
Yep, that's right.
It's the effort that counts.
Work hard, Kaizaki-kun.
O-Okay.
Same to the rest of you.
Right.
I could tutor you, if you like.
Sorry if I'm being too nosy,
but with those scores, who knows
when you'll escape the make-up loop?
I-I'm not sure if I should
feel insulted or not!
Um!
Could I get in on that?
Uh, Onoya-san?
You failed?
Yeah.
All of them.
Another complete failure!
Oh, and...
Kaizaki-kun.
Headed for the cafeteria?
Wanna eat lunch together?
Uh...
What should I do at times like these?
I'd be glad not to eat alone, but...
At this age, a boy and
a girl eating together...
Won't people make fun of her?
Can I join you?
We can get started on
our test prep planning!
Oh, good idea! Thanks!
Nice, Showga!
You coming, Kariu?
I'm eating with Honoka...
With Tamarai-san.
Oh, from the volleyball team?
Shame.
I'm gonna swing by the
staff room for the silver pin.
You know where the cafeteria is?
Yep. We'll grab seats.
What the heck is a silver pin?
Uh, I think it's...
the symbol of the class rep.
Bread
Noodles
Sets/Bowls
Register
Thanks for waiting!
Say, you and Kariu-san
seem awfully close.
Is she, like, your girlfriend?
She came right out and asked him.
But...
I was actually wondering the same thing.
Come on. Fess up.
N-No.
What gave you that idea?
You're not dating?
And here I thought I read people better.
One other question, then.
If she's not your girlfriend,
what's with the matching earrings?
Earrings?
Wow, you actually noticed that?
Well, in first year...
My brother insisted on piercing my ear.
It hurt so much,
I didn't let him do the other ear.
So the other half of this pair
is gonna go unused. Want it?
Are you seriously trying to fob it off on me
because you don't like it?
Figures.
I'll take it.
It's free, right?
But you play volleyball...
What's with you?
Are you giving it to me or not?
Make up your mind!
I am! Here!
Jeez.
Since you insist...
I'll gratefully accept it.
And she came in the very next day
with her ear pierced! Hilarious, right?
Anyway, that's all there is to it.
If you asked her if we were dating,
Kariu would go berserk!
Huh? What?
He might be book smart,
but he's the furthest thing from
an exemplary high school boy, huh?
Seriously. Total waste of a handsome face.
I feel sorry for Kariu-san.
Very sorry.
Why?
You should read more modern lit.
Focus your studies on comprehending
the emotions of the characters.
Wait, what? Why am I
being assigned homework?
Sorry, we can't.
Can't we please work it out?
What happened to prepping
for the make-ups?
Oh, dear.
Please.
Oh, it's the other class rep.
Nothing I can do.
What's she doing?
Looks like they're arguing.
I'll go see why.
Very well.
I'll go to the staff room
and be right back.
What's wrong, Hishiro-san?
It's the guy who got a four.
Don't mention that...
The cigarettes guy, then?
That's what you remember?
Sorry. It left quite the impression.
A-Anyway, are you in trouble?
I didn't bring any money out of habit.
I said to wait while I got the silver pin,
Students with silver pins are to state their name and class every time.
And please wait in line like the others.
- Cafeteria Head
but they'd already made the ramen, so...
Help, I need an interpreter!
Um, so...
Basically, you forgot your money
and can't buy lunch?
I didn't forget it.
I just didn't bring any.
Same thing.
Hishiro-san!
Here.
Borrow this.
Pay me back whenever.
I can't take that much.
Most things here don't cost
more than 300 yen.
And I think 1,000 yen is a pretty
large sum for a high schooler.
How can you lend me
that much money so casually?
It's like...
...you're a grown-up.
I-It's fine!
I just happen
to have extra today! Here!
It was an impulse,
but I just took a high school girl's hand!
Then I'll take you up on your kind offer.
Thank you.
I'll pay you back tomorrow.
What am I getting worked up about?
She's in high school!
No way!
Smooth.
What?
Very cool.
Though you're not at all book smart.
Knock that off!
She forgot her lunch money,
so I loaned her some.
Last year's best student
is a bit of a ditz, huh?
Nah, it's probably just because
she doesn't have her silver pin yet.
Why her silver pin?
When you've got this,
you can eat here for free.
For real?
We also get commute allowance,
tuition exemption, and all sorts of perks.
Whoa, that's pretty sweet.
But we'll never even
get a sniff of all that.
Oh, I get it now!
Kariu was trying for the silver pin—
No, she wasn't.
Onoya-san, you're harsh.
Call me An.
Really?
Then, An-chan.
Feel free to call me Kazu-kun—
I'll stick with Oga-kun. It's easier.
Wh-What are you thinking?
A cell phone at school?!
They'll confiscate it!
I read the school rules.
They aren't banned.
Gotta keep 'em off or
on vibrate in class, though.
What? Really?
Can I get your number?
Sure.
In my day, if you brought one in,
they'd take it for a month!
They don't even yell at you now?!
Arata-kun, what's yours?
You should call me An, too.
Sure. An, then.
Whoa! You just dropped the
honorific like it was nothing!
You're surprisingly good with girls.
I'm normal.
You're just weirdly naive, Oga-kun.
Apology Letter
An apology letter...
I wrote something, but is it good enough?
I have written plenty
of these for work, but...
The 1,000 yen,
score of four,
and cigarette guy.
Seriously, don't remember me like that!
Sorry. I couldn't recall your name.
But you're smart.
I think that's unrelated.
It's Kaizaki.
Kaizaki Arata.
I've memorized it. I'm Hishiro...
Um, why do you know my name?
I think you used it at lunch, too.
We did introductions yesterday,
and you were introduced in
this morning's homeroom, too.
That's all you needed?
But you're dumb.
Hey! That's going too far!
Don't say everything you think!
I apologize. I won't say it anymore,
even if that's what I think.
Oh, come on.
Staff Room
By the way, what were
you doing in the staff room?
Oh, did you get in trouble, too?
Do you actually mean that?
Sorry. That was a joke.
I came to pick up my silver pin.
Also, there was something
I didn't understand on the tests,
so I asked about it.
Whoa. You sure are serious.
Am I a serious, boring girl?
No, that's not it.
I heard you topped the grade last year,
so I just thought, "No wonder."
Sorry if I offended you.
No, I should be the one apologizing.
B-By the way, why do you
speak so formally to me?
Do you think I'm a delinquent
or scary or something?
I sure hope that's the case,
because it feels like she thinks I'm older,
and that's giving me heart attacks.
She said as much at lunch.
You're grown-up.
Not really.
This is how I talk to everyone.
Don't worry about it.
Is that so?
Does that make me unapproachable?
People tell me that a lot.
Even at this age,
I don't have any close friends.
I never thought that was a problem,
but apparently society does.
I keep thinking I need to change,
but I have no idea where to begin.
It would help if you could tell me honestly.
Am I really unapproachable?
Frankly speaking, yeah.
But I also feel like
you'd be worth getting to know.
I dunno, maybe try smiling a little more?
Smiling?
Like this?
You're kidding.
You just freaked out.
S-Sorry, it just wasn't
what I was expecting.
Then... like this?
No, that's the same!
No more! Abandon the smile strategy!
You'll make enemies, not friends!
If I can't even manage a polite smile,
I'll be in trouble in the real world.
Well, you don't have to rush things.
You'll make friends in time, I'm sure.
I thought I would, once.
Did I put my foot in it?
Oh, but I'm the same.
The future I assumed I would have
never came to me.
Of course I'd rush things.
This year is my last chance.
Oh, right.
We're third years.
Oh, sorry.
Kept you talking.
We'd better get home.
Um!
Can I have...
...your phone?
Huh?
Can you have... my phone?
I-I'm not sure how to respond to
this sudden attempt to mug me.
That's not it.
Fill in the blanks, please.
Excuse me?
Basically,
I mean...
I want to know your phone number.
I'm saying I want to be your friend.
I'm trying to take the first step
toward not being a friendless loner.
Please.
Figure that much out.
You really are dumb.
Sorry for not guessing all that.
But when you put it that clearly,
it won't be misunderstood, and I doubt
anyone would turn you down.
Well said.
Don't treat me like an idiot, idiot.
Would you drop the insults
about my intelligence already?!
You also seem like someone
worth getting to know.
Would you look at that?
You can smile.
I see. For better or worse,
she's an utterly straightforward girl.
You smiled when I loaned you
that 1,000 yen, too.
I did?
Ah, but don't try and force it!
Math's the killer.
It's especially easy to
get hooked at your age!
You won't be able to quit!
Yoake
Call
Yes... yeah...
Cigarettes?
Well, only your exterior looks young,
so that's not a problem.
Oh, okay.
But you'll probably find it hard to
buy them with your appearance.
May be a good time to quit!
Hard to shake the smell, after all.
You just got Hishiro-san to smile.
Can't have her turning against you!
What? You were watch—
Is she your type?
What the hell?!
Be nice to her.
I was in the same class with her last year,
and she was alone the whole time.
But, like I told you from the start,
after your one-year ReLIFE period is over,
classmates, teachers, and anyone
you dealt with will forget about you.
This is because 17-year-old
Kaizaki does not exist.
But your own memories
will remain, so don't worry.
If we erased those,
there'd be no point to the ReLIFE.
However...
If I tell anyone else about ReLIFE,
the experiment will end immediately.
And you'll wipe my memories and throw me out?
Exactly.
You can't talk about this. Ever.
If you do, you'll find yourself wondering
how you got to be twenty-eight
without remembering it.
So be careful, okay?
Hishiro Chizuru
New message
Close View
Hishiro Chizuru
Hello. This is Hishiro.
Thank you very much for today.
I promise to return the 1,000 yen tomorrow.
I look forward to knowing you further.
Is this a business e-mail?!
Whoa, a sticker!
Surprising.
Likewise.
Thanks for adding me on LIME.
By the way, this sticker of the sorry cat...
It kinda looks like you.
Uh oh, she's gonna get mad at me
for saying dumb crap again.
I didn't mean it in a bad way!
I dunno if she'll get that...
Meow.
I did not see that coming!
Yeah, she's pretty weird.
And adorable!
NEXT EPISODE
Having ramen for lunch, Hishiro-san?
I only eat tonkotsu ramen
at the cafeteria.
What, every day?
That's right. But the other day,
I ran into some trouble
due to not having my silver pin.
You're Old Now
You should be careful, Oga-san.
Okay!