Yoake-kun.
Got a sec?
What?
I told you not to talk to me
too much at school.
I want the drug that
makes me normal again.
This is the second time.
Before school started, you asked once,
so you could formally quit your job.
What's it for this time?
I want to visit a grave.
I know you've done your homework.
You know about my senpai
at that company, right?
This Monday...
...is the anniversary of her death.
A Trip to the Past
You can't go looking like this?
And risk running into someone else
who worked with us?
Not that any of them will show up.
Okay.
Then I'll come with you.
What? Hell, no.
Now, now, don't be mean.
No, seriously.
I know you need to keep an eye on me,
so just do it from a distance like always.
No need to come with me.
We were watching.
We know you froze up
at Saiki-san's grave last year.
We're worried about it.
Worried you might impulsively follow her.
Or not be able to control yourself
if a coworker shows up.
Th-That was last year!
I'm perfectly fine now.
What's wrong?
You don't look well.
What the hell?
Anyone would go pale if
someone tried to strangle them.
Well, excuse me.
I didn't apply that much pressure, though.
But you're doing better than you were
right after you resigned.
You couldn't even tighten a necktie then.
You know about that, too?
Of course.
You can visit the grave, and I'll get you
the medicine, but only if I can come with.
Understood?
Do whatever you want, you sadist.
Why, I appreciate the compliment!
I didn't give you one!
Trauma from the suicide
of the senpai he'd trained under
Huh? Senpai!
What are you up to?
Writing a medicine request for
Kaizaki-san and myself.
I can tell that much!
I wanna know why!
He wants to visit her grave.
If memory serves, it's dangerous
for him to go alone.
Okay, I'm going, too!
No.
For starters, they'll only approve it
for the assigned support.
I could totally go like this, though!
Two grown men and a high school girl?
No, thanks. I don't want
the police questioning me.
But sorry, Onoya.
I do have a favor to ask.
What's up with that suit?
How'd you know it was a suit?
It looks like one.
Memorial service.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have pried.
It's not often that you start a conversation.
That's true.
You admit it!
This medicine...
The change is done in about an hour.
What do you say?
Should we spend the hour together,
fighting off the drowsiness side effect?
That sounds awful.
We can just nap.
Fair enough.
Kaizaki-san, you wake up well, don't you?
Well...
You even look into that?
Yes.
Meanwhile, I'm the type
to sleep through alarms,
so wake me up if I do.
What? You sleep through alarms?
What do you do every morning?
If I have somewhere to be, I sleep sitting up
so that I don't sleep that deeply.
Like a samurai?!
How do you ever feel rested?
I mean, you've gotta do your job
on top of going to school.
I'm so happy!
We've really grown close.
You're even worrying about me!
You should really get a girlfriend
who'll wake you up.
Maybe An?
Oh, please!
I feel tired just thinking about
her waking me up!
I can see that.
I bet she wakes up hyper.
We'd better take these.
See you in an hour.
Yoake-san!
Yoake-san, it's time!
C'mon, wake up!
I can't. I'm sleepy.
Sleepy, my foot! Get up!
Shut up.
You told me to wake you!
Waking you up is exhausting.
Sorry!
It's been four months since
we met each other as adults.
Good evening.
Nice to meet you, Kaizaki Arata-san.
Time sure flies, huh?
A third of the way through.
Did you just look sad because you were
imagining this experiment ending?
No!
Like I said, I'm only in this for a year's
living expenses and a job introduction.
I won't be sad.
Onoya An
It's okay.
Got it. Thanks.
Saiki
Are you okay?
We've been here a while.
I'm fine. Shut up.
I'm talking to Senpai.
Talking
to
...
...Senpai
Um...
Are you sure you're okay?
Shut up, you tactless bastard!
I'm fine.
Jeez.
Kaizaki-kun.
Where should we get lunch?
This was your first big sale!
Let me, Michiru-senpai, treat you.
I was a new hire, and she was my trainer.
She had the best sales
record of any employee.
At first I was surprised
to be working under a woman in sales.
But Saiki Michiru-senpai was super friendly.
Daily overtime, hard work,
and wages that in no way justified it.
The mood was always tense.
The job I'd struggled to find
was at one of those black companies.
What? Running out of steam?
Keep it together, Kaizaki-kun.
Yet Senpai still visibly enjoyed her job.
She was strong and kind.
I admired her, and she kept me going.
Senpai, this...
This wasn't your mistake.
Someone must've sabotaged you!
A lot of people don't like me
just because I'm a woman.
Well, I've had enough!
If you won't say anything, I will!
You're absolutely right,
and I'm glad you feel that way.
But I want you to stay out of it.
Thank you, Kaizaki-kun.
I'll be fine!
So, Kaizaki-kun...
...grow up.
I heard what she said.
But I couldn't stand it.
Why won't she quit?
Knock it off. The new guy's here.
Oh. She's in charge of his training, right?
Don't rat us out, Kaizaki.
Why don't you stop that already?
You're grown men. Have you no shame?!
In the end,
I ignored what she said,
acted on my own sense of justice,
and wasted all her efforts to endure.
As a result, the harassment got even worse.
I'm fine.
I always thought she was strong.
But she was not "fine."
The cops closed their investigation.
They've concluded it was suicide.
No signs of foul play.
Make sure you keep this confidential.
Yes.
If I hadn't done that...
If I hadn't butted in...
Hey.
Who d'ya think'll get
promoted instead of Saiki?
Dunno... maybe me?
Yeah, right.
You're already doing this now?!
Saiki was very proud of our company.
I'm sure that's why she chose
to end things here.
She just loved this place that much.
I hold her much beloved company
as my pride and joy.
Well, get back to work.
What the hell?!
Knock it off already.
What the hell is wrong with you all?!
Someone just died here!
Don't you feel anything at all?!
How can you act like nothing happened?!
Don't you think that
maybe it was your fault?!
Calm down, Kaizaki.
Don't take it out on the others.
I'm done.
To hell with this company.
I quit.
After only three months?
Society will think you're gutless.
That fact'll be on your resume forever.
Do you think anyone else will hire you?
Resignation
Grow up, Kaizaki.
I'll forget this ever happened.
Grow up.
I'm afraid to go job-hunting again.
But that's better than...
...spending another second
in this rotten company!
Resignation
Kaizaki...
Only upper-level management
gets to "resign."
Scrubs like you "give notice."
You went to grad school,
and you don't know that?
We won't even notice you're gone.
Get out right this instant,
you piece of shit!
Get lost, and don't ever come back!
I lost my job.
I lost my confidence.
I grew afraid to engage with
people and society.
If I'd been more grown-up...
If I'd killed my emotions
and tried to fit in,
could I have remained a
productive member of society?
Would that have been better?
Kaizaki-san.
Are you okay?
Sorry.
I was lost in thought.
This sucks.
Coming here just fills me with regret.
Shall we go?
Yeah.
Um, are you Kaizaki-san?
We're from the same company,
hired a year after you.
I've seen your face in a company album.
And the old hires talk about you a lot.
Kamioka-kun!
Huh?
Sorry, I didn't...
Yeah, I bet that place
is still griping about me.
Yes...
Boss still loves to bring up the story of
the guy who quit after only three months.
He talks about Saiki-senpai
like a fallen warrior.
"She loved this company!
You should follow her example."
We'd just graduated.
We had no idea what
a normal workplace was like.
We didn't even know if we were
working for a black company.
We'd love to quit, but we're afraid
everywhere is like this,
so we just grumble and keep going.
They look half-dead.
Like they're desperately hanging on to
a thread that might snap at any second.
It feels like I'm looking at
myself from a year ago.
So it's an honor to meet you!
You're practically our hero!
Giving that president
a piece of your mind and walking out?
That's awesome.
Nah...
I was just a dumb kid.
No patience, ruled by emotion.
No.
We don't have the courage to take action.
Not everyone can do what you did.
You have no idea what a help it's been to know
we weren't the only ones who thought
our company was messed-up.
We really admire you.
And Saiki-senpai.
I never thought my rebellion
would have such an effect.
Kaizaki-senpai,
has it been hard?
After leaving?
What are you doing now?
Sorry. Just... it would help to know.
After I quit,
I couldn't do anything for a while.
But you have to work to live.
I started looking for another job.
The day of my first interview,
I realized I couldn't wear a necktie anymore.
When they asked me why I quit
after three months,
I couldn't find the words to explain myself.
In time, I regained my ability
to get through interviews,
but I never did get hired.
Then I got sick and tired of it all, gave up,
and got a job at a convenience store.
You still work there?
Uh... no.
Now, I'm...
Keep it together, Kaizaki-kun.
Uh, yeah.
I'm still doing part-time work.
It's kinda hard to face
my friends with real jobs.
Sorry, but that's reality.
Oh, don't be.
But...
Even so,
I'm not selfless enough to give my one
and only life to that shitty company!
Hindsight is 20/20 and all that,
but there are people I've met because I quit.
I'm in a world I would never have
experienced if I'd stayed.
Now...
I'm glad I quit.
Aren't you glad?
Your existence gives strength to
the people who came after you.
Yoake-san.
You knew, didn't you?
What?
That the new hires saw me in that light.
You arranged things so we'd
bump into each other there.
Aw, no way!
That was pure coincidence.
But why'd you lie and say you were
still doing part-time work?
You have a real job!
I do?
You're a test subject, and you're getting
paid enough to make ends meet.
I'd call that a job.
Sure, but it's not a job I found myself.
I really did struggle after I quit.
And I wound up here because
I didn't find work.
It'd be irresponsible to tell them
I'd found a real job again.
You'll pretend you have work
in front of your friends
but tell your juniors the truth?
No wonder you're a hero to them.
Don't mess with me. I'll get mad.
Huh? But I mean it!
Yeah, right.
Sorry, Onoya.
I do have a favor to ask.
I'll be with Kaizaki-san the whole day,
so keep me updated on
what these two are up to.
New hires this year
at Kaizaki-san's old company.
They've visited Saiki-san's grave
several times before.
I thought they might go on
the anniversary of her death, too.
If he learns that what he did gives hope
to those that came after him,
it might help him start looking forward.
Wow...
You dug that deep for Kaizaki-san?
That's what the Support Division's
supposed to do.
But won't they say you're
getting too involved again?
I'm just bringing them together.
The rest is up to Kaizaki-san.
How'd Kaizaki-san do?
I saw him talking to the new hires
but couldn't hear what they said.
What were they talking about?
Tell me, Senpai!
I can't stop thinking about it!
Sorry, sorry.
Yeah, I think he's
feeling better.
Thanks.
I'm glad I talked to them.
Knowing that my voice and Senpai's
reached someone
doesn't erase the guilt
I feel for not saving her,
but it helps.
Whenever I went there, I'd always
end up regretting everything.
And I'm sure she was watching with a face
that screamed, "Get a hold of yourself!"
I could finally tell her I was glad I'd quit.
If not for ReLIFE...
If I'd been alone,
I couldn't have said that.
All I did was stand there and watch.
Shut up!
Just say, "You're welcome!" Yeesh!
I should say the same.
Thank you.
Why? Creepy.
Now who won't say, "You're welcome"?
God, you're obnoxious.
NEXT EPISODE
You're still taking make-ups, Arata?
Shut up. Leave me be.
As you wish.
I didn't mean that! Help me, Oga-sama!
Kazu-kun! Showga!
Summer break's almost here—
wait, what's with that nickname?!
Double Panic
Oh, yeah, summer vacation!