Fireworks Festival
Good morning.
Mornin'!
Not often that you start
a conversation.
Is that so?
What are you grinning for?
It's creepy.
Creepy?!
Huh?
Are those new hair ties?
Yes. Kariu-san and Tamarai-san
gave them to me.
As thanks for the other day.
Seems like Hishiro-san's
starting to change, too.
Morning, Arata-kun!
An! Jeez!
Morning, Hishiro-san!
Good morning, four-eyed braid girl.
I have a name. It's Onoya An.
Remember it already,
Hishiro Chizuru-san.
It is far too early to be that hyper.
I have low blood pressure,
so honestly, I envy you.
Whoa, even Hishiro-san
gets jealous sometimes!
But is that really caused
by low blood pressure?
Onoya-san! Good morning!
Got a minute?
What? Hey!
Sorry, Hishiro-san!
For the loud interruption.
I'm gonna borrow her for a minute!
Okay...
O-Ow! That hurts!
Let go!
I think that's the first time
I've seen you talking to Yoake-kun.
You know each other?
Ryo was in my class last year.
"Ryo"?
W-Wait, you call Yoake-kun "Ryo"?
Yes.
He asked me to.
You're pretty close, huh?
Are we?
Wait. Don't jump to conclusions.
She calls Oga "Kazu-kun" like he told her to.
But...
Ryo
Kazu-kun
What's with this difference?
Kaizaki-san
I can't accept this!
Th-Then call me Arata—
Sorry. Never mind.
Why?
It's just a name.
Double Panic
How old am I?
Summer vacation!
You look super happy.
Damn straight I am!
These long vacations are to be treasured!
Do you even get that, young students?
Oh yeah, Arata. You had to take
make-ups after the finals, too.
Have you passed them yet?
Huh?
No, not yet.
Then you'll be doing make-ups
during summer vacation, too.
Even during summer vacation?!
So I hear.
I've never had to take one myself.
But I've been taking make-ups
the entire first term...
You reap what you sow.
I'll be coming to prep for entrance exams.
Let's eat lunch together.
Entrance exams?
Oga, you're going to some other college?
Hmm...
I'm still considering just going on
to Aoba University,
but I'd like to keep my options open,
so I'm gonna take the
Center Exam Prep Course.
Oh, I see...
Okay, homeroom's starting.
Oga-kun, Hishiro-san.
A big hand for our first-term class reps.
Oh.
Yoake-san mentioned this high school
was affiliated to a college.
Guess most of them go there.
Lucky them.
They get to be together in college, too.
"Lucky them"? Come on.
It has nothing to do with me.
So, to celebrate successfully
surviving the first term...
Cheers!
Again, how come we always
have to drink at my place?
Well, looking like this,
we can't go out to drink.
Can't even buy booze!
But here, we can get the lab to deliver it!
And we can expense it all!
Such horrible grown-ups!
Oh, sorry.
We'd like to know your summer
vacation plans as soon as possible,
but you don't have any, right?
You're too busy taking make-ups
to even visit your family!
Can you pass before the vacation ends?
You two...
Anyway, if you do go anywhere,
let us know ahead of time.
It may be a vacation,
but we still have to observe.
I know.
That said, Onoya and I will be
joining in summer school,
so we'll see you there.
Oh? You will?
Part of our job is studying furiously
so we can convincingly act like students.
First Oga, now you two.
Lots of ways to handle summer vacation.
Oh, yeah! Speaking of Oga-kun!
He really hasn't noticed, has he?
How Kariu-san feels.
Apparently not.
Unless the rest of us do something,
those two will never get anywhere.
I know!
We need to make Oga feel
some danger, you know?
That's it!
Okay, Senpai, go after Kariu-san!
With your adult charm!
Listen to yourself.
If another guy gets close to
Kariu-san and tempts her,
even Oga would have to feel something!
You know...
Kariu-san is one thing,
but how does Oga-kun feel?
Is this really something we should be
getting worked up about?
We're all old enough
to know better than to toy
with the hearts of children.
What is this sadist talking about?
After all the time he's spent
toying with my heart?
No way.
You drunkards.
What about you, Kaizaki-san?
There's no helping those who are
as innocent as Kariu-san.
But there's no reason you couldn't
have something like that.
Get myself a high school girlfriend?
Ha! What a joke.
There's no reason you couldn't.
A one-year, limited edition of youth.
You're an illusion.
They'll forget you, anyway.
I know.
You don't need to remind me.
Arata! Sorry I'm late.
Lunch time?
It's kinda unusual to see you
bring lunch from home.
The cafeteria's closed.
I make one for my dad every day,
so I just double up during holidays.
Huh? You made that?
Yeah. I cook a lot.
Really? I seriously didn't expect that.
Falling for me yet?
Totally...
So, how'd the make-ups go?
I failed them.
Thought so.
Shut up!
Kariu-san is one thing,
but how does Oga-kun feel?
Say, Oga...
I've never heard any rumors
about your love life.
Hm?
No, not "hm."
You ever dated a girl before?
Huh? No! Where'd this come from?
Any ask you out?
Um... yeah.
And you said no?
But seriously, what is this?!
Oh...
I was just wondering
if there's anyone you like.
Anyone I like?
I like everyone!
What kinda answer is that?!
What's wrong with your head?
My head's better than yours any day!
We are clearly talking about love! Romance!
Why do you look baffled?!
Okay, for example...
Like, someone you always
find yourself with, or...
Oh, a girl, a girl.
And you go, "She's interesting."
"She's fun."
You can talk about anything.
You don't want anyone taking her away.
You wanna hold hands.
You wanna kiss her.
Maybe go all the way?
I've never looked at anyone like that!
I was speaking hypothetically.
Asking if you had anyone like that.
Okay, okay.
Studying's important,
but I think love is, too.
It's the last summer of high school.
It's a precious time that won't come again.
Before you know it, you'll be
the only single guy you know!
What's wrong? You okay?
I self-destructed.
My chest hurts.
Arata...
Have you...
...ever done it?
You know,
like, kissed a girl?
I have.
Even though you're dumb?!
Hey! What's that got to do with it?
But it's you!
Don't reject my very being!
Apologize to my parents.
That's so naughty!
Are you really a modern high school boy?
Dirty!
Hey!
English Pop Quiz - 50 minutes
Studying's important,
but I think love is, too.
It's the last summer of high school.
It's a precious time that won't come again.
"Won't come again"? That's every summer.
Idiot.
You wanna hold hands.
You wanna kiss her.
I've never looked at anyone like that.
Ever.
Argh...
I ended up wasting
almost the whole day!
Vacation: Ruined.
But it's still a lot easier than
attending an exam school.
You call this easy? You really know
how to get on my nerves.
Oh, man!
My head hurts.
What the heck?
Kariu!
Kariu and...
It's that new guy?!
Why?!
If anyone finds out about ReLIFE,
the experiment ends.
What's Kariu doing?
He's not a student!
And he's kinda scary!
It's not some sort of hookup site thing?
K-Kariu, of all people,
would never do that.
I don't think he's up to
anything that creepy, either.
He's trying to get her in his car!
What now? He's kidnapping her!
N-No, I really don't think so...
But what are they doing?
This clearly isn't any kind of date.
Kariu's resisting.
Kariu!
Oga?!
Hey! Why did you just run out?!
P-P-Please, don't call my name!
Don't get me mixed up in this!
Um...
Your boyfriend?
No! A friend from class!
What?
What are you doing here, Oga?
Coming home from exam prep.
What about you?
Um... well...
Oh, I see.
A friend!
Perfect timing!
This girl's got a touch of heat stroke.
I just happened to pass by.
Heat... stroke?
I asked if she wanted me
to call an ambulance,
but she said it wasn't that bad.
So I took her somewhere cool
and got her a drink,
and she's doing better.
That's pretty much what I thought.
And given how hot it is,
I didn't wanna let her walk off alone,
so I offered to drop her at the station.
But obviously she doesn't want
to get into a strange man's car.
We were at an impasse.
Well? Can I leave you with him, then?
Uh... yeah...
Bye!
Just 'cause you're young,
don't take the heat lightly.
Careful!
Thank you.
What a gentleman!
I heard all that.
Looks like things are gonna work out,
so I'm going home.
Walk Kariu home, okay?
He went home?!
Oga?
Are you really okay?
Yeah.
I'll walk you to the station.
I'm headed home, too.
Oga...
Um...
Thanks for, uh, worrying about me.
What?
You're being so sincere today
that it's kinda weird.
Ow!
Weird?!
You picked the worst timing to say that!
Sorry! I messed up!
I clearly messed up!
Jeez!
What? Why are you laughing
after I hit you?
You're scaring me!
No, I just thought, we're always like this.
It's fun.
Oh, really. Glad you're enjoying yourself.
I was just wondering
if there's anyone you like.
You don't want anyone taking her away.
You wanna hold hands.
It's the last summer of high school.
It's a precious time that won't come again.
A one-year, limited edition of youth.
You're an illusion.
They'll forget you, anyway.
What do I do, Arata?
I'm in love with Kariu.
I-It's happening!
When I was walking Kariu to the station,
I wanted to hold her hand.
That's how I realized.
Stop giving me that look!
Sorry, I can't stop smiling.
Creep!
Listen up, Oga.
Now that you've noticed,
you've gotta be a man and take action.
There's a fireworks festival soon, right?
Fireworks Festival
Invite her to it, and fess up.
Fess up?
You mean tell Kariu I love her?
Of course.
What else would you tell her?
She'd punch me!
Yeah, maybe.
But are you okay with dawdling about?
Someone else might claim her.
No...
Please, stop doing that!
A confession?
Ah, youth!
When did you all get here?!
Well, we thought you could use
a young girl's point of view.
"Young" girl?
Uselessly dense
Tag-along
But even if I do wanna confess,
I just don't know where to begin.
An-chan, how would you like a boy
to confess his feelings?
As long as he puts his heart into it,
it really doesn't matter.
Hishiro-san?
Sorry.
I have no experience with these things,
so I don't know.
I see...
Yoake-kun, how would you do it?
You seem so grown-up,
I'm sure you'd make for a great reference.
I've never done it, either.
Don't really know.
Sorry!
Then... Arata?
How'd you lure all your girls?
You've had lots, right?
I did not say that.
No, you're so relaxed around them.
You've known a lot of girls.
That's normal!
Kaizaki-san has a lot of
experience with women?
How grown-up.
No, it's normal!
We're in third year!
Well, I apologize for being abnormal.
Not what I meant!
Stop smiling and help me out here,
you support people!
Y-Yoake-kun, surely you've asked
someone out or been asked out!
You're eighteen, right?
I'm still seventeen!
That's beside the point!
But I bet Arata-kun's
pick-up lines are great!
I see. I really am abnormal.
You've gotta tell me! I need help here!
I'm sorry I'm so abnormal.
Stop!
Fine, okay.
I've made up my mind.
I'll invite Kariu to
the fireworks festival...
...and confess!
Kariu, are you free on the 10th?
Wanna go to the
fireworks festival together?
What?! What the hell is this?!
Did he send it to the wrong person?
No, it says "Kariu"...
Why?
A-Anyway, I'd better see
what Honoka and Hishiro think...
It seems Oga just invited me
to the fireworks festival.
I got it, too! Sounds like fun!
I got one, too.
I've been doing homework
and studying all summer,
so it'll be nice to take a breather.
He sent it to everyone...
I got all worked up for nothing...
But sure, why not?
That's just like Oga.
I got one, too.
I've been doing homework and studying all summer,
so it'll be nice to take a breather.
Are you gonna wear a yukata, Hishiron?
I don't have one.
Then let's go shopping together!
I was thinking of getting a new one myself.
NEXT EPISODE
Hishiro, do you like green?
Yeah. You like drab colors, Kaizaki-san?
Drab? I guess I own a lot of dark colors.
Oh, but I like bright colors, too. Red, or...
Confession
I'll keep that in mind.
Huh? What for?