Heart
Stirring
Pangs
Did you mean: Love?
"Did you mean... love"?
No...
Impossible.
That's just...
...not possible.
This Isn't the First Time
Hey there! Arata?
How's your Golden Week going?
What do you want, Oga?
It's going nowhere.
I'm just lying around at home.
Oh, really?
Right now, I'm actually with An-chan...
...right outside your place!
Open up!
Huh? Hang on...
What are you doing here?!
I told you the other day
that we'd need to study
over Golden Week!
Hello?
Gimme ten minutes!
Think he's got something
he doesn't want us to see?
Probably.
Damn it! If you're
coming over, tell me first!
How do they even know where I live?!
It reeks!
Come in.
That took forever!
Thanks for having us!
Sit wherever.
I've only got tea. Want some?
Oh, I'll help!
It's okay!
I've got it! You sit down!
You sure?
Arata, what is this?
What?
This.
An MD.
MD?
Oh, a floppy?
No, an MD.
It's got music on it.
Seriously?
Kids these days haven't even heard of them?
You've got some neat stuff!
Okay! Let's start studying!
Let's pass those make-ups!
I'm beat...
You need to focus!
I solved it!
Only one!
Actually, Arata,
I dunno how you got into Aoba.
We're a pretty decent prep school.
How did you get in when you're so dumb?
Th-That's so rude!
You can't call it rude at this point.
It's just a fact.
I guess that goes for me, too?
Maybe this year's transfer exam was easy?
Huh? Was it really?
An, you're, like, always on your phone.
Huh? Am I?
Yeah, I thought the same thing.
At lunch or whenever.
Is that so? Sorry!
Who are you chatting with?
Boyfriend?
Come on, Arata-kun!
Sexual harassment!
Sorry, I didn't mean to...
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Sorry, I didn't realize.
I'll be more careful.
By the way, Oga-kun...
You wear clothes like those normally.
Normally?
I mean,
the uniform's cardigan
is super baggy on you.
Oh, that's a hand-me-down
from my brother.
Plus you're really skinny.
No wonder you could only throw
that handball two meters.
You're one to talk, Mr. One Meter!
Well, it probably hasn't stopped you
from being popular.
For sure.
Even I find you good looking,
and I'm a dude.
If only he'd just go out with her already.
Seriously. He's just so dense!
What are we talking about?
Oga-kun, if you got a girlfriend,
I think I could pass these make-ups.
Me, too.
Seriously, what are we talking about?!
You always derail things like this!
Please! Just study properly!
Okay.
All said and done,
this sort of thing is kinda fun.
Though calling them "friends"
might be too impudent of me,
a guy who's ten years older.
Okay, this could actually work out!
Numbers... Numbers scary...
I feel sick...
Oga...
You study this hard all the time?
What? This is nothing!
Our standards are totally different...
I mean, you'll be in trouble if you
don't pass the make-ups next week.
Midterms are the week after.
And if we fail those?
More make-ups.
Are you serious?
It's an infinite loop of make-ups!
You don't plan to get out?
Anyway, I think you'd better pass next week.
What about your own studies?
Are you sure you should be
hanging around with us?
Final Interview
3rd and 1st
Resume Deadline
I didn't expect you to
fail this many make-ups.
So he says,
An?!
Where'd that come from?
Er... I, uh...
There!
There was a bug on the wall!
No way!
B-But I got it!
Sorry.
I'll just pop outside.
N-N-N-No!
Why?
My laundry's drying!
Big deal. I don't mind.
I do!
They're gonna hang up! Answer it!
All right...
Hello?
This is Oga.
Oh, thanks for all the hard work.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Right.
Got it. I'll be right over.
Okay.
Sorry. I've gotta go to work.
Work?
The convenience store on Third.
They're short-staffed and
asked me to come in.
Oh, is that why you always
rush out when school ends?
Yup. Sorry.
So, you two make sure
you get through the rest.
We will! Thanks!
Whoa there, Oga!
Take An with you!
Why?
This isn't good!
I'm a dude living alone here!
Huh?
So what?
Do you actually have the brain
of a high school boy?!
How can you be so astonishingly pure?!
No can do. You've gotta
finish your quota.
Bye!
A-Are you sure you don't want to leave?
Yeah, I'm good.
Oga-kun's so nice, isn't he?
He's got his own studies and job,
but he teaches us with all his heart.
We have to pass!
Yeah.
Hello.
This is Yoake from Support.
Requesting permission for status
surveillance on subject no. 002.
Status surveillance?
Please hold.
Connected.
Hey, Arata-kun.
What was up with that calendar?
Notes about interviews and resumes...
What were those?
Work...
I guess?
I was looking for part-time work.
Arata-kun, did you ever work...
...at a convenience store?
By the station?
Y-Yeah.
How'd you know?
I knew it!
I actually met you there!
Remember me now?
Sorry.
Figures.
You seemed more grown-up there.
And really cool.
Well... I guess...
...the store uniforms make you look older?
Do they really?
But I'm really glad that we're
the same age, in the same school,
and that we met again
in the same class.
It's like destiny.
That voice is...!
The regulation five-minute status
surveillance has concluded.
This is Yoake from Support.
Detecting unusual circumstances with
subject no. 002, Kaizaki Arata.
Requesting surveillance extension.
Permission granted. Connect now?
Please do.
I...
...fell in love with you at first sight.
So being alone with you
like this is exciting.
Arata-kun, does being alone
with me do nothing for you?
Aren't you...
...excited?
Uh, well...
I... sorry.
This is too sudden. I can't think.
You're turning red.
W-Well, duh.
Are you in love with anyone?
Why Hishiro-san?!
I don't think so...
You don't think so, huh?
Then...
If I said I wanted to be your girlfriend,
would you accept?
Arata-kun...
I love you.
If it's consensual,
it's not illegal or anything.
But Kaizaki-san could never
do anything like that!
How many times...!
Arata-kun...
Hey, An!
I can't, An.
You should take better care of yourself.
This sort of thing isn't...
Yoake?
Wait, the door!
The lock! Huh?!
Oh, don't worry, I didn't break it.
I have a spare key.
Why do you have one?!
Huh?
Yoake-kun from class, right?
A spare key?
Are you two lovers?!
No!
That's enough, Onoya.
Starting with no honorific?
And your hand...
Would you let go?
What?
Are you mad because you thought
I'd take Arata-kun from you?
Wait...
We're not allowed to make
excessive contact with our subjects.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Eating lunch with him every day...
Deliberately joining his studies...
And now forcing your way into his home...
What are you doing?
This isn't a laughing matter, Onoya.
Y-Yoake-san, what...?
Aw!
Why'd you have to tell him, Yoake-senpai?
I could have done far more to support him
if he'd thought I was a real high school girl.
Shut up!
Who knows what else you'd do?
I wasn't, like, serious about him.
I was just testing him.
Um...
Look...
There have been way too many twists,
and I'm not following this at all.
I mean, I can sorta guess
from your conversation...
Do you work for the ReLIFE Laboratory?
Hello! I'm Onoya An from the ReLIFE
Laboratory Support Division.
Nice to meet you formally,
Kaizaki Arata-san!
Then what was...?
"Love at first sight"?
Oh...
Just kidding!
Just... kidding!
Just
kidding!
So the reason you're always
on your phone...
Yeah, work conversations!
Mostly Yoake-senpai yelling at me
for getting too close to you.
So,
how old are you really?
Forever seventeen, dude!
Twenty-seven this year.
Then what about Yoake-san?
Wait, did I not say?
Same age as you.
Twenty-eight this year.
We're equals?!
Well, sorry for tricking you,
but it was good practice
for the future, right?
Future?
If a real high school girl comes after you,
you'll know just what to do!
You were a total gentleman!
Enough. This is wearing me out.
Is everyone in the Support Division
a walking joke?
How rude!
You're the same!
Grinning while you toy with people's hearts!
I'm not joking around.
Today was a proper part
of your ReLIFE experience!
How so?
Um... well...
Sometimes subjects use the fact
that no one will remember them
to do bad things.
Bad things?
Like messing around with high school girls.
I-I...
Today, I believed in you,
but I tested your character a bit.
Sorry about that!
Honestly, I have no idea what
goes through her head sometimes.
Right, Onoya?
Yikes, Yoake-senpai's mad.
Seriously, I rushed here worried that
we'd have to cancel the experiment.
You needn't have.
That's the subject I picked for you!
Onoya!
Not all of my confession was a lie.
Wait, what?
When I looked over the subject data,
I did fall for "Kaizaki Arata" at first sight.
And we did meet last year at your store.
Onoya!
Truth is, Yoake-senpai wasn't supposed
to be your support. I was.
Onoya!
But I couldn't finish
my training in a year!
Training?
He really doesn't want me to tell you,
but Yoake-senpai is the same.
He was in training at Aoba for two years!
The training period is only
supposed to last a year.
Right, Yoake-senpai?
That's right.
So in place of Onoya,
I took over as your support.
You may still be in training,
but you got too close!
Give it a rest, really.
Ow, ow, ow! Sorry, sorry!
Anyway, sorry for lots of things about today.
We hope to keep working with you.
S-Sure.
Stop that! Raise your heads!
I'm not that mad.
Yoake-san, c'mon!
An, c'mon!
Sorry, Kaizaki-san.
Half of that was true.
Half of that wasn't.
NEXT EPISODE
Senpai, what did you mean,
half of that was true and half wasn't?
I never said anything like that.
But I felt like I heard you thinking it.
My, you talk like you know it all, Onoya.
Test Subject 001 -> 002
Well, I have known you for a long time.