So you came.
Thank you.
You're the one who wrote this love letter?
Yes.  That's right.
Could you... give me an answer?
I hope it'll be a good one.
Um... I don't really know you very well.
Have we met somewhere before?
And... are you really okay with someone like me?
Of course I am!
I wouldn't want anyone else.
Because you're the one I like...
Am I no good?
Not at all!
I'm overjoyed to be able to date a cute girl like you!
No way... cute?
I'm so happy...
If you're fine with me...
Huh?!
W-What's wrong?
I'm happy.
I'm so happy...
I'm happy I was able to tell you my feelings.
I'm Kamizaki Risa from class 2-B...
And I'll be your girlfriend starting today, Tachibana Junichi!
I'll do anything if it'll make you happy.
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Typesetter: fnord
Stuff: ar
I can't wait to try your Oden, Hibiki-chan.
What a shame.  Looks like we ran out of time.
Y-Yeah.
Kamizaki Risa Arc
Truth
Could you come here again during lunch tomorrow?
We'll continue from where we left off then.
Yeah.
Tomorrow at lunch, I'm gonna continue from where I left off with Risa-chan!
1600 AD, in the battle of Sekigahara...
I should probably introduce Risa-chan to Umehara and Kaoru.
They've been worried about me since that Christmas incident two years ago...
But I'm fine now.
I'm sure this year's Christmas will be a happy one.
Because I've have a really cute girlfriend now!
It's finally lunchtime!
I can't wait to meet up with Risa-chan!
Huh?  You're already here?
Yeah.
Um... I couldn't wait to see you, Tachibana-kun...
I see.
I couldn't wait to see you too,
so I came here as fast as I could...
But you beat me to it.
I'm so happy that you came.
O-Of course I'd come!
And... I'm also really happy I could see you, Risa-chan.
We're lovers, aren't we?
Yeah.
So when did you first start to... um... like me?
Since a long time ago.
Huh?
I've always been watching you, Tachibana-kun.
Really...
Um... can I ask you something too?
What?
Are my boobs kinda small?
You prefer big ones, don't you?
I'm sorry I don't have much of a chest...
T-That's not true at all!
It's not like bigger is better.
And I think there are nice things about small ones too...
You don't have to pretend.
I know you like bigger ones.
How do you know that?!
I saw you once before...
You were reading that kind of book at the bookstore.
Big boobs idol
Uh... that was um...
That's what Umehara likes!
T-That doesn't mean I like the same thing!
No... I'm sure guys like them big.
Mine are small now, but I'm working hard.
I'm still growing too.
So... wait a little longer, okay?
Really, it's not like I like big ones that mu-
Wait, what do you mean by working hard?!
That's a secret.
But... I'm doing all kinds of things...
All kinds of...
That's right!
Risa-chan, I'd like to introduce you to my friends...
Is that okay?
As my girlfriend.
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
Why?
That's the one thing I can't do.
We can't let anyone know that we're dating.
We can't.
That's why I want to make sure nobody sees us when we meet.
We can only meet in this unused preparation room in school.
I'm sorry.
I won't tell anyone that we're dating, Risa-chan.
When we meet, we'll meet somewhere secluded.
Tachibana-kun...
I just have to keep that promise, right?
Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Nobody comes here at night, so I don't think anyone will see us together here.
Yeah, this place is okay.
This is a date... right?
I'm so happy.
Yeah.
It's a date.
But are you fine with this place, Tachibana-kun?
Huh?
I don't think it's a place you like very much.
So you know about what happened two years ago?
Ah... yeah.
I see.
I was stood up here on Christmas Eve two years ago.
I guess it's true that my memories of this place aren't exactly great.
But you know...
I'll remember this place as the place where I had my first date with you, Risa-chan.
2 days until the
Founder's Festival!
Boss!
It's the Founder's Festival the day after tomorrow.
Yep.
Unfortunately, I still don't have a nice girlfriend.
If by some freak chance I don't
find one before the day arrives...
I don't mind walking around the place with you, boss.
Sounds good.
But if I were to suddenly find an awesome girlfriend...
I'm afraid you'll have to walk around on your own.
Oh?
Big words, buddy!
Hey, how about putting meat buns in the Oden?
What?
No good?
I really want to go to the Founder's Festival with you tomorrow...
Indeed, it's Christmas Eve.
I do want to tour the festival with you too, Tachibana-kun...
But...
Just for tomorrow!
Ever since my heart was broken two years ago, Umehara's always been looking out for me.
But I have a cute girlfriend now.
I want to let him know I'm okay!
Please let me think about it.
I'll let you know before the Founder's Festival tomorrow.
Will I be able to go to the Founder's Festival with Risa-chan tomorrow?
Ugh!
Now that I'm finally Tachibana-kun's girlfriend, what should I do?!
Of course I'd want to go to the festival with him!
I want all the girls to see he's my boyfriend so they'll know to keep their hands off!
But...
I can't let people know that I'm his girlfriend at this point.
I've done horrible things to every girl who got close to him...
Purr, meow!
Why is he getting along so well with Morishima-senpai?!
Meow!
Didn't she already reject him?!
No, of course not.
In fact, I loved it!
This is bad.
They might grow close and even start dating at this rate!
I can't let that happen.
He might be hurt like he was two years ago.
I have to protect Tachibana-kun.
So you have some business with me?
Yes.
Um... I'd like you to look at this.
Is this a picture of Tachibana-kun?
Yes.
And could this girl with him in the picture be...
Yes, she seems to be his girlfriend.
So after seeing the two of you get along so well, I felt the need to let you know.
I'm surprised.
Yes, I was surprised myself.
Well, I have nothing more to say now that I've seen this photo.
I'll be sure to stay away from him so I don't give him the wrong impression.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Thanks for telling me.
See you.
Senpai, I'm sorry.
But it's for the best.
I have to protect Tachibana-kun.
Wait a minute, why is she being so friendly with him at work?!
Actually, do your damn job!
They're supposed to just be friends!
I can't just ignore this.
Is this what I think it is?
Yes.
I'm pretty sure it is.
Since you didn't seem to know about it, Tanamachi-san...
Thanks for letting me know.
He's such a baby.
He should've just told me he already had somebody.
And here I was working myself up...
I feel like such a fool.
I'm sorry.
But it's for the best.
Instructor, I see her as a vending machine!
Wait, now he's getting close with that underclassman?!
All right, now try again!
I know Tachibana-kun is a wonderful person...
But this isn't good!
I feel bad for her since she seems like a timid girl, but...
It's for the best.
Excuse me, do you have a moment?
Y... Yes?
She looks really shocked.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure she'll find someone else right away since she's so cute.
Her boobs are huge though.
I wonder if Tachibana-kun really prefers girls with bigger boobs...
In that case, I'm sorry, but could you wait outside until practice is over?
Yeah, okay.
Making Tachibana-kun wait until practice is over?
What's wrong with her?!
Don't tell me she's already acting like she's his girlfriend?
I can't let that happen!
So that's how it is.
Tachibana-kun already has a girlfriend.
Sorry.
I know it's not really my place to have told you this...
Doesn't really matter to me.
Thank you for letting me know.
I'll be careful not to give him the wrong impression.
Huh?  It didn't seem like much of a shock to her.
But I guess that's a good thing.
I won't feel quite as bad for doing this...
Ouch!
So it was a shock to her...
I'm sorry.
She's supposed to just be his childhood friend, but they've suddenly gotten really close!
I can't let this continue.
I don't want to hurt her since she's my classmate, but...
Junichi...
Sakurai-san, cheer up!
Sorry to make you come with me like this.
She's taking advantage of Tachibana-kun's good nature and working him so hard...
Not at all.  Let me know if you need anything else.
Unforgivable!
It looks like she's been using him after he
joined the committee to do all kinds of work.
Wait, is she after Tachibana-kun himself?!
If that's the case, I must do something!
Hmph.
Ayatsuji-san, so that's who you're really are...
She's like a completely different person!
She'd have no problems deceiving Tachibana-kun for sure.
I'm glad I was able to protect him.
If that incident two years ago had never happened...
I could've just confessed to him normally without having to get in everyone's way.
Huh?  Tachibana-kun?
Makihara... san?
It's been so long!
So you're attending Kibitou right now?
That uniform looks good on you.
And you're attending Kibina?
Yep.
It's close to where I live.
How is Makihara-san able to speak to me so casually?
She's the one who stood me up for our Christmas date two years ago...
You know...
There's something I've always
wanted to ask you, Tachibana-kun.
Can I?
Huh?  What is it?
That day... Christmas, two years ago...
Why didn't you show up where we were supposed to meet?
Huh?!  But...
I waited in this park the whole time!
Huh?
Didn't you change the meeting place?
I never did that.
But a girl in our class told me you
wanted to change the meeting spot.
I was waiting in front of the cinema for ages.
I don't know how that happened.
Well... you know her?
She doesn't exactly stand out very much, but that one girl...
Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
Welcome.
Did you think about going to the festival with me?
T-The festival doesn't matter as long as you're by my side, Tachibana-kun...
Is it because you don't want to be seen with me?
Maybe we don't make a good couple...
That's...
That's not it at all!
But I can't.
I really don't have the right to date you.
Please tell me.
What are you hiding from me, Risa-chan?
I'm sure you'd hate me if you knew everything.
That's why I don't want to tell you.
I like you, Risa.
So seeing you suffer alone like this is hard on me too.
I'm begging you, please tell me.
Okay.
I'll tell you.
The fact that you were stood up on Christmas two years ago...
That was my fault.
It's because she was waiting with all her classmate friends at the meeting place...
She was going to dump you right there.
They were going to make a joke out of your date invitation simply to have some fun.
It doesn't look like you remember...
But I was in the same class as you at the time, and they invited me as well.
It's unacceptable.
Even though I've always truly loved you, Tachibana-kun,
I was going to give up if she actually loved you.
That's why I lied to Makihara-san that you had changed the location.
So Risa-chan was who Makihara-san was talking about.
But in the end, you were terribly hurt that day.
So I felt responsible that I wasn't able to protect you that day...
And decided never to confess my feelings to you.
But recently you seemed ready to move on from what happened two years ago.
You actively got friendly with other girls.
And I started to think...
What if Tachibana-kun gets hurt by another girl again?
And so I thought of becoming your
girlfriend and protecting you forever!
So you...
Yes.
I gathered my courage and confessed to you.
So that's why.
But if that's the case, what's the problem with us going out?
Makihara-san's attending a different school, and I barely see her.
That's not all.
Lately, whenever it seemed like things were going well between you and a girl...
I intervened.
I told them you already had a girlfriend and showed them a doctored photo.
Why would you do that?
It's like I said.
I didn't trust any girl other than myself to not hurt you.
And that's why I ended up hurting many other girls.
I told myself it was to protect you...
But in the end, maybe I was just jealous of them.
I just didn't want them to take you from me.
Since I did all that, I can't just tell them we're dating.
Why do you care for me so much?
It doesn't look like you remember...
But I was in the same elementary school as you too.
I transferred in, though that was during mid-year...
Sorry, I don't remember.
It's okay.
I was a rather plain girl after all.
So it was when I'd just transferred in, had no friends, and didn't know what to do.
They were really strict about leaving food on your tray in that school, remember?
U-Uh... yeah.
I really didn't handle milk very well...
But we weren't allowed to leave anything on our tray.
However, there was a boy who'd drink it for me.
That was you.
After that, you'd always come and drink my milk for me.
That's it?
That's probably what it looks like to others.
But to me, it was something very special.
I've been in love with you ever since...
I've only had eyes for you.
I'm sorry.
But that's why I can't go with you to the Founder's Festival.
I'm also really sorry you can't have a fun Christmas again this year because of me.
But my dream came true in the short period where I was your girlfriend...
I was so happy.
Thank you.
Please find a girlfriend you can have fun with for next year's festival.
I won't get in the way anymore.
I'm sure you'll find someone wonderful right away.
So...
Goodbye.
Wait.
Risa-chan, are you going to dump me too?
No!
That's not it!
Are you going to leave me with
another lonely Christmas memory?
Of course I don't want to.
But...
I'm sick of being lonely at Christmas.
No...
I want you to always be by my side.
I don't have the right to.
I like you, Risa-chan.
Let's go apologize together.
Let's go together and apologize to the people you lied to.
And let's tell them that we're dating.
You'll forgive me?
I finally understand just how much you love me, Risa-chan.
You confessed out of the blue but didn't want anybody to know, so I wasn't really sure what you wanted.
That's why I feel a lot better now that I know the truth.
Let's wrap everything up so we can date with no regrets.
No.
Not together.
This is something I have to do.
So I'll go take care of it myself.
Risa-chan...
I'm going to go apologize to everyone.
When I return, will you please join me at the Founder's Festival?
Yeah, I'll be waiting.
I want to eat some fried squid with you!
Okay.  Let's do that.
Netemo sametemo koishikute
I miss you in my sleep and when I'm awake
Zutto mitsumete ita no
I've always had my eyes on you
Ukarehashaideta yuugure mo
On happy and joyful nights
Ochikonda hi mo
And on sad and lonely days
Yorisou kata ga atatakai
Your shoulder feels warm next to mine
Mune ga kurushii
My heart is aching
Gyutto shite
Hold me tight
Dare yori mo zutto suki datta
I've always loved you more than anyone else
Seiya no hi musubareru
We're joined together on this holy night
Anata no koto ga daisuki yo
I love you so much
Itsumademo
Forever and ever