I had a lot of fun today.
You also got to take a photo with Inago Mask.  That's good.
Actually, um...
I had fun... because I was with you, Senpai.
I'm glad my first date was with you.
Uh... um...
I like you.
Due to the girl's efforts, the
merry-go-round of love really began to spin.
However, the spinning was troubling the boy.
I need to tell her properly myself.
But...
The painful Christmas of two years ago had made him afraid of falling in love.
Young man.
All it takes is a little confidence and courage!
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator: Ershin
TLC/Editor/QC: Raze
Timer: Kusion
Typesetter: Kemeko
Stuff: ar
They really are cute!
So this was the restaurant you wanted to go to.
Yes.
The boy realized that he didn't really belong here.
Nakata Sae Arc
Final Chapter
Lovers
Um...
They have cute uniforms here too, don't they?
Huh?
You're right.  They're cute.
You wanted to see the uniforms of this restaurant?
Huh?
Um... yes.
She managed to fudge an answer.
But her real objective was something different.
Huh?  Isn't that Tyrolean café pretty close to the station?
You're right.
Wow...
I hear all the couples who have their special
banana parfait together stay in love forever!
Oh?
I didn't know about that.
She came to this restaurant because she wanted to share a special banana parfait with him.
She wanted him and her to stay in love forever.
Just a minute, girl.
Are you sure you want him?
Have you decided on what you want?
Um...
Uh...
You want this?
Recommended!
Special Banana Parfait
Uh... yes.
Recommended!
Special Banana Parfait
But I don't think I can finish it alone...
Well then, why don't we share it?
R-Really?!
Thank you so much.
We're aiming for first place in the Best Couple contest,
so today's goal will be to finish this parfait together!
Yes, Instructor.
Wow.
Yeah.
Well, let's dig in.
Okay.
Sae-chan, are you all right?
Y-Yes.
You shouldn't force yourself.
Ah, no...
I'd feel bad for the owners if we leave any.
All right.
Let's work together to eat it all up!
What's with that guy?
I'm barely making a dent...
Senpai?
I-I want to win the Best Couple contest.
Yeah, me too.
Time passed in the blink of an eye, and it was the day of the Founder's Festival.
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
The day of the Best Couple contest had arrived.
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Will this do?
Yeah, thanks.
Hibiki, no one is more handsome than you.
Hey, don't you agree?
Yes, it looks really good on her.
Now even Nanasaki thinks so...
What's wrong?  It really does look good on you.
Your praise doesn't make me any happier.
Why not?
Geez, why did Hibiki-chan have to be a girl?
It's such a shame.
But is this even okay?
There aren't any other joke couples like us around.
We're just making a memory, so it's fine.
Geez...
I'm no match for you, Haruka.
Hey.
Don't tell me that pink thing is your partner.
Of course it is.  Who else would it be?
A sushi chef's partner has gotta be a fish!
What are you laughing at, Tanamachi?
Don't make fun of Toroko!
TL Note: Toro is high-grade fatty tuna; ko is a common ending for girl names.
He just called it Toroko...
Kaoru, you're laughing too much.
But he...
Just look at how supple Toroko is!
She's prettier than an amberjack today!
You guys... you're really mean!
Sae-chan sure looks nervous.
Y-Yes, I am...
Onii-chan, you too.
I-I guess...
But you guys look good together.
Shut up.
Sae-chan, didn't your mom prepare the outfits?
U-Um...
When I told Mom I was competing, she ordered them...
She ordered them?
That's amazing!
All right, you two.  Good luck!
I'll be cheering for you from the audience.
This year's Best Couple contest has more competitors than ever.
The competition will be fierce!
Best Couple Contest
Out of all these lovely participants,
who will win the glorious grand prize?
Best Couple Contest
Let's get them on the stage!
First up, entry number 1.
Umehara Masayoshi-san from class 2-A and Toroko-san!
Toroko!
You guys really match!
Ladies and gentlemen, thanks for
coming out today for me and Toroko!
Make Toroko happy!
Toroko, I'm gonna open you up tonight.
Open her up, huh?
All night long?
The number of customers suddenly dropped.
Just like a business slump.
That's because they're doing a
Best Couple contest in the gym.
It looks like everyone went over there.
I see.
In that case, I guess we'll just have to enjoy the break.
Should I make some tea then?
Allow me.
Wait a minute!
None of that Russian Roulette stuff you pulled last time.
Do it normally this time.
Pity.
Morishima-senpai!
Senpai!
Now, let's introduce the final couple.
Tachibana Junichi-san from class 2-A and Nakata Sae-san from class 1-A!
Sae-chan?
Y-Yes...
Let's go.
I'll be right with you.
Yes.
What a charming couple.
This looks just like a marriage ceremony.
How adorable...
Nakata-san looks different today.
Just like a grown-up.
Yeah, Sae-chan's beautiful.
Are you okay?
Sorry.
Now for some Q&A.
Tell us what you like about each other.
Let's start with you, Tachibana-san.  Well?
Um...
She's really cute!
And you, Nakata-san?
H-He's a really reliable instructor!
Huh?  Instructor?
Uh, I mean...
H-He's really reliable.
I see.
Yes.
Tachibana-san and Nakata-san.
Thank you very much.
With that, we've now seen all of the couples.
Now the judges will begin their evaluations.
I know we've got first down for sure, but you guys better take second!
Right... that's some serious confidence.
To be frank, Toroko and Nakata-san are worthy rivals,
but I'm clearly way better than you are.
Right, Toroko?
I see.
The boy had nothing more to say to his friend.
Thank you for waiting!  The judges' results are in.
Announcing the results!
This year's best couple is...
Unanimously...
Tsukahara Hibiki-san and Morishima Haruka-san!
Congratulations!
Let's all give them a round of applause!
Thank you!
In second place we have...
Tachibana Junichi-san and Nakata Sae-san!
It looks like everyone voted for us out of amusement.
First place really should've gone to them.
Yeah, they're really cute!
I want to take them home with me.
Hey, now.
The couple that shone brightest, Tsukahara-senpai and Morishima-senpai, win tickets to the Yamaneko Restaurant.
And the couple that shone second-brightest, Tachibana-san and Nakata-san...
...win tickets to a private room at the movies!
Both couples, please enjoy these prizes together!
Sorry.
Huh?
We weren't able to win.
No, it's not your fault, Senpai.
It's my fault.
Huh?
I mean, you were better-looking than Tsukahara-senpai,
but we lost because I was no match for Morishima-senpai.
I'm sorry, Senpai.
That's not true!
You were cuter than Morishima-senpai, Sae-chan.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, about the movie...
Yes...
Is tomorrow okay?
A-Are you sure?
It's Christmas...
Huh?
Yeah.  Well?
I'd love to.
They weren't able to win the Best Couple contest, but they put up a brave fight.
She was too embarrassed to tell the truth,
so she said her mother ordered the costumes.
However, she actually sewed the pure white dress and suit herself.
And she was rewarded for her efforts.
This is a really nice room.
Yes.
Whoa, this couch is really comfortable!
Sae-chan, have a seat.
Okay.
I-I'm going to the bathroom.
I-I'll go buy some drinks.
W-What the heck am I doing?
I've got to tell her today.
I have to.
Huh?
You... took your coat off.
Ah, they turned up the heat in here and it got warm...
Senpai, your face is all red.
It really is quite hot in here, isn't it?
Have some juice.
Are you sure you're okay?
I feel a little better now.
That's good.
To be honest, I was quite taken by your outfit.
Really?
Y-Yeah...
I'm glad.  Actually...
So you asked Miya for advice.
I asked Miya-chan for advice.
I wasn't confident if it would look okay or not, but I'm glad.
It looks really good on you.
Senpai, this movie...
Love's Course
Love's Destination...
It says that after filming, the relationship between the director and the lead actress was revealed.
Love's Course
Love's Destination...
Because they were lovers, he was able to capture her beauty perfectly on screen.
He gained a reputation for it.
Really?
What's the matter?
I saw the director in the bathroom earlier!
What?
Really?
I wonder if the actress is here too.
Who knows?
Well, the two of them are lovers.
So I'm sure they'd come together...
Yeah.
I can't really see.
You're right.
The director's feelings for the actress really came out on the screen.
It was full of his love for her.
My feelings are just as strong.
I could capture beauty even better.
I'm the director, and Sae-chan, you're the actress I'm filming.
What?
I-It's embarrassing.
No, no.  You shouldn't hide from the camera.
Well, get ready!
Well, well, well!
I...
Senpai?
Don't be afraid of failure, young man.
If you have courage, things will go just fine!
Senpai...
Really... thank you so much for everything.
Sae-chan?
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
It's not that.
I'm not upset.
Huh?
Spending time with you like this, Senpai...
It makes me really happy.
I'm happy too.
Um, Senpai...
Please say something.
O-Okay.
Ah, no...
Sorry, I can't really put it into words.
Please don't apologize.
You've done nothing wrong.
Y-Yeah.
I'm gonna say it today.
Senpai?
I like you, Sae-chan.
I really do.
Senpai...
Even though I'm older, unreliable, and insensitive...
That's not true at all!
Ever since I met you, Senpai...
I began to change, and every day is filled with so much fun...
My feelings of love for you won't lose to anyone else's.
Sae-chan...
Senpai...
I'm so happy.
At that moment, her eyes pierced through his heart, and he died from moe.
Moe Death
To die from moe is to have your chest tighten suddenly,
and have your heart taken from you as you rise to paradise.
Senpai?  Senpai?!
Senpai!
It's so pretty.
Um...
Yeah?
Do you think that we look like a couple?
Yeah, we do.
Because we really are lovers.
Yes.
Ah, it's snowing.
It is.
No wonder I thought it was cold today.
I hope the snow piles up.
A shy, cowardly chicken of a boy traumatized by his first love...
...and the shyest girl imaginable.
Their love story now comes to a close.
At long last, they've only just taken one step forward,
but let's wish their love may last forever from the bottom of our hearts.
And after some time had passed...
All right, looking good, Sae-chan.
Ah... yes!
Okay, for the next pose-
Nii-nii!
Are you filming some weird movie again?
Miya...
Miya-chan.
Sae-chan, you look so cute as a penguin!
Hey, don't interfere.
And what's with that outfit?
It's a black kitty!
Let me play too, meow!
Miya-chan, you look really cute.
I'm so happy, meow~
Hey, come on, hurry up!
Guess I have no choice.
Miya, I'll film you too.
Yay!
Senpai, from now on and forever...
Film me the cutest I can be.
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
Anata no koto omou dake de
Just thinking about you
Watashi shiawase desu
Makes me so happy
Ippai oshaberi shitakute
I want to have long chats with you
Ima sugu ni
Right away
Itsumo futarikiri dattara
If only we could always be alone together
Ii no ni na
It would be so nice
Tsugi ni au made wa sukoshi oazuke tsurai kedo
It'll be hard to wait until the next time we can meet
Motto daisuki ni nareru hazu ne
But in the meantime I'll grow to love you even more
Nareru hazu ne
I'll love you even more
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
My Darling itsumo soba ni itai
My darling, I want to always be by your side
Zutto anata shika mienai wa
I'll never look at anyone but you
Daisuki yo
I love you
Preview
Next episode preview.
Hey, boss!
W-What's the matter, Umehara?
What are you doing in the preview?
Don't tell me you're the heroine starting next week!
Hey now, obviously not.
Y-You're right.  Thank goodness.
According to my data, the next girl's pretty tough.
Really?  Am I gonna be all right?
Next episode: "Worst".
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai Arc: Chapter 1
Worst
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai Arc: Chapter 1
Worst
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai Arc: Chapter 1
Worst
H-Hey, wait a second.
Doesn't that title sound ominous?
Yeah, you'd better get ready.