Nii-nii!
Nii-nii, are you up yet?
You're gonna be late!
What's wrong?  You look terrible!
Don't tell me you didn't get any sleep!
I couldn't sleep.
You look terrible.
Are you okay?
Leave me alone.
No, you really look terrible.  I'm not kidding.
It's really bad.  You look really bad.
Tachibana-kun, what's wrong?
You should go rest in the infirmary.
I'll let the teacher know.
Ahh...
I guess I'll do that.
Infirmary
Excuse me.
Huh?  The nurse isn't around?
Well, whatever.
I'm borrowing a bed.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Timer: Kusion
Typesetter: Kemeko
Being Cool: Ershin/ar
W-Why is Morishima-senpai here?
I like you, Morishima-senpai.
I see.
Hmm.
You kinda surprised me.
But no.
I prefer someone who's reliable and older than me.
Huh?  Tachibana-kun?
S-Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Ah, well, I mean... I uh...
What are you doing in the infirmary?
Are you not feeling well?
I-I didn't really get enough sleep, so I'm not feeling too well...
I see.
I stayed up late yesterday too, because there was this interesting late night show on TV.
So I borrowed a bed.
Just like you!
Y-Yeah.  Just like me.
Huh?
Why is Morishima-senpai acting so normally?
Didn't she reject me yesterday?
What's the matter?
You don't really seem like yourself.
Ah... well, I'm a little surprised...
Hmm?  About what?
Well, I mean...
You're no different from how you usually are...
Even though you rejected me...
Huh?
I mean, you completely rejected me yesterday,
so I'm wondering if it's okay for us to talk like we normally do.
Why?
Huh?
I don't think you have to be in
a relationship to get along with others.
I'm actually quite interested in you.
Does it bother you?
What's this supposed to mean?
I see.
I guess so.
I'm sorry.  Even if I'm fine with it, I guess you're not.
Hibiki always gets mad at me for that.
She keeps telling me to be more considerate.
I'm sorry for talking to you so insensitively.
I must've bothered you.
T-That's not true at all!
In fact, I was thinking that you'd be bothered if I talked to you.
Really?
Yes.
Well, are you fine with us continuing to get along?
Y-Yes!  Let's get along!
Good!  That's a good answer.
U-Um, Senpai...
Hmm?
Can I ask you one thing?
What is it?
You said that you prefer an older, reliable guy yesterday.
But... is there anything else you look for?
Huh?  Did I say that?
Didn't you?
Hmm, my type of guy, huh?
Let's see...
I guess I'd be attracted to a tough guy.
Tough?
A guy who looks like he'd protect me no matter what.
A charismatic guy wouldn't be bad either.
Charismatic?
Or maybe someone who fascinates those around him,
a charming guy with leadership skills...
Leadership?
Ah, but I also get the feeling none of them are it.
You're kidding...
But I guess people like that are pretty amazing.
Well, I've slept enough.
Tachibana-kun, be sure to rest well too.
Okay.
Morishima Haruka Arc
Chapter 2
Approach
You look a lot better now for some crazy reason.
You're creeping me out.  What happened, boss?
I'm so glad.
I can continue to talk to Morishima-senpai.
It'd be nice if things stayed the way they are.
No, actually, we might get even closer to each other.
All right, I'm giving it all I've got!
What's that?
A bionic accelerator?
So cute!
Sign: A new family member has arrived
This puppy kinda looks like him.
He was blushing so hard.
His eyes were just a little cool at that time.
Yep, just a little.
Ah, my bad.
Don't dodge it!
Like I'd just stand there and take it!
Ah, that person...
Hmm?
N-Nii-nii?!
"Nii-nii"?  Miya-chan, do you know him?
N-No!  I don't know him.  I don't know him at all!
I've never seen him before either!
S-Sae-chan, let's go!
Why did you suddenly want to do pro wrestling?
I've been thinking.
Toughness.  Charisma.  Leadership.
This is intensive training for obtaining all of that.
And that's why you chose pro wrestling?
Whatever, let's keep going!
No fair!  Ow...
Ah, that looks fun!
Let me play, let me play too!
M-Morishima-senpai?
No way, seriously-
What are you doing here?
My last class was P.E.
All right, bring it!
Come on, come on!
Uh, I don't know about that...
What, you're not attacking?
Then I'll have to use my moves on you!
Like a Manji Hold!
M... Manji Hold...
TL Note: A "Manji Hold" is a wrestling move with lots of body contact.
Let's have a fair fight.
No fair!
Wait, Haruka.  What are you doing?
Hibiki-chan.
Oh, you're the guy from before.
H-Hello.
That reminds me, I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm Tsukahara Hibiki, a senior.  Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Umehara Masayoshi.
I'm his best friend.
That's perfect!
Hibiki's here too, so let's have a two-on-two tag team match!
Fight!
What do you mean, "fight"?
All the equipment has been put away.
Hurry up and change so we can go home.
Eh?  I don't wanna!
I want to do some pro wrestling!
I'm sorry she interfered.
You can continue.
Uh...
Um...
We were just about to end it here too... right?
Yeah.
Really?  What a shame.
I'm sorry, maybe next time.
Don't forget!
I won't.
It's too bad, I guess.
Well then, why don't we all go home together?
We're just about to go home.
You're fine with it, right?
I don't mind.
Both of you are okay with it too, right?
Hmm...
Yes, we'd be glad to!
Hey, Hibiki-chan...
Everyone's looking this way.
It must be because of Morishima-senpai.
Hey, boss.
Can you believe our luck?
We're walking home with Morishima-senpai!
Y-Yeah.
Walking home with Morishima-senpai.
That's a huge step forward.  Yep.
Bye, Morishima-senpai!
Bye!
Take care on your way home.
I will!
Morishima-senpai's really popular.
You just realized that?
I heard that Morishima-senpai
used to join one club after another.
She'd say "something isn't right",
drop out, and then repeat the process.
That seems to be the secret to why she's so well-known.
Normally you drift away from a club you've dropped out of,
but as you can see, they still get along with her and adore her.
I guess that's her charm.
That's not the only reason why Haruka's popular.
You were listening?
We could hear you.
Recently, the most popular guys from both the junior and senior year confessed to her at the same time.
Confessed?!
Oh, I remember hearing about that!
The same time, on the same day,
they called her out to different places.
She had to run all over the school to turn them down.
She was busy.
So she turned them down...
Thank goodness.
I'm kinda jealous.
I'd like to receive love letters from
my classmate and my underclassman,
and run all over the school to meet them on the same time and day too.
That was just a coincidence!
Geez, and you know it.
Nothing like that has happened recently, and I'm getting really bored.
Oh?
So you peek at the Girls Swim Club activities alone because you're bored?
That's because the girls are so cute when they're
hard at work, not knowing they're being watched!
That's totally sexual harassment.
Excuse me.
Since you're that popular with the guys,
has anyone ever confessed to you again even after you rejected him?
Now that you mention it, there hasn't.
What would you do if it happened?
You mean, if he confessed again?
Yes.
Let's see...
It's never happened before, so I don't really know...
But I guess I'd probably turn him down again.
I guess so.
Though, I wouldn't know for sure until it happens.
Nobody would try anyway.
I guess.  I've never heard of anyone confessing a second time.
And so, the feelings I swore that day crumbled all too easily.
You're looking terrible again.
Is it because I ate your share of meat buns last night, Nii-nii?
Though I understand.
I don't think I'd be able to sleep either if someone ate my share of meat buns.
I'm sorry.
Morning, Tachibana-kun and Miya-chan!
Morishima-senpai, good morning!
Hello.
Miya-chan, you're cute, as always!
M-Miya?
Oh?
See you later.
Miya!
I'm sorry, Senpai.
She really is like a kitten.
I'll definitely become friends with her someday!
Miya, what's with that attitude?
You were also like this the last time.  It's rude!
Do you dislike Morishima-senpai?
She really likes-
Shut up!
I know that much!
What's wrong, then?
You don't even respond to me when I talk to you,
but when Morishima-senpai comes along, you keep grinning and...
Grin?
Ooh, you're dripping wet and incredibly handsome!
What happened this time?
In the year 1600, Tokugawa Ieyasu won the Battle of Sekigahara and received the title of Shogun in the year 1603...
Grinning?
Maybe I was.
You
look
retarded
Cut it out, both of you!
Damn that Kaoru.
Saying she has a part-time job and going home after the teacher said that we'd be punished with cleaning duty.
I'll definitely pay her back...
Tachibana-kun!
Morishima-senpai.
Good timing!
Do you happen to have a girl's swimsuit?
I said, a girl's swimsuit!
There's no way I'd have one.
I see, I thought you might've had one...
It'd be creepy if I did have one.
I know!  Why don't I take Miya-chan's swimsuit?
What are you going to do with Miya's swimsuit?
I'm gonna wear it, obviously.
Miya's swimsuit?
Yes!
No no no, it won't work.
It'd be pretty bad if you tried to wear Miya's swimsuit.
Really?
Though, why do you suddenly need a swimsuit?
Well, after seeing the Swim Club do their training,
I felt like swimming too.
So that's why.
I know!  Should I ask one of the girls in the Swim Club?
Huh?  But...
It'll be fine.
I don't think they use their usual
school swimsuits during their training.
Really?
All right, time to invade the pool!
Go go go!
W-Wait, Senpai?!
Huh?!  Y-You want my swimsuit?
That's right.
You want this?
Not that, your usual school swimsuit is fine.
It's only gonna be for a bit, so could you lend it to me?
Okay... I'm fine with that.
Okie dokie, thanks!
Well then, I'm gonna get changed!
Wait, S... Senpai!
Why is there a guy here?
This is when the Girls Swim Club has its practice.
What do you think you're doing?
I-It's not what you think!
There's an explanation for this...
You're saying you mistook this place for the rubbish dump?
Ah, no...
There's also an explanation for this...
Sorry I took so long!
Well?
Does it look good?
O-Of course!
Thanks.
Morishima-senpai.
Ooh, Ai-chan.  What a coincidence.
Well, does it look good?
Senpai, do you know him?
Yep.  He's Tachibana Junichi-kun, a junior.
H-Hello.
And she's Nanasaki Ai-chan, a freshman.
I'm Nanasaki Ai.
Now that you've been introduced to each other, it's time to swim!
President.
I come to see what's causing all the commotion, and I find two outsiders.
Hibiki-chan, please.
Let me swim just for a bit.
No.
Don't be such a spoilsport.
No means no.
Non-club members aren't allowed in here.
Get changed and get out of here.
Come on...
Tachibana-kun, you too.
O-Okay.
Geez, Hibiki-chan's so stingy.
She didn't have a choice.
Tsukahara-senpai has her own duties as club president.
What?  You're on Hibiki's side?
I didn't mean it that way...
Ah, I know!
Why don't we go to the library and look at some photo albums of puppies?
It'll cheer you up.
Huh?  But I already borrowed most of them recently.
I wonder if they have other books with cute things in them?
Don't worry, I'm sure there are
other books we haven't found yet.
I'll find them for you.
Really?
Yes.
Okay!  Then let's go!
Make sure you find an awesome book!
Gotcha!  Leave it to me!
All right, let's go!
S-Senpai, at least let me drop off this dustbin at the classroom...
Well then, I'll go and look.
Yep, I'll be waiting.
Rihoko?
Junichi?!
Why are you here?
Why, you ask?
I'm here to look for a book.
I see.  This is a library, after all...
What are you hiding?
Let's see...
A book on dieting.
H-How did you know?
We've been friends since childhood.
I'm pretty sure you'd only go for books on dieting and cooking, Rihoko.
You must be thinking that I'm trying again , right?
Well, I did see you repeatedly fail at dieting since middle school.
You'll probably fail again.
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Meanie.
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
I don't think you need to be that worried about dieting.
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Anyway, good luck.
Ah...
Okay!
I couldn't really find that many...
Wakey wakey, Senpai.
I'm sorry, I fell asleep.
Only for a bit.
Ah, you put it on me.
Thanks.  You're nice.
No problem...
I'm sorry.  These were all I could find.
It's fine, thanks.
Ah, I haven't seen this one yet!
This one, or this one either!
Good job!
It was nothing.
This is so adorable!
This picture's cute too!
Senpai.
I like you.
Huh?
I like you, Morishima-senpai.
Geez, again?
Sorry.
If it bothers you, I'll never say it again.
It doesn't bother me, but...
Why?
I have so much fun when I'm with you.
It's like, I want to talk to you about all kinds of stuff, and...
That was unexpected...
Sorry.
Don't apologize.
Sorr- Ah.
Why?  I mean, I already...
I couldn't give up.
You said you weren't bothered by it, so I didn't want to give up if I could have another chance.
I don't care how many times you reject me.
What I'm most afraid of is being unable to even get a reply.
I-I wouldn't do that.
Thank you.
W-Why are you thanking me?  You're weird.
Um...
Is it okay if I continue to like you?
If it annoys you, I'll stop.
It doesn't annoy me...
Then... you don't mind?
No.
Yay!  Thank you so much!
Geez...
Huh?
Geez, why do you try so hard?
If you try that hard...
I can't just say no...
Senpai?
Geez.
Take this!
Huh?  W-What was that...?
Your eyebrows were furrowed from trying so hard.
They were kinda cute, so I kissed them.
See you later!
"Kawaii" sore dake de
"Cute".  With just that one word
Muchuu de nadetaku naru urunda hitomi
I'm in a daze, and I want to rub my teary eyes
Jarete iru toki wa
When you were flirting with me
Natsuite iru dake da to
You were just being friendly
Omotteta n da
At least, that's what I thought
Koi no hajimari nante
The beginning of a romance
Yohou hazure no tenki mitai
Is like a missed weather forecast
Ameagari no niji no sora ni te nobasou
I stretch my hands towards the rainbow-filled sky after the rain
Kimi no tonari wa sunao na
Because when I'm by your side
Kimochi ni nareru kara
I can be honest with myself
Kizuita kimi no koto omou
I've realized that when I think about you
Jikan wa mune no oku ga konnani takanaru koto
My heart starts to pound so much
Kinou yume no naka ni
In my dream last night
Mata kimi ga dete kita
You appeared again
Preview
Next episode preview!
What's the matter, Nii-nii?
You're surprisingly upbeat today.
Miya, you have no idea just how happy I am right now!
Huh?  Just how happy are you?
I'm pretty happy if I can have my meat buns,
but you're happier than that?
Happier than if you got twenty meat buns!
What?!  You're that happy?!
Next Episode: "Jealousy".
Next Episode
Jealousy
I feel bad for you, Nii-nii.
You've pretty much used up all your happiness in this life.
Don't say such ominous things!