Sakurai!
We came all the way out here to skate, so let's skate together.
Y... Yeah...
Come on, I'll even hold your hand for you.
It's no use...
You're hopeless.
Hey, Tachibana-kun!
What is it, Kanae-san?
Do something about Sakurai here.
All right.
I-I'm fine.
S... See?
W-Whoa, Sakurai!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Waah, it's so cold!
Of course it is.
Sheesh.
Didn't you come here to exercise?
You haven't been moving around at all.
But... I'll fall.
Well, you've always been bad at skating, Rihoko.
Tachibana-kun, you take it from here.
Ah, Kanae-chan!
Come on.
Gimme your hand.
I'm fine.
Don't be shy.
I'm not being shy...
I can practice on my own.
Hey now...
I-I-I'm gonna hit somebody!
Move, move...
There you go.  You're fine.
Sorry!
R-Rihoko...
What is it, Junichi?
I can see them.
No!
Junichi, you pervert!
You're the one who had them on display!
I wasn't showing them on purpose.
It's your fault for falling.
That's not...
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
Sakurai Rihoko Arc
Chapter 2
Assistance
That fall was worth a lot of points!
Huh?
What do you mean, Kanae-chan?
It's true that Tachibana-kun couldn't avoid it, but don't
you think he really reacted when he grabbed your chest?
No, he definitely reacted.
My chest...?
All right, let's plan your next move!
My next move?
Don't worry about it.
Just leave it to me!
Let's see...
The Founder's Festival is coming soon.  Maybe at the campfire...
T-Thank you, Kanae-chan.
But I'll be busy at the festival with Tea Club activities.
Oh, I see...
Hey!
Let's take a picture!
Yeah, sure!
Skating was really fun.
Huh?  What happened to your gloves, Junichi?
Oh, I lost them not too long ago.
I wonder if I'll make it before Christmas...
I'm from the Tea Club.
I'd like a Founder's Festival
equipment rental application, please.
Okay.
Just fill out this form here.
Um...
Yes?
What should I write?
Could you write what equipment you need to borrow?
I wonder what we need...
Rihoko's chest was pretty big...
About as big as this meat bun?
About this big?
No, Rihoko's were even bigger.
Hey, you there who's daydreaming and blushing while squeezing a meat bun.
Your name's Tachibana Junichi, right?
Come with us for a bit.
How do you know my name?
Um... who are you?
Sakurai Rihoko.
I find that pretty hard to believe...
You sure like to nitpick on little details for a guy.
Whiny little fellow.
So are you gonna help us or not?
What'll it be?
Um... what can I do for you?
Could you help us carry this?
What is it?
A giant fish cake.
I just need to help you carry the top of your kotatsu, right?
Bingo.
Correct.
You're pretty quick on the uptake.
Rihocchi has good tastes.
Uh... are you friends with Sakurai?
Ah, so we haven't met before.
I'm the President of the Tea Club, Yuzuki Ruriko.
Hiba Manaka.  The Vice President.
Oh, so you're the seniors from the Tea Club.
This is a lot heavier than I thought it would be.
I'm tired already.
You should've just set it down while we were talking.
Aren't you clever?
You get five points.
Thank you.
Good work~
It's fine...
I'll make some tea, so please have some.
But I don't really know the proper etiquette...
Is there etiquette for regular tea?
Never heard of it.
I mean... you're the Tea Club and all, so I thought...
It's just lunch break, so it's not like we'll be making any high-end tea.
I-I guess not.
Whoa, it's really good.
Really?  Thanks.
By the way, how did you know I'm Sakurai's friend even though we've never met?
Surveillance.
What?!
Joke.
Well, Rihocchi talks about you all the time.
Any more and we'd be deaf.
About me?
Um... what does she say about me?
So it's something you can't say...
You sure have a lot of stuff here.
Are they all for tea?
PERSISTENCE YIELDS RESULTS
Do you like this room?
Or the Tea Club?
Senpai, I turned in the application for the Founder's Festival.
I'm completely worn out.
Junichi?  Why are you here?
Y-Yo.
Huh, Ayatsuji-senpai?
What's wrong?  You look exhausted.
Ah, I'm fine.
Filling out the application for the Tea Club was pretty tough.
Junichi, so you helped to carry this?
Yeah, it just happened.
Thank you.
Kotatsu sure are nice.
I could stay here like this forever...
Time's up.
You get the consolation prize!
Come back after school.
Aw, man...
Well, I'll be heading back now.
Ah, I'll come with you.
Well then, excuse me.
Ah, wait a minute.
Yes?
You really helped us out today, so I dunno about asking this...
But could you help us out at the Founder's Festival too?
As you can see, we have no guys in the club.
Us girls can't do much with our weak arms.
I was hoping you could help us with the muscle work.
Right.
Well, if you don't mind me...
Really?
All right, let's do that.
We're counting on you.
Okay.  Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Junichi, I'm glad that you'll be
helping us for the Founder's Festival.
Your seniors were pretty interesting.
Yeah.  They're good people.
Looks like he's the one.
The gods have chosen.
For the sake of the Tea Club.
For the sake of Rihocchi.
Swim Club
Oden Stand Recipe
Secret Formula!!
Now everything's ready for the Founder's Festival tomorrow.
Thank you, Rihocchi.
Good work~
The tea you make really is delicious, Rukko-senpai.
Your flattery won't get you anything.
Empty flattery.
Hey, it wasn't empty flattery.
I mean, I can't make tea this good no matter how hard I try.
But Rihocchi, you'll need to make it for the underclassmen once we're gone.
Though... we don't have any of them, so I guess we don't need to worry.
Ding.
Hey, Rihocchi.
This year's Founder's Festival won't be like last year's.
Prepare yourself.
Huh?  For what?
Member recruitment.
After all, if it's just you, Rihocchi, the Tea Club will be disbanded.
I'll do my best!
I'll definitely keep the Tea Club going!
Whoa there...
There's no need to get that fired up.
Just sit down for now.
Well, there's something we want to discuss.
Yes?
Tachibana Junichi.
How about bringing him in as a new member?
J-Junichi as a new member?
When he came here the other day, he seemed pretty interested.
Suitable.
You think so?
Got it, Rihocchi?
Y... Yes...
It's decided.
But will Junichi really join?
Leave that to us.
We have a plan.
Huh?  What are you gonna do, Senpai?
Christmas Eve, huh?
Nii-nii, what are you doing?
Aren't you going to the Founder's Festival this year?
Didn't you promise to help Riho-chan and the Tea Club?
Yeah, you're right.
Guess I'll go.
I'm meeting up with a friend, so I'll head out first.
Okay.
Kibitou High School
Founder's
Festival
Just watch.
My goal is the folk dance that will take place in a few hours.
I'll definitely emerge victorious!
What?  You still haven't given up?
Fool!
The verb "to give up" doesn't exist in my vocabulary!
I'll go all out and fight until the very last second!
Right, best of luck.
Boss.
Watch carefully how I live my life!
Okay.
TEA CLUB
Sorry I'm late.
Ooh, you came just at the right time.
There's no time to waste.
Could you carry this sweet sake for us?
Yes.
We serve sweet sake at the Tea Club every year.
Oh?
It's pretty heavy.
Nice timing.
You can have some tea and sweet sake as thanks afterwards.
Yes.  I'll do my best to help.
It looks like you finally see yourself as a Tea club member.
I'm not a member.
Pity.
Wow, guys sure are different.
T-This is pretty heavy.
Where should I set it down?
Over there would be good.
Okay.
Thanks.  You saved us a lot of trouble.
Oh, by the way...
What is it?
How about joining the Tea Club?
I don't know about that...
Huh?  Junichi, you're here already.
Putting this on took a while, so that's why I'm late.
R-Rihoko...
What, Junichi?
You look... nice in a kimono.
You know, we're in kimonos too.
They look great on you both too.
It's a little late for that.
Can you help distribute the fliers next?
Okay, sure thing.
Well, Rihocchi, let him know what to do.
We don't have enough people on our end either, so come back as soon as you can.
Roger!
There's a lot to do at the Founder's Festival.
Yep, that's right.
It was really tough for me last year
because I didn't know how to do anything.
I'm glad both of my seniors were there for me.
Though, that's also the case this year.
Hey, Junichi.
Why don't you take this opportunity to join the Tea Club?
Hmm... I'm not really interested right now.
I see.
We're serving sweet sake at the Tea Club!
We're also having a tea party on the grounds!
Riho-chan!
Ah, Miya-chan.
Is Nii-nii of any help?
Yeah, he really helped us out with the muscle work and stuff.
Oh?
Did he really?
Hey, Miya.
I get things done when I put my mind to it.
Here.
Hey, Sae-chan.  Wanna go to the tea party?
Yes, I do...
but I wonder if the Girls Swim Club's... Ai-chan's Oden stall will still be there.
Ah, right.
Then let's have tea after some Oden.
Okay.
Well, we'll be there later.
Yeah, we'll be waiting!
I think I'll have Daikon and...
Miya!  Don't get carried away and eat too much!
You're annoying!  I know already!
Hey, Rihoko.
What?
Shouldn't we be heading back to the Tea Club soon?
I'd imagine that it's getting pretty busy over there.
You're right.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Yeah, leave it to me.
Well then, are you ready everyone?
Yeah!
What?  What?
What's going on?
It's coming from the gym.
Let's go see.
Yeah.
Five!  Four!
Three!  Two!  One!
Zero!
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
Rihoko.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, Junichi!
Miss Santa Contest
Our next entrant is Itou Kanae-san!
Merry Christmas!
Oden
Girl's
Swim Club
It's hot, so be careful.
Rihoko.
What?
Don't we need to head back soon?
Oh no!
We'd better hurry!
Don't fall over!
Y-Yeah...
Junichi, thanks for today.
I should be thanking you.
It's been a while since I've had a fun Christmas.
It wasn't a bad idea to participate in the Founder's Festival.
Really?
Yeah.
That's good.
It's gotten really cold out though.
Yeah.
It has.
It's like there's mint in the air.
It feels cool when you breathe in.
Mint, huh?
Oh?  You didn't like it?
I read it from a novel and thought it was pretty clever...
Well, I kinda get it.
But it just sounds weird coming from you, Rihoko.
What's that supposed to mean?
Snow!
No wonder it's so cold out.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, back then when we were kids, whenever it snowed...
Huh?
...you'd look right up at the sky with your mouth open, right?
Boobies, boobies... big boobies...
Hmm?  Rihoko, what are you doing?
I'm hungry, so I'm eating snow.
It's cold and delicious!
Huh?  Does that really fill you up?
Rihoko, you couldn't stop doing that for quite a while.
Geez... it's true that it didn't fill me up, but it tasted nice.
You sure?
It's a white Christmas.
Yeah.
It's getting cold.
Let's go home.
Wait, Junichi.
This is a Christmas present for you...
Gloves?
Yeah.
Thank you again this year.
Can I try them on?
Yeah!
Huh?  My fingers...
Did I make it too thin?
It's fine.
I'm sure it'll stretch out after a while.
Will it really?
Look, it's nice and warm.
That's good.
What's wrong?
I don't have a present for you.
Don't worry about it.  It's fine.
But I didn't give you anything in return for the
polar bear keychain you gave me for my birthday...
I know.  Tell me what you want, Rihoko.
What I want?
I can't really think of anything since you asked right out of the blue...
Nothing in particular.
You don't have to tell me right now.
Yep, okay!
There is no end to a man's battle.
Merry Christmas!
Hey, what should I do, Kanae-chan?
What should I ask him for in return for the present?
What?!  I can't ask for that!
Kokoro ga kyunto
The area around my heart tightens
Sukoshi dake kyunto
Just a little bit
Shimetsukerareta nara
Since it's tightening like this
Hontou no koi na no ka na
Could this be true love?
Futari shibafu no ue
Didn't the two of us use to
Fuzakete nekoronda ne
Play around and lie down on the grass?
Mujaki datta
We were so innocent
Osanakatta hibi
During our childhood days
Demo kokoro no oku de
But deep in my heart
Sodatte yuku kanjou wo
A feeling was growing
Sukoshi zutsu kizukihajimeteta
And I slowly came to realize it
Onaji toki wo sugoshita bun dake
The more time we spent together
Sunao ni narenakute
The less able I was to be honest
Toomawari shita
I did things indirectly
Kokoro de gyutto
My heart tightens
Tonari de sotto dakishimete
As you gently embrace me
Anata wo mitsumeteru yo
I can't take my eyes off you
Sore wa chiisa na koi no hajimari
That's the beginning of this small love of mine
Ima wa mada ienai kedo
I can't tell you this just yet
Anata ga suki da yo
But I love you
Preview
Next episode preview.
Riho-chan, Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas, Miya-chan.
Here's your present.
They're woolen panties, Miya-chan.
You won't catch a cold with these.
Oh, thank you!
Now I'll feel nice and warm even when it's cold out.
That's right!  Nice and warm!
Nice and warm!
Next episode: "Succession".
Next Episode
Succession
Well then, your present from me will be this meat bun!
Uh, I'm on a diet right now...