So boss, this is what I'll tell her.
"It's so cold outside, but my heart is filled with warmth."
"It's all thanks to you."
Just like that!
Then I'll quietly take her hand, pull her to my chest, and...
Hey boss, you listening?
Y-Yeah.
Your Christmas date fantasy, right?
Yup!
But who's gonna go on a date with you?
It's all over if you say that!
More importantly, how're things going between you and Tanamachi?
Remember?  You went crazy looking for her when she was absent the other day.
Tanaka-san told me all about it.
So how'd that go?
What do you mean?
Well, um...
You know, you should just go ask him out.
Big events like these don't come everyday.
Christmas, huh?
It's right around the corner.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Timer: commander`A
Typesetter: Kemeko
Stuff: Ershin, Kusion, ar
Timing Check: Nikon
Ow!
What happened?
I got a paper cut.
Hey, do you have a bandage on you?
Sorry, I don't.
Ow...
If you don't get me a bandage...
I'll die.
Ahh, please!
Hurry up and get me one!
All right, fine.
Boss, I'll die if you don't hurry!  Ow...
I'll go get you some from the infirmary.
Thanks, boss!
You two seem to be having fun.
Did something interesting happen?
It's about to.
Right?
Yeah!
Yeah.  It's almost Christmas, isn't it?
Yup!
Right, Tanaka-san?
Don't get carried away.
No good, huh?
Okay, then.  Time to sew this...
Excuse me.
Hi, hi!
Welcome to the infirmary!
I thought you were Keiko...
Why are you here instead?!
Kaoru...
What are you doing dressed up like that?
Part-time job, I guess...
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc
Final Chapter
Progress
Or something...
I have a job for you, then.
A job?
Yeah.
Umehara got a paper cut on his finger, so I need some bandages.
Okay.  Bandages, right?
Bandages...
Oh, there they are.
Here.  Will one do?
Yeah, thank you.
By the way, why are you dressed like that in school?
Well, Keiko just told me the hem of my skirt was a bit loose,
so she's fixing it right now.
Even so...
We don't have PE today, so I didn't bring in my jersey.
Luckily, I found my clean work uniform in my bag.
I see.
W-What?
I gotta go since Umehara's waiting.
Hey.
What?
Well...
That's not like you.
Just say it.
Okay.  It's... well...
Kaoru, do you have any plans for Christmas Eve?
I do.
Oh, I see...
What are you saying this late?
That's when we're having our date, of course.
I figured you weren't gonna ask me, so I just made the date myself.
Got a problem?
Not... really...
All right!
I scored a date with Kaoru on Christmas Eve!
Seeing her in that uniform at the
infirmary was pretty refreshing, though.
I'm so lucky!
Why are you so surprised?
Ah, you were thinking about something weird, weren't you?
I wasn't!
When you see Keiko, tell her to bring my uniform back to me.
S-Sure, no problem.
Wow.
Christmas dinners are expensive no matter where you go.
Huh?  Really?
Yeah.
It's expensive to do anything on Christmas.
Everything costs about 20 percent more.
20 percent more?
Yeah.
People going on Christmas dates have a lot to worry about.
I see...
Well Nii-nii, it doesn't really concern you anyway.
W-What are you saying?!
This year...
This year, I'll...
What's wrong, Nii-nii?
Are you okay?
This year... This year...
Don't tell me the meat buns we just ate...
I kinda want to just go and buy something new, but...
It's Christmas Eve... and my first date!
The outfit is important, but...
Should I wear my fancy underwear?
Geez, what am I thinking?!
I've already decided to go there with Junichi.
Sign: Kibitou High School Founder's Festival
Preparations seem to be coming along nicely.
Yes.  We ran into some problems, but we're doing fine.
I see.
With more people participating in the garage sale,
the Founder's Festival gets bigger and bigger by the year.
Well done, Festival Committee President.
Sensei, it's still too early to say that.
Huh?  For me?
Yeah, since you can't make it to our party later.
Here's one from me.
Thank you.
I don't have anything for you, though...
Don't worry about that!
I really wanted to go to the Christmas party too...
Then let's throw another one tomorrow!
It's not Christmas Eve, but it's still Christmas!
Yeah, I agree!
Thanks!
Oh, right.
The Swim Club made some Oden.  Do you want some?
I do!
Yes.
I prepared the daikon radishes.
It's been cooking since yesterday, so it'll be tasty!
You want me to distribute leaflets for the tea party?
That's right, Rihocchi.  You're in charge of promoting it!
We're counting on you to bring us more guests.
Yes, I understand!
Rihocchi.
Wear this while you're at it.
You'll definitely gather more attention this way.
I... I'll try...
Kaoru sure is late.
Well, that's how she is.
I expected her to be 10 or 20 minutes late, but...
I was naïve.
I didn't expect to have to wait for more than 30 minutes.
Wait, is she not coming?
Will I be stood up again like I was two years ago?
No, Kaoru wouldn't do that.
She always shows up, no matter how late.
...I think.
But...
Sorry I'm late!
You're late!  Really late!
What on Earth were you doing?!
Sorry, I went a little overboard with some stuff.
You should be trying harder to get here on time instead.
Yeah, that's why I apologized.
Apologizing doesn't make it okay.
Come on, don't be mad.  Cheer up.
I'm not.
I was just worried.
I thought you weren't going to show up.
I would never do that.
There's no way I'd do something you don't like.
Come on, it's our all-important first date.
Let's have some fun!
Kaoru...
Come on, smile!
Like this?
Actually, that's kinda gross.
Then don't make me do it!
There we go.
You're back to your normal self again.
No one asked you to butt in.
Anyway, let's get going.
Yeah, let's go...
Wait, where to?
There's a place I want to go with you.
Here we are!
This is... that Port Tower you told me about?
Yeah!
It's actually pretty tall when you look at it up close!
Well, why don't we go up the tower?
Go up this thing?
Of course!
Well, there's a park here...
Maybe we can go for a walk.
Yeah, sure.
We still have plenty of time.
Geez, you pervert.
Hey, doesn't walking along the shore like this bring back memories?
Back in middle school, didn't we use to walk home like this after hanging out?
So much has happened.
Yeah...
Umehara-kun chased you, and you panicked and dove straight into the girl's bathroom.
You also got a nosebleed from falling asleep
during class and smashing your head on the desk.
Come on, Kaoru.
Shouldn't you bring up better memories at a time like this?
I know!
Like the time you tried to prank me, but got your nuts kicked instead!
On the same vein, you're always doing crazy things.
Your skirt flipped up all the time, and everyone could see your underwear.
You were looking too, right?
You'd jump on the back of my bike and ask me to give you a ride....
That's right, didn't we fall really hard once?
That's because you were thrashing around.
Was I?
You were.
Well, then.  Let's get going.
It's almost the time when the night scenery is best.
You can't mean...
We've come this far, so of course we're going up there.
Come on!
What?!
Come on, get in.
Sorry I took so long, Hibiki-chan!
You're late-
Wait, what's with that outfit?
Is that for the Miss Santa contest?
Didn't that end already?
It did...
But the girl who won didn't accept
her victory because I didn't participate,
so now we're facing off one-on-one.
Hibiki, come with me.
I don't mind, but...
Isn't that outfit a little small?
Really?
That's kinda against the rules, in more ways than one.
Hmm?
So you're afraid of heights?
I-I'm not!
Then come here!
Come on.  Here, here.
So you are afraid of heights!
I-I just don't like it because it's cold by the window.
How cute.
Don't call me cute!
A-As long as I don't look down, I can handle this...
Hmm, not bad.
Of course.
T-This is nothing.
Oh?
Wait, they'll see your panties from below...
Ah, you're wearing pants.
So they can't.
Well, it's not like I mind.
I'm wearing my fancy under-
What?
Nothing!
Out, out, out!
You really are afraid of heights!
Y... Yeah.
Fine.
Do you feel better if we hold hands like this?
Yeah.
Then let's stay like this for a while.
Thanks, Kaoru.
Don't mention it.
Look, it's snowing!
So it'll be a white Christmas...
Yeah.
It's really wonderful.
Hey.
Isn't it kinda weird to watch falling snow from above?
It feels like we witnessed something special.
It's a rare coincidence.
Yeah.
It feels like I'm being sucked in.
Hey.
Doesn't the city seem small when
you look down from a place this high up?
I guess so.
But I was born and raised here...
Yeah.
And... I fell in love here.
What-
Yeah.
You know, there's something I want to tell you today.
Buddies, pals, inseparable...
There are many ways to describe our relationship.
But I don't want any distance between us anymore.
Kaoru...
I've finally realized my own feelings.
Up until recently, I was satisfied with simply pulling you around.
But that all ended a while ago.
Before I knew it, I was being pulled by you.
We've built up so many memories over time,
and that's what led me to realize my feelings.
Yeah.
You know...
I can say 100 bad things about you.
But...
I can say 101 good things about you.
Junichi, I...
...like you.
W-What?
I'm so uncool.
You just noticed?
I made you say something you normally wouldn't.
Yeah, you idiot.
If you're fine with someone like me, I'll be with you forever.
Things haven't been clear between us,
but now I have the confidence to say this.
Yeah.
I want to be with you forever, Kaoru.
Can I be with you?
You're missing just one line.
I know.
I...
I like you too, Kaoru.
Yeah.
See you!
Yeah.  Thanks for having me over today.
Bye-bye!
It's freezing...
I missed the last bus home.
Do you wanna come over?
Mom and dad left for the hot springs today, so Miya's the only one home.
It's fine, I'd only be a bother.
I'll just spend the night at a family restaurant or a convenience store.
No, I can't possibly let you do that.
Is it really okay?
Yeah.
Then I guess I'll come over.
Excuse me...
Shh!
Wow.
Hey.  It just occurred to me that we've known each other for a while now,
but this is the first time I've ever been to your room.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm surprised at how tidy it is.
What kind of room were you expecting?
Something more-
Actually, don't tell me.
Really?
What's the matter?
Nothing.  Wait...
Crap!
Y-Yeah?
Huh?
Nii-nii, you're not spending the night at Ume-chan's place this year?
Y-Yeah.
I thought I heard someone else just now.
Nii-nii, don't tell me...
I can tell even if you hide it.
You're watching porn because you're feeling so lonely for being alone at Christmas.
You're wrong!
Keep the volume down, okay?
I'm going to bed.
I already said you're wrong!
I'm safe, but why do I feel like I lost?
What a nice and understanding sister.
So was this what she meant by porn?
Four Seasons
of Japan
Shh!
Say, why are there stars on the walls of your closet?
It's my special place.
This closet?
Yeah.
I'll be honest.  That's weird.
That hurt.
I'm just kidding.
Should I lick your wound?
That was also a joke.
I'm gonna sleep.
Then let's sleep together.
Is that a joke too?
No, I'm serious.
I don't wanna sleep on the floor.
Are we really gonna sleep together?
It'll be fine.
I'll just be sleeping next to you.
I'll go home before Miya-chan wakes up in the morning.
Then I'll just sleep in the closet.
What's wrong with sleeping together?
B-But that's kinda...
I'll show you something better than stars.
Just kidding.
Well, good night.
Y-Yeah.
M-My heart's beating way too fast!
I need to calm down...
I know!
Miya's the one sleeping behind me.
It's Miya, who has terrible sleeping habits and drools in her sleep!
Believe it... believe it!
I can't!
How is Kaoru sleeping already?
I-I can at least see her sleeping face, right?
You were awake?
Hey.  What were you thinking about?
Huh?  What do you mean?
Was it this?
K-Kaoru, I couldn't breathe...
Kaoru?
She's asleep?
You're kidding me.
Hey, Kaoru.  You're not actually sleeping, right?
Hey!
Hey.
Now that our relationship has taken a step forward,
there's even more fun waiting for us in the future, huh?
Yeah.
Naze naze
Why, oh why?
My Heart kurushii no
Why does my heart ache like this?
Daijoubu nante ne
I tell you that everything's fine
Sokkenai furi shitari
And behave coldly
Namaiki mo urahara
I act outrageous and disagreeable
Saidaigen no tsuyogari
It's the ultimate bluff
Doushite kana namida dechau
Why am I starting to cry?
Aitsu no kao matomo ni mirenai
I can't even look squarely at his face
Ashita wa kitto kinou yori
Tomorrow for sure, even more than yesterday
Tomodachi ijou no kankei ni naritai
I want us to become more than just friends
Ashita wa kitto yume mo kitto
Tomorrow for sure, and in my dreams for sure
Koi suru kimochi kirameku
These feelings of love will shine brilliantly
Just A Friend
Such A Friend
Still A Friend
Naze naze
Why, oh why?
I Can't Tell You My Heart
Why can't I tell you what's in my heart?
Preview
Next episode preview.
You're up in the next episode, Nakata-san.
Y-Yes.
I'm Nakata Sae, and I'm 15 years old.
Nice... t-to meet you.
Nakata-san?
You seem really nervous already.  Are you all right?
I... I'll try harder.
Y-Yeah.
Next episode: "Underclassman".
Next Episode
Nakata Sae Arc: Chapter 1
Underclassman
Next Episode
Nakata Sae Arc: Chapter 1
Underclassman
Next Episode
Nakata Sae Arc: Chapter 1
Underclassman
Having met one summer, the boy
and girl are swept into the wheel of love.
Wheel of... love?