Tsukahara-senpai.
Time me again, please.
Okay.
Go ahead, Nanasaki.
She's right.
Cream Oobanyaki are pretty tasty, just like Nanasaki said.
Do you have a moment?
No need to be frightened.
These are for you.
It's a fun amusement park.
Bring everyone along!
T-Thank you...
Huh?
Young ladies, do you like amusement parks?
We're opening soon.
Don't forget to come!
A wonderful amusement park is opening soon!
Have you started preparing for the finals?
Yep, I have.
Really?
Just kidding.
Come on!
You shouldn't take it so lightly.
Tsukahara-senpai, I'm going home.
See you.
Butterfly 50m: Senior Tatamino Miku
Butterfly 100m: Junior Yoshida Yuka
Backstroke 50m:
Backstroke 100m: Senior Mita Hanami
Breaststroke 50m: Junior Kawakami Yuu
Breaststroke 100m: Senior Umeda Takaka
What am I gonna do about this?
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi wo kureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Typesetter/Stuff: ar
Senpai.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
Nah, I didn't wait at all.
I just got here myself.
Really?
I'm glad it's so nice out today.
Yes.
Huh?
By the way, where's Ikuo-kun?
Um...
He's ill.
He's ill?
I guess he kicked his blanket off last night while he was asleep.
So...
You mentioned your little brother recently,
so I thought the three of us could go together...
Well?
The three of us?
Yeah.
An amusement park...
Okay.
I'll talk to Ikuo about it.
Mom will be at home to watch him today, so I'm sure he'll be fine.
I see.
That's a relief.
So it's just the two of us?
I guess so.
You don't like it?
That's not true!  At all!
Let's go, Senpai.
It is an amusement park, after all.
We need to have as much fun as we can!
You're right.
Okay, let's go!
Um, Senpai?
What?
Don't you have anything to say about my outfit?
Nanasaki Ai Arc
Chapter 3
Transformation
I'm sorry.  You look really nice.
Too late.
Sorry.
Are you okay, Senpai?
I don't mind the speed of roller coasters, but the height...
I see...
Well then, why don't we ride that next?
Onii-chan's such a jerk.
He left me behind and went to an amusement park.
In that case, we've gotta have just as much fun as him!
Right, Sae-chan?
Yes, but where will we go?
I dunno yet.
Oh?  Miya-chan!
Riho-chan!
Is she your friend?
Yeah.  She's my classmate, Nakata Sae-chan.
And she's a childhood friend of mine, Riho-chan.
She's a junior in our school.
N-Nice to meet you.  I'm Nakata Sae.
Good afternoon.  I'm Sakurai Rihoko.
Riho-chan, what are you up to?
Well, isn't the Founder's Festival coming up soon?
I'm doing research on the sweets we'll be serving with the tea.
So I'm going to a Japanese candy store that was recently built here.
I hear their stuff is so good that people line up for them.
Wow, amazing!
What about you guys?
Well, we're still figuring out where to go.
Wanna come with me?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
You guys can help me figure out which sweets are the best.
We'll definitely go!
Sae-chan, you don't mind, right?
Sure, it sounds like fun.
All right!  It's decided!
Let's go, Riho-chan!
Candy, candy!
Pharaoh's Riddle Entrance?
It looks like a haunted house...
Pharaoh's Riddle Entrance
Wanna go in?
Okay.
It looks interesting.
It's pretty dark in here.
Senpai, watch your step, okay?
Yeah.
There it is.
I was wondering when something like this was gonna show up.
Take a closer look, Nanasaki.
It's really well-made, but it's just a fake.
Senpai, are you good with scary stuff?
I wouldn't say I'm good with it, but I'm not bad with it either.
I see...
Well, let's keep going.
Okay...
Man, that scared me.
I'm glad I was more than prepared for that.
I can't let myself scream in front of Nanasaki.
Kaoru, you're so cool.
Really?  Am I really that handsome?
You are, you are!
I'd say okay right away if you confessed to me!
"Keiko, you won't be getting any sleep tonight."
Something like that?
You're so cool!
What's the matter, Senpai?
Nah, it's nothing...
Am I just imagining things?
What's going on?  Are you crying?
Huh?  Ayatsuji-san?
Senpai?
What was that?
Maybe I'm just tired.
We've come to a really large room.
You're right.
What?!
An earthquake?!
You have disturbed my rest!
Prepare to receive the curse of an ancient kingdom!
This must be the main attraction...
It's pretty intense.
Senpai!
I have no need for your idle banter.
Prepare yourself!
Prepare myself?
Did it stop?
Huh?  Nanasaki?
Nanasaki?!
Senpai.
Here.  I'm right here.
I can't believe I'm asking this...
But is that Miso Ramen you, Nanasaki?
Huh?  Senpai, what are you talking about?
But look...
Now that you mention it, I get the feeling you're right...
I'm... Miso Ramen?
Um, hello?
I don't know what kind of trick this is,
but could you please turn Nanasaki back-
Senpai!  Are you okay?!
Senpai!  Senpai!
What a relief.  You're all right.
Senpai?
Ishikawa Butter
Nanasaki.
Yes, what is it?
Nanasaki, you smell really delicious.
Huh?
I get the feeling Miso Ramen is best with melted butter.
S-Senpai?  You're joking, right?
More importantly, please get me back to normal!
I'll go stale if you don't hurry!
The butter is...
Your finger...
Senpai, your thumb is...
Your breath is...
Senpai, you're going to...
...eat me...
Nanasaki?
S-Sorry!
Um... for a while it was like I wasn't myself or something...
Um, I'm really sorry.
I don't care anymore.
That was weird.  What on Earth was wrong with me?
Here.
It's nice and warm.
I'm not going to thank you.
I know.
This is an apology.
I'm really sorry.
You were trying to eat me.
I said I'm sorry.
What?
Well, it was pretty amusing now that I think about it.
R-Really?
Actually... my times haven't been improving during practice.
I was a little stressed because of that.
But I feel much better now.
Really?
Does that mean I helped you out a bit?
Yes.  So I guess I'll forgive you.
Thanks.
Senpai.
Do you remember?
This park is where I first met you.
Ah, now that you mention it...
Umehara and I showed up here,
and you were on the swings.  Then...
You tried to peek up my skirt.
That's not right at all!
I know.
Senpai.
Why don't we ride the swings together?
Are you sure you want to ride it like this?
Yes.
But isn't this kinda...
Come on, Senpai!
Here we go!
We're just getting started.
But...
We're gonna go even higher!
There!
Senpai?  How is it?
Doesn't this feel great?
Senpai, where do you think you're looking?
Uh... where, you ask?
Careful, we're still swinging!
This is punishment.
Punishment?
This way, you can't look up my skirt anymore.
That's true, but...
Nanasaki...
You really are perverted, Senpai.
I didn't think she'd kiss me.
Does this mean Nanasaki's interested in...
In that case, I...
Yo.
Sup, boss?
You look pretty down today.
Are you getting enough sleep?
Are you eating properly?
You'll definitely cheer up right away after you see this though.
Wanna see?  I'm sure you do.
Fine, just a little.
Look, it's my brother's secret porn mag I've been talking about.
Borrowing it was really tough, man.
Whoa, I can't let you see it now though.
Guys need to hold back from time to time.
That way, the pleasure you get afterwards is magnified...
Wait, you're ignoring me?
Are you ignoring me, Tachibana?
Hey!
Good afternoon, Senpai.
G-Good afternoon, Nanasaki.
What's the matter?
Your face is really red.
Do you have a fever?
I'm good, I'm fine.  It's nothing.
Oh?
Huh?  Nanasaki's no different from usual.
Am I caring too much about this?
Senpai?
Hey, Nanasaki.
Yes.
About what happened yesterday...
Um... at the park-
Senpai.
What is it?
Um... they're doing special offers at the store today,
so could you come with me again?
Huh?
Yeah, okay.
Yay.
Then... I'm sorry, but could you wait for me on the grounds somewhere until practice is over?
Yeah, okay.
Nanasaki's late.
I wonder if practice ended already.
Huh?
Um... you're all in the swim team, right?
We are.
Ah, he's the guy who...
Has practice ended?
Yes, it ended.
Looking for Nanasaki?
Y-Yes, well...
Nanasaki was talking to Tsukahara-senpai when I last saw her.
I think she's still at the pool.
T-Thank you very much.
Whoo, whoo!
Go for it!
Since practice's over, going to the pool should be fine.
Excuse me!
What's the matter, Nanasaki?
Nanasaki, wait!
Tsukahara-senpai, what on Earth-
I'm sorry, now's not the time.
Nanasaki.
Nanasaki!
I love you feeling baby my heart
I love you need you baby
Your voice in my heart
Watashi to futari iya desu ka
Don't you like being alone with me?
Nanika iu koto nai desu ka
Don't you have anything to say to me?
Kurayami no naka fureta yubisaki
As you touched the tip of my finger in the dark
Nanasaki!
Ureshi hazukashi "mou shirimasen"
Happy and embarrassed, I said "I don't care anymore!"
Hajimete no kouen
In the park where we first met
Omoide no buranko
On the swing of our memories
Doko wo mite iru n desu ka
Where do you think you're looking?
Aikawarazu desu ne
You haven't changed one bit
Kodou sae todoku kyori
Close enough to feel your heart beating, I said
"Oshioki desu"
"This is punishment!"
Koigokoro tsutsumikomu minamo
The water surface envelops my love for you
I see.  So that's why.
Yes.
Tsukahara-senpai told me one of the juniors was selected as the backstroker for the swim meet this year.
But Nanasaki, you were occupied with the math makeup, your brother, and all sorts of things...
It's okay.
That has nothing to do with it.
Even I know that I'm having trouble improving my time.
But I still have another two years, so I won't give up.
I see.  I'll be rooting for you.
Thank you.
You know...
I dunno if I should be asking this, but...
Yes?
Why did you take off back then?
I... didn't want Tsukahara-senpai to see me cry...
So that's why you took off.
Yes.
But Tachibana-senpai, I wanted you to see it even less.
Sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
That's not what I meant...
I was happy.
Huh?
It made me happy to see a different side of you, Nanasaki.
Senpai...
Why did you... uh... chase after me?
I actually don't really know.
Huh?
But when I saw you cry, before I knew it,
I started chasing after you with all my might.
Really...
Yeah.
Oh yeah, the special offers-
There's no way we'll make it now.
You're right.
Sorry, I was the one who asked...
Nah, it's fine.  Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Well, I'm going this way...
Yeah.  See you.
Um, Senpai...
Are you free now?
Huh?  Now?
Nah, I'm sorry.  It's nothing.
By the way, Senpai.
Do you have any plans for Christmas?
Christmas?
No, nothing in particular.
Well, our Swim Club is doing an Oden food cart.
Would you like to help?
It looks like there'll be a lot of muscle work,
so it'd be great if you could be there.
Hmm, I do owe the Swim Club for all the trouble I've caused.
Yeah, sure.
Well then, I'm counting on you.
Yurayura yureteru Surface Of The Pool
The surface of the pool shakes and sways
Takaku tobikomu kakikomu
I dive in and it carries me under
Watashi tsutsunde
It envelops me
Kokoro no okusoko he michiteku
And fills the depths of my heart
Nani shiteru n desu ka
What are you doing?
Nani wo mite iru n desu ka
What are you looking at?
Toikaketeru n desu
I'm asking you a question
Poker Face
Childlike
Mitai kawaii awai kitai
I want to see it, it's cute, it's faint, the expectation
Tanoshii desu
It's all fun
Majime sugata fui ni miserare
When I unexpectedly saw your serious side
Mune no oku ga tsukiugoite
Something stirred deep within my chest
Kokoro yurayura yureteru Feel Comfortable
The swaying and shaking of my heart feels comfortable
Takaku habataku koeteku
I want to flap my wings and fly over
Ashita aeru
So I can see you tomorrow
Utakata uiteru koi moyou
Patterns of love bubble on the water surface
Konna kanjou nan da to omoimasu ka
What do you think these feelings are?
Tawai mo naku soba de
I want to be by your side
Waraiaitai desu
And laugh with you without a care in the world
Watashi no kimochi na n desu
These are my feelings
To You Innocent
Preview
Next episode preview.
So she's having trouble improving her time, huh?
I wonder if she can improve her time once she gets over this.
Yeah.
I'm sure Ai-chan'll become a really fast swimmer.
Morishima-senpai?
Ah, you're always peeking at the Swim Club, right?
That's right.
I'm always peeking in secret, since Hibiki gets mad at me whenever she finds out.
Next episode: "Confession".
Next Episode
Confession
Ai-chan's armpits are pretty sexy
when she's swimming the backstroke.
A-Armpits?