Three weeks have passed since the wheels of fate
began to turn for Tachibana Junichi and Nakata Sae.
Um...
A-Aren't warm drinks nice when fall comes around?
Like sweet-bean soup, or corn soup...
Or maybe cocoa...
Um...
I-I prefer milk tea.
Could I have some milk tea?
Her training for her job interview
is starting to bear fruit thanks to him.
In particular, her communication skills are almost at a passable level.
However, that's only if she's talking to a vending machine.
Hey, are you still deciding?
Sorry.  Please go ahead.
Really?  Thanks!
Wow, they already have warm drinks in there.
I wonder when they swapped them in.  Don't you?
It's a real mystery.
Okay, I'm gonna get Panda Cocoa!
Hey, what was all that about?
Training.
I know she's shy and all, but do you
really think she's ready for the interview?
I'll figure something out.
You have a long way to go.
Anyway, give it your all.
Nakata-san.
Instructor.
As long as you're talking to vending machines, it looks like your conversations skills pass.
But I can't really seem to make the conversation go anywhere...
It would be pretty scary if it did...
Wanna try having a real conversation with one of the cafeteria ladies?
But...
I-Instructor, I'm still not...
You'll be fine.
You can definitely do it now after all that training.
Yes, Instructor.
Good.
Thus, he encouraged her to tread into the
unknown territory of speaking with the cafeteria ladies.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator/QC: Raze
Translator Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Editor: IGChris
Typesetter: Kemeko
Stuff: ar
Here's your lunch set A.
Thank you very much.
Go ahead, Nakata-san.
Y-Yes.
Don't worry, they aren't gonna eat you.
In fact, we're the ones who'll be eating our lunch here.
That made no sense.
Okay.
Nakata Sae Arc
Chapter 2
Training
Off I go.
Yes?
U-Um...
Yes, what can I get you?
Uh, well...
U-Um...
Hmm?  What's the matter?
Uh... well...
You haven't decided yet?
U-Um... yeah.
Well then, just call me over when you're ready.
I'm so sorry, Instructor.
Listen, Nakata-san.
They're not actual people.
They're just cafeteria lady-style vending machines!
Huh?
Cafeteria ladies across the country, please forgive his rude comment.
Just try and imagine that, okay?
Instructor!  I see her as a vending machine!
All right, now try again!
Okay!
Ah, excuse me...
Yes?
Um...
Isn't it a little cold today?
The cafeteria ladies Nakata Sae
is seeing right now are not
actually vending machines.
Yes, it's almost fall.
Washing the dishes must be tough when it gets colder.
It sure is!
Well, we've got dishwashers here, so it's not that bad.
I see...
Thanks for your concern all the same.
Y-Yes.
Well, excuse me.
See you.
H-How did I do?
It was a little stiff, but I think you did well.
Really?
Yeah.
Of course, the conversation was still quite random and rough,
but it was definitely the most natural of them all so far.
Y-Yes.
Let's call that one a success for now.
Thank you so much.
Let's keep it up.
Yes.
Please continue to teach me, Instructor.
At the time, neither of them realized they hadn't ordered anything.
This is today's training area.
After the coffee incident, they were prohibited from training at home.
Though training at school would probably be worse.
Nakata-san should be here soon.
All right, let's start.
Tachibana-kun?
What are we starting?
Oh... uh, nothing.
What are you doing here, Ayatsuji-san?
Oh, I was asked to return these.
All right, see you later.
Yeah, good work.
Man, she surprised me.
Oh yeah, Nakata-san's on cleaning duty today.
We're going to do some agility training today.
Okay.
They'll need you to be fast at your job.
Y-Yes, Instructor.
And so...
Today's training will be speed-changing!
Speed-changing, Nakata-san!
Speed... changing?
Yes, changing quickly into your work uniform.
It's very important.
Uh... yes.
I guess you're right...
All right, let's get started!
Did you bring the clothes?
Yes.
I did just as you asked, Instructor.
Good.
Then let's begin with speed-changing
from your uniform into your P.E. clothes!
H-Here?
Well, I won't be able to see you if you do it behind that desk.  Don't worry.
B-But...
S-Someone might come...
That's the point, Nakata-san!
Huh?
Training in realistic situations is the most effective!
What do you mean?
I'm talking about tension!
T-Tension?
A real job is going to be even harder.
It'll be a very stressful environment.
Getting properly changed in time...
That's the point of speed-changing training.
You can't be worried about somebody coming along!
R-Really?
Yeah.
I'm amazed at this guy.
He's never even had a job, so how does he talk with such confidence?
Do you understand now?
Yes, I think get it!
All right, then let's get started!
Let's begin with PE clothes!
Yes!
Why PE clothes?
And does "begin with" mean there's more to come?
Okay, get ready.
Y-Yes!
Okay Nakata-san, here we go.
Here's the scenario.
You've got work today, but you got absorbed in a conversation with Miya after school and left late.
The start of your shift draws near.
You've only got three minutes to
change and punch your time card.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Ready...
Start!
Two minutes have passed.  Only one minute left!
How far have you gotten?
I've changed my top.  Just the pants now...
O-Okay, keep it up!
Huh?  Did I get it backwards?
Huh?  Um...
You're slowing down!  Hurry!
Y-Yes!
I'm done, Instructor!
All right.
You changed within the time limit.
However, I need to make sure your clothes are on properly.
P-Please do.
All right, check complete!
Looks okay.
Now...
Take your pants off!
Why is he telling her to undress?
Yes!
And why is she doing it?!
I took them off...
All right...
Next is your swimsuit!
Okay!
Wait, why a swimsuit?!
Start!
Um...
U-Um... huh?
I'm done!
Sorry!
I'm a little late-
She was met with the sight of her brother
groping her friend's breasts over her swimsuit.
Nii-nii...
What do you think you're doing?!
I see.
You're working hard, Nakata-san.
It's all thanks to Miya-chan and Tachibana-senpai.
That's not true at all.
Aren't you working hard in your club too, Ai-chan?
Yeah.
You're both such hard workers.
It's amazing!
Maybe I should try do to something too.
I know, I'll cheer you guys on!
I'll be your cheering team captain!
So cute!
I'll cheer for the cheering team captain!
Geez, you're so cute!
Morishima-senpai?
So this is what a captain feels like...
Yes.
I know where our next training session will be.
Sign: Koedo Hot Spring Adventure
Sorry!
Were you waiting?
No, I just got here myself.
I see.  Thank goodness.
Geez, the reason we're late is because Miya overslept.
I set my alarm, but I just couldn't get up.
That's because you stayed up late reading manga.
But I couldn't stop reading Beaver Romance of the Three Kingdoms once I started!
Well, you didn't have to read it last night.
Sorry we're late.
I'm really sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Really?  Thanks.
Well, let's go.
Yeah.
Um, isn't this place...
That's right, it's a hot spring.
This is where you're training!
What?
I can't wait!
Okay.
I read about this weird bath they have here from a magazine.
Weird bath?
Yeah.
Today's training will take place there.
Okay.
This is the first time I've been to a place like this!
You brought your swimsuits, right?
Yes.
Well then, we'll meet at the footbath corner once you're done changing.
Gotcha!
Footbath Corner
Sorry I took so long.
Huh?  Nii-nii, why aren't you in a swimsuit?
Nobody would want to see me in one.
He really gets it.
Nakata-san, that swimsuit...
...looks good on you.
Huh?  R-Really?
Yeah, it really suits you.
Thank you.
It's thanks to Miya.
Huh?  How is it thanks to Miya?
Nii-nii, I've always known exactly what you like.
The mag you left in your room the other day-
Um...
I'm really happy that... you think it looks good on me.
Well, let's get going.
O-Okay.
Doctor Fish Corner
Whoa, there's so many of them.
All these fishes swimming around in the bath...
They're called Doctor Fishes.
Apparently they help you relax.  It's like getting a massage.
They also do all sorts of good things to your body, like removing excess keratin from your skin.
Really?
Let's try putting our feet in.
Okay.
It'll be fine.  These fishes are tiny.
It's also my first time doing this, actually.
Really?
Yeah.
This is a footbath, so you just need to put your feet in.
Okay.
Whoa, this feels kinda weird.
It tickles!
Wow, they're all gathering at our feet.
Whoa, what's this?
Ah, no!
Huh?
Ah, my... my toes...
Y-Your toes?
They're going between my toes, and...
Oh, no!
It tickles...
No more...
Nakata-san?
Sae-chan sounds kinda erotic right now.
Y-You're right...
It tickles...
No!
All right, let's start the special training!
H-Here?
We'll have a mock interview.  Ready?
Y-Yes.
What is your name?
N-Nakata Sae.
What school do you go to?  What year are you in?
I'm a f-freshman at Kibitou high school.
Ah, they're going between my toes again...
Nope.  You fail if you pull your feet out.
Okay, I'm sorry.
It tickles...
Nakata-san?
It's the master of this hot spring!
This is bad!  It'll attack Nakata-san!
Senpai... Senpai!
Nakata-san!
Senpai.  Senpai!
Senpai!
Nakata-san!
Senpai?  Senpai?
Are you okay?
Huh?
You passed out at the footbath...
I see.
The footbath wasn't the reason he passed out though.
Fruits
Here.
Thanks.
Huh?  Where did Miya go?
She's taking a look at the souvenir shop.
I see...
Hmm?  What is it?
Nothing...
Miya-chan's fast asleep.
Yeah, she is.
Um, how did I do in the mock interview?
Ah, yes.  You did a good job today, so you pass.
Yay!
But please train me more.
Still don't feel ready yet?
Yes.
Well then, let's continue training at my place.
Yes, Instructor.
He had yet to realize why she wanted more training from him.
Hey, let's play this for a bit since Sae-chan's here!
Easy Millionaire Game
is easy!!
Easy stage
Basic stage
Life has mountains and valleys
Let's live an easy life and aim to be a billionaire
Didn't we get this from our richest uncle?
Yeah, he told us to get lots of practice from it so we can be rich like him.
Yeah, I think I remember.
Come on, let's play.
Okay.
You're pretty bad at this game, Nii-nii.
Sae-chan, wanna play too?
Okay.
It's not a difficult game, and you can learn the rules as we play.
What about you, Miya?  Do you still remember the rules?
Of course!
Um, we take turns rolling the dice and go around the board.
And?
We collect money.
Well, that's pretty much it in a nutshell.
Well then, rock, paper, scissors!
In other words, this game is like a miniature copy of one's life.
Scissors!
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
A goat ate the neighbor's hedge.
Pay ¥100,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
A goat ate the neighbor's hedge.
Pay ¥100,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
A goat ate the neighbor's hedge.
Pay ¥100,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
Stocks have risen.
Each stock certificate
is selling at ¥800,000.
Pay ¥5,000,000 to
expand your business.
High-quality Shiitake
mushroom field in
Oita. You may
purchase this for
¥2,000,000 if
no other player has
already purchased it.
An envoy from space has arrived.
Spend ¥500,000 on a reception.
Pay ¥5,000,000 to
expand your business.
Hmm, let's see...
"High-quality Shiitake mushroom field in Oita."
"You may purchase this for two million yen if no other player has already purchased it."
Wow, this Shiitake mushroom field is pretty expensive.
Yeah.
No, it also says "You must pay the owner, if there is one, a hundred thousand yen for the Shiitake mushrooms."
It's good property that will give me steady income.
All right, I'm buying it!
All right, here I go!
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
You may purchase this newly constructed
apartment for ¥5,000,000.
Your hometown's museum has placed
their collection of Kappa hands in your care.
Pay ¥100,000.
A real estate square.
"You may purchase this newly constructed apartment for 5 million yen."
Don't want it!
You sure?  Newly constructed property is popular.
You don't get it at all.
I'm not gonna buy a newly constructed mansion
that will instantly drop in price with an event card.
I-It can?
Be careful when investing in property.
Miya-chan, you're amazing.
It's your turn now, Sae-chan.
You can draw an event card!
Hey, what does it say?
"You make your debut as a writer after winning the newcomer-novelist award."
"Your first release is such a bestseller that you receive royalties from it."
"You use these royalties to establish your own publishing firm."
Sae-chan, amazing!
You've become a multi-millionaire right at the start!
That's incredible, Nakata-san.
Y-Yes.
All right, my turn!
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
However, kids cannot play it
due to it receiving an M rating.
You lose all the money you invested.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
The game company you have
just invested in has successfully
produced a game.
However, kids cannot play it
due to it receiving an M rating.
You lose all the money you invested.
However, kids cannot play it
due to it receiving an M rating.
You lose all the money you invested.
What is it?
"The game company you have just invested in has successfully produced a game."
"However, kids cannot play it due to it receiving an M rating."
"You lose all the money you invested."
Ah, you failed?
Well no, the game was completed.
But you lost the money you invested.
I-I guess.
Then you failed!  You failed, you failed!
Whatever!  To produce a game is
every man's dream, and I did that!
It's not about the money!
It really does seem that this board game is linked to reality.
Oh no, we got too into the game and it's gotten late...
We haven't trained yet...
Since it's a Saturday, why don't you stay the night, Sae-chan?
Is it really okay?
We don't mind at all, so call your parents and ask.
Yeah, do that.
Okay.
Sae-chan's dad is a little protective, so I hope he won't be mad.
My dad said I can.
Yay!
Sae-chan, your boobs are really big.
Really?
Wow, awesome!
They're floating, they're floating!
Mine don't float.
They're three times...
No, four times my size?
They're probably twice the size of a meat bun...
Huh?  Meat bun?
Sae-chan, your body's really soft!
And here he is wishing he could be the soap in the bath.
Unfortunately for him, it won't happen.
Those pajamas...
Miya-chan lent them to me.
They look pretty different on you than they do on Miya.
They don't look good on me?
No, they do.
It's cute.
It makes me want another little sister just like you, Nakata-san.
I don't want that.
Huh?
I don't want to...
I don't want to be your little sister.
What?
Their wheels of fate are on the verge of spinning even faster.
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
Anata no koto omou dake de
Just thinking about you
Watashi shiawase desu
Makes me so happy
Ippai oshaberi shitakute
I want to have long chats with you
Ima sugu ni
Right away
Itsumo futarikiri dattara
If only we could always be alone together
Ii no ni na
It would be so nice
Tsugi ni au made wa sukoshi oazuke tsurai kedo
It'll be hard to wait until the next time we can meet
Motto daisuki ni nareru hazu ne
But in the meantime I'll grow to love you even more
Nareru hazu ne
I'll love you even more
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
My Darling itsumo soba ni itai
My darling, I want to always be by your side
Zutto anata shika mienai wa
I'll never look at anyone but you
Daisuki yo
I love you
Preview
Next episode preview.
Nii-nii, didn't Sae-chan sound really erotic when those fishes were poking her feet?
W-What are you saying?!
I was just training her.
I wasn't thinking about anything like that.
Oh?
Then why couldn't you take your eyes off Sae-chan's boobs, Nii-nii?
W-Well...
Next episode: "Change".
Next Episode
Change
I wonder what Nakata-san meant with those words.
Someone as thick as you wouldn't understand, Nii-nii.