All right...
The New Year has begun, and the new school term starts today.
I need to start finding new members for the Tea Club.
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timers: Kusion/Nikon
Typesetter: fnord
Stuff: ar
No progress at all?!
What have you been doing all Winter Break?
I thought things went really well during the New Year's shrine visit...
Yeah...
And I thought things would start picking up after that.
Tachibana Junichi is a lot dumber than I thought.
This is gonna require some pretty drastic measures.
All right, just leave it to me!
What do you mean?
I've gotta think up some kind of event to get things moving.
Hmm, what would be best?
You know, Kanae-chan...
I wouldn't mind if things stayed this way.
Huh?
I've liked Junichi ever since kindergarten, and
this is how we've always been the whole time.
Sakurai Rihoko Arc
Final Chapter
Farewell
That's why I don't think I need to
suddenly change our relationship...
Sakurai...
Kanae-chan, I'm really happy you're so worried about me, but...
I'm sorry.
Oh no, don't apologize!
Okay.  If that's what you want, I'll just look out for you both from a distance.
Okay, thanks.
Oh yeah, how's your diet going?  You still at it?
Well... you know, it was tough with all
the temptations during the New Year...
I don't think it's limited to the New Year in your case.
Geez, Sakurai, you're so adorable!
So how much did you gain?
Um...
Ah, that was satisfying.
You seem happy.
Rihoko?!
Was Lunch Set B really that good?
H-How did you know what I ordered?
Oh, I know.
You were watching me eat all by myself.
Nope, wrong answer.  I wasn't watching.
Wrong?  Then how did you...
I could tell from the smell.
Amazing, right?
That lie again...
Actually, I just looked at your plate.
I could see that.
Hey, wanna go get an after-meal drink?
Okay!
Four Leaf Tea
Rihoko, what would you like?
Cocoa!
Actually no, I'll have tea.
Four Leaf Tea
So how's your diet going these days?
It's going well this time, isn't it?
Huh?
Well, didn't you wish for that during our New Year's shrine visit?
So now you have divine power on your side.
Yeah, I guess you're right...
I wish my diet will be successful
I wish new members will join the Tea Club
I wish my feelings will reach him someday ♥
Rihoko
Hey.
Mind if I drop by the Tea Club today?
Really?
Yeah, come!  I'm sure the seniors will be glad to see you!
Okay.
Good afternoon.
Huh?
Where'd they go?
Maybe they're hiding somewhere so they can scare us...
But I guess there's no way that'd happen...
They aren't Miya, after all...
Senpai!  Where were you guys?
The park.
We were having a duel.
By Morishima... you mean Morishima-senpai?
That's right.  Morishima Haruka.
The legendary dog master.
Come to me, my puppies!
You can't!
The dogs were following Morishima Haruka's commands and doing all kinds of tricks.
Down!
Sit!
Shake!
We figured we could use her leadership skills, so we challenged her to a duel.
The condition was that Morishima Haruka
would have to join the Tea Club if we won.
Come!
Ahn, you can't!
Pity.
There are no dragonflies in Kibitou during the winter.
Huh?
Defeated by the seasons.
Anyway, that's why we couldn't get Morishima Haruka to join the club.
Wait, why would you want Morishima-senpai to join?
She's graduating along with you guys.
That's a good point.
Uh, right...
I guess so.
It's almost time for you guys to graduate.
That's right.
Normally, it'd be about time to
promote the new club president...
You haven't done that yet?
Well, the only junior we have is Rihocchi.
I really don't know about entrusting the position to her.
You're right.
H-How come?
And so, I'll be straight with you.
Straight to the point...
What about you?
Isn't it about time you felt like joining the Tea Club?
Well, I suppose I'm starting to feel pretty comfortable here...
There we go!  So why don't you just join the club and become its new president?
Huh?  Junichi's the president right off the bat?
He'll just be a figurehead.  Don't worry about it.
Just by name.
Oh, I see.
Well, I appreciate the offer, but...
How about it?
If you join now, we'll throw her in for free.
Huh?  So I'm just a bonus item?
Graduation Ceremony
Hey...
How are those gloves fitting around your fingers now?
Oh, these?
Well, it felt like the blood to my fingers was
being cut off when I first started wearing them.
But I gradually got used to it, and it's not a problem anymore.
That's good.
Listen.  About the Tea Club...
Yeah.
Will it really be disbanded at this rate?
When I first joined, the two Senpai were the only members...
So I think only two people need to be in it.
I see.
Which means it'll really be a problem once the seniors graduate...
Since you'll be the only member after that, Rihoko.
Yeah.
You're right.
I've always been with them both these past two years, so I've been taking their presence in the Tea Club for granted.
The thought of them graduating doesn't seem very real to me...
But I guess they really are leaving.
It's going to be lonely.
Yeah.
I need to pay them back for everything they've done for me by taking care of the Tea Club.
I see.
I have to do it!
What's wrong?
Did you hear my stomach growling just now?
No, I didn't.
I guess being all fired-up made me hungry.
Well, let's go get cake or something.
Really?
But I'm on a diet...
It's okay to do it once in a while.
I'll treat you.
Thanks.
Sorry, only for the drinks.
Then I'll pay for the cakes.
But then you'd be the one treating me.
That's fine.  Come on, let's go!
There's no need to hurry...
My favorite cake might sell out!
Come on, come on!
Hey, that's dangerous!
You don't have to run, Rihoko!
It's done!
Yep, looks good.
Tastes good.
And the love is also good!
Or not...
Um...
Just plain chocolate is okay,
but it might also be good to have
almonds and nuts as toppings too.
Yeah.
I'm gonna try putting some orange peels on mine.
All right!  I'm gonna put everything on mine!
I don't think that's possible...
All right, I did it!
Wow.
How bold.
Good, isn't it?
I dunno...
Onii-chan!
My classmates Nanasaki Ai-chan and Nakata Sae-chan.
Good afternoon.
P-Please excuse us.
Hello.
We're making chocolate together.
Oh?
So all of you have people to give chocolates to.
The three of us are making chocolates to give to each other.
I see.
Well, I guess we can give you the leftovers, Onii-chan.
It's not like you'll be getting chocolate from anyone other than me, Mom, and Riho-chan anyway this year.
Um... how's Rihoko doing lately?
Huh?  Rihocchi?
Hmm... lately, huh?
Why do you want to know?
Well...
The other day, she said that it'd be lonely once you both graduate...
W-What is it?
And what about you?
What exactly is Rihocchi to you?
What?  Uh...
She's just my childhood friend.
Is that so?
You know, Rihocchi is pretty popular with the guys.
Seems like it.
One of the guys in my class even asked me,
"That underclassman in your club is pretty cute.  Does she have a boyfriend?"
...and so forth.
PERSISTENCE YIELDS RESULTS
Even though I'm the cuter one and don't have a boyfriend either...
Is he messing with me?
Lonely.
Well, that aside.
Isn't she really cute?
It's true that her happy face when she's eating something is cute, just like a small animal.
Yes, just like a squirrel with its mouth full of nuts.
Well, jokes aside.
I think you and Rihocchi make a great match.
Manaka, don't you think so too?
Indeed, they do.
So you see?
I've said this before, but Rihocchi has a lot of fun talking about you all the time.
Where she saw you today.
What you were doing.
Et cetera.
I see...
B-By the way, Rihoko's pretty late today.
Ah, so you really did come here to see Rihocchi.
T-That's not it!
So you came to see us?
How popular.
T-That's not it either.
So that means...
You want to join the club, right?
Club of Interest
Name
Entry Form
All you need to do is sign right here.
Uh... it's about time I left.
Is that so?
Don't be too shy about coming again!
Looks like there's still hope in more ways than one.
For the Tea Club, and for Rihocchi.
Choux crèmes?
Y-Yeah.  Is that weird?
Would normal chocolate be better to give on Valentine's Day?
No, not at all.
I mean, it's chocolate cream choux, right?
Y-Yeah...
But why are you going with choux crèmes again?
Um...
Rihocchi, do you know the etymology for the word "choux crème"?
In ancient Hebrew, "shook" stood for "love", and "lim" meant "charm".
It was originally a treat you'd give to
someone you like when proposing to them.
That's what Senpai told me the other day.
That doesn't really sound right to me...
But whatever.  I'm sure Tachibana-kun'll like it.
Yep!
Ugh, what a horrible day.
Yeah.
Boss, you're my only companion.
Tachibana-kun, you have a visitor.
Hmm?
Oh, it's Sakurai-san.
I get the feeling she has a great present for you.
Boss, you're kidding me!
Damn it!
Tachibana, I'm so jealous!
I hate this day the most out of the entire year!
Hurry up and end already!
Don't cry, don't cry.
Tanamachi, give miserable old me your hand of love...
No, chocolates of love!
Oh, it's my policy not to give obligation chocolate.
See ya.
Ayatsuji-san~
I'm sorry, but I have the same policy as Tanamachi-san.
Here.
Thank you.
I decided to change things a little this year.
Whoa, choux crèmes!
Yep.
Wow, they look delicious.
Did you also make these?
Yep.
I see...
Well, I guess I'll have one right now.
Rihoko, why don't you have some too?
Okay.
Ooh, it's chocolate cream!
Yeah.
How's the taste?
It's good.
Really?  I'm glad.
Hey, Junichi.
Is there anyone that you wanted to receive chocolate from?
W-Why the sudden question?
Why do you want to know?
W-Why, huh?
Uh... I was just wondering...
What about you, Rihoko?
Do you have someone you like?
You're apparently pretty popular.
Huh?  Huh?!
I'm not very popular at all!
I wonder about that.
There's cream on you.
Huh?  Where?
Here.
Thanks.
Geez...
Kaerimichi no kouen toki ga tomatte hoshikute
In the park on the way home, I wish time could just stop
Me ga aeba hora ne kokoro ga setsunaku naru
Look, my heart aches so much when our eyes meet
Club Financial Report
Tea Club
Activity Log
Kawarenai tokoro mo sukoshi ganbatte miru yo
I'll try to work on the parts of me that I can't change
Anata ni suki ni natte moraetakute
Because I want you to love me
Tea Club
Recruiting
New Members
Please feel free
to visit our clubroom
Chocolate
Sora ni hoshi ga yorisoiau you ni
Just like the stars huddling together in the sky
Dondon omoi ga kasanatte yuku yo
My feelings accumulate over time
55TH KIBITOU HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATION CEREMONY
Kibitou Municipal Kibitou High School
Nee itsudemo soba ni itai n da yo
Hey, I want to always be with you
Sono hitomi ni kakedashita omoi
These feelings that reached out for your eyes
Rukko-senpai.  Manaka-senpai.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you, Rihocchi.
And...
I-I'm sorry.
I wanted to find new club members before you graduated,
but I wasn't able to in the end...
I'm really sorry.
You don't have to worry about that.
It'd be better if the person who joined actually liked tea.
Don't force yourself.
S-Senpai...
Rihocchi.
It's been a real pleasure for us to spend these two years with you.
Rihocchi, we're thankful for you.
It's been fun.  Thanks.
Senpai, I...
Me too, being with you both...
...has been a lot of fun.
Rihocchi.
Hang in there.
We'll always be looking out for you.
The best we can.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Rihoko?
Junichi.
I'm glad I made it.
Both of you are still here.
What's the matter?
What do you need from us?
Senpai, congratulations on your graduation.
Ah, thank you.
Appreciated.
This is a graduation present from me.
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Entry Form
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Entry Form
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Entry Form
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Entry Form
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Entry Form
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Entry Form
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Entry Form
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Entry Form
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Entry Form
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Entry Form
Name:   2-A Tachibana Junichi
Club of Interest:   Tea Club
Junichi...
I dedicate my remaining year of high school to the Tea Club.
Since the Tea Club probably won't last with just Rihoko.
Junichi...
Senpai, leave the Tea Club and Rihoko to me and graduate with no worries.
Well said!
I wouldn't have expected any less of the man Rihocchi favors!
What a man.
Junichi...
Thank you.
PERSISTENCE YIELDS RESULTS
Freshmen Welcoming Tea Ceremony
Huh?
The snacks aren't here, Rihoko.
Where did I put them?
I might've forgotten them.
I'll go check the club room.
Thanks, Junichi.
Everything's ready.
Yo, there she goes!
There, there.
Rukko-senpai, Manaka-senpai!
Thanks for the invitation.
Thank you very much for taking the time to come here today.
Ooh, you sure have your act together.
Impressive.
Rihoko, I found them.
Ah, Senpai!
Yo!
Club vice-president and new member.
The two of you really do make a great match!
My eyes did not deceive me.
Best couple.
Isn't that a good thing?
Make the Tea Club more popular as a loving married couple!
S-Senpai, not that again...
Come on, hurry up and get ready.
Don't you have to do your best to recruit new members today?
May you have lots of visitors.
Yes.
Everyone, please come in!
Please give the Tea Club a try!
I'm an absentminded and unreliable club president,
but with Junichi constantly by my side supporting me,
I'm sure the Tea Club will grow more and more popular.
And it'd be nice if my feelings could reach Junichi someday.
I hope.
Rihoko, when are the people from the Wind Instruments Club coming?
They should be here soon.
Since I just talked to them earlier.
Kanae-san.
Kanae-chan, thanks!
Junichi, I'm gonna go see how things are going.
Okay.
Don't fall!
Okay-
By the way, my diet still continues.
Kokoro ga kyunto
The area around my heart tightens
Sukoshi dake kyunto
Just a little bit
Shimetsukerareta nara
Since it's tightening like this
Hontou no koi na no ka na
Could this be true love?
Hikaru shibafu no ue
Didn't we use to play around
Fuzakete nekoronda ne
And lie down on the sunlit grass?
Mujaki datta
We were so innocent
Osanakatta hibi
During our childhood days
Demo kokoro no oku de
But deep in my heart
Sodatte yuku kanjou wo
A feeling was growing
Sukoshi zutsu kizukihajimeteta
And I slowly came to realize it
Onaji toki wo sugoshita bun dake
The more time we spent together
Sunao ni narenakute
The less able I was to be honest
Toomawari shita
I did things indirectly
Kokoro de gyutto
My heart tightens
Tonari de sotto dakishimete
As you gently embrace me
Anata wo mitsumeteru yo
I can't take my eyes off you
Sore wa chiisa na koi no hajimari
That's the beginning of this small love of mine
Ima wa mada ienai kedo
I can't tell you this just yet
Anata ga suki da yo
But I love you
Preview
Next episode preview!
Oh, Tachibana-kun.
What is it?  You seem pretty happy.
Ah, Ayatsuji-san.
Well, I'm all fired up since it's been so long since I did a preview.
That's good.
Yep.
Okay, you're up starting next episode, Ayatsuji-san.
I'm so nervous!
Please go easy on me.
Okay, just leave it all to me!
Next episode: "Discovery".
Next Episode
Ayatsuji Tsukasa Arc: Chapter 1
Discovery
Next Episode
Ayatsuji Tsukasa Arc: Chapter 1
Discovery
Next Episode
Ayatsuji Tsukasa Arc: Chapter 1
Discovery
I'll be relying on you, Tachibana-kun.
Gotcha!