So we're switching to winter uniforms today.
All right!
Huh?  Nii-nii still isn't up yet?
Geez.
Huh?  Nii-nii?
Geez, shutting yourself in the closet again.
Oh, he's not here.
Bit by bit, the colors of fall began to stain the town.
In the midst of all this, early morning at school, when few others were around,
the boy and girl were training hard for the job interview exam.
Okay, Nakata-san.
Project your voice from your stomach.
O-Okay.
Now, repeat after me.
Yes!
"Welcome!"
Welcome...
That's no good at all.  I can barely hear you.
All right.  "Thank you very much!"
Um, thank mew very much...
You're fumbling your lines!
One more time!
Thank you very much...
What's the matter?
Speak from your gut!
B-But Instructor... um...
The wind is really strong here...
That's a good thing!
No one can hear you in a wind this strong.
So speak up!
"The customers are gods!"
The customers are gods.
"Welcome home, Master!"
W-Welcome home... Master...
What's wrong with you?!
S-Sorry!
Next.  "Thank you very much!"
Thank you very much...
One more time!
Y-Yes!
No!
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Editor: IGChris
Typesetter: Kemeko
Stuff: ar
I think the Low-Angle Detective Club is the best...
I don't want to be your little sister!
Hey.  What's up, boss?
Uh, nothing.
You're thinking about that big-breasted girl with the face of a small animal, right?
I-I'm not!
She's not really...
You seem to be doing a lot for her.
Well... I can't just leave her alone.
But that's not all, right?
Wait, boss.  Don't tell me you really don't know.
Hey...
What does it mean when a girl says
"I don't want to be your little sister?"
Huh?!
You really don't understand that?
I'm asking you because I don't understand.
You really don't understand what that means?
That's no good.
If she doesn't want to be your younger sister, it means she wants to be your older sister!
Or maybe even your mom!
Uh...
At any rate, it means you'll have to play the role of younger brother or child.
Simple, isn't it?
Morishima-senpai?
Wow, a Miss Santa contest.
Miss Santa
Contest
They actually have events like this at the Founder's Festival.
Miss Santa
Contest
I heard that Morishima-senpai won this the last two years.
Really?
Nakata Sae Arc
Chapter 3
Change
Hey, isn't this Santa cosplay really cute?
I know!  Sae-chan, you should compete!
Aw, I think you'd do pretty well, Sae-chan.
I-It's too embarrassing.
They have a Best Couple contest too.
Princess Nukata, one of the
representative poets of the Asuka period,
is also known as a woman who had many lovers.
She would later become Emperor Tenmu's wife...
He was still wondering what she meant with "I don't want to be your little sister."
What?  You're having the job interview exam today?
Yes.
So I'm heading over there to take it now...
I see.
In that case, I'll go with you!
You'll come with me?
Of course.
I want to know the results right away.
I'm so glad.
I was afraid to go alone.
And...
I wanted you to be the first to know the results,
so I wanted you to go with me, Senpai...
Nakata-san?
Um...
It's all thanks to you, Senpai.
Thank you so much.
Thanks to me?
You thought so much about everything for me and worked really hard to teach me.
That's why I've managed to come this far.
It's strange, isn't it?
I haven't even taken the interview yet and I'm saying all this.
Uh, not at all.
I'm happy to hear you say that.
Really?
But...
What is it?
It's still too early to thank me.
Wait until after you've passed, okay?
You're right.
All right, shall we get going?
Yes, Instructor!
Good luck out there!
The whole Instructor thing became natural to them.
Or rather, they couldn't stop doing it.
S-Senpai!
Nakata-san, how was it?
I...
I passed!
Hooray!  That's great!
Yes!
I was able to pass thanks to your training, Senpai.
No, it's because you worked so hard.
T-That's not true at all!
You gave me a lot of first experiences.
I think that's related to why I passed...
When he heard her say "a lot of first experiences,"
all he could think about was the fact that they were also his first experiences.
I guess it's about time for my adorable student to graduate.
Senpai...
Um, about that...
I don't want to graduate yet.
I think the really hard part has just begun.
I'm still really nervous about whether I can hold down a part-time job.
Nakata-san...
I still want you to give me advice.
Is that... okay?
Well... I don't mind.
I'd like you to be my instructor forever.
Please.
Okay, got it.
Leave it to me!
Thank you very much.
Um...
I'd like to thank Miya-chan as well.
Is it okay if I come over?
Yeah, sure.
I'm sure Miya will be really happy that you passed too.
One day, after she had gotten used to her part-time job...
The boy, his sister, and his friends
paid a visit to where the girl worked.
So this is where she ended up working.
Yeah.
She said they had cute uniforms here,
and she was afraid she'd depend on you too much if she worked with you, Kaoru.
She didn't have to worry about that.
Though they do have cute uniforms here.
I didn't know we had such a fearsome rival nearby.
Welcome.
Thank you all for coming today.
I really wanted to come!
I couldn't wait to see you in all your glory, Sae-chan.
I'd be embarrassed if you all came
before I was able to do my job properly.
Senpai?
The uniform looks good on you.
T-Thank you.
This guy right here is the son of the
sushi chef, the "Welcome!" guy, Umehara.
Hello, I'm the "Welcome!" guy, Umehara.
Wait, what's that about?
N-Nice to meet you.
You're always with Senpai... right?
That's right, we're porn mag buddies-
Are you getting used to your job?
Yes.
Bit by bit, but I'll manage.
I see.
So what would you like?
Hey, hey.  Any recommendations?
Um...
I recommend the Mont Blanc set,
since it's only available for a limited time.
Wow, it looks delicious!
Mont Blanc Cake Service Set
Hey, Kanae-chan.
Why don't we try this?
Aren't you dieting right now?
I am, but...
I'm just saying, this looks like it has a lot of calories.
I see...
I'll pass up on it today, then.
I'll come back after I've lost one kilo!
Hey, now.
Sae-chan.
You're really cute!
They really have cute uniforms here.
I'll bet people who like this sort of thing would love this place.
I see.
This restaurant is the reason why
we've been losing customers recently.
Hey, maybe Tanamachi would look cute in that uniform.
You think so?
Welcome!
No way!
Agreed.
Even I'm laughing!
Here you go.
It's here!
Oh no...
S-Sorry you had to clean it up.
No, don't worry about it.
I'll get you another glass of water.
Thanks.
Hey, feeling lonely there?
About what?
Your student no longer needs you.
Not really.
Just like when he met her for the first time, that throbbing in his chest shook his heart.
A-Amusement park?
Yes.
One of our regular customers gave me invitation tickets.
And you want to go with me?
Yes.
I want to thank you, Senpai.
Will you go with me?
Cosmos
Park
I'm glad it's so nice out today.
Yes.
So which ride shall we go on first?
Maybe the ferris wheel?
Actually, he has a fear of heights.
N-Nakata-san?
Yes?
Well... how about the merry-go-round?
The merry-go-round would be wonderful!
Well, let's go!
That went by really quickly.
You seemed like you were having a lot of fun.
When I'm on the merry-go-round, I feel like I'm a princess.
Oh?  Really?
I guess that's a little childish.
Not at all.
It's just like you to think that.  It's cute.
Thank you.
Which ride do you want to try next?
Senpai, there's actually another attraction I want to go to.
Which one?
Um...
Well... I want to see the Hero Show.
The Hero Show?
They have that here?
Y-Yes.
So you like Hero stuff?
Um... well...
Yes, I do.
But if you're not really interested, then...
Okay, let's go.
Really?
Hmm, we're really close to the stage.
Wow Senpai, the stage set is incredible.
Yeah, it's pretty amazing.
Yes.
By the way, this series features the thirteen Inago Masks.
I'm so excited to be able to see them all this close.
Yeah, we got good seats.
All of the Inago Masks are really cool,
but I like Gold Wolf the best!
Which of the Inago Masks do you like best, Senpai?
Silver Leo, I guess.
I knew it, Senpai!  That's awesome!
You actually chose Gold Wolf's rival...
I like Silver Leo best after Gold Wolf!
I see...
Y-You sure know a lot about this, Nakata-san.
I-I don't really think so...
I know just as much as everyone else...
The passion with which she talked was
different from usual and definitely not normal.
Squid-id-id!
Oh?  We have a lot of energetic little squirts in the crowd today!
Squid-id!
Maybe I, the great Squid Man, will capture you all and turn you into my minions!
All right, you!  Come with me!
M-Me?
Come!
S-Senpai!
Oh no!  One of our friends has been captured by a minion!
Come on, Squid Man!
You're not squidding anywhere!
Kids these days sure mature quickly.
Hey, you.  What year are you?
I-I'm a first-year student.
Are you squidding me?!
How can an elementary school
first-year have a body this mature?!
She's a first-year all right, but not the kind he thinks.
She'll make a good reserve minion, won't she?
He felt bad for her, but he could barely contain his laughter while thinking "This is way too funny, Nakata-san."
All right, let's turn her into a minion!
Are you ready?!
P-Please stop!
Oh no!  Everyone, we have to save our friend here!
I know!  Let's call the Inago Masks!
Forget it!  Nobody's coming to save her.
Everyone, let's summon the Inago Masks together!
Inago Mask!
That was awesome!
I-It was embarrassing.
Nah, I think that was a pretty valuable experience.
R-Right.
But they mistook me for an elementary school girl...
Do I really look that much like a kid?
Well, isn't that because you're small, Nakata-san?
I mean, height-wise...
Here you go!
Thanks to that, you got a souvenir photo...
And you shook hands with all of the Inago Masks.
Yes...
What's the matter?
Um... the two of us...
You and I...
Do we look like a couple together?
A couple?
The boy was confused.
"Why does my heart race when I'm with her?"
He had yet to understand the reason why.
Um... I have a request.
What is it?
T-The Best Couple contest...
O-Oh, for the Founder's Festival?
Can we... compete in that together?
You don't... want to?
Sure, let's go for it.
Really?
Yeah.
Thank you!
And...
I'm sorry I keep making all these requests, but...
What is it?
Um... uh...
Don't call me Nakata...
Call me Sae.
Please call me Sae.
Yeah, okay.
Sae... chan.
Yes.
Sae-chan.
I'll do my best so I won't be a burden to you, Senpai.
I'm the one who'll burden you.
T-That's not true!
You'll be fine the way you are now, Sae-chan.
Senpai...
You passed the job interview exam,
and you're doing really well at work.
When I went to the restaurant the other day
and saw you working, I was honestly surprised.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm sure you can do anything now, Sae-chan.
U-Um...
What's the matter?
Y-Your...
Y-Your hand...
Hand?
Um... it's nothing.
Huh?
Really, it's nothing.
L-Let's do our best!
That's right.
Our next goal is to win the Best Couple contest.
We have a month until the Founder's Festival.
We'll start the training again!
Yes, Instructor!
The days have really gotten short.
You're right.
Are you cold?
I'm fine.
What's the matter?
S-Senpai, y-your hand...
Y-Your hand...
Um...
Uh, well...
Senpai?
The moment their hands finally joined together,
the merry-go-round of love slowly began to spin for the two.
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
Anata no koto omou dake de
Just thinking about you
Watashi shiawase desu
Makes me so happy
Ippai oshaberi shitakute
I want to have long chats with you
Ima sugu ni
Right away
Itsumo futarikiri dattara
If only we could always be alone together
Ii no ni na
It would be so nice
Tsugi ni au made wa sukoshi oazuke tsurai kedo
It'll be hard to wait until the next time we can meet
Motto daisuki ni nareru hazu ne
But in the meantime I'll grow to love you even more
Nareru hazu ne
I'll love you even more
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
My Darling itsumo soba ni itai
My darling, I want to always be by your side
Zutto anata shika mienai wa
I'll never look at anyone but you
Daisuki yo
I love you
Preview
Next episode preview.
Senpai...
Sae-chan...
Sae-chan.
Senpai.
Senpai!
Sae-chan!
Next episode: "Lovers".
Next Episode
Lovers
Will I be able to turn our wheel of love?
Senpai.