I don't know who said this,
but I've heard that love is the source of all of one's vitality.
And sure enough, my motivation for studies and sports is overflowing!
The sky is so beautiful today.
I never knew the world could shine so brightly!
What's wrong with him?
Dunno.  Some sort of disease?
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Lord of Destruction: Raze
Awesome Timer: Kusion-sama
Nordic Battleaxe: IGChris
Copypaster: Kemeko
Moral Support: Ershin/ar
So this is what they mean when they say, "Even the world seems to change".
Tachibana-kun.
Ah, Takahashi-sensei.
You were really enthusiastic in class today.
Did something good happen?
Not really!
Looking at you, it must be something pretty incredible.
Yeah.
Could it be...
Something to do with love?
How did you know?
I am a teacher, after all.
Oh?  How rare to see the two of you together.
Are you telling Junichi off?
Nope.
We were talking about how spring has come for Tachibana-kun.
What's that supposed to mean?
What's with you?
If that's the case, you should've told me about it first.
Geez, treating me like a stranger!
Spring hits you first, and now him...
Oh?  Did spring also come for Tanaka-san?
Kaoru!
Ah, I'm sorry.
I take that back.
Geez...
B-By the way, I've been thinking recently.
Love plays a major role in one's development, doesn't it?
It's like an essential nutrient.
Geez, you're already getting way ahead of yourself.
Kaoru, good luck to you too.
I don't want the likes of you telling me that!
Morishima-senpai?
Could I borrow him for a bit?
Yeah, go ahead.
Thank you, and excuse us.
S-Senpai?
Why are you pulling me by my sleeve?
I just suddenly felt like pulling on the sleeve of your uniform.
I see...
Not bad at all.
S-Senpai?
What?
Where are we going?
Huh?
Morishima Haruka Arc
Chapter 3
Jealousy
Hmm... where was it again?
That's what I'd like to know.
I forgot!
Geez, and it's your fault.
You looked like you were having so much fun talking to Takahashi-sensei and the girls.
What were you talking about?
Don't tell me she's... jealous?!
Hey, what were you talking about?
I'm happy that we've grown closer.
That's what we were talking about.
Oh... okay.
Yes.
I see.  Okay...
One more time...
I want her to kiss my eyebrows one more time...
U-Um, Senpai.
Well, I...
What?
I, uh...
I want you to kiss my eyebrows one more time...
What?!
Please!
O-One more time?
Yes.  I'm fine with just one more!
A-Actually, you can do it two or three more times if you want...
You... don't want to?
Your eyebrows aren't very cute right now, so nope.
My eyebrows?
Yep.  Your eyebrows tell me you're thinking perverted things right now.
T-That's just...
I know!
How about you kiss me this time, Tachibana-kun?
What?!
Well, I kissed you the last time, right?
It's your turn to kiss me this time.
Yep, I think that's a pretty good idea!
A-Are you sure?
Ah, but I don't want to do it here.
Huh?
Like I said, this place is no good.
W-What if it's somewhere else?
Geez, don't make me repeat myself.
Sorry.
Well, let's go someplace else...
Let's see...
I think I'll have you decide where to go, Tachibana-kun.
Huh?
This is a rare opportunity, so I'll have you escort me!
Wow, this is great!
E-Escort?
So where will you take me?
Oh yeah, if we meet someone along the way, no kiss for you!
What?!
Now you're making it harder for me?
Come on, it's more fun this way!
What should I do?  Where should I go?
Time left: 10... 9... 8...
What?!
7... 6... 5...
Is there such a place?
A place where nobody will find us...
4... 3... 2...
Hmm...
1!
That's it!
Let's go, Senpai!
Where are we going?
Just trust me.  Follow me!
Okay.
My heart's pounding a little.
Mine's pounding like mad!
Um, where are we going?
It's a secret.
Senpai, here.
Huh?  We're leaving the school grounds?
Yes.  Please crawl through here.
Wait until I've finished crawling through, okay?
Okay.
Hey, isn't it about time you told me where we're going?
We shouldn't go too far.
We won't have enough time to have lunch.
Over there.
There?  That water pump shed?
Yes.
I see.  It's true that nobody would be here.
No good?
It's good.
Well done, you solved that difficult problem!
Okay, you passed!
Yay!
Oh?  So this is what it's like inside.
There's more room than I thought.
Yeah, it's roomier than you'd think.
All right, I brought Senpai into the shed!
I'll kiss Senpai here!
H-Hey!
Don't just suddenly get quiet.
It scares me.
I'm sorry, I'm just so happy...
Huh?
I mean... we're alone together now...
Geez, you're saying things like that again!
Sorry...
Well, it's fine.
Then let's get started.
My lips are off-limits!
What?  No fair!
Even if you look at me like a little puppy, they're still off-limits.
Anywhere but the lips, okay?
Anywhere but the lips...
Or would you rather... not do it?
Of course not!
I know!
I'm just kidding.
So?  Where will it be?
Where, you ask...
Don't disappoint me!
It'd be nice if you could think of someplace interesting.
Think of someplace interesting...
Yep, I might change my mind
if you pick somewhere predictable!
If you don't hurry up, lunch break'll be over!
B-Back of your knee...
What?
Please, let me kiss the back of your knee!
What?  The back of my knee?!
I underestimated you, Tachibana-kun.  I didn't expect that.
W-Well?
The back of my knee, huh?
Hey, why the back of my knee?
Well, don't dogs often lick you there when they're playing with you?
Ah, yeah.  You're right.
And so, I thought maybe we'll know why dogs lick the back of your knee if we put ourselves in their shoes.
I see.  That's actually pretty interesting.
I've always thought it was strange.
But the back of my knee?
Come on, I'm kinda like a puppy too...
What?
Just a minute ago, you said that
I was looking at you like a puppy...
I see.  I guess you're right.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
T-Then I guess I'll have to expose the back of my knee.
I-I guess...
I-Is this okay?
Y-Yes.  That's perfect.
W-Whenever you're ready.
W... Well, here I go.
Well?  Isn't this awesome?!
I can't get enough of these artistic curves...
Sure-Victory Diet!!
If you chew
thoroughly
you'll lose
weight
for sure!!
Where did Haruka go, I wonder?
It tickles...
H-Hey, are you done?
Hey, wait!
That's not where you're supposed to be kissing!
Woof, woof~
Sit!
That area's still off-limits.
Haah, that was amazing!
Geez, that really tickled, you know.
I'm sorry.
Well, how was it?
It was amazing!
It was really smooth...
That's not what I meant!
Did you find out why dogs do that?
Geez, did you forget about it halfway?
T-That's not it!
Uh, well...
I can't really put it into words yet...
You're hopeless.
I'll tell you about it once I figure it out.
Really?  I'll be waiting.
Let's head back or we'll miss out on lunch.
Okay!
What is it, Nii-nii?
You're smirking and stuff.  It's creeping me out.
Mommy!
Nii-nii's gone crazy!
I kissed the back of Morishima-senpai's knee.
I made so much progress!
What should I do?
I can't suppress these feelings any longer.
I want to kiss the back of
Morishima-senpai's knee one more time!
One more time...
The back of Morishima-senpai's knee...
Morishima-senpai
Back of the knee
Legs
Knees
Thigh
Kiss
Kiss!
Junichi!
Look, look.  I lost 970 grams of weight by following the diet in that book!
Isn't that amazing?
Oh?
Morishima-senpai!
Oh, Tachibana-kun.  What is it?
Well...
Yeah.  What is it?
I wanna kiss the back of your knee one more time.
What?!
Please!
Please.
Geez!
And?  What do you want to do, Haruka?
What do I want to do?
It's kinda troubling when he keeps begging me...
Hey.
Just making sure, you said this is about a cute puppy, right?
Y-Yeah.
W-What?
I see.  If you're fine with it, one way
would be to just let him do what he wants.
Really?
You don't want to?
Well, I don't really mind...
You could also do the opposite and scold him harshly.
That's also an effective method during training.
Training?  He's not an animal.
Aren't we talking about a puppy?
You slipped up.
Hibiki, you meanie.
Hey, Haruka.
W-What?
Is that what you actually wanted to talk to me about?
Huh?
Be honest.
I'll hear you out.
Well...
I-Is it difficult with younger guys?
Difficult with younger guys?
Like, how do I say this...
Hmm?
Is it weird if I... let him spoil me?
Will he hate me for it?
I see, so that's what you wanted to know.
T-That's what I want to know.
I mean, from his point of view it's like... kinda...
Haruka.
W-What?
Just go for it.
Huh?  What do you mean?
Next time you see Tachibana-kun, go for it and let him spoil you.
B-But... I'm older than him...
That doesn't matter.
There isn't a single guy who doesn't want to spoil his girl.
Really?
Yep, try it and see.
With a "meow", even.
With a "meow"?
Will it really be okay?
He won't think that I'm a weirdo, right?
It'll be fine.  Don't worry.
Go ahead and let Tachibana-kun spoil you.
I see.
Thanks, Hibiki.
Yep.
With a "meow", huh?
It tickled...
That kiss.
Sign: Eat and lose weight!
Eat all you want, it's okay!  Just read this and you'll lose weight!!
What's with that giant robot leg?
Is that the signboard for the Founder's Festival?
Go for it, huh?
All right!
Purr, meow!  Meow!
M-Meow?  Morishima-senpai?
Meow, meow!
What are you doing, meow?
W-What am I doing?
Senpai, what are you doing?
Hmm?  The Meow Meow Attack.
Meow Meow Attack?
People are looking...
Do you give up, meow meow?
I-I give up.
Were you surprised?
I'm pretty surprised, yeah.
What on Earth is the matter?
You didn't like it?
No, of course not.
In fact, I loved it!
I see.  That's good.
Go ahead and keep on doing it!
Thanks.
Ahh, that was refreshing!
Hey, have you decided what you'll have for lunch yet?
No, I haven't...
Senpai, what will you have?
Let's see... cafeteria food, maybe.
I'm sick of everything on the menu, though.
Oh, really?
I'm wondering if they have something interesting, though.
Something interesting?
Something exciting, maybe.
Exciting...
Senpai, leave that to me!
I, Tachibana Junichi, will prepare an exciting meal for you!
Wow, really?
Yes, leave it to me!
Isn't this just... ramen?
Yes.  It's just salty ramen.
Huh?  What's exciting about this?
Don't be so impatient.
There's no way I'd be able to prepare an exciting meal in the time I have.
So the excitement won't be in the dish itself, but in the situation.
You'll make the situation exciting?
That's right.  Please imagine.
You've just been kidnapped, and your arms have been bound behind your back.
We're pretending that's what's happening, right?
That's right.  Please imagine that.
Yep yep, that sounds fun!  What's next?
Two days have passed since you were kidnapped.
Wow, that's horrible!
What's more, you haven't had a meal since.
That's scary...
The kidnapper's got to be Hibiki.
Yep yep, and?
Your hands have been bound so that you can't escape.
Oh no!  I can't eat, then!
And so, I'm one of the kidnappers, and I'm about to feed you, Senpai.
That sounds like fun!  Let's do it!
O-Okay...
I didn't expect her to be this happy about it.
Come on, hurry up!
Well then... are you ready?
Hmm, my hands are supposed to be tied behind my back, right?
Okay.
Ready... start!
Food?  Is that for me?!
Y-Yes.
Hey, you need to be more serious about this.
Y-You're right.
Food?  Is that for me?!
Yeah.
I'm only feeding you because I have to.
Please, quickly!
Now now, it's hot now, so we have to wait for it to cool down a bit first.
Don't be so mean!
Geez, you're hopeless.
Here, have some soup first.
Ahh... it's delicious!
The soup's dripping... and gleaming...
Incredible.
It's really delicious.
Ugh, the soup's dripping out of your mouth.
You're a troublesome girl.
Please, more, give me more!
Don't be so impatient.
You'll get burned if I don't let it cool first.
But... I want more!
Geez, you're a greedy one.
E-Everyone's looking again ...
Hurry, hurry!
O-Okay.
What's happening over there?
Haruka is letting Tachibana-kun spoil her.
Like that?
We shouldn't bother them.
Let's leave them alone, Nanasaki.
Okay.
Here.
I had so much fun today.
Nee-chan, you're being loud.
I'm sorry, Satoshi!
"Kawaii" sore dake de
"Cute".  With just that one word
Muchuu de nadetaku naru urunda hitomi
I'm in a daze, and I want to rub my teary eyes
Jarete iru toki wa
When you were flirting with me
Natsuite iru dake da to
You were just being friendly
Omotteta n da
At least, that's what I thought
Koi no hajimari nante
The beginning of a romance
Yohou hazure no tenki mitai
Is like a missed weather forecast
Ameagari no niji no sora ni te nobasou
I stretch my hands towards the rainbow-filled sky after the rain
Kimi no tonari wa sunao na
Because when I'm by your side
Kimochi ni nareru kara
I can be honest with myself
Kizuita kimi no koto omou
I've realized that when I think about you
Jikan wa mune no oku ga konnani takanaru koto
My heart starts to pound so much
Kinou yume no naka ni
In my dream last night
Mata kimi ga dete kita
You appeared again
Preview
Next episode preview.
At long last, Christmas is approaching.
Will I have a happy Christmas Eve?
Nii-nii, don't just sit there and think.
It's no good if you don't make an attack!
Miya...
Go straight for it and get your heart crushed!
Hey.
Next Episode, "Romance".
As the snow falls on Christmas Eve,
will a small miracle fall upon me as well?
Next Episode
Romance
I wonder if Santa will give me meat buns for my present?