In order to avoid being late to the date she finally agreed to,
I ran over to the meeting spot as early as I could that day.
Perhaps it was because it was Christmas?
The place was bustling with more couples than usual.
I was waiting for someone just like
everyone else, and it made me happy.
Weird...
I'm pretty sure I got the time and place right...
That was Christmas Eve, two years ago.
She never showed up to the date.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator/QC: Raze
Timer: commander`A
Editor: IGChris
Typesetter: Kemeko
Stuff: Ershin, ar
All right!
Huh?  Nii-nii still isn't up yet?
Geez.
Why didn't she come to our date two years ago?
I still don't know why.
Ever since then, I've...
Nii-nii!
Geez, you shut yourself in the closet again?
You're gonna be late for school if you don't get up now!
Nii-nii!
Be quiet, I still want to sleep.
It's cold and I don't wanna get out yet.
All you needed to do was turn the heater on...
Well, if Nii-nii won't come out, I'll go in instead!
It's been so long since I saw your closet planetarium too.
Hey, stop it, don't come in!
This is a masterpiece I made for my own private enjoyment!
Masterpiece?
You just drew it with a highlighter!
S-Shut up!
I'm coming in too!
All right, I'll come out.
What's the matter, Miya?
Nii-nii, you dummy!
Nii-nii, it's been so long since we walked to school together.
Really?
Yeah, Nii-nii, you usually go ahead and leave me behind.
That's because you keep taking your time, Miya.
Also, we're not at home now, so don't call me "Nii-nii".
Ah, right.
I forgot.  Sorry!
Weren't you the one who asked not to be so clingy at school?
Ah.  Onii-chan, see you later!
Okay.
Morning!
Good morning, Miya-chan.
So she's Miya's friend.
Walking to school with a hot chick.
There's nothing hotter than that in the morning.
It really blows away the winter cold, eh, Tachibana?
Do I know you?
Oh?  This again?  This trick again?
I don't recall having a friend who'd
tease me like that knowing she is my sister.
You're no fun.
And I was going to share something new with you too...
Is that the photo album you were talking about?
I brought it with me for the sake of my best friend,
but it looks like this friendship is one-sided.
Oh!  Now that I take a closer look,
aren't you the second son of a sushi chef,
my best friend who's been in my class
since elementary school, Umehara Masayoshi?
You change personalities pretty quickly.
My bad.
Don't worry about it.
Even so, you're still my best friend, Tachibana Junichi.
In fact, I was just waiting for that reaction.
So how was it?
Now now, no need to get that excited.
It was awesome.
Really?
I see.
It does sound pretty awesome.
I'll lend it to you, don't worry.
Don't stain my precious book, though.
Of course I won't!
I'm just kidding, man.
What's the matter?
Isn't she Morishima-senpai?
Oh come on, Hibiki!
She's so beautiful, it's surreal.
She makes the photo album look dull.
Yeah, you're right.
Morishima-senpai is beautiful, as always.
She also has a lot of fans at our school.
If I remember correctly, she recently rejected some guy in our class.
Crap, let's hurry or we'll be late.
You're not getting anything if we're late because of this!
Let's run!
Okay.
Morishima Haruka Arc
Chapter 1
Longing
This year's Founder's Festival is fast approaching.
Thus, we need to decide on
committee members from this class.
Any volunteers?
Takahashi-sensei.
If no one wants to do it, I will.
Ayatsuji-san?
You're already working as the class representative.
Are you sure you want another position?
Yes.  I don't really have much work left as
class representative now that it's November.
Also, it's only a short while until the
Founder's Festival, which is around Christmas.
I see.
In that case, please do your best.
Yes.
Now, we're halfway through November...
Ayatsuji-san always does the things no one else wants to do.
She's really hardworking.
Okay.
Sup, boss.
Let's have lunch.
Sure.
Should we buy some bread today?
Wait right there!
What's the matter, Kaoru?
I was thinking of having bread today too.
Wanna tag along then, Tanamachi?
It's no fun if we all go together.
Let's have a game of rock-paper-scissors!
Whoever loses has to buy bread for all three of us.  What do you think?
Oh, I see.
Here we go!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I want Yakisoba bread and a chocolate cornet!
I want a pork sandwich and a red bean paste bun.
Yeah, yeah.
Wow, this looks bad.
She must be a freshman.
There's a trick to buying bread at times like this.
All right.
What would you like?
You're here to buy bread, right?
Yes...
U-Um...
I'd like a milk and one of the sweet breads...
All right, leave it to me.
Here you go.  Milk and something sweet.
T-Thank you.
I just chose whatever.  You okay with that?
Yes.
Um...
H-How much?
Oh, the price?
It was 360 yen.
Do your best next time.
That girl just then...
She was all red and flustered.
Maybe I shouldn't have offered to help.
Hey, you.
Crap.  I'd better pick them all up...
You there with the big appetite!
M-Morishima-senpai.
Oh?  Have we met before?
Here you go.
You dropped it, big appetite-kun.
S-Sorry.
Thank you.
Hey.
Y-Yes?
You have adorable eyes.
Huh?
So did we meet somewhere before?
No...
I see.  That makes sense.
I usually remember people I've met before.
Hey, weren't you the guy who bought bread for that freshman?
Um, yeah.
I did...
Good.  You're really nice.
Bye.  Make sure you don't fall over again!
I got to talk with Morishima-senpai...
I can still smell her wonderful scent.
Hey!
Hey.
Rihoko.
Junichi, what's the matter?
Nothing at all.
Hey.
What?
Are you really going to eat all of that?
Of course not.
I guess!
You'd probably be able to finish all of this yourself though, Rihoko.
Huh?  I definitely can't eat that much.
You were so slow I thought I was gonna die of hunger!
Geez, what were you doing?
It's not my fault.
Lots of things happened.
Like what?
Sorry to disturb you while you're eating,
but do you have a moment?
Ayatsuji-san, what is it?
Takahashi-sensei asked me to collect
everyone's guidance papers by today,
but you're the only one who hasn't turned one in yet, Tachibana-kun.
Could you turn it in before you leave today?
Sorry, I forgot about it.
I'll turn it in later.
Okay, I'd appreciate it.
Okay, thanks.
I'll turn it in to the teacher.
Sorry you had to wait for me.
No, it's fine.
Is something wrong?
Ah, I was just wondering where Umehara went.
His bag is still at his desk, so I don't think he went home yet.
If you're looking for Umehara-kun,
he said something about going to the library.
Really?
He hasn't paid me back yet for the bread earlier,
so I need to bug him about that.
Is that so?  You should definitely talk to him about that.
Yeah.  Well, I'll go look in the library.
I also need to get a good look at his new photo album!
Ow...
S-Sorry!
Morishima-senpai?
Oh?  Aren't you the one with the big appetite from lunchtime?
Nice timing!
Sorry about that.
I got impatient looking around for someone...
Don't worry about it.
I wasn't looking where I was going either.
Anyway, you're doing me a big favor by carrying those books.
Is it okay, though?
Weren't you looking for someone?
Oh, it's fine.
I had some business with him, but it can wait.
Well, there aren't many things more important than carrying stuff for Morishima-senpai.
Hibiki-chan!
What is it, Haruka?
Look, look!
They actually had all these
photo books of cute dogs at the library!
Borrowing them wasn't that bad,
but carrying them around is tough.
So I got him to help.
Hello.
Sorry about that.
It seems Haruka has troubled you.
Oh, it's fine.
It wasn't a big deal.
I was free too.
Haruka, go ahead and thank him properly.
Okay.
Thanks, uh...
That's right, I still don't know your name.
Oh, you're right.
I-I'm T-Tachibana Junichi from Class 2-A.
Thanks, Tachibana Junichi-kun.
I-It's fine.
I'm shocked.
You didn't even know his name, and yet you made him carry all this, Haruka?
I may not have known his name,
but I knew I could count on Tachibana-kun.
Why?
That's because Tachibana-kun's really nice.
Yo, Tachibana!  Check this out!
They actually kept photo book treasures like these hidden away at the library!
I went to get them right after I heard about them.
One of the former students probably left it behi-
Uh, what's the matter with you?
Maybe I'll try again.
Huh?  Try what again?
Those feelings I lost two years ago...
I wanted to find them again.
Hey, what's wrong?
Morishima-senpai.
She's the school idol and probably unreachable,
Y-You okay?
but I think I'm falling for her.
Hey-
Whoa, your face is all red!
Is it a cold?  Are you not feeling well?
Two years ago on Christmas, my heart was broken.
I became afraid of having to go through that again.
But this year I'll definitely have a blessed Christmas!
Unfortunately, Morishima-senpai is way out of my league.
In fact, I haven't seen her since that incident at the library.
I guess there's no way things would go that smoothly.
Let me play too!
Morishima-senpai?!
Morishima-senpai?
What's the matter, Morishima-senpai?
Here I was thinking there were a bunch of kids
playing leapfrog, until I saw you with them.
So I thought I'd join in too!
You came out of nowhere, so you really surprised me.
I thought you'd be fine with me jumping in, Tachibana-kun.
I mean, it's because you're really nice.
It's been so long since I played leapfrog!
I used to play it with the boys from my elementary school.
Oh, really?
Huh, Onii-chan?
Oh, Miya.
Miya, this is Morishima-senpai.
I'm sure you've heard of her.
Yeah...
Senpai, this is my sister, Miya.
Good afternoon.
Your sister's adorable.
You think so?
She's nothing but cheeky.
I have to switch classrooms for
my afternoon classes, so I'm off.
Hey, Miya!
What's wrong with her?
She probably hates me now.
Oh, Miya-chan is so cute though.
She's just like a kitty.
Really?
Yeah.
I want to get closer to her, so we can go shopping and take baths together!
Eh, b-baths?!
Yep!  It'll be fun!
Morishima-senpai and Miya together in the bath...
Hey, Haru-chan.
Is this all I need to do to make my boobs bigger?
Yep, that's right.
Oh, but you should do it like this...
Like this?
Yep.  You're good, Miya!
But this kinda tickles.
Yeah.
A-Anyway, I'll have to ask Miya
why she wasn't very happy later.
Miya!
Oh, Onii-chan.
What's the matter?
Why were you so rude to Morishima-senpai this lunch break?
She said you were cute and wanted to get closer to you.
Yeah, right.
Aren't you the one who wants to get closer to her, Onii-chan?
Since Morishima-senpai is really pretty and has a nice body?!
What's wrong with you, getting all lovestruck?!
Nii-nii, you dummy!
It's Morishima-senpai...
She's beautiful.
Senpai, take this.
Tachibana-kun...
Is that a disposable hand warmer?
You'll catch a cold otherwise.
Thanks.
You're really nice.
What were you doing?
Well...
I was looking at the water.
The... water?
Yeah.
I like looking at water.
Like the sea, the river...
...and the fountain.
That sounds nice.
I think it suits you somehow, Morishima-senpai.
You and Hibiki are probably the only ones who've said that to me.
You're so nice.  Why, you!
T-That's not it at all.
Really?
Then are you saying you're only this nice towards me?
Could it be that...
...you like me?
Just kidding.
N-No, well...
I see.
That's a shame.
It's so warm...
I like you.
I like you, Morishima-senpai!
Really?
Yes, really!
I see.
Hmm.
You're more of a man than I thought, Tachibana-kun.
Really?
Yeah.
You kinda surprised me.
Thanks.
I'm really happy.
Senpai...
But no.
I prefer someone who's reliable and older than me.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Well, see you, Tachibana-kun.
Oh, and thanks for the hand warmer.
It's really warm.
Tachibana-kun?
Huh?
Was I rejected?
Wait, did I really confess to her?
No, no.  That wasn't a confession.
But...
I guess I'll go home for now.
Nii-nii, you're home?
I have some steamed meat buns.  Do you want some?
It's cold.
Guess I'll go in.
"Kawaii" sore dake de
"Cute".  With just that one word
Muchuu de nadetaku naru urunda hitomi
I'm in a daze, and I want to rub my teary eyes
Jarete iru toki wa
When you were flirting with me
Natsuite iru dake da to
You were just being friendly
Omotteta n da
At least, that's what I thought
Koi no hajimari nante
The beginning of a romance
Yohou hazure no tenki mitai
Is like a missed weather forecast
Ameagari no niji no sora ni te nobasou
I stretch my hands towards the rainbow-filled sky after the rain
Kimi no tonari wa sunao na
Because when I'm by your side
Kimochi ni nareru kara
I can be honest with myself
Kizuita kimi no koto omou
I've realized that when I think about you
Jikan wa mune no oku ga konnani takanaru koto
My heart starts to pound so much
Kinou yume no naka ni
In my dream last night
Mata kimi ga dete kita
You appeared again
Preview
Next episode preview...
Nii-nii, you're not having any steamed meat buns?
I don't want any.
What?!
But they're so good!
The juices overflowing in your mouth,
and the chewiness and savory taste of the meat...
Good for you, Miya.
You seem happy.
Next episode: "Approach".
Next Episode
Approach
Nii-nii, the sun will rise again tomorrow!
Everyone, p-please look forward to the next episode.