Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
Oden                   Girls Swim Club
Everyone!
Thanks to you all, all that's left to do is decorate the Christmas tree.
It looks like we'll successfully make it for the Founder's Festival.
Thank you all... so much.
Isn't it a little too early for that, Ayatsuji-san?
That's right.
Save that for after we've actually had the festival.
You're right.
Yes, you're right.
Tomorrow is the long-awaited Founder's Festival!
Let's work hard together until the very end!
Yeah!
What do you mean, that girl no longer exists?
So you mean you have a split personality,
and that side of you disappeared yesterday?
So I have a split personality?
That's an interesting way to explain it.
But that's wrong.
Then what is it?
In any case, that girl ceased to exist yesterday.
That's all you need to remember.
Well, everyone's waiting.
Let's go back and continue
preparing for the Founder's Festival!
Tachibana-kun?
Why are you daydreaming?
Uh, well... nothing at all.
Come on Tachibana-kun, let's go decorate the Christmas tree with everyone else!
Sorry.
I still need to do the final equipment check and some committee work.
I'll be back.
Best of luck!
I do think Ayatsuji-san's cute right now.
Not bad at all.
The class atmosphere is also much livelier.
But...
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Typesetter: fnord
Stuff: ar
Did you watch me, Tachibana-kun?
Y-Yeah.
Your speech was great.
Thank you.
Isn't the Christmas tree pretty?
It's all thanks to everyone.
Ayatsuji Tsukasa Arc
Final Chapter
Promise
Yeah.  You're right.
Ayatsuji-san.
Hurry up.
Ah, okay!
Just a minute!
I promised to walk around with Yayoi and her friends during my free time.
Tachibana-kun, do you want to come with us?
Oh nah, I'm...
Sorry...
Ah, that's a shame.
Well, I'll see you later.
Welcome!
An egg and Chikuwa, right?
Just a moment, please.
Raawwwr!
You adorable little rabbit!
I'm having you for dinner!
Oh...?
Please stop, o great one!
Moving right along, entry number seven!
She's won the Miss Santa Contest twice in a row.
The one you've all been waiting for...
Morishima Haruka-senpai!
Whoa!
That outfit's risky!
Wow!
Very risky, Morishima-senpai!
I knew this would happen.
Hey, do you think I can get away with this outfit?
It was acceptable when I was the one wearing it...
Haruka suddenly decided she wanted to compete.
But...
Well, she seems to be having fun, so whatever.
Everyone!
I'm counting on you, okay?
Miss Santa Contest
It'll probably be Morishima-senpai again.
She's really pretty, after all.
It looks like she'll score her third victory.
Hey Ayatsuji-san, don't you also think Morishima-senpai's gonna win?
I don't know.
Everyone's really cute, so I can't really say for sure.
Sorry, Yayoi-chan.
It's about time I returned to the committee work.
Okay, later then.
See you at the after party!
Junichi!
Yo, Rihoko.
So you came.
Yeah, during my rounds.
I promised, after all.
Looks like things are going well.
Thank you very much.
Junichi, you should have something to drink.
Tea?  Or maybe some sweet sake?
Ah no, nothing for me.
I have to go soon anyway.
Junichi, is something bothering you?
No, it's nothing like that.
Rihocchi.
These kids are waiting for their snacks.
Oh, sorry!
I'll be right there!
I'm sorry, Junichi.
It's cool.
Hang in there, Rihoko.
Yep!
Sorry for the wait.
Hey, Sakurai!
I came to see you!
Kanae-chan!
Ooh, aren't you popular?!
Why did Ayatsuji-san become like that?
It's not exactly a bad thing, but...
Why am I feeling so gloomy about it?
Umehara...
Wait!
Think it over!
Just because you couldn't find a girlfriend this year...
It doesn't mean you have to start a fire in your despair!
I see.
So it was a love letter from your elementary school days.
Yeah, that's what it is.
But why now?
I mean, back then...
Wasn't it really uncool to love or hate someone?
Yeah, it was.
So I stubbornly refused to write her a reply.
It's such a shame now that I think back on it.  I really regret it!
So instead of holding on to my regrets forever,
I figured I'd just burn it and be done with it.
You have my respect.
Don't respect me!
All I do now is regret!
Regret, huh?
What is it, boss?
I failed again.
Even though I said I'd try my best for Christmas this year.
It's pathetic.
What are you talking about?!
Christmas Eve isn't over yet!
If you feel like you're pathetic, then do something about it!
Before you regret it like me.
Thanks, Umehara...
You really are a good guy.
I know, right?
I wonder why you can't get a girlfriend...
Shut up.
You'll make me cry.
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas.
Whoa, heck yes!
I got a present from Ayatsuji-san!
Here, Merry Christmas.
There's candy inside.
Don't want it.
Kibitou High School
Founder's  Festival
And with that, the 57th Founder's Festival comes to an end.
Thank you all very much for attending.
Please have a wonderful night.
Now then, in celebration to a
successful 57th Founder's Festival...
Cheers!
Thank you all so much.
It's all thanks to everyone.
That's not true at all.
It's because you worked so hard, Ayatsuji-san.
There was lots to do, but it was pretty fun.
Yep, yep!
They say that preparing for the festival is
when you have the most fun, and it's true.
The more hectic it is, the sadder you'll feel once it's all over.
Kaoru, you were great as the contest MC.
Really?
I actually wanted to participate in the Santa costume contest.
Well, Morishima-senpai scored her third victory in a row this year...
So it was a good thing I skipped work to be the MC.
Tachibana-kun.
Where were you?
The after party started without you.
Ah, sorry.
You should've come to see it too.
I was really popular as Santa Claus!
You know, Ayatsuji-san...
Hmm?  What?
Do you have a minute?
You wanted to talk?
Yeah.
Tachibana-kun?
I still have people to give my thanks to, so I'm going back to the classroom.
I love you.
You're late, Umehara.  Where were you?
My bad, but the hero's supposed to show up last.
And who said you're the hero?
You were barely around for the Founder's Festival too.
I had some business to attend to.
I bet you got rejected again anyway.
Thank you, Tachibana-kun.
I'm happy.
Me too, I like-
I...
I have an unpleasant Christmas memory,
so I don't handle this time of the year well.
It was so bad that I ran away from
attending the Founder's Festival last year.
But I knew that I couldn't stay like this forever, so I volunteered to be on the committee.
I figured I'd work hard this Christmas...
And I ended up doing work with you, Ayatsuji-san.
Do you remember?
When I picked up your notebook.
You brought me to the shrine after that.
I was really shocked that you had that side to you.
But...
I'm glad I found out.
You told me off for various things while I did my work.
It was tough since there was lots to do, but it was fulfilling to say the least...
Yes, I didn't even have the time to think about how much I dislike Christmas...
It was so fun that the thought had disappeared before I knew it.
I think that was when I fell in love with you, Ayatsuji-san.
Tachibana-kun.
Do you hate the way I am now?
I don't.
I like the way you are now too.
But...
But?
The obstinate Ayatsuji-san from before...
And the Ayatsuji-san who puts on an act of friendliness...
I like them all.
That's why I don't want you to tell me sad things like part of you has disappeared.
I'd like you to scold me if there's anything I need to improve.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
Why?
Why are you saying this?
Ayatsuji-san?
Ow-
What was that?!
What the heck do you want?!
I tried to erase the real me because of what you said...
But...
Thank goodness.
The Ayatsuji-san I love still exists.
What?
Founder's Festival Planning
Committee Headquarters
What... was that noise?
Takahashi-sensei.
I heard a loud scream coming from this direction...
It's nothing!
Founder's Festival Planning
Committee Headquarters
Sorry!
I got a little drunk from the sweet sake and fell over,
so I screamed, "Ouch!" without thinking...
Sorry about the noise.
Okay Tanaka-sensei, we should go to the after party too.
Founder's Festival Planning
Committee Headquarters
Ah... uh, okay.
Geez, you guys are hopeless.
This will be my Christmas present to you.
Ahh, I want a boyfriend too!
Uh...
I think you should start by cutting back on your alcohol...
CONGRATULATIONS!!
FOUNDER'S FESTIVAL SUCCESS!
THERE'S A KARAOKE
AFTER-PARTY!!
Ouch...
Take this little bit of pain at least.
This was your fault in the first place.
Huh?!
It's sexual harassment to hug a girl from behind.  Sexual harassment.
I'm sorry.
Mind if I tell you something?
What?
It's about my past.
Okay.
One day, I realized that Santa Claus doesn't exist.
And the reality of it hit me hard...
Huh?
I know this happens a lot, but I basically saw my parents place the presents under the tree.
It was worse in my case though.
I-In what way?
That's a secret.
I see.
And so, I made a decision having realized that Santa doesn't exist.
That I would become Santa.
I knew that I couldn't become the real thing.
But I thought that I could become something like Santa.
Something like Santa?
Yes.
I could bring happiness to everyone by giving them presents.
And that's why you volunteered for the planning committee?
Yeah.
If I could make everyone's Christmas even just a little happier through my own efforts...
Wouldn't that be wonderful?
Yeah, you're right.
I attended the Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival when I was a kid.
This was what I thought.
If I could make the Founder's Festival a success with my own hands...
Wouldn't I bring happiness to everyone?
But that was no good.
Before I knew it, my aim of bringing happiness to everyone changed into one of satisfying myself.
That's not true!
Everyone had fun.
Thanks.
But it was something even a kid could tell.
My Santa Claus was well received among my peers...
...but the kids didn't warm up to it at all.
It looks like even the great Ayatsuji-san is unable to deceive children.
I suppose you're right.
Ayatsuji-san.
Christmas isn't over yet.
Huh?
Christmas will come again next year and the year after.
Why don't you just bring happiness to everyone each time?
You're right.
That's why...
I'd also like you to bring me happiness.
Isn't that what the girl is supposed to say?
You don't want to?
I don't mind, but...
Ahh, your hair's all messed up now.
It's fine, I'll straighten it myself.
But...
I love you too, Tachibana-kun.
I won't ever let you go.
Is that an agreement?
No.
It's a promise.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
Mujaki na sono egao wa
That innocent smile
Watashi dake ga shitteru
I'm the only one who knows about it
Igai to amaenbou na anata no koto
And just how unexpectedly spoiled you really are
Tsukahara Hibiki
Kodomo mitai ni sunao ne
You're as honest as a child
Otoko wa sukoshi kuuru na
"Guys are supposed to be cooler!"
Kurai ga kakkoii to ijimetari
That's what I say to tease you
Donna toki mo kono te wo hanasanaide
Don't ever let go of my hand
Saigo no koi ni shiyou tte chikatta koto
We promised that we'd be in love forever
Ima wa mada naisho ni shiteokou ka
Maybe I'll keep it as my own secret for now
You sure it's okay?
Hitori de niyaketeru gozen reiji sugi
As I lay there past midnight grinning to myself
Yes, this should be fine.
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
=10 Years Later=
Mama!  Papa!
Hey hey, is it this?
Papa and Mama's memory tree.
That's right.
This was where Papa and Mama made an important promise.
Promise?
What kind?
Hey, Junichi.
What is it, Tsukasa?
Are you happy now?
Of course I am.
I'm happy too.
Oh, me too!
I wish that everyone in the world can be happy on this wonderful day...
Just like us, right?
Yes.
Merry Christmas!
Hodou wo kazaru aoi Illumination
The blue illumination adorns the sidewalk
Nigiwau hitogomi ni hitori tatazumu
And I stand alone in the swarming crowd
Koboresou na egao
Smiles peeking through
Yorisou koibitotachi
Lovers snuggling against each other
Ima no watashi ni wa subete ga
Everything to me now is so bright
Mabushikute mirenai no
That I cannot bear to look
Dareka ni aisareru deshou ka
Will anyone love me?
Tsuyogari no oku ni kakureta
I'm hiding underneath a facade
Watashi ni kizuite yo
Please realize that
Hontou ni jiyuu ni nareru deshou ka
Can I really become free?
Douka oshiete
Please tell me
Fuyu no machi ni mayoikonda
Having lost her way in the winter town
Samishige na tenshi ga nageku
The lonely angel sighs
Yasashiku
Gently
Preview
Next episode preview.
Nii-nii, there's something I want to ask.
What?
What would you do if a cute girl you
didn't know confessed to you one day?
Huh?  What's that?
Whatever, just answer me!
So what would you do?
Hmm... I'd be happy if the girl who confessed is cute...
But I can't just say okay if I don't know her very well.
Oh?  I wasn't expecting such a respectable answer from you.
Next episode: "Truth".
Next Episode
Kamizaki Risa Arc
Truth
That winter memory where I was rejected surfaces once again...