Did you come here to see it too?
Huh?
Look.  There's a big mountain over the sea, right?
You're right.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator/QC: Raze
Timer: Kusion
Editor: IGChris
Typesetter: Kemeko
Witty Banter: Ershin/ar
Onii-chan, what are you doing?
Miya, Rihoko.
I'm not really doing anything right now.
Really?
You look kinda suspicious, staring around like that.
Hey.
Miya-chan and I are about to go shopping.
Junichi, would you like to come with us?
What are you shopping for?
They're having a Christmas sale, so we're gonna see if there are any good deals.
Window shopping, I guess.
I see.
I guess I'll give up on walking home with Morishima-senpai for today.
Sure, I'll go with you.
Yay!
Riho-chan, now we have someone to carry our bags!
Yeah!
Wait, I feel bad about making Junichi carry everything!
Don't work me too hard.
Yeah, yeah!
Well, let's go before Nii-nii changes his mind!
Miya-chan, you don't have to rush-
Sh-Sh-Sh-Sho, shopping~
Sign: Shopping District
Wow, you're totally in Christmas Mode, aren't you?
Yeah.  It's almost Christmas, isn't it?
Aww, is Nii-nii gonna have another lonely Christmas?
T-This year, I'll...
Riho-chan, look, look!
What, what?
I'd rather have a chocolate cake...
It's almost Christmas.
I need to ask her out soon.
I'm gonna spend this Christmas happily with Morishima-senpai!
Morishima-senpai?
Junichi, what's the matter?
Um... uh, I...
Nii-nii?
"Ah"?  What do you mean, "ah"?
I know!
Nii-nii, you need to go to the bathroom, right?
Geez, you should've just said so earlier!
Come on, hurry up and go.
Yeah, it's not good for you to hold it in.
All right, I'll go.
You can go home first if you want!
Pretty girl, I can't bear to stay in here any longer!
Tachibana-kun?
Did I scare you?
Geez, you really surprised me.
Wow, I did it!  Teddy bear, get!
Morishima Haruka Arc
Final Chapter
Romance
That's good.
Yep.
I only happened to win because you surprised me.
Thanks!
Morishima-senpai's... really cute.
Hey, are you free right now?
Yes, I am.
Well then, let's go have some fun over there.
Ah, but I don't really go to arcades often.
I wonder if they have any two-player games?
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
We input our initials here...
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
What's this mean?
Is it good or bad?
Ah, let's see.
It's really bad.
Senpai's all unhappy because it says we're not very compatible.
Does this mean that she likes me?
I'm kinda happy.
One more time.
Huh?  We'll probably get the same result even if we go again...
Anyway, input your initials again, Senpai.
Senpai, aren't your initials H.M.?
This is fine.
O-Okay...
What's with the "L"?
Whoa, amazing!
We did it!  Huge success!
That was satisfying!
What's with the "L", though?
Shouldn't it be "M", for Morishima...?
The "L" stands for "Lovely".
Tachibana-kun, I don't think I've told you yet.
My actual name is Morishima Lovely Haruka.
Lovely is my middle name.
A-type
Blood Type
Blood-type
Fortune-Telling
Compatibility Fortune-Telling
What?  So you're actually half-Caucasian?
Nope.
Compatibility Fortune-Telling
Let's see.  My grandpa on my mother's side is English, and my grandma is Japanese.
So I guess that makes me quarter-Caucasian.
I-I see.  So that's why.
What am I saying?  I need to ask Senpai out for Christmas!
Taiko
Ahh, I feel great.  Let's go home.
Senpai.
Signs: 12 Constellation - Compatibility Fortune-Telling.
Could you come with me?
How rare of you to ask me like that.
Senpai, are you cold?
Nope, I'm fine.
It's been so long since I was here.
I used to come here every day.
We can't really see it today.
Don't you remember?
We've met here before, in the past.
I think the sun was also setting a year ago, just like this.
Look.  There's a big mountain over the sea, right?
You're right.  There's actually a mountain there...
You can see far out into the sea when the weather's fine.
I guess so.  I didn't notice at all.
You really are just like him.
I'm just like someone?
You know, you're just like the dog we used to have.
A... dog?
Especially when you have that perplexed look.
Sorry.
Really?
I was feeling pretty down at the time,
but I felt a lot better after you talked to me.
A little later, I was pretty surprised to find out you were in the same school as me.
Wait a minute.
So Tachibana-kun, that means you're Park-kun?
Park-kun?
You know, that day left a deep impression on me.
So when I talked to people about the interesting guy I'd met,
I would call him "Park-kun" because I didn't know his name.
And you're actually him!
I see.
That's right, I'm Park-kun.
There's a good reason why I went to the park that day.
John, the dog we've had since I was three, died on Christmas the year before.
Since then, I'd feel sad whenever I thought of him.
But I realized that John would continue to worry about me in heaven if I stayed that way.
So I decided to go to the park John had liked and cheer up.
Then I saw this guy sitting at the bench that John had loved.
That was me, wasn't it?
Yep.
John would sit just like that whenever he was feeling down.
And so I couldn't just ignore you...
So that's how it was.
Yep.
I'm sure that John brought us together.
Hey Tachibana-kun, why were you down at the time?
I was waiting for someone at this park on Christmas two years ago.
For a girl?
Not bad at all, Tachibana-kun.
But... she stood me up.
For the next year, I was constantly brooding over it.
That was what I was thinking about when I was feeling down in this park last year.
Senpai, you saved me when you talked to me then.
Could you save me again?
How?
Christmas Eve, on the 24th.  Please go on a date with me.
I can't.
Y-You can't?
Y-You don't want to go on a date with me?
No, that's not it.
My grandpa and grandma from England come back
each year for Christmas, and we have a party at our home.
So...
I see.  That's why.
Hey.  Will you come to the party if I invite you, Tachibana-kun?
If you're fine with that, let's spend Christmas Eve together.
Yes, I'd be glad to!
Crap, I'm totally not gonna make it!
It's all because Miya said something weird!
Where could Senpai be?  Did she go back already?
Hey.
You're a bad boy for making a girl wait on a day like this.
S-Sorry!
Oh no, Tachibana-kun.  Steam's coming out of your head!
I ran really hard coming here.
Geez, you're hopeless.
I can't get mad at you if you ran hard enough to make steam come out.
T-Thank you.
Well, let's get moving.
U-Um...
Where are we going?
To your house?
I-Isn't this...
A hotel?
Yeah.
What are we doing at a hotel?
I'm happy that you ran so hard for me,
but I can't introduce a sweaty boyfriend to my family, right?
So let's wash off your sweat here.
What?!
What's wrong, all of a sudden?
Wow.  Is it really okay to go to a hotel on the very first date?
Well... Senpai, are you sure about this?
Um... about what?
I'm so glad they rented out swimsuits.
I didn't expect her to mean washing off my sweat at the hotel pool...
Though... the pool, huh?
I'll get to check out Morishima-senpai in a swimsuit again!
Sorry I took so long!
Y-Yes!
It's a new swimsuit...
How is it?
Weird?
No way, totally not!
It looks good on you!  It's beautiful!
Really?  Thanks.
You should've just said so immediately.
I'm sorry, I couldn't stop staring.
I see.  So you were entranced.
W-Well, let's swim!
I'll go first!
Hey, wait for me!
Isn't going for a swim at the pool on Christmas surprisingly nice?
I-It's actually pretty fun, but...
But?
I'm not used to it, after all.  It feels weird.
Really?
Yeah.
It's amazing enough just to be spending Christmas with Senpai.
But swimming together at the pool on top of that... it's unreal.
Hey.
You have me already, so don't look at other girls.
What?
You got it wrong, I wasn't looking!
I mean, I already have you in front of me,
so there's no need for me to look at other girls!
R-Really?  Okay, then.
Okay.
Now that I'm all cleaned up, Senpai will finally introduce me to her family.
I'm nervous.
I'm sorry I took so long to change.
Don't worry about it at all.
More importantly, will we still be
on time to meet up with your family?
Oh, yeah.  I forgot.
You can't forget something like that, Senpai!
So when were we supposed to meet up with them?
We planned on meeting an hour ago.
Where's the meeting place?
Let's see...
Here.
What?!
The place where we're supposed to meet up is just upstairs.
So there's no need to rush.
Right...
Wait.  Even so, we're already an hour late, so we gotta hurry!
Wait!
Geez, you're so pushy.
S-Sorry.
Whoa, we're going higher and higher!
I have a fear of heights.
This is way too scary.  I've gotta start a conversation.
S-Senpai, who in your family is going to be there?
Oh, yeah.  Actually, because of flight delays,
my grandparents weren't able to come today.
We'll be alone together.
I see.
Alone together?!
That's right.
What about your parents?
They said there's no point in going if my
grandparents couldn't make it.  They're at home.
O-Oh, at home.
I didn't want to waste the room we already reserved, so I came to spend the night.
It would be a waste, I guess...
What a shame.
I wanted to look at the night scenery a little longer.
Let's go.
O-Okay.  We're going...
E-Excuse me.
Look, look.
We can see the night scenery!
Y-Yeah.
I wonder what the bathroom's like?
S-Senpai?
Hey, the bathroom's really great too!
Ooh, the bathtub's really big!
Amazing!
W-Wow.  Amazing.
Since I'm already here, I think I'll take a bath.
A bath?!
You rarely see a bath this big, so it'd be a waste not to.
Y-You're right.
No peeking.
I-I won't!
Wow, good answer.
Well, I'll be taking my bath.
She's actually taking a bath.
S-Should I go in with her?
No no, we're not close enough for that yet...
Hmm, but I'd like to get that close...
Ugh, what am I thinking about?!
I can't believe I'm actually spending
Christmas Eve with Morishima-senpai.
I wouldn't have even dreamed of it not too long ago.
It was really tough when she turned me down once.
But I'm glad I didn't give up and went on the offensive again.
Thanks to that, I'm able to spend Christmas Eve with her.
Here you go.
Thanks.
French Fries
TL Note: Oden is a winter dish, most closely analogous to stew.
I'm so glad I managed to get Oden from the Swim Club before they sold out!
Thank you.
French Fries
Looks like things have settled down, Tsukahara-senpai.
It has.  Nanasaki, you can go home now.
Your brother's waiting, isn't he?
Yes, but we still need to clean up-
I'll do the cleaning up with the other club members.
Then... thank you very much!
French Fries
I wonder how she's doing right now.
A white Christmas, huh?
So how will we spend the time?
Should I take a bath too, after Senpai's done?
Well, it'd be bad if I didn't...
TL Note: In Japan, showering/bathing is a prelude to sex.
Wait, why would it be bad?!
That's no different from what you were just thinking about!
A power outage?
Nope.
Senpai?
It's embarrassing, so I turned the lights off.
Why are you only in a...
Senpai?
Dummy.
Why didn't you come and peek at me?
Why didn't you come and peek?!
Crap!  So I was supposed to go and peek!
You don't... like me?
I-I like you.
Wouldn't you peek without hesitation if you really did like me?
Well, I wonder...
I don't understand.
Senpai?
Why won't you confess to me again?
Even though you said that you'd
confess as many times as it'd take...
I...
I like you!
I really do!
Senpai.
I've been waiting...
I've been waiting all this time...
I thought that maybe you didn't like me anymore...
I thought that maybe you'd given up...
I was so lonely... and scared...
That's not it at all.
But I don't understand!
I've never fallen this deeply in love with someone before.
It's the first time I've ever wanted to keep someone for myself.
I don't know what to do!
I'm sorry.  I should've done better.
I couldn't even confess properly to you.
Would you still want someone like me?
No, your confession was really great.
When you confessed the second time, it was the
first time my heart's ever raced from a confession.
But because of that, I wasn't sure how to let you know how I feel...
I'm the one who can't even confess properly...
I was afraid that you'd give up on me, Tachibana-kun...
I was worried... and scared...
It's okay.
You can stay just like this.
That's the Morishima-senpai I fell in love with.
I'll get it all right from now on.
So please don't cry.
Call me "Haruka".
I don't want you to keep calling me "Senpai".
If you call me by my name, I won't cry anymore.
Haruka.
Well done.
I love you.
I want to be with you forever.
I love you too.
I really do.
Kiss me.
And don't let me go.
10 Years Later
So it's been ten years since then.
Are the two of you getting along well?
Oh, come on, Hibiki.
We're all lovey-dovey.
Well, since you're both weirdos,
I figured you guys would get along fine.
Criminal scum, you're under arrest!
Hibiki, run!
Right, Tachibana-kun.
Do you do this every day?
No, well...
We do that rarely.
Really rarely.
It's been so long, Tsukahara-senpai!
You must be busy as a doctor, right?
Well, I'm somewhat busy.
Though, since you're actually a real detective,
I'm worried for Japan's security.
Hibiki.  Junichi might not be able to keep Japan safe,
but he promised me he'd keep me safe forever.
Haruka.
Junichi.
I love you as much as the number of stars in the sky!
Okay, thanks for the meal.
I love you too, Junichi!
Haruka.
Junichi!
"Kawaii" sore dake de
"Cute".  With just that one word
Muchuu de nadetaku naru urunda hitomi
I'm in a daze, and I want to rub my teary eyes
Jarete iru toki wa
When you were flirting with me
Natsuite iru dake da to
You were just being friendly
Omotteta n da
At least, that's what I thought
Koi no hajimari nante
The beginning of a romance
Yohou hazure no tenki mitai
Is like a missed weather forecast
Ameagari no niji no sora ni te nobasou
I stretch my hands towards the rainbow-filled sky after the rain
Kimi no tonari wa sunao na
Because when I'm by your side
Kimochi ni nareru kara
I can be honest with myself
Kizuita kimi no koto omou
I've realized that when I think about you
Jikan wa mune no oku ga konnani takanaru koto
My heart starts to pound so much
Kinou yume no naka ni
In my dream last night
Mata kimi ga dete kita
You appeared again
Preview
Next episode preview.
All right, the Tanamachi Kaoru arc starts next episode!
Kaoru, don't take things too far.
What are you talking about?
We'll start things off with a bang!
Uh... keep it reasonable.
Well, let's have fun!
Gotcha.
Oh, darling, I know you're actually happy about this.
Don't snuggle against my elbow.
And don't call me darling!
Next episode, "Buddy".
The new story with Kaoru, my
friend since middle school, begins.
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc: Chapter 1
Buddy
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc: Chapter 1
Buddy
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc: Chapter 1
Buddy
Please look forward to it!