Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
Entrance
- 1 Year Ago -
Thank you very much!
Tonight is Christmas Eve.
The busy Founder's Festival was taking place at school.
Miss Santa Contest
Right around this time last year...
My heart was broken.
I'm not sure if it's because of that, but I don't like this time very much.
Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
Entrance
I can't bring myself to join the fun.
Are you going in, boss?
Umehara.
I've been waiting this whole time for you to show up.
Let's hurry up and go see the Miss Santa Contest.
Or we'll miss Morishima-senpai's turn!
What's wrong?
Sorry, Umehara.
I...
I see.
Christmas still hurts, huh?
Well, why don't us lonely single men have a gaming and porn mag reading party at my place tonight?
I don't have anything fancy like a Christmas cake or anything,
but you can have as much sushi as you want.
Plus, instead of champagne, you can have some hot green tea!
That sounds good.
56th Annual
Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
Miss Santa Contest
Winner
And the winner of the Miss Santa Contest is...
Last year's winner, Morishima Haruka-kun!
Thanks!
Founder's Festival
Planning Committee
Next year for sure...
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Typesetter: Bob64
Stuff: ar
Morning, Junichi!
Oh, morning.
Hasn't it gotten cold lately?
That's because it's winter now.
That's right, it's winter now...
Ayatsuji Tsukasa Arc
Chapter 1
Discovery
Obviously...
Hey, Junichi.
Huh?
About Christmas...
Are you coming to the Founder's Festival this year?
Let's see... I dunno.
You should just come if you don't have anything else to do.
After all, it's an important school event.
The Tea Club is doing a store this year too, so come hang out!
I'll even give you stuff!
Like tea or sweet sake.
Tea and sweet sake, huh?
You're not really interested?
That's not quite it...
It's already been a year since then.
Christmas is approaching again.
I have unpleasant feelings about it as usual...
But...
Let's try harder next year.
I'm saying it's too bad this year, but let's find
girlfriends and have a fun Christmas Eve next year.
You can't stay like this forever.
I'll definitely find a girl!
So don't hate me if you end up spending Christmas Eve alone next year.
I'll make you eat those words!
That's right...
Okay, I'll go to the Founder's Festival this year.
Really?  That's a relief.
Huh?
Ah, it's nothing!
Rihoko, you're gonna fall over!
I'm fine!  Hurry up, Junichi!
As juniors, you should all know this already.
Every year, on the birthday of our school's founder, December 24th,
we hold a Founder's Festival with the aim of interacting with neighboring residents and family members.
On that note, we need to pick a committee
member from each class for this year's festival.
Are there any volunteers?
Nobody?
I'll do it.
Ayatsuji-san, are you sure?
Yes.
I did it last year as well, and it
seems no one else is volunteering.
But you're already working as the class representative.
I think I'll be fine.
I don't really have much work as class
representative around this time of year.
Even so, I still think having another person would be helpful.
Would anyone like to help Ayatsuji-san?
Well, I need to help at the restaurant...
Um...
I'd like to help...
What's gotten into you, boss?
It's the Founder's Festival!
Christmas Eve!
And anyway, you're not the type to become a committee member!
Wait... are you going for Ayatsuji-san?
I'm not!
Do you have a fever or something?
Maybe your pulse has weakened...
That's not it either.
You guys are jerks.
Yeah, but still...
Right?
I just figured I'd try a little harder.
For what?
For Christmas.
I might change my mind like last year when the time comes.
So I figured I'll have to go even if I don't want to if I'm on the committee.
Ah, I get it.
I don't.
Anyway, that's what it was.
Tachibana-kun.
Ayatsuji-san.
I didn't expect you to volunteer, Tachibana-kun.
I don't know how much help I'll be, but let's get along.
I did this last year too, so ask me if you have any questions.
Okay.
Best of luck.
I'll be cheering for you in my heart.
In your heart, huh?
Anyway, I'll be watching over you.
Help me instead.
Well, I'm planning to work on Christmas Eve.
You shouldn't.
Nope, I will.
Nii-nii, you're in the Founder's Festival committee now?
Yeah.
We had our first meeting today after school.
In that case,
I'll take you on!
How did it go?
Well, my classmate Ayatsuji-san was chosen as the committee president.
Mumumu!
She was nominated directly by last year's president.
She knew that many look up to Ayatsuji-san.
So Nii-nii, are you and this Ayatsuji-san girl really close?
Not really.
Why?
Well, you could ask for favors if my class decides to do something!
Hey now, Ayatsuji-san isn't that kind of person.
Then I guess you'll do, Nii-nii.
"Then"?  What do you mean, "then"?
Why not?  It's all for your cute little sister!
I said no.
Founder's Festival
Planning Committee Headquarters
The Girl's Swim Club would like to run an Oden stall.
We're from Class 1-A!
We'll be performing a play!
Founder's Festival Activity Registration Form
Class/Club Name
Tea Club
Event
Tea Room (Tea, Snacks, Sweet Sake)
Location
The Tea Club garden
We're from the Tea Club.
Founder's Festival Activity Registration Form
Class/Club Name
Tea Club
Event
Tea Room (Tea, Snacks, Sweet Sake)
Location
The Tea Club garden
Founder's Festival Activity Registration Form
Class/Club Name
Tea Club
Event
Tea Room (Tea, Snacks, Sweet Sake)
Location
The Tea Club garden
Founder's Festival Activity Registration Form
Class/Club Name
Tea Club
Event
Tea Room (Tea, Snacks, Sweet Sake)
Location
The Tea Club garden
We're doing a simple tea party and selling sweet sake as usual.
Huh?
Junichi, you're on the committee.
Yeah.
Does this mean you'll be too busy to come hang out on the day?
I'll try to find some time to at least drop by.
Okay, I'll be waiting!
Let's go, Rihocchi.
All right, hang in there.
Yeah.
Is she your girlfriend, Tachibana-kun?
Nah, she's just my childhood friend.
All right.
Is this all?
Not even close.
There'll be plenty of people scrambling to hand it in on the day of the deadline.
I see.
Yep.
You're pretty amazing though, Ayatsuji-san.
Huh?
Founder's Festival Activity Registration Form
Class/Club Name
Tea Club
Event
Tea Room (Tea, Snacks, Sweet Sake)
Location
When did you make all these application forms and informational fliers?
I had no idea.
There was plenty of data from last year, so it wasn't too bad.
What's more, you've almost finished handing them all out.
I handed them out slowly during breaks and after school.
I would've helped if you asked.
It was something I could handle alone.
I know!
In that case, could you help me with something?
Sure!
Supply Room
My predecessor told me this last year,
but there's a little trick to opening this door.
So this is the supply room.
It's where the lights for the Christmas tree and various things used in the Founder's Festival are stored.
We technically only use them once a year.
Oh, don't close that.
The doorknob is a little broken, so the door can't be opened from the inside.
I see.
Got it.
Okay, please help me check the equipment here.
Gotcha.
It's really dusty in here though.
Let's get some fresh air in here.
Sorry.
It won't open...
I don't think we can fit through there...
And we can't exactly get down from here.
I don't think there's any need to worry too much.
I let the other committee members know that we're here.
I'm sure someone will come soon.
You think so?
Even if nobody shows up, and we have to spend the night here...
Tachibana-kun, won't you protect me?
All right, let's get to work.
Y-Yeah...
What's wrong, Tachibana-kun?
It's nothing, I'm fine.
By the way...
Why did you join the committee, Ayatsuji-san?
Well, isn't it a wonderful thing?
I can help bring happiness to so many people.
Hmm, that's true.
What about you, Tachibana-kun?
Huh?
Why did you join the committee?
I didn't think you were the type to.
Umehara said the same thing.
So why?
I... thought I'd try a little harder.
Try harder?
I've always been kinda unmotivated.
So I thought I'd change myself.
And this is the first big step for that.
That's wonderful.
N-Not at all.
Ayatsuji-san, what kind of music do you listen to?
Why the sudden question?
I just kinda felt like asking.
I see, you just felt like it...
Well, that's a tricky question now that I think about it.
Why?
I listen to a lot of different genres.
Like classical...
And J-pop?
Yeah, and other stuff like...
Okay.
That should be all.
Yeah.
Good job.
You too, Tachibana-kun.
Though...
Nobody came in the end, huh?
Don't tell me we're really gonna have to spend the night here...
Don't worry, the guard will make his rounds around here before that happens.
Ah, I see.
Ah, there it is!
Sae-chan, I found the supply room!
That's Miya's voice!
I think that's my sister!
Huh, that's weird.  It won't open.
Do you think it's locked?
Miya!
Onii-chan?  Why are you in there?
And wait, why did you lock the door?
I didn't lock it, it got locked.
Try pushing down on the doorknob as you turn it.
It's the trick to opening this door.
L-Like this?
It opened!
We're saved.
Why are you in here?
Hide and seek?
No, it's committee work.
We got locked in while doing that.
Thank you.  You really saved us.
Not at all, you're very welcome.
So what did you come here for?
Oh, that's right.  Our class wanted to use some costumes for our play.
So we came to borrow some.
We've already filled out a request form.
Yes, this is it!
A rabbit and a shark?
Are you doing The White Hare of Inaba?
TL Note: The White Hare of Inaba is a classical Japanese folktale, in which a hare tricks some sharks into acting as a bridge for him.
That's a secret!
Supply Room
Let's go, Sae-chan.
O-Okay.
Um... thank you very much.
Sorting out all the equipment really helped, didn't it?
Yeah.
Supply Room
Miya!  Why did you shut the door?!
Miya!
Ah, I'm sorry!
Geez, Miya's unbelievable.
My heart was beating really fast.
Beating?  My heart almost flew out of my chest!
Huh?  Tsukasa-chan?
Ah, it really is Tsukasa-chan.
You're out with a boy, huh?  I underestimated you.
W-Who's this?
My older sister.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tsukasa-chan's older sister, Ayatsuji Yukari.
I-I'm Ayatsuji-sa-
Uh, Tsukasa-san's classmate, Tachibana Junichi.
So you've been taking care of Tsukasa-chan... right?
N-Not at all.  More like she's taking care of me.
I see.
What are you doing here?
I was asked to do the groceries for tonight's dinner.
Oh.
Sorry, Tachibana-kun.
I just remembered there's something I need to do.
I see.
See you tomorrow!
Y-Yeah.  See you tomorrow.
Tsukasa-chan, you're walking too fast!
Founder's Festival
Planning Committee Headquarters
What's going on here?!
We turned in the request form like we were supposed to.
So why do other classes get what they need and we don't?!
W-Well... I wonder why...
Maybe there's a mistake...
Two power outlets aren't nearly enough!
Give us at least three!
I'd also like another location...
I'm not sure I can help you...
Senpai!
W-What?
How many pamphlets were we supposed to print?
We just got a call from the printing press...
U-Um... let's see...
I-I can't!
I can't handle this without Ayatsuji-san!
I think she said she'd be in the pool today...
Excuse me.
Ayatsuji-san, that hurts...
You need to do your warm up properly.
Ayatsuji-san, you monster...
What's this?
Oh, Tachibana-kun.
What are you doing?
Supplementary swimming lessons.
For PE.
I help with supplementary lessons for swimming and track.
The teacher is taking care of the track today...
So I'm acting as the instructor over here.
Wow, that's amazing.
Swimming isn't one of my strengths though.
What is it, Junichi?
Did you come to stare at us in swimsuits?
Obviously not, idiot.
I was looking for Ayatsuji-san.
Me?
Yeah.
There's a lot going on at the committee room.
Like not enough equipment, what's happening with power outlets, how many copies of the pamphlets we need...
Okay, I see.
I'll go straight to the committee room after I'm done here.
That'd really help.
Don't worry about it.
Didn't you become a committee
member to support Ayatsuji-san?
Pull yourself together.
So why is this noisy girl having supplementary lessons?
I'm pretty sure she can swim.
Tanamachi-san skipped too many lessons.
I'm pretty sure you've been coming to school.
I just don't like swimming.
My hair gets all wet.
Hey now...
Well, Tachibana-kun.  I'll see you later.
Y-Yeah.
She's the class rep, the committee president, and she even fills in for the teachers.
Ayatsuji-san really is amazing.
Though...
The three of them are so full of life, aren't they?
Y-Yes, you're right.
And when you combine the three of them together...
Ah, how do I say this... I just can't get enough!
Y-Yes.
W-What?!  M-Morishima-senpai?!
Shh.  They'll find out we're peeping.
What do you mean, peeping?
Normally, I'd be warning you at this point...
But I understand your inability to withstand such charm.
It's so nice to be young!
Uh, um...
Come on, you need to hide.
They'll see you if you stay there.
E-Excuse me!
Oh my, he left.
Well, whatever.  I'll just take my time to enjoy the view by myself!
And just what are you enjoying?
What do you think you're doing, Haruka?
Uh, um... I was looking for you,
Hibiki-chan, and I didn't see you here...
You don't have practice today?
Yeah.  The teacher said the pool would be used for supplementary lessons.
Okay, let's go back now that you've found me.
Hibiki-chan!  Five more minutes, just five more!
Don't use excuses that sound like they're from someone who's half-asleep.
Just a little more.
I'll go home once this is done.
Though, this still takes forever to do without Ayatsuji-san.
Huh?  What's this?
A notebook?
I wonder who dropped this...
Hopefully there's a name written somewhere...
Ah, it's finally over.
I'm completely worn out.
Wow.
Everything is really well planned out.
And the handwriting's really neat.  I wonder whose this is?
I'm pretty sure there'd normally be a name written at the back of something like this.
A-Ayatsuji-san?
Tachibana-kun.
Why are you still in a swimsuit?
What's the matter?
That... that notebook.
Is this yours, Ayatsuji-san?
That's good, I just picked it up.
I see...
Did you read it?
Oh, sorry.
I was hoping I'd find a name in there, so just a little.
I see.
Ayatsuji-san?
So you read it.
Hodou wo kazaru aoi Illumination
The blue illumination adorns the sidewalk
Nigiwau hitogomi ni hitori tatazumu
And I stand alone in the bustling crowd
Koboresou na egao
Smiles peeking through
Yorisou koibitotachi
Lovers snuggling against each other
Ima no watashi ni wa subete ga
Everything to me now is so bright
Mabushikute mirenai no
That I cannot bear to look
Dareka ni aisareru deshou ka
Will anyone love me?
Tsuyogari no oku ni kakureta
I'm hiding beneath a facade
Watashi ni kizuite yo
Please notice the real me
Hontou ni jiyuu ni nareru deshou ka
Can I really become free?
Douka oshiete
Please tell me
Fuyu no machi ni mayoikonda
Having lost her way in the winter town
The lonely angel sighs
Sabishige na tenshi ga nageku
Yasashiku
Gently
Preview
Next episode preview.
Junichi, what happened?  You look terrified.
K-Kaoru!
Aren't you a guy?  Pull yourself together!
Ayatsuji-san is...
Ayatsuji-san is...!
What about Ayatsuji-san?
Ah, so helping out with the committee work was tougher than you thought?
N-No, that's not it... it's...
Next episode: "Inner Side".
Next Episode
Inner Side
She has a much stricter side to her than you thought, huh?
She's an honest girl at heart though.
At heart...
At heart...!