Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
Welcome!  Welcome!
Would you like some of our delicious Yakisoba?
The fish cakes have a high oil content, so you need to boil them before putting them in with the rest.
As for the soup stock, you should put it into the pot with an equal amount of water.
The stock will begin to dilute as it's cooking,
so keep an eye on it and replace it as necessary.
I think that's it.
I've explained everything to Nanasaki, but do you have any questions?
I think I'll be fine.
I'll just ask Nanasaki if there's anything I don't understand.
Leave it to me!
I'll take care of things even if
Tachibana-senpai is a little unreliable.
H-Hey!  Nanasaki, that's not true, right?
I'm just kidding.
You two are a good combination.
Haruka!
Geez.  I take my eyes off you for one second, and this happens.
What are you talking about?
I'm just sampling the food.
I'm tasting the food to make sure it's acceptable for the customers.
So how is it?
I'll have to eat a little more to know for sure.
I see.
Don't you think trying to convince us that
you'll only have a little more is more than enough?
Huh?  Y-Yeah, I guess that's what I was thinking...
Huh?
Haruka'll probably eat it all if we
stay here any longer, so we're going.
I'm counting on you guys.
Y-Yes!
Nanasaki, hang in there.
Okay!
Hibiki-chan, one more bite.  Just one more, okay?
Yeah yeah...
Morishima-senpai...
Senpai, it's just about time to begin.
Let's sell as much as we can!
Yeah!
We'll now have the opening greeting from the President of the Founder's Festival Planning Committee, Ayatsuji Tsukasa-san.
Thank you all so much for attending tonight's Kibitou High School Founder's Festival.
This festival was started in the spirit of
our appreciation to the founder of our school.
This year will mark our 57th annual celebration.
As with previous years, the school has worked hard under student leadership
Miss Santa Contest Waiting Room
to prepare several activities that will
hopefully meet everybody's expectations.
With gratitude to all of you who assisted,
as well as all of our visitors...
I now announce the opening of the 57th annual Founder's Festival!
Nanasaki Ai Arc
Final Chapter
Confession
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Typesetter: Bob64
Stuff: ar
Excuse me.
TL note: Daikon is a type of radish, Chikuwa is a tubular fish cake,
and Ganmo is deep-fried tofu with veggies mixed in.
I'd like Daikon, Chikuwa, and Ganmo, two of each!
Oden
Girls
Swim Club
O-Okay!
Hanpen and Mochiirikinchaku for me.
TL note: Hanpen is a pounded fish cake, and Mochiirikinchaku is a pouch-shaped item filled with Mochi (glutinous rice paste).
Oh, and maybe some Konbu.
TL note: Konbu is a type of edible kelp used in many dishes.
Grab a nice flavorful one for me, please.
Okay.  Thank you very much.
Nanasaki, we're almost out of Daikon and Hanpen.
I made some more.
I'll put the extras right here next to you, okay?
Okay.
Oh?
Looks like business is booming.
We're here to see if the flavor of
Kibitou High School has been truly passed on.
Kibitou's Winter.  Japan's Winter.
Um... who are you?
You can call us the "Wandering Tea Club".
Wandering?
More importantly!
Isn't this the Girls Swim Club's Oden stall?
Why is there a guy here?!
Oh, I'm just helping out.
Helping out?
Accepting help from a guy?
It appears the fabled Girls Swim Club's Oden stall has fallen.
I'm disappointed.
Hey!
Just a minute.
I'm the one who prepared this Oden.
Please have some if you're unsure about the taste.
I learned from Tsukahara-senpai herself!
Tsukahara...
I see.  So that's how it is...
Okay.
Fine.
If that's the case, I'll give it a try.
However, I won't accept anything but the taste of the traditional Girls Swim Club's Oden!
Yes, I understand.
Nanasaki?
It's okay, Senpai.
Konbu.  One from the very bottom.
I'll take a Daikon.
Give me one with a nice color.
Understood.
Here you go.
Yeah, thanks.
I'm grateful for seafood.
How... is it?
Is... it good?
It... It...
It's delicious!
Yes, yes!  It's delicious!
You've captured the Girls Swim Club's traditional flavor wonderfully!
Thank you very much.
That's good.
Yes!
This flavor is exactly what we were looking for!
The traditional flavor from the
Kibitou High School Girls Swim Club.
With this, I can look forward to this next year.
We'll come again next year.
Oh yeah, what's your name?
Me?
I'm Nanasaki Ai, and I'm a freshman in the Swim Club.
I'll remember that.
Ooh, looks like Manaka's taken a liking to you.
All right, the bill.
I'll leave the money right here.
O-Okay.
We'll be sure to spread the word everywhere we go.
That the traditional flavor of the Swim Club is going strong.
Very satisfying.
Thank you very much.
Wow, what a nice smell.
T-Takahashi-sensei?!
That's right!  I'm Takahashi Maya-chan!
Is she drunk?
What's going on?
Ah, um... the thing is...
The Tea Club serves sweet sake
at the Founder's Festival every year.
Does this mean...
Last year, Takahashi-sensei caused a lot of trouble after drinking some sweet sake.
So this year we warned everyone not to let her drink...
But Rihocchi let her have some in the short time we took our eyes off her.
Rihoko, what have you done?
We brought her to the infirmary to sleep it off, but...
The great escape.
You didn't know about it, Tachibana-senpai?
I didn't go to the Founder's Festival last year.
So how much did she drink?
Well...
That much?!
What's wrong with that?!
I'm only human.
Sometimes I drink, lose control of myself, and do crazy things.
Sensei...
Wait, drinking is fine and all, but
losing control and doing crazy things isn't...
Whatever!  Gramps, give me some Oden!
And some Shouchuu Dashiwari!
Huh?
I said gimme some Shouchuu Dashiwari!
What's that?
Don't you know?
It's Shouchuu mixed with Oden
soup stock.  Now give me some!
I'd like to, but I don't have any sake since this is a school festival...
You don't have any?
Geez, this stall is useless.
Ugh... my image of Takahashi-sensei is crumbling.
What's going on here?
What's all this ruckus?
Ayatsuji-san.
Ah, Class Rep!
Takahashi-sensei?  Not again...
Sorry about this.
You even gave us permission to serve sweet sake this year too.
No, it's not your fault.
Sorry about this.  Can you guys handle this?
Yes.
Takahashi-sensei, let's go to the infirmary.
Wah~  Shouchuu!
Thanks, Ayatsuji-san.
No, don't worry about it.
It's part of my job.
Senpai.
Give this to her.
Ayatsuji-san, take this as a thank you.
Eh?  Really?
Yeah.
Thanks.  I'll go ahead and take it, then.
Yep.
All right, both of you hang in there.
Sorry about all the trouble, guys.
We need to head back to the
Tea Club soon, so we're going too.
We'll let everyone know about your stand.
We keep our promises.
All right!  Let's get back to work!
Yes!
Huh?
That's strange.
What's the matter?
Well, something isn't right...
Sorry we're late, Rihocchi.
You're both really late!
It was really tough all by myself.
Miss Santa Contest Waiting Room
Next up, entry number 8!
Tanaka Keiko-san!
Go for it, Keiko.
Y-Yeah!  Here I go!
No way...
Hey, cuties!
Hey, pretty girl!
Sae-chan?
Sae-chan!
Where are you, Sae-chan?
There's no way I can enter a contest like that...
Here you go.  Thanks for waiting!
Excuse me for a bit, Senpai.
Huh?
H-Hey!
Here.
Tsukahara-senpai would probably do the same.
I guess so.
They sure look happy.
Yes.
Namaiki desu ka
Am I cheeky?
Sokkenaku miemasu ka
Do I seem cold?
Hanashite kudasai
Talk to me
Kuuru heddo
Cool head
Can't you make up your mind?
Mayoi nayami futari katari
I'm lost, I'm troubled, but when we both converse
Ureshii desu
It makes me so happy
We're sold out, huh?
We are.
Ah, I wanted some Oden myself...
I've set some aside for you.
Really?
Yes.
But you can't have it until we've finished cleaning up.
I guess.
All right, let's start cleaning up!
We can take care of that for you guys.
Tsukahara-senpai?
What's with that outfit?
I've overcome a hurdle.
Huh?
Anyway, both of you did great.
The girls we had running as barkers are coming back soon,
and all the seniors had enough time to enjoy their last Founder's Festival.
We'll clean up after the hard work of our salespeople.
But...
Free time as a reward for a complete sellout.
You can't complain about that, right?
Okay, got it.
Thank you very much.
Man, I'm tired.
We were selling non-stop.
I can finally have a normal chat with you, Nanasaki.
When we were selling, there wasn't any time for that at all.
I... guess so.
All right, I'm eating this Oden you saved for me.
Mmh, it's delicious.
I can see why we sold out!
Really?
Yeah.
By the way...
Didn't you ask me if I was free the other day?
Remember?  It was when you asked me to help out with the Oden stall.
How come?
Well...
Do you want to find out?
Senpai, hurry!
The bus is going to leave!
Wait, Nanasaki!
We barely made it.
I'm glad we caught the last bus.
But where are we going?
It's a secret.
I'm sorry I didn't participate in the contest in the end...
Nah, I'm the one who's sorry.
I misunderstood you when you said you wanted to wear a Santa costume.
Me too, I didn't make myself clear...
Anyway, is it really okay to spend the night at your place?
Yeah.  My dad said it's okay.
I think dinner's ready too.
Yay!  We're having a Christmas party at Sae-chan's place tonight!
Miya-chan, that's not a Christmas song.
Oh really?
Nanasaki, what are we getting off here for?
Let's go.
Huh?  Where to?
This way.
What?!
We're gonna go up the hill now?
Yes, that's right.
You'll get left behind if you don't keep up!
Wait for me, Nanasaki!
We've been walking for a while, so we must be pretty deep in.
It's just a little further.  Hang in there.
Okay...
Just what could be out here?
Maybe...
Um... Senpai.
Do whatever you want with me.
That...
I can't wait any longer.
Or that...
Senpai.  You aren't going anywhere.
No one can hear you here, no matter how loudly you scream.
I don't think I'd like that.
I guess I prefer what's coming to be erotic, after all...
Senpai.
Y-Yes, what is it?
Why are you so flustered?
It's nothing.
You didn't notice?
Notice what?
The smell.
The smell...
Huh?  This smell...
The smell of boiled eggs... sulfur?
This place...
A hot spring?
Yes.  This is our destination.
I've brought hot spring supplies too.
So that's what's in your sports bag.
I've prepared your share too, of course.
You should've just said so if that was the case.
I wanted to surprise you.
This hill belongs to my grandfather.
I frequently use this place for things like
when my muscles ache from swimming practice.
I see.
Something like your own secret hot spring, I guess.
Here.
Senpai, this is for you.
I'll go get changed, so feel free to go in first.
Okay.
Ah, this feels great.
We did walk up the hill all the way here, after all.
Though, what's Nanasaki trying to do?
Bringing me to a deserted hot spring up the hill at this hour...
Senpai?
Y-Yes.
Did you go in already?
Y-Yeah...
Then... I'll go in too.
Okay.  I'll be facing this way so I can't see you.
You can look.
I'm wearing my swimsuit underneath.
Sorry for the disappointment.
It's fine...
I guess that makes sense.
I actually don't mind either way,
but I figured it'd be better for you if I wore my swimsuit.
Y-Yeah...
I guess so.
It's true that I probably wouldn't be able to hold a conversation with her if she wasn't wearing one.
I... I'm feeling nervous for some reason.
Yes.
I-I'm glad we managed to sell out all the Oden today.
Y-Yes.
We had a lot of customers.
The Senpai at the Tea Club also
acknowledged your cooking ability.
Yes.
I never would've imagined I'd be selling Oden together with you when we first met.
Me neither.
What's more, here we are in the hot spring, together...
Yeah.
So much has happened in such a short time.
Senpai.
There's something I want to tell you.
What is it?
My... feelings.
Senpai, I...
...like you.
I like you.
Nanasaki...
I like you so much, I can't hold these feelings inside me any longer.
I can't hide them anymore.
It's overwhelming me... I can't hide it any longer.
I'm happy.
Huh?
Because I like you too, Nanasaki.
I like you, Nanasaki.
I'm helplessly in love with you.
Huh?  Nanasaki?
Nanasaki?
Nanasaki!
N-Nanasaki, didn't you say you had a swimsuit on?
I lied because it was too embarrassing.
You lied?
But it was nothing compared to confessing to you, Senpai.
It was nothing?
This is a little too...
There's nothing wrong with this.
But...
It's okay.
Because I love you, Senpai.
Sign: Please take your trash home with you!
Sign: Keep our beaches clean!
Senpai.
Senpai...
Wake up.
You'll catch a cold if you keep sleeping.
Just a little longer.
Sleeping on your lap feels so warm and nice, Ai.
Geez, you're hopeless.
Just a little longer!
Even if you were to catch a cold,
I'll be there to nurse you back to health.
Thanks, Ai.
I don't mind at all if it's for you, Senpai.
Yurayura yureteru Surface Of The Pool
The surface of the pool shakes and sways
Takaku tobikomu kakikomu
I dive in and it carries me under
Watashi tsutsunde
It envelops me
Kokoro no okusoko he michiteku
And fills the depths of my heart
Nani shiteru n desu ka
What are you doing?
Nani wo mite iru n desu ka
What are you looking at?
Toikaketeru n desu
I'm asking you a question
Poker Face
Childlike
Mitai kawaii awai kitai
I want to see it, it's cute, it's fleeting, the expectation
Tanoshii desu
It's all fun
Majime sugata fui ni miserare
When I unexpectedly saw your serious side
Mune no oku ga tsukiugoite
Something stirred deep within my chest
Kokoro yurayura yureteru Feel Comfortable
The swaying and shaking of my heart feels comfortable
Takaku habataku koeteku
I'll flap my wings and fly over
Ashita aeru
So I can see you tomorrow
Utakata uiteru koi moyou
Patterns of love bubble on the water surface
Konna kanjou nan da to omoimasu ka
What do you think these feelings are?
Tawai mo naku soba de
I want to be by your side
Waraiaitai desu
And laugh with you without a care in the world
Watashi no kimochi na n desu
These are my feelings
To You Innocent
Preview
Next episode preview.
Junichi, I have something important to tell you.
What is it, Rihoko?
Well, apparently I'm the protagonist in the next episode.
What do you mean?
I think that's exactly what it means...
Am I wrong?
Don't be stupid, Rihoko.
It's gotta be someone's prank.
Really?
Next Episode
Sakurai Rihoko Arc: Chapter 1
Memories
Next Episode
Sakurai Rihoko Arc: Chapter 1
Memories
Next Episode
Sakurai Rihoko Arc: Chapter 1
Memories
Next episode: "Memories".
Actually, it really looks like I'm gonna be the protagonist.
Then what about me?