Seriously, what's wrong with me?
Why do I suddenly feel this way?
I thought you were gonna confess to me, Kaoru.
Isn't he just a buddy I've had since middle school?!
No more, no less...
But he's not the one who's changed.
I am.
But why?  How come?
It's true that I'm not satisfied with our current relationship...
If you described it as a color, it'd be a pale pink.
But it's all too sudden!
I don't even know what I want.
Ah, I'm so uncool.
I'm just going around in circles...
Geez, what's wrong with me?!
Could it be that...
I'm in love?!
No.  No way.
No, no.
Nii-nii, what are you eating?
You can have some.
It's the limited-edition stuffed rice cake flavor.
You seem happy.  Did something good happen?
Huh?  Not really.
Oh?
What's the matter, Miya?
Nothing.
These are actually good!
They even taste a little like stuffed meat buns!
Uh, you've gotta be kidding.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Editor: IGChris
Typesetter: Kemeko
Stuff: ar
Brr, it's so cold!
Don't screw with me!
What are you doing, Tanamachi?!
That's my line!
Did you even consider how she feels?!
You're always acting like a kid!
This has nothing to do with you, Tanamachi.
Not directly, no.
But it pisses me off when you do such malicious things to people around me!
Well, does it feel that good to hurt the feelings of others?!
Think hard on what you've done with that empty head of yours!
If you'd just shut up and listen...
What?  You wanna fight?
H-Hang on!
Stay out of this!
You don't know what's going on, so keep your mouth shut!
I may not know what's going on, but I can't just ignore it!
What on Earth is the matter?
What's the matter, Tanamachi-san?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Wait, Tanamachi-san!
Hey, where are you going?!
Geez, what was that about?
Seriously, getting all worked up over something like that.
Hey.
What happened?
Tanamachi lunged at me out of the blue.
For no reason?
It's my fault.
Kaoru... did it for me...
What?
Kaoru.
Hey.  What exactly happened?
Could you tell me?
Those guys passed Keiko's letter around and laughed at it.
Wait, so he's the one Tanaka-san likes...
Everything happened the way I feared it would.
Since the whole kissing incident,
I knew he was that kind of person.
But Keiko said she liked him,
so I thought I'd give her my support.
Keiko followed your advice and did her best to write the letter last night.
She kept calling me over the phone and asking me, "how's this?"
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc
Chapter 2
Hesitation
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc
Chapter 2
Hesitation
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc
Chapter 2
Hesitation
She said that she still likes him even
though he says horrible things to her.
With all her heart.
I see.
I tried to stay calm at first.
But when I heard them laughing...
Sorry, Kaoru.
Why are you apologizing?
If I'd known that, I wouldn't have stopped you.
It's fine.
Either way, I didn't intend to say anything more to him.
What's more, after all that, he'll definitely think it over.
Think?  About what?
About Keiko.
I wonder about that...
Keiko's problem was that the guy she
confessed to never gave her an answer.
The problem's completely solved now, isn't it?
Keiko knows what kind of guy
he is now, and I feel so much better.
And how does your feeling better help the situation?
Oh, yeah.  You have a point.
Geez.
I don't really like the cold, but I like how the sky looks during the winter.
Oh?
How do I put it...
It's nice and clear, and you can see really far up.
Yeah.
The end.
Huh?
"Thoughts on the sky".  The end.
That's it?
Yeah.
In that case, you're the one at fault.
In these circumstances, anyone would get mad.
It didn't have to be Tanamachi-san.
Hey, Kaoru.
I kinda learned this through the love letter incident,
but Tanaka-san's pretty assertive despite her timid look.
Yeah.  I was pretty surprised myself at first.
So you thought so too.
Well, things turned out pretty bad this time.
Yeah.
But next time, I'll definitely make everything work out!
You should just watch over her quietly.
I guess.
Kaoru.
I'd like to ask you something.
Do you have someone you like?
W-Why do you need to know that?!
Eh, no particular reason.
No particular reason?
Well, do you?
Can't you just tell me?
Don't wanna.
Why not?  Stingy.
Well then, do you have a girl you like?
I don't.
I see.
I wonder what you'd call our relationship?
Huh?  What made you say that?
I've been thinking about it.
I wonder what you'd call our relationship?
Even in high school, nothing's really changed from how we were in middle school.
We maintain a certain distance, all lukewarm.
It's such a vague relationship.
Just like... pale pastel colors.
Pale... pastel?
P-Pastel pink...
I don't think you've learned your lesson yet.
N-No, no, no.  So what about pastels?
It's an example to illustrate our relationship.
What would you call it?
Something like... buddies?
I guess that's about where we are.
I already knew that.
So?
Yeah, that's why...
I was thinking it's about time to change it just a little.
Change, huh?
We met each other in middle school,
but we've matured quite a bit since then.
Well, that's true.
But there's no need for a change in our relationship now, right?
T-That's not true!
It's definitely, definitely, needed!
What are you so worked up for?
I-I'm not worked up at all!
Okay.
I don't really know what you're thinking,
but I'll play along with making a change if you want.
Well, what should we do?
I didn't think about that at all.
I thought so.
Well, lemme ask you.
Isn't there anything you want to do?
Not really.
Then give me some time.
I'll think about it.
What do you mean, you'll think about it?
Well, okay.
Haruka, it's about time you narrowed down your options.
I'm lost.
A strong, sturdy one isn't bad,
but I also really want a small, cute one that wants my affection.
Though, maybe one with a long tail would be...
Haruka, what are you talking about?
We're talking about career plans, career plans.
Oh?  Well then, I'm planning to test into a liberal arts university.
Yes, and we were talking about how you need to narrow down the course of study you'll follow.
Oh, I see.
All right, I've decided!
Whoa, wait a minute!
You haven't decided anything at all!
What are you gonna do?
Something nice.
"Something nice"?
Quit fooling around!
Just shut up and stay still!
Kaoru!
It's pointless to resist!
No, I mean...
Hey, you've gotta be kidding...
W-Wai- Kaoru...
Y-You idiot!
Now we actually kissed because you couldn't stay still!
This was supposed to be just a joke...
But uh, this means...
It was my first.
S-Sorry.
That didn't count!
No count!
Got it?  Bye.
W-Wait!
That was my first too!
You're gonna run away after stealing a kiss from me?!
No count?
Sup, boss.
I got my hands on another porn mag today...
Sorry, Umehara.
I have plans for today.
What's with him?
Kaoru.
W-What is it?
Revenge for earlier.
Come to the library room.
Whatever, just come.
What was that for?
This seems like it'll get interesting.
She'll come, won't she?
So apparently...
Our Tea Club isn't actually pronounced Sadou , but Chadou .
Oh?  Our school is an Urasenke.
Oh, really?
Wait, you're in the Tea Club and you don't know about it?
Nope.  Not at all.
Ah, Junichi!
You're as spacey as ever.
I know, right?
Sometimes the things you say, Sakurai...
I can't tell if you're being serious or not.
I think she's mostly serious, which is why they end up dumb.
That's mean.
It's true though.
Your way of thinking is pretty special, Sakurai.
Oh, wait!
See you, Junichi!
I wonder if this will be on the test.
I think it will.
Thanks.
Hey, wanna come over to my place for Christmas?
Huh?
We can all have cake together!
That sounds fun.  I'd like to go.
Ai-chan, what about you?
Sorry.  My family is getting together for a party.
I see.
Ah, but don't worry about me.
The two of you can have a party.
A two-person party...
You want to?
Sure.
This is gonna be great!
Miya-chan, isn't that your brother?
I'm gonna get you back for earlier.
Like a man.
Oh?  Like a man, huh?
What's with those hands?
The last time I tickled your sides, you almost died laughing.
So prepare to meet the same fate!
You'll regret this.
I'm ready for this.
Even if I have to do this by force...
Stop, stop!
No, I can't!
This won't make me feel any better.
It's not revenge at all.
What are you mumbling to yourself about?
Mysteries of the
Human Body
That's it.
That's it!
All right!
I'm gonna kiss your belly button!
What?  Are you serious?!
Dead serious!
I see.
But what if I say no?
Are you gonna?
I dunno...
I-I take that back...
That's not manly at all.
F-Fine.
Even if you say no, I'll do it by force!
Then... what if I say okay?
Well, what would you do?
In that case, I'll give it all I've got.
W-What?!
I should've known!  You really are funny!
Revenge for earlier, you said?
You've got it.
Let's see your manliness in action.
T-Then-
Kneel down.
What?
Just do it.
Hey, what are you staring at?
You're gonna kiss here, right?
Y-Yeah.
I'm gonna, but...
You know, this is pretty embarrassing for me too.
Try to keep that in mind, okay?
I... I know that.
Then... hurry up and do it.
It tickles.
I never knew girls had such silky smooth skin.
Just touching it with my lips feels incredible.
Quit talking with your lips against me!
Are you done yet?
I don't know about that...
It smells really good for some reason.
A-And it'd be a waste to just let go.
All right, if it's just for a little bit...
H-Hey!  Did you just lick me?!
No!
What are you doing?
We're done!
Aren't you making it harder for me to
get away by putting your clothes over me?!
Nii-nii...
That really was something!
How'd you like it?
I know something well now.
You're a bad boy.
I'm not!
Even after saying you'd show me
your manliness and doing all that?
That was...
Oh, yeah!
Because you were wide open!
You sure know how to talk.
Maybe someone's bad influence is working on me.
Well, whatever.
It was really embarrassing, but...
It was also fun in its own way.
Though whether it was manly or not is something else.
Something else, huh?
Of course it is.
Hey, I have some time until my part-time job.
Wanna go somewhere?
Uh, sure.
Where do you wanna go?
Let's see...
How about a walk in the park?
Sure, let's do that.
What should we do?
Let's go.
Hey, boys.
What is it?
Want some help with that?
Really?
But there's no way you can reach that high.
Hey, you should be able to reach it, right?
Don't be ridiculous.  That's way too high up.
Well then, you'll be on the bottom.
Come on, base.  Hurry up and get down.
I should've known that it'd come to this.
Well, of course.
There's no other way.
Onii-chan, you okay?
Yeah...
Now then...
W-Whoa...
Her thighs feel really...
I'm ready.  Stand up.
O-Okay.
Nice, this is perfect.
Though, can you really reach it riding piggyback?
Of course not.
Well then, what are yo-?!
If you look up, I'll kill you.
Just a little further!
Got it!
Yes!
Onee-chan, you're amazing!
You're so cool!
Come on, Kaoru.  It's dangerous.
Hurry up and get down.
What's the matter?
Do you need my shoulders again?
It's not that.
I can't come down with you watching.
What?
You'll see them, won't you?!
Oh, I see.
Pfft.  Stingy.
What do you mean, "pfft"?
And what do you mean, "stingy"?!
Problem solved!
Yay!
You really are reckless.
You've never been able to ignore someone in need.
Crap!  I'm gonna be late for work!
I'm sorry.
Even though I invited you, we weren't
able to take a walk in the park in the end.
Oh, don't worry about it.
We'll do it another time.
Really?
Okay.  Next time, we'll take our time!
Bye!
Bye-bye!
She seems... different from usual.
Was Kaoru... always that cute?
Why is my heart pounding like this?
Hey, hey.
She's a pretty nice girl.
Have you kissed her yet?
Mom!
Mom-
Mom...
Who... is he?
Who on Earth is he?
Naze naze
Why, oh why?
My Heart kurushii no
Why does my heart ache like this?
Daijoubu nante ne
I tell you that everything's fine
Sokkenai furi shitari
And behave coldly
Namaiki mo urahara
I act outrageous and disagreeable
Saidaigen no tsuyogari
It's the ultimate bluff
Doushite kana namida dechau
Why am I starting to cry?
Aitsu no kao matomo ni mirenai
I can't even look squarely at his face
Ashita wa kitto kinou yori
Tomorrow for sure, even more than yesterday
Tomodachi ijou no kankei ni naritai
I want us to become more than just friends
Ashita wa kitto yume mo kitto
Tomorrow for sure, and in my dreams for sure
Koi suru kimochi kirameku
These feelings of love will shine brilliantly
Just A Friend
Such A Friend
Still A Friend
Naze naze
Why, oh why?
I Can't Tell You My Heart
Why can't I tell you what's in my heart?
Preview
Next episode preview.
Hey, Junichi.
Why were you at the library today?
Uh, I was...
Could it be...
I see, so you were also studying for the exams!
I'll need to work hard on Math, my weakest subject.
Y-Yeah... good luck!
I can't exactly tell her I was kissing Kaoru's belly button.
Next episode: "Betrayal".
Next Episode
Betrayal
Rihoko.  If you need any help in math, I'll teach you, okay?
Really?  Thank you!