Yep.
It's another beautiful day.
Nii-nii!
You'll be late if you don't get up soon!
Don't blame me if Takahashi-sensei yells at you.
Geez...
The sunny weather in Japan should continue throughout the week.
We're leaving early for work.
Mom and Dad
However, from the weekend until the start of next week, parts of the country may experience bad weather.
We're leaving early for work.
Mom and Dad
Nii-nii!
Are you up yet?
I'm gonna leave without you.
What?  It's this late already?!
Why didn't you wake me up?!
But I did...
No way!  I don't remember that!
I really did though!
This is bad!
Nii-nii?!
Nii-nii, are you okay?!
We'll be late if we don't hurry.
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたら
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
何度も季節を重ねたね　あの日から
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
今日までどうもありがとう
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
狭い路地裏目指し
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
白い息が踊る
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
痛いくらい握った手をひいて
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
君は進んでいく
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
今すぐキスしたかった
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
隠れた自販機の裏
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
ハニかんで見つめあった
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
優しいキモチ溢れた
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたなら
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
２人は１つだよ
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
どんな小さな幸せも
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
見つけ出せる気がするよ
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
優しくなれたのは　君のおかげ
Ow...
Are you okay, Nii-nii?
I fell down the stairs when the day began...
Today's not my day.
That's because you wouldn't get up.
And that's because you didn't wake me up.
I already told you, I did!
Yo!
The couple's getting along together early in the morning, as usual.
Who are you again?
Oh, so that's how it's gonna be?
Well then, I guess I'll just keep this to myself...
No way, is that...?!
I begged my older brother and finally got my hands on this.
Ooh!  You're a true friend!
You're so easy to read, boss.
Talking about treasure books again?
Miya, this is an eternal topic for us men!
It's the ultimate form of beauty that must be pursued!
That's right.
It's the truth of the universe passed down from the mythological age!
Yeah, okay.
Geez, I wonder if Nii-nii will be okay if he stays this way.
You're a true friend!
Don't mention it!
At this rate, I don't think he'll ever get a girlfriend.
So what do you think, Ai-chan?  Sae-chan?
What do you mean by that?
Well, this morning alone...
My brother overslept, fell hard enough to leave a bump, and talked with Ume-chan about their treasure books...
Treasure books?
Ume-chan?
Oh, you know, those pervy magazines that guys like.
Oh.
As far as those magazines go, I'm
pretty sure that's normal for any guy.
S-So that's what they are...
Hey, what do you two think about my brother?
What I think?
I thought he was weird at first...
I know, right?
But after I got to know him, he
turned out to be quite interesting.
What about you, Sae-chan?
I-I think he's...
...kind and... reliable.
My brother?!
Yeah.
You really love your brother, don't you?
W-Why?
Well, I don't think you'd care this much if you didn't.
No way, I'm just worried about his future.
At this rate, he's gonna become a failure at life.
He'll graduate from college without ever getting a girlfriend, find a job...
But he'll still be talking about pervy magazines, oversleep too much, and get fired.
Then he'll spend all his time holed up in that planetarium he made in the closet.
I don't think that'll happen.
Tachibana-senpai will be just fine.
Really?
Yeah.
I wonder about that...
Tachibana Miya Arc
Little Sister
Ai-chan and Sae-chan's impressions of Nii-nii are totally different than mine.
I wonder if he's a different person at school than at home.
Yeah.  I'm gonna find out.
All right, let's do it!
Yeah!
Thank you, Tachibana-kun.
What's this?
I appreciate you helping me carry all this.
You're planning the Founder's Festival on top of your duties as Class Rep, Ayatsuji-san.
I'm happy to do such simple stuff anytime.
That'd really help.
He's pretty friendly with Ayatsuji-senpai.
Junichi!
Yo, Rihoko.
What's up?
Well, I made a sweet potato tart as a Tea Club snack.
Try some out.
So I'm your guinea pig again?
Don't be like that.
It's good, so try it out.
Fine...
How is it?
Oh?  This is pretty good!
I really like the taste!
He and Riho-chan are childhood friends, after all.
Really?  I'm glad.
Of course they'd get along well.
How's that?  You give up yet?!
If you're ready to give up, just say so!
Never!
Then how's this?!
You giving up?  Giving up?
I give up...
The winner, Tanamachi!
Heck yes!
Damn it...
He gets along well with Tanamachi-senpai too.
Get me some yakisoba bread!
I think...
Oh?  Tachibana-kun.
What's wrong?
Good afternoon, Morishima-senpai.
I'm just here to uh... recover from a battle.
Oh that's right!  Listen to this!
I saw this really moving film last night.
A movie, huh?
Yeah.
It was about a girl who took in a cute
puppy after her sick mother passed away.
There was a scene where the girl was
sleeping alongside the puppy on her bed...
It reminded me of John, a dog I used to have.
I know!  Tachibana-kun, why don't you take John's place and sleep with me?
Just kidding.
Ah, of course.
He even talks casually with the famous Morishima-senpai!
Nii-nii, you looked so stupid getting excited like that.
by Beaver
Senpai, thank you very much.
Three Kingdoms
Beaver
by Beaver
Three Kingdoms
Beaver
by Beaver
Three Kingdoms
Beaver
The beaver Kan'u was really cool.
Yeah!  Isn't he a great character?
His name totally gives off the vibe of a real man!
What?
Try not to make Miya worry too much.
Huh?
Senpai, pull yourself together.
Hey, wait!
What's that supposed to mean?
Nanasaki!
Since when did Nii-nii and Ai-chan get close enough to share manga?
Nakata-san!
Senpai!
How's your part-time job going?
Oh, just fine.  I'm keeping at it.
It's all thanks to you, Senpai.
Not at all.
It's thanks to your own hard work, Nakata-san.
Um... Senpai?
M-Miya-chan...
What about Miya-chan?
Um... well, uh...
Sae-chan looks so happy...
At any rate, I had no idea Nii-nii was friends with so many girls.
You're too naïve, Miya-chan.
Oh!  It's my childhood friend and Riho-chan's fellow 2-B classmate, Kamizaki Risa-chan!
Shh.  Thanks for the introduction,
but keep it down or they'll hear us.
Risa-chan, what are you doing?
Right back at you, Miya-chan.
Oh, he's going.  After him!
I didn't know Nii-nii is friends with so many girls.
Exactly.  That's why I'm so uneasy.
About what?
Oh, nothing...
I see.
Thank you, Risa-chan.
I was able to spy on Nii-nii thanks to your help.
Don't worry about it.
Um... I think of you as a little sister, Miya-chan.
Risa-chan...
You can call me Nee-nee, if you'd like.
You're not my real sister, so I can't call you that.
Oh, I see...
Maybe Nii-nii's more popular than I'd thought.
So why can't he land a girlfriend?
N-No way!
What are you doing, Miya?!
Don't scare me like that!
Nii-nii...
What do you want?
Oh yeah, what did you say to Nanasaki and Nakata-san?
They were both acting really weird.
Uh... is something wrong?
I'll really try.
Even if you like guys, I'll try really hard to understand!
So don't brood over it by yourself.  You can talk to me about anything.
Hold on a minute!
What did you just say?
Don't brood over it by yourself.
No, before that.
I'll really try.
No, after that... or before that?
Even if you like guys?
Yeah!  That!  That part!
Why would you think that?!
Well, you're friends with so many girls, but you still can't get a girlfriend...
So, I was thinking maybe you actually liked guys or something.
You were holding hands with Ume-chan this morning too...
You've got it all wrong!
You've held hands with your friends before, right?
Yeah, but...
There's no way I could ever like guys.
Really?
Yes!
For sure?
For sure!
I like girls!
On top of that, I love pervy stuff!
Wait... why am I saying this to my little sister?
Okay, well that's good.
Wa...
Wait a minute, Miya!  That's not good at all!
It's true that I like girls... and I also love pervy stuff...
No, wait!
Miya!  Hear me out!
Miya!
So yeah, I was so relieved to find out Nii-nii doesn't like guys.
Why would you suspect that?
But haven't you wondered, Risa-chan?
He's friends with so many girls,
but he can't seem to land a girlfriend...
You never thought that he might've liked guys?
No way.
His collection just keeps getting bigger.
What?
Oh, nothing.
Anyway, I'm so relieved.
At this rate, I'm sure Nii-nii will get a girlfriend soon.
Maybe even by Christmas!
I won't allow that!
You know, don't they say couples that form quickly break up just as fast?
That's why I think it should be someone
who's been watching him for a long time.
Since she'll know what he likes, she
can fulfill any requests he might make.
I don't really get it, but is that how it is?
Absolutely.
So just call me Nee-nee whenever you like.
You're my friend, so I can't possibly call you Nee-nee.
I see...
E-Excuse me, Tachibana-san...
Do you know him?
Yeah, but I've never talked to him...
He's from a neighboring class.
I've been interested in you for a long time, Tachibana-san.
I've always had my eyes on you.
Tachibana-san, you have a lot of fans, and I was ready to give up...
But I happened to see you today.
I thought this might be my chance.
I like you, Tachibana-san!
Please go out with me!
Kibitou City Third Park
Why did you turn him down?
He seemed pretty handsome.
Yeah...
He's not your type?
If you can't figure something out, discuss it with your Nee-nee!
Sorry, Risa-chan.
I'm going home.
I don't really get stuff like dating somebody, love, and hate...
Maybe Nii-nii feels the same way.
Welcome home.
You're pretty late today.
What've you been up to?
O-Oh, just some shopping...
I see.
Where's Mom and Dad?
They said they'll be late, as always.
Myaa?
M-Myaa!  I'll go up and get changed.
Okay.
H-Hey!
Don't go that way!
Hey, what's with all the noise?
And what's this supposed to be?
A kitty...
I can see that.
Where'd you pick it up?
Bring it back there.
I can't!  It was all alone in the park!
Don't you feel bad for it?
Of course I do.
But you know as well as I do that both
Mom and Dad don't like cats very much.
I know...
The mommy cat might be looking for its lost child right now.
Yeah...
I'll help you look, okay?
Okay.
Kibitou City Third Park
Where did you find it?
Over there...
Well, let's take a look.
What's wrong?
I took it home without thinking, so now
the mommy cat's probably really worried.
She's probably searching around frantically.
Miya...
Then let's hurry up and return it to its mom!
Right?
Yeah!
So you found it here?
Yeah...
It doesn't look like the mommy cat's here...
What should we do?
Let's split up and look.
Okay.  I'll try really hard!
Nii-nii, did you find her?
No, I didn't.
Maybe she went somewhere else...
It's snowing...
Nii-nii, this isn't good.
Since it's cold enough to snow,
the kitty'll die if we leave it out here!
The mommy cat might already be...
Calm down!
I'm sure the mommy cat's fine.
It's an adult cat, after all.
Then what about him?
I guess we don't have a choice.
Let's bring it home just for tonight.
What?
B-But if we do that...
We'll look for the mommy cat again tomorrow.
Okay?
But...
I'll try to convince Mom and Dad.
Really?
Yeah.  Leave it to me!
Thanks, Nii-nii!
Just for tonight, okay?
Oh, and you'll be in charge of taking care of it.
Of course!
Isn't that great, little kitty?
All right, let's go buy some cat food.
Okay!
Little kitty!
That cat... must be the kitty's mom.
Yeah.
Whoa, don't do that!
Your mom didn't do anything!  It was my fault!
I'm the one who took you away!  Don't bite her!
Don't worry about that, Miya.
Why?
That's just a playful bite.
Playful bite?
Kittens playfully bite their mothers and siblings a lot.
It's just having fun.
I see...
Look, the mommy cat doesn't seem to mind, right?
You're right.
It's giving her playful bites.
That's because it's so happy to see its mom.
It's an expression of love.
I see, I see.
Isn't family a wonderful thing?
Yeah.
Nii-nii, you were absolutely right.
Hmm?
The mommy cat was looking around for it everywhere.
Even in this cold.
Indeed.
I guess it's best for a family to be together.
Yeah.
Let's head home.
Okay!
Hey, Nii-nii...
Yeah?
Um...
Hmm?
Well...
What is it?
If I got lost, would you look for me?
Huh?
Like that kitty...
If I got lost, would you look for me?
Don't be silly.
Of course I would.
You're my precious little sister.
Nii-nii...
I'd find you for sure.
Right.
Thanks.
No problem.
Miya?
Nii-nii, turn back around.
Just do it!
Fine...
Now what?
Take that!
Hey!  What are you doing?!
Don't give me that!  Why are you biting me?!
I'm giving you a playful bite too!
It's an expression of love!
Hey!  That hurts!
Don't run!
Give me a break!
Miya!
Of course I would.
You're my precious little sister.
Nii-nii's a slob and pretty uncool sometimes...
He's even a little perverted to boot...
But he's still a good Nii-nii.
It's just a feeling...
But I think I understand why he's
friends with so many different girls.
I'm sure he'll find a girlfriend soon.
Nii-nii can play with me until that happens.
Sorry...
Nii-nii, you pervert!
Stupid Nii-nii!
Itsumo hidamari no you ni
いつも陽だまりのように
Like being in the sun
Atatakaku tsutsunde kureru
暖かく包んでくれる
Your warmth always wraps around me
Daisuki na basho
大好きな場所
My favorite place
Itsudemo soba ni ireba
いつでも側に居れば
As long as I'm always by your side
Yasashii kimochi ni nareru no
優しい気持ちになれるの
I'll be at peace
Hotto suru
ホッとする
I can relax
Nagareru
流れる
The drifting clouds
Kumo wa doko he mukau no
雲はどこへ向かうの？
Where are they going?
Toikakete mo
問い掛けても
Even if I ask
Tayorinai henji bakari
頼りない返事ばかり
All I get are vague replies
Ne chanto kiiteru
「ねぇ、ちゃんと聞いてる？」
Hey, are you even listening?
Neko ni kiite mo
猫に聞いても
If I ask a cat
Komatta kao shiteru
困った顔してる
It just looks confused
Hana ni kiite mo
花に聞いても
If I ask a flower
Wakaranai
分からない
It doesn't know
Hidamari wa kyou mo sotto
陽だまりは今日もそっと
I'm in the sun again today
Atatakaku tsutsunde kureru
暖かく包んでくれる
And the warmth gently wraps around me
Taisetsu na basho
大切な場所
My precious place
Miageru sora wa itsumo
見上げる空はいつも
Whenever I look up at the sky
Kawaranai egao afureru
変わらない笑顔溢れる
It greets me with its unchanging smile
Yasashiku
優しく
So tenderly
Mou sukoshi
もう少し
For a little longer
Ima wa kono mama de
今はこのままで
Just like I do now
Mimamotte ageyou
見守ってあげよう
I'll keep watching out for you
Soba de
側で
By your side
Preview
Next episode preview.
The Madonna of our school, Morishima Haruka-senpai.
When I, disappointed in love, and Senpai meet...
...will a love story begin?
Huh?!  No way!
When it begins, and why it begins...
Not knowing the answers is what makes it love.
I-Is that really what it is?
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka Arc: Chapter 1
Longing
Next episode: "Longing".
Memories of a failed love hold me back.
Will you save me?
That depends on you.