Two years ago, on Christmas Eve...
I gave up on waiting for her to show up,
and was about to go home alone.
I couldn't have imagined this
crushing loneliness on my way here.
Was I... rejected?
I don't know how I'll face her at school tomorrow.
What are you doing?
Kaoru!
What are you doing here?
Don't tell me someone stood you up?!
Y-You're wrong.
Hey, give me a ride.
I was just about to go pick up a Christmas cake.
Every year, my mom and I have a Christmas party together.
Oh?
I know!
Wanna come over to my place?
My mom and I can't finish the cake with just the two of us.
You can have the leftovers.
What?
Whatever, just give me a ride to the bakery.
You can decide whether you want to come or not on our way there.
O-Okay.
All right.  Let's go!
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator/QC/Can't Backlog: Raze
Timer: Kusion
Editor: IGChris
Typesetter: Kemeko
Backlog Ninja: Ershin
Karaoke/Workraw Patch: ar
Yes, yes!  What a reaction!
O-Oh, it's you, Kaoru.
Don't just suddenly bite my ear!
Did it feel good?
It wasn't anything special.
Here, if you like biting so much, go ahead and bite this ear too.
D-Don't actually bite it!
Didn't you tell me to?
I did, but you don't normally do that!
I can, because of the relationship we have.
In other words, because we're strangers.
Whoa, you'd really go that far?
Yep.
I see.
Then I guess this is farewell.
Yeah.
When I think back on it, it's been such a short...
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc
Chapter 1
Buddy
Such a short...
We've known each other since middle school, so three years.
That's right, three years!
The two of us met with a bang and brought our relationship to fruition...
No we didn't.
Sup, boss?  Married couple stand-up comedy again?
Obviously not!
Geez, don't be so cold.
You must be having it tough too, Tanamachi.
I'm the one who has it tough!
It's fine, Umehara-kun.
I do this because I like it.
How brave.  I could cry!
Yes, you can call me the bravest and prettiest girl in town.
Oh yeah, Umehara-kun.  Maybe you'll know about it.
I've been hearing about it at my part-time job.
Have you been to the newly-finished Port Tower?
Tanamachi, that's a painful question you're asking.
There's no way I could go to that date spot alone!
Really?
They have an aquarium and viewing platform there.
Doesn't it sound fun?
Hey, how about we all go together?
Together?  You mean, all three of us?
Yeah.
Well, it's a place I'd rather go to for a date,
but I guess I'll have to give up on that.
Yeah, I could just look at it as checking the place out.
Yep.
It's decided!
Then when should we go?
I'm not going.
What?
That place sounds boring.
What's the matter, boss?
There's only gonna be couples there anyway.
We're just gonna feel left out if we go.
You don't know that for sure unless you go!
I'm pretty sure there'll be families there.
Come on, darling.
We're not family!
Umehara-kun and Tanamachi-san, class is about to start,
so could you please take your seats?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Geez, she's so strict.
Right?
Don't say that.
Ayatsuji-san has to fulfill her role as the class rep.
Ugh, who's side are you on?!
Sorry, are you okay?
P-P-Pan...
Punch?
You dodged my right hook pretty well.
Panties...
You idiot!
Junichi, you're awake?
Huh?
Why am I in the infirmary?
You don't remember?
I don't remember anything...
Y-You fell over and hit your head and stomach.
I see.  You brought me all the way here then, Kaoru?
That's right, be thankful!
Liar!  You're the one who hit me!
Oh, so you knew.
Geez, you didn't have to hit me that hard.
I stopped right before I hit you!
But you just happened to get hit.
You can't say that you stopped then!
Ow...
A-Are you okay?
S-Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Don't tell me... you've been with me the whole time?
Yeah, pretty much.
Are you mad?
I can't get mad at you if you make that face.
It's fine.
But...
I said it's fine.
You did hit me, but... well...
I got to... see yours, Kaoru...
Anyway, that's how it is, so let's call it even.
You were worried for me, right?
Yeah, I was.
There haven't been many times when you've worried about me.
I don't really think so...
Either way, it's still rare for you to do that.
Well, I guess so.
It brought back memories.
Of what?
When we were in middle school, we
skipped class in the infirmary just like this.
Do you remember?
No.
I wasn't the one skipping class back then, and I'm not now.
Don't worry about little details like that!
Kaoru, you haven't changed at all.
You've been unpredictable since middle school.
You even earned yourself the nickname "Warhead of Kibitou".
Don't call me that.
Sorry.
Well, I'm going.
Okay.
Want me to close the curtains?
Yeah.
Well then, take care!
Wait, I don't want you telling me that!
I forgot to tell you something important.
What?
Come to the flower beds at the
back of the campus after school.
You have to come.
What was that all about?
Why would she go out of her way to tell me to go to a deserted place after school?
Kaoru's gonna confess to me?!
No, no way.
Which means...
Sucks for you that I'm the "Warhead of Kibitou"!
No, she wouldn't need me to go to the back of the campus for that.
Which means...
Junichi!
K-Kaoru!
You came!
I love you!
Junichi...
No way!
She's been a buddy of mine since middle school!
For that to happen now...
No, no, no!
But she was really worried for me just then...
Could it be...
What's this?
Welcome home, dear.
Will you have dinner?
Will you take a bath?
Or will you...
Hey, could you keep it down?
Someone's asleep.
This is an infirmary, you know.
O-Okay.
I-I'm sorry!
Inou Tadataka became known for his very
accurate map of Japan during the Edo period.
Does anyone know how he made it?
Rihoko!
Ah, Junichi!
Here.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
Me too.  I wasn't paying attention.
Huh?
Junichi, your face is all red.
What?  Uh... really?
Do you have a fever?
No, I'm fine.
Hmm... you don't.
By the way, what are you doing out here?
Um... some graduated members of the
Tea Club are coming today, so my seniors...
What's wrong?
Oh no!  I forgot what I came here to do!
What?!
This is bad!
Don't trip, Rihoko!
Okay!
I wonder if she'll be okay.
Wait, I gotta worry about myself first.
O-Once I go around that corner...
Go around that corner...
Junichi.
I actually like...
Ah, Tachibana-kun.
Junichi?
What's the matter?
Why is Tanaka-san here?
Hey, are you listening?
You're supposed to hear what Keiko has to say and give your opinion.
I'm saying I chose you to represent all the boys in this school.
Well, I don't know about that...
I'm sorry, Tachibana-kun.
There's nothing to apologize to this moron about.
Moron, huh?
First you say I represent the boys in this school, then you call me a moron.
Which one am I?
It's true.  You also have it tough, Tachibana-kun.
You too, Tanaka-san.
I'm used to it.
What's with this mutual understanding between you two?!
Keiko, hurry up and hit the main subject!
Um...
Well, I confessed to a guy in our class.
So that's what you wanted to talk about.
Whatever, just hear her out.
Okay.
He then told me to wait for his answer,
so I waited for a while...
For how long?
Probably around a month.
For a month?!
Yes.
How should I put it...
There aren't many girls like you, Keiko.
A typical person wouldn't wait that long.
Though, when he finally asked for her, that happened.
What happened?
Yes, what do you think he said to Keiko?
I have no idea.
He said, "let me kiss you".
Even if you're making fun of someone, you shouldn't go that far!
A kiss?!
He doesn't give her an answer and
leaves her alone, then he asks for a kiss ?!
S-So Tanaka-san, what did you do?
Did you kiss him?
No, I didn't.
I turned him down then, but if he asks me again...
And so we're just thinking about what to do.
I see.
I'm sorry for asking you for weird advice.
No, I don't mind...
Well then, as the representative of the boys in this school,
hurry up and give us your opinion.
I don't know about my opinion...
Well, I predict that he'll end up making Keiko cry.
What?!
Hey now, you didn't have to be so blunt.
My prediction doesn't matter!
So let's hear what you think!
Let's see.
Why don't you write him a letter?
A letter?
That's pretty lame.
Isn't there an easier way to solve this?
If there's an easier way, you
wouldn't need me in the first place.
Yeah, you're right.
But what are we gonna write in the letter?
Something along the lines of,
"I'm still waiting for a proper reply"?
Since you already confessed to him before,
I think you should take a more indirect approach instead of being persistent.
He might ask you to kiss him again if you meet him directly, and we don't want that.
You have a point.
Keiko, well?
Okay, let's try that.
Tachibana-kun, thanks.
You're welcome.
Hey, Kaoru.
Who's that guy Tanaka-san was talking about?
Well, it's not something I can just tell anyone about.
I guess not.
I hope things work out for Tanaka-san.
I intend to do what it takes for that to happen too.
Don't overdo things.
Don't worry.
I'll make it all so perfect, it won't get any better.
No.  Every time you say "perfect", it's always something destructive.
Really?
What do you mean, "really"?
Crap, I have work today!
You're still working at that family restaurant by the train station?
Yup.  We're doing a Winter Flavors fair right now.
Winter Flavors fair?
That's right.  We're putting gratin in crab shells and stuff.
Ooh, that sounds delicious.
It wobbles and it's slippery.  Carrying it around is tough!
Like the "Crab From The North Gratin",
or the "Full Enogi Mushroom Japanese-style Pasta".
They have names with really lame puns.
They're pretty lame, yeah.
"Understood!  You want a 'Crab From The North Gratin', is that right?"
Repeating the order is embarrassing!
Yeah, I guess that is kinda weird.
Should I look for another part-time job?
Have you tried looking for a job that isn't in a family restaurant?
Yeah, lots of them.
An assistant at an attraction in a theme park, for example.
That sounds kinda fun.
I know, right?
But the competition seems fierce...
Don't worry, you'd make it for sure.
Really?
Thank you.
Sign: For pedestrians and bikes
Hey.
What's fun about a job?
You get money.
Just kidding!
Though, that's half-true.
I mean, it's just me and my mom at home.
That's why my mom and I
promised each other we'd work hard.
I see.
What a shame Ai-chan couldn't come.
Nothing we could do about it.  She has club activities.
I wonder what I'll eat today?
Maybe I'll have ice cream with it!
Really?  It's so cold though.
Miya-chan, what's wrong?
My brother's right there.
Huh?
So he's your brother, Miya-chan...
Let's go!
But your brother... are you sure?
Yep.
We see each other at home all the time anyway.
I-I see.
All right, I think I'll have salmon and wieners with it!
For pedestrians
and bikes
Well, I might be in it for the money,
but the work itself is pretty fun.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
It makes me happy when customers show me their appreciation.
I see.
You should probably give it a try too.
You, with an apron over your uniform... it'll probably look good on you!
Why would I be in an apron?
Anyway, you should come as a customer first.
I'll come when I feel like it.
I'll give you some freebies...
...not!
You won't?!
Well, I'm headed this way.
Hey, Kaoru.
When you told me to come to the flower beds today,
I thought you were gonna confess to me.
But there's no way that would happen.
Even if I'm getting the wrong idea, I shouldn't go too far.
Maybe your punch made me a little crazy, Kaoru.
In that case, it's partly your fault too.
Kaoru?
There's no way that'd happen!
Are you stupid?!
Ow...
Geez, I have to get to my job...
I'll be late, late!
Come on, I said I got the wrong idea.
You didn't have to hit me.
Uniform, huh?
Sign: Café Restaurant Totosu
No, no.  There's no way!
All right, time to work hard!
Yo.  I decided to come right away.
Welcome.
Didn't I already say you won't be getting any freebies?
What would you like?
I'll leave it to you.  Something cheap.
Let's see, the cheapest item.
How about coffee?  Refills are free.
Yeah, I don't think I can pay for anything pricier.
You're a coward.
You should just go all out and order a steak or something.
How about the "Crab From The North Gratin" from our Winter Flavors fair menu?
You mean that hard to carry item?
I see.
Wait, where do you think you're looking?!
W-Well, I'm not...
You pervert.
No, I definitely wasn't looking in a perverted way...
Is that all for you today?
Yes, thank you.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I'd like some more coffee, please.
Understood.
Here you go.
I'm sorry!
Please enjoy.
What... what's happening?
Don't tell me I...
I... like...
This morning too, when I punched him...
Ayatsuji-san has to live up to her role as the class rep.
It's because he said it like he was protecting Ayatsuji-san.
Also...
I thought you were gonna confess to me, Kaoru.
My heart won't stop thumping because he said that...
No way!
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
What happened to Kaoru?
I was hoping to tease her one more time before heading back.
Naze naze
Why, oh why?
My Heart kurushii no
Why does my heart ache like this?
Daijoubu nante ne
I tell you that everything's fine
Sokkenai furi shitari
And behave coldly
Namaiki mo urahara
I act outrageous and disagreeable
Saidaigen no tsuyogari
It's the ultimate bluff
Doushite kana namida dechau
Why am I starting to cry?
Aitsu no kao matomo ni mirenai
I can't even look squarely at his face
Ashita wa kitto kinou yori
Tomorrow for sure, even more than yesterday
Tomodachi ijou no kankei ni naritai
I want us to become more than just friends
Ashita wa kitto yume mo kitto
Tomorrow for sure, and in my dreams for sure
Koi suru kimochi kirameku
These feelings of love will shine brilliantly
Just A Friend
Such A Friend
Still A Friend
Naze naze
Why, oh why?
I Can't Tell You My Heart
Why can't I tell you what's in my heart?
Preview
Next episode preview.
Oh?  What are you staring at with that huge grin on your face?
Morishima-senpai?!
Hey, hey.  What were you looking at?
I guess you could say I was captivated by the pristine sight of a devoted girl working hard at her part-time job.
Or you could say that I looked without thinking...
I just couldn't help it, being a guy...
Aha, so you were captivated by her thighs!
Next episode: "Hesitation".
Next Episode
Hesitation
Where, where?
Where's the girl with such sexy thighs?
Uh... Senpai?