Christmas Eve, two years ago.
I was walking home alone in the snow after I was stood up for my date.
My emotions were almost unbearable.
I finally managed to buy the toy Ikuo wanted!
Sorry!  I was in a hurry.
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry for spacing out too.
Did I hit you?  Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
My little brother's Christmas present is also safe!
Okay, excuse me!
That girl will probably have a nice Christmas Eve with her family.
When I thought that, I wanted to share in some of that happiness.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Editor: IGChris
Typesetter: Kemeko
Stuff: ar
What should we do today?
Go to an arcade or something?
I'm a little short on pocket money right now...
Please excuse me.
Ayatsuji-san.
Hello.
Are you doing committee work?
Yeah, for the Founder's Festival planning committee.
It must be tough for you since you're also the class rep.
Thanks for your concern.
But I willingly volunteered to be in the planning committee,
and I'll only be busy for the short time between now and the festival.
It's about a month until the Christmas Founder's Festival, huh?
That's right.
All right you two, take care getting home.
Don't go loitering anywhere on your way.
All right, Class Rep.
See you.
See you tomorrow.
It'd be nice if someone could help her with her committee work.
Then why don't you help her?
Nah, I can't.
I've gotta help with the sushi restaurant at home.
And what about you?
Hmm... good question.
Well, I suppose you're busy with your own things too.
Let's go.
Okay.
Whoa, it's so cold!
Winter has definitely arrived.
It's the season for cold amberjack.
Then flounder and tilefish.
Fish taste best in-season, after all!
Nanasaki Ai Arc
Chapter 1
Worst
You really are the son of a sushi chef.
Umehara...
What's up, boss?
T-Toilet.  I've gotta go.
Maybe it's all this wind, but suddenly I can't hold it anymore.
Whoa, hang on.
Hey, this way.
There should be a toilet in the park here.
Yeah.
What are you looking at?
N-Nothing...
Well...
Hey, what now?
That was quite a jump!
I've never seen anyone jump so high.
Um... you're from the same school as us, right?
I don't think I'd be wearing this
uniform if I was from another school.
I... guess you have a point.
Um...
I'm Tachibana Junichi from class 2-A.
And this is my friend from the same class, Umehara Masayoshi.
Nice to meet you!
How rare for perverts to introduce themselves.
This'll make it much easier to file a report.
Hey now, you've gotta be kidding!
Yeah!  We're not perverts or anything.  I was just looking for the bathroom!
Well, I hope the police take your word for that.
P-Police?
W-Wait a minute.
You're mistaken!  Listen to what we have to say!
Why are you panicking?
I was joking.
Oh.
That didn't sound like a joke to me.
Hey!
What is it?
You're... not gonna actually report us, right?
Hey.
What?
Do you still need the bathroom?
It must've drawn back in...
"Myaa"?
No!  Not "myaa".  "Nyaa"!
"Myaa"?  "Nyaa"?  "Myaa"?
It's "nyaaa"!
I see.  "Nyaa", right?  "Nyaa".
Okay, so what about this "nyaa"?
Well, a black cat has been hanging around school lately.
It's gotten pretty popular among cat-loving freshman girls.
Girls sure latch onto random stuff...
I haven't seen it yet, but I hear it has really pretty fur that's silky smooth to the touch!
Silky smooth, you know!
Ah, I wanna touch it too!
Now wasn't that a cute yell, Junichi?
Kaoru...
What do you think you're doing?!
Tanamachi-senpai, good morning.
Good morning!
Listen, you...
What's wrong?  It was just a little morning "hello".
Don't tell me you liked it...
I think you'll understand what it's like to have your butt groped if you experience it yourself...
Whoa, a pervert!
Hey, wait a sec!
He's trying to grope my butt!
Wait, Onii-chan.
This is embarrassing, so cut it out.
Yeah, but...
You're a high school junior already, but you're still too impulsive.
Dad thinks so too.
Nanasaki, morning.
Good morning.
Let's go.
Okay.
Hey Nii-nii, are you listening?
Sorry, what?
As I was saying,
I think meat buns make the greatest dinner of all time.
Where did that come from?
The delicious taste of seafood and the spice of curry.
Should I go for the miraculous blend of flavors that is the Seafood Curry?
Or perhaps...
Crispy batter and juicy pork.
Maybe I'll go with the large-portioned Tonkatsu Special.
The Seafood Curry or the Tonkatsu Special?
That is the question.
What are you doing?
That is a difficult question!
Please hurry up.
Hey, you're the girl... from yesterday...
It's your turn already.
You're holding up the line, so hurry up.
Uh... um...
What would you like?
Seafood Curry or the Tonkatsu Special.
Have you decided which one you want?
How did you know what I was agonizing over?!
You were agonizing out loud.
Was I?
That kind of indecisiveness is quite disgraceful.
Lunch Set B, easy on the rice please.
Okay!
What's wrong with thinking about what to get?
It's not like it'll cause trouble for anyone.
It causes trouble for everyone in line behind you.
Sorry guys.
Okay!  Lunch Set B, easy on the rice.
Thank you very much.
So what will you have?
Uh... let's see...
So why ramen?
Faced with an impossible choice, I decided I'd pick neither.
So you chickened out.
Why am I always so tired after eating?
I totally know what you mean!
That must be the black cat Miya was talking about.
I don't have much time today, so I
probably won't get much swimming done.
Nanasaki?
Tsukahara-senpai?  What is it?
I forgot something in the clubroom.
You're quite dedicated to be practicing during lunch.
The tournament's coming up, so I want to practice as much as I can.
I see.  Do your best.
All right, see you later.
Yes, thank you.
All right...
Pooh?
That's weird.  I thought it came this way.
Hey black kitty, where'd you go?
What are you doing?
You again?
Again?
You did that yesterday, and now this?
Are you doing this on purpose?
Of course not!
And you seemed to be acting the pervert this morning too.
She did that to me!
Really?
So now you're gonna peek up skirts from under the staircase?
N-No!  I was looking for a black cat.
Cat?
That!  That cat!
Oh, you mean Pooh?
Pooh?
That cat's name is Pooh?
Yeah.  At least, that's what I call him.
Wow, I see.
Pooh, nice one.
You really want to see it that badly?
You want to see what's under my skirt, don't you?
W-Well, if you ask me, I... uh...
Okay, I'll let you see.
Whoa, I'm not looking!
I'm not looking, okay?!
I don't mind if you have a look.
I won't think anything of it.
Can I really look?
B-But there's no way that's...
No no, they say a man has to eat what's put in front of him.
I-It was a swimsuit?!
You finally realized?
W-What the heck?  Don't surprise me like that.
Sorry.
But... why a swimsuit?
I'm in the swimming club.
Swimming club?
A minute ago, I was all set to practice in the indoor pool when I heard Pooh.
So that's why you wore your uniform over your swimsuit.
I see...
Wait, then...
Yes.
What you saw yesterday at the park was my swimsuit.
Our advisor forgot the key, and I couldn't get into the pool.
So I was just killing some time at the park.
And that's when we showed up.
Pity it was just a swimsuit, right?
I-It's not really a pity...
You're a pretty simple guy, Senpai.
You were pretty cute when you were looking at my skirt like you wanted to bury your face in it.
However...
I won't allow any actual groping though, Tachibana-senpai.
Wh- How do you know my name?
You told me yesterday.
Oh yeah...
I'm Nanasaki Ai from class 1-A.
Nanasaki, huh?  Nanasaki...
Wait, 1-A is...
Yes.  Same class as Miya-chan.
Huh?  Did I tell you Miya's my sister?
No, but you've got the same surname.
And I saw you walking together this morning, so I kinda figured it out.
You should stop being a pervert, okay?
I don't want the brother of my classmate to be a criminal.
L-Like I've been saying, that's...
You should hurry up too, Senpai.
Ah, N-Nanasaki!
She's gonna go to class wearing her swimsuit under her uniform?
Come in.
Hey, Nii-nii...
Hmm?
Did you do something weird to Ai-chan?
Ai-chan?
Ah, you're talking about Nanasaki.
I don't think I did anything to her.
Ai-chan suddenly asked me what kind of guy you are today.
Are you sure you didn't do anything?
I didn't.
Then why did she ask me about that?
Beats me.
You really didn't do anything?!
I didn't.
Geez...
Anyway, don't do anything weird to Ai-chan.
She's an important friend of mine.
Oh yeah Nii-nii, did you hear about this?
Tada!
A lucky draw at the shopping district!
Shopper's District Appreciation Festival
Look, the grand prize is a trip to Hawaii!
Wow, that's cool.
Nii-nii, don't you buy manga and
video games at the shopping district?
Go get some lucky draw coupons and give it a try!
For the sake of your cute sister!
Yep, you're cute.
You're cute, Miya.
Really?
You're even cuter when you keep your mouth shut though.
Nii-nii, you moron!
I won't forgive you if you don't win a trip to Hawaii!
Nanasaki, I'll see you after school.
Ah, yes!
Ai-chan, bye-bye!
I'm sorry...
Win a trip to Hawaii!
Is it gone now?
Yes, it's gone.
I had no idea that was on my forehead.
So that's why they were laughing at me.
I don't think being laughed at by Tsukahara-senpai and Morishima-senpai is something to be so upset about.
Thanks for the towel.
I'll return it to you after I wash it.
You don't have to.
I laughed at you without thinking, so I lent it to you as an apology.
Please don't worry about it.
Really?
Yes.
Then... thanks.
But why would anyone write that on your forehead?
I think... no, I'm pretty darn sure Miya did it.
Miya-chan did?
She said something last night about the grand prize in the shopping district lucky draw being a trip to Hawaii.
But she didn't have to scribble that on my forehead.
There's no way I would've known unless I looked in a mirror.
Senpai, you don't wash your face in the morning?
Huh?
I was almost late this morning, so...
Um, Senpai...
Are you free today?
Oh?
Where did you come from?
What's your name?
Hey, what are you doing here?
Senpai.
Look, it's a cat, a cat!
Stop wasting your time and carry this to the club room.
Okay.
See you, kitty!
What was it thinking?
"I want to snuggle inside a kotatsu."
I see.
It has gotten pretty cold out.
Handcraft supplies?
Yeah.
There's some cloth I want to buy.
I was thinking of making some new western clothes...
Sae-chan, you can make western clothes?  Wow!
Show me the clothes you've made sometime!
I-It's embarrassing...
They're embarrassing clothes?
T-That's not it...
I was wondering what you needed me for...
To carry your stuff, huh?
It's thanks to you that I was able to buy all these special limited items.
I'm glad to be of service.
Do you do all the shopping, Nanasaki?
Both my parents work, so I do all the stuff at home.
I actually like doing housework quite a bit.
I see.
Yes.
Senpai, here.
Lucky Draw Coupon! !
These are the lucky draw coupons I just got,
and some leftover support coupons.
Are you sure?
As thanks for today, and also for Miya-chan's sake.
Congratulations!
Lottery Area
You won the 6th prize, a 500 yen gift voucher!
You did it, Senpai.
Congratulations.
Thanks, Nanasaki.
Though all I managed to get in the end was the smallest 6th place prize.
Here.
You can have these gift vouchers, Nanasaki.
I won these using the lucky draw coupons you gave me, after all.
But...
It's fine.
I can't go to Hawaii with just 500 yen.
I'll just tell Miya that I didn't win anything.
Then... why don't we use them?
I won these using the lucky draw coupons you gave me,
so you could say we both have a right to them.
That sounds good.  I agree.
What should we buy with it?
Let's see...
Oobanyaki
TL Note: Oobanyaki is like a Japanese pancake; traditionally filled with sweet bean paste, but other fillings are available.
Nanasaki, does it actually taste good with cream?
It's the first time I bought one with cream in it.
I normally play it safe and go for the bean paste ones...
But I figured I might as well try a
flavor I've never had before today.
Ah, I see.
Here.
If fhin, e'll fust pheow if afey mafelf-
I have no idea what you just said.
Just give me the trash.
Hey.
I could just throw it away in that bin over there.
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Our swim club provided the trash bins
at the beach as part of our volunteer work.
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Keep
our
beaches
clean!
Also, you should take your own trash home with you, Senpai.
Nanasaki, do you pick up trash as part of your volunteer work?
Yes, of course.
I see.
Sign: Please take your trash home with you!
You're amazing, Nanasaki.
Why that, out of the blue?
You're in a club, you do volunteer work...
You also do all the housework.
As for me, I have no good points.
That's not true at all.
Your perverted eyes are pretty cute
when you look at swimsuit-clad girls.
Is that a good thing?
Ah, trash!
Who threw this away, geez...
What a pain, seriously...
Senpai.
The cream Oobanyaki was really tasty!
I'll try it sometime too!
Wait, you piece of trash!
Damn it!
Yurayura yureteru Surface Of The Pool
The surface of the pool shakes and sways
Takaku tobikomu kakikomu
I dive in and it carries me under
Watashi tsutsunde
It envelops me
Kokoro no okusoko he michiteku
And fills the depths of my heart
Nani shiteru n desu ka
What are you doing?
Nani wo mite iru n desu ka
What are you looking at?
Toikaketeru n desu
I'm asking you a question
Poker Face
Childlike
Mitai kawaii awai kitai
I want to see it, it's cute, it's faint, the expectation
Tanoshii desu
It's all fun
Majime sugata fui ni miserare
When I unexpectedly saw your serious side
Mune no oku ga tsukiugoite
Something stirred deep within my chest
Kokoro yurayura yureteru Feel Comfortable
The swaying and shaking of my heart feels comfortable
Takaku habataku koeteku
I want to flap my wings and fly over
Ashita aeru
So I can see you tomorrow
Utakata uiteru koi moyou
Patterns of love bubble on the water surface
Konna kanjou nan da to omoimasu ka
What do you think these feelings are?
Tawai mo naku soba de
I want to be by your side
Waraiaitai desu
And laugh with you without a care in the world
Watashi no kimochi na n desu
These are my feelings
To You Innocent
Preview
Next episode preview.
Tachibana-kun, what are you eating?
T-Tsukahara-senpai?!
I'm having some Oobanyaki, would you like one?
Oh, thanks...
Did you actually think I'd want one?!
S-Sorry.
By the way, it looks like you're making moves on Nanasaki in my club.
You know what you're getting into, right?
W-What do you mean?
You're in trouble if you're just playing with her.
Next episode: "Heartbeat".
Next Episode
Heartbeat
I do wonder who your heart beats for, though.
For you, Tsukahara-senpai... maybe?