Teacher's Lounge
About the Founder's Festival...
It looks like things are running behind schedule.
Will you be okay?
We'll be fine.
It's true that things are running a little slow, but we can still make up for the lost time.
I see.
Listen, Ayatsuji-san...
Didn't you collapse the other day?
Yes, but...
We discussed the issue in the last staff meeting.
It was suggested that we could do a little less for this year's Founder's Festival.
For example, we could forego lighting the
Christmas tree or reduce the number of events.
We'll be fine!
A-Ayatsuji-san...
Everyone in the committee is trying their absolute best to help.
Could you wait a little longer and see what happens?
Please.
All right.  However...
Don't overwork yourself.
Got that?
Okay.  I understand.
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Typesetter: fnord
Stuff: ar
Founder's Festival Planning
Committee Headquarters
Damn it.
That was humiliating.  Really humiliating.
I can't believe I was called in and coached like that...
So what did she say to you?
I wouldn't have to suffer like this if
everyone else had their act together.
Sorry.
I'm not saying it's your fault.
She said that we're behind schedule.
She also suggested that we forget about lighting the Christmas tree this year.
There's no way I'd accept that.
Ayatsuji Tsukasa Arc
Chapter 3
Pride
Yeah, you're right.
Everyone's also looking forward to it.
I'll do everything I can to help!
Thanks.
But still...
Is there something else?
It's true that we don't have enough time.
Hey you, can you think of-
Excuse me, Tachibana-senpai.
Huh?  Me?
I was looking for the main stage lights, but I can't seem to find them.
Ah, they should be in the supply room.
But they might be a little heavy.
Tachibana-kun.
I'll be fine by myself here, so go help them out.
You sure?
Yeah.
Here's the key.
Thanks.
Okay, I'll be back.
See you.
So I had too many meat buns yesterday...
I thought about what to do with the lack of time all night yesterday.
But I couldn't come up with any good ideas...
Hey, any suggestions?
What's with that stupid look on your face?
I mean, I didn't expect you to make lunch for me...
I'm so happy.
Mmm, delicious!  It's incredible!
You reward your dogs when they perform tricks.
I'm just rewarding you in advance.
So I'm a dog now?
More importantly, I need ideas.
Any suggestions?
Hmm, let's see.
I think it'd be best to have more people help out.
No way.
Why not?
Because it's pathetic!
Am I supposed to say, "we just realized we need more people, so please help us"?
My pride won't allow that.
But we won't make it on time at this rate.
I see why you'd want to keep the work to committee members...
But we were told not to overwork ourselves.
I think it's best if we play it safe.
Besides, even if we pull in a whole crowd of people to help,
I'm sure that it'll still improve your standing as long as the festival is successful.
Your ability to lead, that is.
Ability to lead...
Yeah.  Well?
Fine.  Not like I have a choice anyway.
Great.
So let's start with asking our class to help.
Yeah.
But before that...
Before that?
Since I also did consider getting more people...
I'll take this.
I was saving the fried chicken for last!
I already ate it, so you're not getting it back~
No fair...
Hey, look.
Hmm?
Ayatsuji-san and Tachibana-kun?
Yeah.
Hmm...
Ugh, I've had enough.
Yeah, right?  Why do we have to do this anyway?
Those two were the ones who volunteered to be in the committee, not us!
Why did they have to cause trouble for us?
I'm sure they're too busy flirting with each other.
We saw them do it.
Ayatsuji-san and Tachibana-kun looked real close having lunch together.
Yeah.
Sorry, we're late because of the meeting.
Huh?
What's the matter, guys?
Is there a problem?
I heard that we aren't doing a
Christmas tree this year.  Is that true?
You made all these plans for an even grander Festival than last year's.
But now you're making everyone help because things aren't going well?  What gives?
So you'll take all the credit as committee president if things go smoothly?
Aren't you having it a little too good?
I wasn't planning anything like that...
Aren't we behind schedule because
somebody was flirting around with a guy?
I know all about it.
You two are always alone together when you work.
Just like a couple.
T-That's...
Tachibana-kun has been assisting me with my work, so we may have given off the wrong impression.
But we haven't done anything except work.
I don't believe that.
Yeah.
Hey!
Really, you girls...
You shut up, Tanamachi-san.
You're mistaken.
Ayatsuji-san was just helping me out because I'm inexperienced...
I wasn't asking you either!
Ow...
Well, Ayatsuji-san?
Say something.
Uh oh, did we make her cry?
Ayatsuji-san?
Ahh, this is stupid.
What does any of this have to do with the Founder's Festival?
What's the matter?  You jealous?
I'll tell you something.
The Christmas Tree isn't going anywhere.
The schedule is on track to go just as smoothly as last year.
And the purpose of having all of you help is to assure that.
I can show you all the data if you don't believe me.
So people like you who spread baseless rumors and do nothing but complain really exist!
You look down on others to feel superior even though you can't do anything on your own.  How pathetic!
Go ahead if you want to respond.
But what can any of you do?
What have you accomplished?
Do you really think there's anything about you that's better than me?
If you know the meaning of the word "shame"...
Come back after you've taken a good look at your own lives.
Now, be my guest if you have anything to say.
Nothing?
Then you shouldn't have opened your mouth in the first place.
You should get some work done instead.
That's all the lot of you are capable of anyway.
Ayatsuji-san...
I think you might've gone a little too far there...
Ayatsuji-san?
Hey, do you remember this?
Yeah, I do.
Good.
Ayatsuji-san, what are you doing?!
It's fine.
I don't need this anymore.
I've realized that I now have something more important.
Will you listen?
Yeah.
I want you to become mine.
Huh?!
Huh?  Did I skip a few steps?
A few?  You skipped a lot!
What do you mean, become yours?
I-I have fun and am happy when I'm with you.
Well... to the point where I can barely understand it.
I want to be with you forever if I can.
It's enough for me if you'll stay by my side.
But I can't force you to.
That's why I'll give myself to you.
In exchange, give me days filled with you!
Are you sure you want someone like me?
I won't say it again.
Give me a clear answer.
I'm pretty anxious right now, so...
Okay.
If you'll have me...
I'm gladly yours.
I see.
This will serve as proof of the agreement.
Whenever you're ready.
O-Okay.
Now the agreement has been made.
Yeah.
I was... a little nervous.
Me too.
All right, let's clean up the ashes and head home.
Okay.
Ayatsuji-san!
What?
Uh... your nose.
My nose?
Ayatsuji-san, looks like even you get excited sometimes.
Ouch!
It still stings...
Morning.
Ayatsuji-san, morning.
Did you put together the data we'll be using for today's committee meeting?
Y-Yeah.  I did.
Thanks.
"Something came up, so just run ten rounds for now."
I don't know what happened, Sensei, but aren't you slacking a little too much?
Huh?
So you finally noticed.
Is Ayatsuji-san's team losing?
She's the only one left in the court.
No, it seems like she was on her own to begin with.
Huh?
That's exactly what's happening.
I'll go on ahead.
I've gotta finish my ten rounds quickly!
Yeah, go for it!
Hey, Kanae-chan.
Look.
It looks like there's trouble in the game next to ours.
Come on now, what's the matter?
You tired already?
Looks like you won't be giving up anytime soon.
All right Tanamachi-san, go for it.
I'll pass.
Huh?
Well, being in this team is boring.
So I'll be joining this team.
Wait, Tanamachi-san!
I don't really need a teammate.
Don't say that.
Let me have some fun at least.
Hey, Keiko!
Come over to this side too!
O-Okay...
Now we have three people.
No, four people!
Tachibana-kun!
Is that okay, Ayatsuji-san?
Wait, why are you barging into the girls' dodgeball game?!
I've already finished running the assigned ten laps.
I was feeling a little bored, so I was wondering if I could join in.
You seem really out of breath though.
You're so cool!
You're really cool, Junichi!
Thank you.
Hey, Tachibana!
You're way too fast!
Hey, what should we do?
If that's how you guys want it, then play by yourselves all you want!
Huh?  That's it?
That's lame.
So we've at least ordered everything we need.
Yeah.
We just have to wait for their delivery now.
So that's another job taken care of.
Yeah.
Sorry we took so long... huh?
Where's everyone?
They all went home.
They said they had stuff to do...
I see.
Well, that's fine.
It's better to have a small but skilled team anyway.
Let's do the work ourselves!
That's right!
I'll handle all the work those home-goers were supposed to do!
Talking big again?
I get stuff done when I actually try.
Don't fall in love.
Okay okay, that's enough talk.
Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
Let's begin.
Yeah.
Okay!
Ahh, I'm so tired!
I don't think I've stayed behind at school this late before.
Hey, you guys wanna go somewhere?
Huh?
You serious?
I'm totally exhausted!
Exactly, we should be going home!
Ayatsuji-san?
What's the matter?
Looks like I left something in the classroom.
I'm gonna go get it.
Want me to come with you?
No, it's fine, so head home first.
Okay.
I'm fine.
I'm doing okay.
I can still do it.
But...
Ayatsuji-san.
So you really are working by yourself again.
Tachibana-kun.
I would've helped if you had just asked.
Ayatsuji-san?
Thanks.  I'm fine now.
You're fine?
You know...
Don't you think we should ask for everyone's help again?
Huh?
Are you being serious?
Well, we won't make it at this rate.
Umehara-kun and the others are helping already.
But I'm sure you know their help alone isn't enough!
I'll work all night... I'll do anything if it comes down to it!
And what if you collapse again?!
Anyway, I won't ask for help.
Why not?!
That's not like you!
That's not like me?
That's right!
Ayatsuji-san, aren't you someone who
confidently handles situations like this?!
Actually, you'd take care of it before it even-
What do you mean, not like me?!
You think you know anything about me?!
Hey, I'm asking you what you think you know!
But I do know.
I know that you're giving it your all for the Founder's Festival, Ayatsuji-san.
That's why you should apologize to
everyone and ask for their help again.
If you don't want to, we could try to scrap some of the events...
Ow... huh?
Why?
Why do you say things like that even though you know?
Wouldn't it look better if you used these here instead?
Nobody can see what's on top of the tree anyway,
so why not hang just the lights and the tinsel there?
This way, decorating the tree will be a breeze!
You can then hang the dolls on the lower part, which I'm sure the kids will love!
Yeah, you're right!
Thank you!
I'm so glad I discussed this with you!
What's going on?
Good morning!
Ah, Kaoru.
What's that about?
Oh, that?
I didn't actually see it happen, but...
I'm sorry!
Why the apology?
What do you want?
I went a little too far the other day...
I'm really sorry!
And... well...
If you'll forgive me, I'd really like your help with the Founder's Festival...
Huh?!
What the heck are you talking about?!
Even after you said all that?!
We won't forgive you with just an apology!
I'm... really sorry...
But...
I really want this Founder's Festival to be successful...
I was hoping everyone would have fun preparing for it...
And so...
What's that?
Did they make her cry?
Ayatsuji-san may have gone too far, but as for them...
Yeah, during PE, right?
She already apologized, so why not just forgive her?
Yeah, okay, I get it!
We went too far as well.
We'll help you prepare for the Founder's Festival.
Look up, okay?
Really?
Yeah, really.
I promise.
Thank you!
And that's what happened.
That's gotta be a lie!
It sounds like one, but that's apparently what happened.
Morning, Tachibana-kun.
Morning.
Listen to this!
Everyone said they'll help prepare for the Founder's Festival!
I see.
Yeah, everyone's so kind!
I'm so glad I'm in this class!
So what did you call me out here for?
Don't tell me...
You want to kiss again?
That's not it!
Though that does sound pretty attractive.
Anyway, what on Earth happened?!
Huh?  What?
Weren't you really against asking the rest of the class for help yesterday?
Didn't you slap me for suggesting that?
What are you talking about?
You're asking me?
Ah, could you be talking about that girl?
That girl?
That stubborn girl who was ready to do anything to prepare for the Founder's Festival alone.
But that girl you once knew doesn't exist anymore.
And thanks to that, everyone's giving us their help.
This way, the Founder's Festival will surely be a huge success!
What on Earth happened to her?!
Hodou wo kazaru aoi Illumination
The blue illumination adorns the sidewalk
Nigiwau hitogomi ni hitori tatazumu
And I stand alone in the swarming crowd
Koboresou na egao
Smiles peeking through
Yorisou koibitotachi
Lovers snuggling against each other
Ima no watashi ni wa subete ga
Everything to me now is so bright
Mabushikute mirenai no
That I cannot bear to look
Dareka ni aisareru deshou ka
Will anyone love me?
Tsuyogari no oku ni kakureta
I'm hiding underneath a facade
Watashi ni kizuite yo
Please realize that
Hontou ni jiyuu ni nareru deshou ka
Can I really become free?
Douka oshiete
Please tell me
Fuyu no machi ni mayoikonda
Having lost her way in the winter town
The lonely angel sighs
Samishige na tenshi ga nageku
Yasashiku
Gently
Preview
Next episode preview.
Tachibana-kun, just a little more to go until the Founder's Festival!
Yeah, you're right.
I also made up with everyone in the class,
so I'm sure the preparations for the Founder's Festival will go well!
Yeah.
Let's have a wonderful Founder's Festival.
Christmas Eve is approaching once again...
Next episode: "Promise".
Next Episode
Promise
Where did the Ayatsuji-san I fell in love with go?
I am me.
I am... me.