A... Ayatsuji-san?
Don't talk without permission.
S-Sorry...
H... Her chest...
Tachibana-kun, you read it.
I see...
I apologize if I offended you.
So just let me go!
S-Sorry!
Could you come with me for a bit?
But...
Could you... come with me?
Y... Yes.
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: commander`A
Typesetter: fnord
Stuff: ar
All right, we should be able to have a nice long chat here.
Now, on to the main subject.
You read this, didn't you?
Sorry.
I thought I might find the owner's name inside, so just a little...
So that means you read the thing I scribbled...
What a shame.
Sounds like I'm about to lose a classmate.
Wait a minute.
What?
What do you mean, the thing you scribbled?
Huh?
I thought your handwriting was really neat...
Hang on...
Let me ask again.
You read what was inside this notebook, right?
Yeah.
Which means you read the thing I scribbled.
Yeah, and I'm asking what you mean by that.
What?
All I saw was a schedule and some memos.
Huh?
Could this be a misunderstanding?
Oh, looks like it.
Shut up!
You weren't being clear.
You didn't give me a chance to.
If you didn't see anything, you
should've just said so loud and clear!
It's your fault I read too deeply into this!
But...
Geez...
Hey, uh...
What?
So... is your normal personality just an act?
W-
Heh, that was easy to see.
So what?
Ayatsuji Tsukasa Arc
Chapter 2
Inner Side
What's so bad about it?
Are you saying that I'll trouble others that way?!
Sorry, I'm not saying it's bad.
Well, that's fine.
It's not a problem as long as you don't tell anyone.
All right, repeat after me.
"I saw nothing."
"Ayatsuji-san is a wonderful person with nothing to hide."
Huh?  Why do I have to?
But Tachibana-kun, you touched my chest...
T-That was-
You're horrible!
You've defiled my innocence!
I'll have to talk to your family and the teachers about this...
Okay, I get it.
I saw nothing, and uh...
"Ayatsuji-san is a wonderful person with nothing to hide."
Ayatsuji-san is a wonderful person with nothing to hide.
Very good.
As a reward, how about touching it again?
Huh?!
That's um... uh...
I'm obviously kidding.
Geez, don't take that kind of thing seriously.
Anyway, you saw nothing, and you'll say nothing.
Got it?
Understood.
All right.  Since that's taken care of, let's go home.
U-Uh, can I ask you something?
What?
What exactly is the thing you scribbled?
Ah, let's see.
I guess you could say it's something that'd
make me leave the school if someone read it.
And for that, I'll make sure the person who read it won't want to come back either.
I-I saw nothing!
Ayatsuji-san is a wonderful person with nothing to hide!
Yes, very good indeed.
Huh?
What's wrong, Nii-nii?
Miya, there are things in this world we're better off not knowing.
Huh?
Princess Nukata, one of the
representative poets of the Asuka period,
is also known as a woman who had many lovers.
Even if I told someone that
Ayatsuji-san has a hidden side to her,
I'm sure nobody would believe me.
Huh?
What about Ayatsuji-san?
Well, the truth is, yesterday...
Um... yesterday...
Tachibana-kun.
Oh, speak of the devil.
What?
Oh, he was just telling me he had something to say about you.
Oh, he must be talking about my notebook.
Notebook?
Yeah, Tachibana-kun found and returned the notebook I dropped yesterday.
What?  That's all it was?
Hey, Tachibana-kun.
There's some committee stuff I'd like to talk to you about.
Do you have a moment?
Y-Yeah.
Boss, hang in there.
Yeah.
Founder's Festival
Planning Committee Headquarters
Didn't you promise not to tell anybody?
Y-Yeah...
So why were you about to tell Umehara-kun?
Because...
Because?
I wanted to see if anyone would believe me if I said that you had another side to you.
Right, so you wanted to see.
I-I'm sorry!
Well, whatever.
Huh?  You'll forgive me?
Forgive you?
I'll make sure you don't get any more funny ideas.
I'm going to have you work your butt off.
57th Annual
Kibitou High School Founder's Festival
Courage   Camaraderie
Contact   Conventions
Event Date: 12/24
Event Location: Kibitou High School Grounds
I'm finally done for the day!
Whoa, it's this time of night already?
It's gotten really late.
Nice work.
Ayatsuji-san, you're doing this too?
Here.
Thanks.
Morishima-senpai said she wanted to do it so I let her, but it looks like she gave up halfway.
So, Ayatsuji-san...
Hmm?
Why do you work so hard to prepare for the Founder's Festival?
Isn't that obvious?
It's for my own sake.
Huh?
If things get delayed, my standing as the committee president will be damaged.
I obviously can't let that happen.
I'm trying to look perfect here.
Right.
Besides, I like being in charge anyway.
Having held positions like class rep and committee
president will help me get recommendations for college.
You sure are looking out for yourself.
What?  You have a problem with that?
N-No, that's not what I meant...
Anyway...
Thanks for this.
Ah, should I help?
Huh?  You don't have to.
But...
Tachibana-kun, you're weird.
Huh?
I mean, you know my secret, don't you?
If I were you, I'd distance myself from someone like me as much as I can.
You have no idea what I'm thinking about.
There aren't any clear benefits from being with me.
Yet you offer to help me and bring me refreshments, all by yourself.
So why?
You're asking me why?
Let's see...
Because it's fun, I guess.
Fun?
Yeah.
You're really talented, so it's pretty fun to do all this together.
And while there's lots to do every day,
the more I work the more fulfilling it gets...
The committee work is also proving to be very interesting.
I see.
Hmm...
Hey, I think I'll help after all.
Didn't I already say you don't have to?
But Ayatsuji-san, didn't you stay behind yesterday and the day before?
Whatever, just go home and sleep!
Don't forget that you are part of the
Founder's Festival planning committee!
If you fall asleep in class again...
...your standing as the committee president will be damaged?
Exactly right.
So you do understand.
Well then, see you tomorrow.
Gotcha.
Hmm... is it just me?
It's like Ayatsuji-san doesn't want to go home...
Morning.
Ah Junichi, you're finally here!
Why are you freaking out so early in the morning, Kaoru?
How can you be so calm?  This is serious!
What's serious?
Ayatsuji-san passed out from working too hard!
Huh?
I'm pretty sure Ayatsuji-san's house is around here.
Here, come on.
Uh...
Oh?  Good afternoon.
Hello, and good afternoon.
Um... you must be Tsukasa-chan's friend, Takahashi-kun.
I-It's Tachibana.
Ah, that's right.  Tachibana-kun.
Ooh, are you visiting Tsukasa-chan?
Yeah, I guess...
Ah, but if Tsukasa-san isn't feeling very well at all...
Could you please give this to her?
I... don't really know how she's feeling.
Tsukasa-chan hasn't been talking very much.
I see.
You're already here anyway, so you might as well go see her.
Our home is right there too.
Um, but...
It's all good.
It's best that you ask her how she's feeling face-to-face!
W-Wait, Onee-san!
Tsukasa-chan?
Tsukasa-chan.
Looks like she's fast asleep.
Geez, couldn't she just let me sleep in peace?
Ah, I'm really sweaty.
T-T-There's an explanation for this...
Wait, listen to me!
I see, that woman...
Yeah.  She said I should at least see you since I'm already here.
Damn it, she's always doing whatever she wants...
Sorry, I'll leave right away.
You don't have to.
Thanks for visiting me.
Though I don't know what to think about you bringing bananas and energy drinks for a girl.
I heard you overworked yourself, so I
thought these would help you recover.
Anyway, how are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I just have a light fever, so I should be able to go to school tomorrow.
I see... that's a relief.
You really are a weirdo.
Huh?
I'm saying you're a weirdo.
Am I now?
Though, your sister's personality is also pretty unique, Ayatsuji-san.
What?
It's like she's zoned out...
Or you could say she's lost in her own world...
She feels like a totally different person from you, Ayatsuji-san.
I see.
Ayatsuji-san, your sister...
Sorry, I'm going to sleep for a bit.
Ah, okay.
Sorry I stayed for so long.
Well, I'm off.
Tachibana-kun.
Thanks for visiting me.
It's cool.  Take care.
Oh?  Going home already?
Hello.  Thanks for having me over today.
You could've stayed just a little longer.
I shouldn't stay for too long.
Is Tsukasa-chan awake?
Yes.
We talked a little, and she just said that she's gonna sleep some more.
How is she?
She said that she just has a light fever and should be able to go to school tomorrow.
I see!
By the way Onee-san, what are you doing?
Oh, I bought this sports drink for Tsukasa-chan,
but she doesn't want it, so I'm giving it to this dog instead.
Tachibana-kun, do you want it?
No, I'm fine.
I see.
You know, I wonder if stray dogs nowadays have been trained not to warm up to people.
Huh?
He isn't warming up to me at all.
I-I see.
Uh... well, I'll be going now.
Okay.
See you.
It's a little hard to believe that she and Ayatsuji-san are sisters.
Actually, it looks like Ayatsuji-san doesn't like her sister very much...
This looks complicated.
Morning, Tachibana-kun.
Morning, Ayatsuji-san.
I'm glad you recovered.
Yes, didn't I say that I'd recover soon enough yesterday?
But it's possible that the bananas and the energy drinks worked.
Then I guess it's a good thing I brought them over.
Whoa, it's Morishima-senpai!
What's she doing on the junior-year floor?!
Tsukahara-senpai's here too!
What a lucky morning!
Do you have a moment?
Sorry for disturbing you this early in the morning.
I'd like to ask the committee president about something regarding the Founder's Festival.
What is it, Tsukahara-senpai?
Well...
Yes.
The truth is...
Hmm?
Geez, I can't wait anymore!
The truth is, Hibiki decided to come out of her shell and create a final high school memory.
She finally decided to participate in the Miss Santa contest!
Wait, Haruka!
Tsukahara-senpai is...?
The Miss Santa contest?!
Since this is pretty rare, I suggested that she wear a bikini or something.
Something naughty like this!
Huh?!
A... A naughty bikini?!
Ouch!
Ayatsuji-san, you're stepping on my foot!
Ooh, I'm sorry.
Well, I'm worried Haruka'll make me wear
something incredible if I leave it to her to decide,
so I thought I'd confirm with you if there are any rules and the like.
So... well?
Just how far can we go with the costumes for the contest?
Hibiki's curves from her back to her ass are really nice, so we'll definitely want to expose them!
Her curves from her back to her ass?!
Ouch!
Ayatsuji-san, you're stepping on my foot again!
Ooh, I'm sorry.
I see.
It's a high school festival, so people from outside this school will be present.
I'd appreciate it if you'll avoid going for something too daring.
Come on...
But I'm not saying you can't at all.
Okie-dokie!
We did it!  That's what we need!
However, please keep it reasonable.
W-We understand.
This year's Miss Santa contest is going to be amazing!
Though, why do we need mackerel cardboard boxes?
I have no idea at all what they'll be used for...
That cry...!
Ayatsuji-san!
Tachibana-kun.
What happened?
N-Nothing, really.
Did you hurt your foot?
Lemme see.
Ayatsuji-san.
What?
Why is your foot wet?
Ayatsuji-san?
He... on me.
He urinated on me.
W-Who did?!
Idiot!  A dog, obviously!
A... A dog?
I saw this expensive-looking dog on the school grounds.
I thought that I could probably use him for something, so I tried to catch him.
And then he really warmed up to me...
Ah, dogs urinate when they're happy.
This is quite the disaster!
This isn't funny.
S-Sorry.
Here.
Huh?
What?
What else?  I'm carrying you.
Huh?!
I mean, not like we can do anything about this here.
We'll need to wash your shoes and stuff, so I'll carry you to the taps.
What'll people say if they see us like this?!
It doesn't matter what people'll say.
We have nothing to hide.
I'm not fine with this!
Okay, I'm sorry.
Just stay still, or you'll fall!
Where do you think you're groping?!
B-But I'm not groping...
Pervert!
Whatever, say what you want.
Everyone, there's a pervert right here!
Actually, please give me a break.
Nope!
But someone might see us if you make too much noise.
Tachibana-kun's a real mystery.
Maybe it's because he has different values than I do?
I'm a little curious.
Huh?  Thinking about it, isn't this the first time I've ever been curious about someone?
How strange.
Hey there Tsukasa, don't tell me you're interested in him?
Geez, what the heck am I thinking?!
Ahh, it's Tachibana-kun's fault that I'm losing my studying time!
Geez, I'm mad!
I'm really going to toy with you next time!
Step Up
For Dummies
Math II
Question Book
Prepare yourself!
Hodou wo kazaru aoi Illumination
The blue illumination adorns the sidewalk
Nigiwau hitogomi ni hitori tatazumu
And I stand alone in the swarming crowd
Koboresou na egao
Smiles peeking through
Yorisou koibitotachi
Lovers snuggling against each other
Ima no watashi ni wa subete ga
Everything to me now is so bright
Mabushikute mirenai no
That I cannot bear to look
Dareka ni aisareru deshou ka
Will anyone love me?
Tsuyogari no oku ni kakureta
I'm hiding underneath a facade
Watashi ni kizuite yo
Please realize that
Hontou ni jiyuu ni nareru deshou ka
Can I really become free?
Douka oshiete
Please tell me
Fuyu no machi ni mayoikonda
Having lost her way in the winter town
The lonely angel sighs
Samishige na tenshi ga nageku
Yasashiku
Gently
Preview
Next episode preview!
Tachibana-senpai, you seem happy.
How do I say this, isn't it nice to find a sense of fulfillment through hard work?
Let's see... I don't know if working too hard is a good thing,
but I do enjoy doing housework quite a bit.
Ooh Nanasaki, you're more domestic than I thought.
R-Really?
All right, I'm gonna work even harder on the committee stuff!
Next Episode
Pride
Next episode: "Pride".
Senpai, be sure to follow up after Ayatsuji-senpai.
Huh?  Oh, but of course!