Kibitou High School
Founder's
Festival
Everyone, make sure you don't get hurt.
Follow the instructions of the committee officials, and let's get everything cleaned up.
Okay!
Looks like we had another successful Founder's Festival.
We even got a certificate from the alumni saying that our Oden maintained its traditional flavor this year.
That's a relief.
Yes.
Nanasaki, I'm thinking of giving this recipe to you.
Girl's Swim Club
Oden Stall Recipe
Secret Formula!!
To me?  Not one of the juniors?
Yeah.
I want you to have it.
The Daikon you cooked was delicious.
No... it was no match for your Konbu, Senpai.
Nanasaki, I want you to take this recipe and maintain the traditional flavor of the Swim Club from now on.
I understand, Senpai.
Ai-chan, make sure you prepare lots of the Chikuwa that I love next year.
I'll look forward to it when I come with Hibiki.
I don't know if I'll come next year.
Come on...
Come and eat some Chikuwa with me!
Rihocchi.
Are you all done there?
Yes, I'm just about finished.
All right.
It's almost the end of this year.
Yes.
Time really does fly.
Yeah, it really does.
Well, let's get going.
Come with me.
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Typesetter: fnord
Stuff: ar
Huh?
Junichi, why are you here?
Because Senpai asked me to come.
It's to thank him for helping us out.
Isn't drinking tea under the blue sky like this pretty nice?
It feels really refined.
Yeah, it does!
The road to refinement is difficult.
Well, it's better than doing this on a blazing hot summer day.
Plus, don't you feel the elegance from going through the trouble to have it outside?
Sakurai Rihoko Arc
Chapter 3
Succession
The road to appreciating elegance is difficult.
You're probably right.
Ahh, the kotatsu is just like heaven.
Rihocchi, any more and you'll be rooted to it.
So you guys have open-air tea ceremonies from time to time?
Yeah.
We also do one at the start of spring to attract new members.
Wow, I never knew.
It's not very exciting, so we don't get many visits.
We also had to cancel it last year because it rained.
The snacks we prepared got left over...
That must have been tough...
Well, our only new member over there took care of that problem easily.
I see...
Thank you very much.
Open-air tea ceremonies are quite nice.
Right?
I was thinking it'd be even better if we had some music to go with it.
Ah, but I guess that interferes with enjoying the outdoor atmosphere.
Music...
Music, huh?
That's pretty clever!
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe we should start doing that next year.
Good idea.
Should we ask the Wind Instruments Club if they want to recruit with us?
Ah, that sounds good.
We're counting on you, Rihocchi.
We'll come visit next year.
Yes!
I see.
You'll both graduate next spring, right?
Pretty much.
It'll get lonely around here.
Don't worry!
I'll definitely keep the Tea Club going!
All right, time to clean up.
Oh?  So you have some interest in tea?
Huh?
It's actually a lot harder than it looks...
Right?
Tea is a deep discipline.
It's no good...
I can't do it well.
You're hopeless.
Junichi, want me to do it?
Yeah.
That doesn't look like how they do it at all...
Rihoko, you don't seem much better than me.
That can't be true!
Okay, Senpai.  Off we go.
We're going.
Yeah, take care on your way home.
Don't fall over.
Yes, see you la-
Ow...
H-Heavy...
Are you okay?
Man...
You really live up to expectations, Rihocchi.
I'll count on you next year too.
S-Sorry, Junichi!
Go for it, Rihocchi.
Thank you for cleaning up.
The Tea Club's event was a big success, wasn't it?
Thanks.
Sorry I caused so much trouble yesterday...
You're probably the only one who gets that drunk from sweet sake, Sensei.
Ahh, how embarrassing.
Sensei, be careful next year, okay?
You need a lesson.
I'll be careful...
The committee president sure has her act together.
Rihocchi should take a leaf out of her book.
She might as well take the whole book.
Yeah.
Merry Christmas!
It's Christmas Day instead of Christmas Eve,
but I'm glad the three of us can have a Christmas party like this.
I agree.
It's the second one in a row for Miya and me.
Thanks for doing this for me...
Did you bring this cake and food, Nakata-san?
Yeah.
When I told my dad we're having a party at Miya's place, he prepared it and told me to bring it with me.
Isn't it amazing?
What a big cake.  I wonder if we can finish it.
No worries there.
I have a spare stomach for cake!
Both of you gave me a present yesterday, so I'm returning the favor.
Here.
Thank you!
Hey, Junichi.
Are you free today?
Um...
I know you're on a diet, but making me order alone...
You're just having water?
You should order something too, Rihoko.
Well, I just ate a lot of snacks in the clubroom...
I need to control myself...
What?
I can't eat it if you keep staring at it.
You can have half.
I can't!  I have to hold back!
Then stop staring at my cake.
But...
Would you like some more coffee?
Ah, Kaoru.
Working on Christmas, huh?
Must be tough.
I guess so.
But in exchange for that, I'm planning on having New Year's Eve and New Year's Day off.
Every year on the 31st, my mom and I clean up the house and prepare food for the New Year.
And when midnight arrives, we visit the shrine.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Okay, enjoy.
So what did you want to talk about?
Well, Junichi...
It's about returning the favor for my last present...
Oh, did you think of something?
Yeah.
Uh, um... well...
I want to go on a New Year's shrine visit with you... or something...
Sure.
Really?!
Yeah.
But are you sure that's all you want?
Okay, come to my place at night on the 31st then.
Okay!
I guess I'll have the cake after all!
Yeah, go ahead.
So good!
Oh, it's Kanae-san!
Kanae-chan?
Where?
Look, over there!
I'm sure Kanae-san would be upset if she saw her friend Rihoko eating cake when she's supposed to be on a diet...
Uh... where is she?
Look, over there!
Where?!
Here.
Just kidding.
Aw... Geez, Junichi!  All you do is lie!
H-Hey, Rihoko!
What was that?
Didn't you ask me to help you with your diet?
I guess I did...
I'll definitely work out for what I ate later...
Yeah.
I'll exercise more than I usually do, so I'll be just fine.
Phone, phone...
Beaver
Three Kingdoms
By
Beaver
Nii-nii, the phone's ringing!
The phone, Nii-nii!
Okay, I'll go get it!
Miya!  What's with that get-up?
I was in the middle of taking a bath!
It's cold, so hurry up and get it!
Who is it?
Ume-chan.
What could it be?
How nice!
A pretty girl came out of the bath to pick up my phone call!
And she's only in a bath towel...
Bye.
Aw man, wait, wait!
Can I come borrow that new video we were talking about for winter break?
Sure... when are you coming?
How about New Year's Eve?
If anything, we might as well have a
viewing party right at your house, boss!
We could pick out the porn video of the year or something...
Ah, and let me try that new shooting game you told me about.
Sorry, I can't on New Year's Eve.
I'm going for a shrine visit with Rihoko.
What?!  You traitor!
What are you talking about?!
You're going for a shrine visit with Sakurai-san!
Since when did the two of you get that close?!
You're a horrible person to keep that from me...
You're so cold!
Well, I dunno how many times I've said this,
but Rihoko is just my childhood friend.
Boss, did you know?
Sakurai-san is apparently pretty popular.
She gets letters from guys and stuff...
Oh, really?
Happiness may be found at a place closer than you think.
Wait... wasn't I quite the poet?
Well?  Wasn't that pretty clever?
Yeah, right.
Oh, that's right.
Come over today if you're gonna.
There's something I want you to lend me too.
Oh?
So you actually asked him?
Good job, Sakurai!
That's good.
Yeah, that's good, but I also have some bad news.
Entrance Ceremony
Huh?  What's the matter?
Well... there was this sweet cake, and...
You ate it?!
Yeah, Junichi said I could have it, so I couldn't help it...
Geez, you're hopeless.
But I'm definitely gonna exercise!
You know, working out for what you ate...
Okay.  Well, go for it, Sakurai.
Yeah.
Two...
Three...
My goal is a hundred...
But it's impossible...
A shrine visit with Junichi, huh?
I can't wait...
Hey, Miya!
Get the door!
Miya, you there?
Geez, guess I'll get it.
Coming!
Oh, Miya.
So it was you, Rihoko?
Nii-nii!
Sorry!
Geez, Junichi!
You came over pretty early.
Yeah, I wanted to have a nice chat with Miya-chan since it's been a while.
Let's have some New Year's soba together!
Yeah!
All right, it should be about done.
It's delicious!
Right?
Nii-nii keeps making the tea for us recently.
Even though he's never done anything like this before...
The Tea Club seniors taught me how to make good tea, and I kinda got addicted to it.
Junichi's tea might even be better than mine.
The water temperature and steeping time are important.
That's how you make good tea.
What are you showing off for?!
Does it matter?
Okay, okay.
The two of you shouldn't fight over something that small.
Oh yeah, have some of this.
I'm challenging myself to make new stuff!
Cheese soufflés!
Wow, they look delicious!
Cheese soufflés...
What happened to your dieting, Rihoko?
I-I took care not to use too much sugar in these cheese soufflés!
Doesn't cheese have a lot of calories?
Uh, um...
Ah, it's delicious!
Whoa, you're right.
This is really good.
Really?  I'm glad.
Well, I'll have one too!
Doesn't the singing program on TV start soon?
Yep, yep!
Who's the highlight of this year again?
Sabu-chan, obviously.
Ah, you're right.
Oh, I see.
That reminds me, that idol unit is
performing in this year's show, right?
I can't wait!
Look!
Miya-chan, you like it too?
Yep, I do!
Wow, Riho-chan!  You're so cool!
Yeah, that was pretty good.
Really?
Now the two of us will have to make our debut!
I don't know about making a debut...
Huh?  Why?
I like singing, but I don't know about becoming an idol...
Why not?
Why not?  No real reason...
Ah, it's starting!
Hey, Nii-nii, hand me the remote.
Don't you have it?
No, I don't.
That's because I definitely can't have New Year's Eves like this if I become an idol.
Well, we should get going.
Yeah!
Miya-chan fell asleep though.
She's hopeless.
Well, I'll go get ready, so could you wake Miya up for me?
Yeah, I will.
Miya-chan.  Miya-chan.
All right, I'm ready!
Huh?
Geez, what'll we do if the hunter becomes the hunted?
Nnh... soybean flour is good too, but peanut butter might be...
Heh... snacks even in her dreams, huh?
I wonder if Sakurai is with Tachibana-kun around now?
Ah, I fell asleep...
The shrine visit!
J-Junichi!  Miya-chan!
Wake up, wake up!  We slept in!
It's probably a good thing there aren't many people around.
Yeah.
We'd probably have to wait in line for about an hour to pray if we came around midnight.
Oh yeah, didn't we also come here to pray for our high school entrance exams?
Yep.
Rihoko, you'd always fall asleep in the middle of solving math problems.
Rihoko, did you solve question 2 yet?
That's right.
It was during Summer break.
Ah, time for a break.
In the end, I just kept getting distracted.
In the end, I just kept eating.
But... we still managed to pass...
Happy New Year
Here.
Oracle
Hmm?
In return for your present.
Thanks!
They said to write your wishes on it and hang it over there.
Okay.
What should I do...
Have you decided what you'll write?
Ah, that's right...
I wish my diet will be successful
I wish new members will join the Tea Club
Rihoko
I wish my diet will be successful
I wish new members will join the Tea Club
Nii-nii!  Riho-chan!
Let's go draw our oracles!
Okay.
Okay, wait for me.
Yay!  I got "excellent luck"!
"Small luck".
I got "uncertain luck"...
So I win.
"Uncertain luck" and "small luck", I wonder which is better?
Well, "uncertain" means it might not happen, so isn't it the worst?
It could be "uncertain" as in "uncertain boundaries", so it could be there's no end to my luck.
Out of the way!
Lord "Excellent Luck" is coming through!
What the heck is that?
Ah, they have Zenzai!  Let's have some!
TL Note: Zenzai is a thick, sweet red bean soup with mochi.
Zenzai...?
Well, I guess it's fine, since it's New Year's.
Huh?  What, Junichi?
I wish my diet will be successful
I wish new members will join the Tea Club
Rihoko
Rihoko, you'll be having Zenzai with no mochi, right?
I wish my diet will be successful
I wish new members will join the Tea Club
I wish my feelings will reach him someday ♥
Rihoko
What?  It wouldn't be Zenzai then!
join the Tea Club
I wish my feelings will reach him someday ♥
Rihoko
Kokoro ga kyunto
The area around my heart tightens
Sukoshi dake kyunto
Just a little bit
Shimetsukerareta nara
Since it's tightening like this
Hontou no koi na no ka na
Could this be true love?
Futari shibafu no ue
Didn't the two of us use to
Fuzakete nekoronda ne
Play around and lie down on the grass?
Mujaki datta
We were so innocent
Osanakatta hibi
During our childhood days
Demo kokoro no oku de
But deep in my heart
Sodatte yuku kanjou wo
A feeling was growing
Sukoshi zutsu kizukihajimeteta
And I slowly came to realize it
Onaji toki wo sugoshita bun dake
The more time we spent together
Sunao ni narenakute
The less able I was to be honest
Toomawari shita
I did things indirectly
Kokoro de gyutto
My heart tightens
Tonari de sotto dakishimete
As you gently embrace me
Anata wo mitsumeteru yo
I can't take my eyes off you
Sore wa chiisa na koi no hajimari
That's the beginning of this small love of mine
Ima wa mada ienai kedo
I can't tell you this just yet
Anata ga suki da yo
But I love you
Preview
Next episode preview.
The New Year has finally arrived, Rihocchi!
Happy New Year.
Let's have a good year together!
Yeah, let's have a good year to-
Wait, we're graduating this year!
Oh, you're right.
Absentminded.
Get a grip now!
Next episode: "Farewell".
Next Episode
Farewell
I'd better get new club members...
Are new club members all you'll be getting?
Huh?
A darling.
Huh?!