This boy's name is Tachibana Junichi.
He is 17 years old and a junior in high school.
He experienced a very shocking
disappointment on Christmas two years ago.
After carrying those scars for so long, he's now afraid of love.
It doesn't sound that bad,
but he wasn't exactly the type to
pursue a relationship even before that.
Perhaps he's just weak-spirited, or simply lovelorn-
Um... could you just leave it at that?
At any rate, he's the protagonist of our story.
What a cute girl.
Her chest is... i-incredible.
A fated encounter between boy and girl...
...didn't happen just yet.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Ichinichi no hajimari to
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
My feelings will never change
UTW Staff
Translator/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Editor: IGChris
Typesetter: Kemeko
Stuff: ar
Summer vacation ends, and the second semester begins.
After all kinds of events over summer, there are new couples budding all over the school.
All right!
Let's have some of that summer-only
Chinese meal set today and boost our stamina!
What would you do with that extra energy?
Well, guys have to be prepared for when the time comes!
Boss, wanna come with me?
No thanks.  I don't think I'll need it.
Unfortunately for them, none of those summer events actually occurred.
Tachibana-kun, Umehara-kun.
I'll be collecting your summer physics homework after school, so make sure it's ready.
Oh, okay.
We had physics homework?
Come on, didn't they give us printouts?
Oh yeah, that's right.
Did you forget?
Ishigaki-sensei is pretty scary, you know.
Yeah... I have until after school, right?
So I'll skip fifth period, and...
Don't be skipping classes now.
I guess I'm not having lunch today.  No food, huh?
Fine.  I'll go buy something for you.
Oh, you're a true friend!  I owe you one!
All right.  A cutlet-sandwich, croquette bread, and a Chinese noodle sandwich, please.
Okay.
Sorry.
You're awfully flustered.
Um... I'm so sorry.
You should be more careful going around the stairs.
O-Okay.
Morishima-senpai...
The girl saw that coin purse and thought, "C-Cute".
Ah... um...
Junichi!
Oh, Rihoko.
Nakata Sae Arc
Chapter 1
Underclassman
I got you a souvenir from my summer trip!
Ah, your coin purse...
A trip?  Did your whole family go?
Yeah, it was a lot of fun!
I'll give you your souvenir next time, okay?
Yeah, thanks.
See you!
Um... excuse me!
At that time, there was no way her voice could've reached him.
This was because the face of his waiting friend was on his mind.
He had to get those sandwiches as soon as possible and return to his friend!
Run!  You must run!
Umehara is waiting!  He believes in you!
Pardon me, I'm cutting through.
Sorry about that.
It's okay...
Uh, a cutlet-sandwich, a croquette bread, and...
Oh no!  The Chinese noodle sandwiches are sold out!
Sign: Sweet Bean Bun - Chinese Noodle Sandwich
Sorry, Umehara.
I'll give this to Umehara...
And I guess I'll just have udon or something.
Whoa.  Looks like that'd take a while.
I guess I'll just have some bread too.
Huh, where's my coin purse?
No way.
That's strange.  I had it just a minute ago.
U-Um...
Oh, that's my coin purse!
Did you pick it up for me?
O-On... the stairs...
Oh, I must've dropped it when I ran into Morishima-senpai.
You really saved me.
If I didn't have my Tarako coin purse, I'd have had to skip lunch today.
TL Note: Tarako, or cod roe, looks fairly similar to that purse.
Tarako?
Tarako...
Wait, this girl...
I saw her the other day...
Hey, you were wearing the uniform
of another school the other day, right?
Are you a transfer student?
Freshman?
What class are you in?
What's your name?
I... I'm sorry!
I-I've gotta go!
W-Wait up!
What's with her?
Oh, crap!
Sign: Bread roll
The lunch battles at our school are
getting more and more intense, huh?
You were just a little late, and that's all you could get.
Are we expected to share this bread roll like good friends?
What's up, boss?
I'm gonna go look for her.
What?
I've gotta thank her properly.
Hey, can I eat the whole thing then?
Go ahead.
Hey, Miya.
Do you know a freshman with her hair tied up like this?
Um... do you mean pigtails?
Yeah!  And she's kinda timid.
She's cute, like a small animal.
She looks like she's about to cry.
And she's short, but how do I say this...
She's big where it matters?
Yeah!  That's exactly it!
Ah, I think I know who you mean.
But what about her?
She found my Tarako coin purse and brought it to me earlier.
I wanted to properly thank her.
Oh, so that's why.
I... I'm back.
Sae-chan, welcome back.
How'd it go?  Were you able to get your lunch?
Let me introduce you.
This is Nakata Sae-chan.
And this slightly perverted-looking guy here is my brother.
M-Miya!  What's that supposed to mean?
What?  You were practically drooling over her chest a minute ago.
That was...
Geez, you're pathetic.
Well, I don't blame you though.
Sae-chan's got a pretty nice body.
Sometimes I'll touch her for good luck.
T-Touch her?
Wow, incredible.  It's so soft.
Are you done yet?
It's so tender.
This is great!
Onii-chan, you look like a pervert.
What?  No, um...
Sae-chan.  I know Onii-chan's like this, but I hope you and him get along.
I already said this earlier...
But weren't you in a different uniform when I saw you the other day?
Sae-chan just transferred here for
the beginning of the second semester.
She finally got her own uniform too.
Thank you so much for bringing my coin purse back to me.
You ran away without warning, so I came looking for you.
That's because Sae-chan is afraid of strangers.
S-Sorry...
It's a very cute coin purse.
Oh, thanks...
I'm glad I was able to thank you properly.
This time, they were able to properly have their fated encounter.
A few days later...
Huh?
Nakata-san?
T-Tachibana-senpai.
What are you doing here?
T-There's a dog...
Dog?
I... I'm scared, so I can't pass.
Where is it?
Um... that house there.
There's a dog without a leash on the other side of the gate.
I'm scared it'll get past the gate and come after me.
I think you're safe with the gate there.
Okay, I'll go with you.
But...
We should be fine if we go together.
Okay.
Thank you... very much.
It's not scary at all.
I think...
Okay, let's go.
Yes.
What?  It's just a puppy.
Look, it's okay.
It's not scary at all.
Nakata-san?
Nakata-san!
Feeling better?
S-Sorry.
It's okay, don't worry about it.
We got past it just fine.
Though... you're scared of a puppy that small?
Y-Yes...
Excuse me.
Have you decided on what you want?
Kaoru.
What's with that look?
Is she your girlfriend?
S-She isn't!
Don't be such a baby.
You don't need to hide it!
I already said she isn't!
Well, introduce her to me.
She's Miya's classmate, Nakata Sae-san.
She's not my girlfriend, okay?
I'm Tanamachi Kaoru, Junichi's classmate.
Nice to meet you!
I've known Kaoru since middle school.
All right, now go away.
But you still haven't told me.
What?
How close the two of you are.
I-Idiot!
Just kidding.
I still haven't taken your order, right?
That's what you meant?
Coffee, then.
Okay, coffee with free refills,
perfect for those with empty wallets.
Shut up.
What about you, Nakata-san?
I'll have... the same thing...
Very well.
Two coffees, is that right?
Please wait a moment.
Well, enjoy.
What's wrong?
You couldn't stop staring at her.
Her uniform's... really cute...
Really?
You like that stuff?
Yes.  I'd like to try wearing one someday...
Nakata-san, have you ever had a part-time job?
I haven't.
I wasn't allowed to work in my previous school.
Well, I haven't either.
It's okay to hold part-time jobs at our school, so why don't you go ahead and try?
Okay.
I know!
Let's ask Kaoru if this restaurant is hiring.
Uh... okay.
Here is your coffee.
Would that be all for your order?
Coffee refills are free, so please
let me know if you'd like some more.
Please enjoy.
Uh, Kaoru.
Is this restaurant hiring right now?
Yeah, it's always hiring.
There you go.
You'd like a part-time job?
Uh, um...
Could you tell her about that in detail?
Sure.
I should be done in about an hour,
so we'll talk then.
All right, thanks.
Okay, later then.
What's wrong?
I'd like to have a part-time job...
But...
You should at least hear what she has to say.
I'm sure Kaoru can help you.
She's an idiot, but she's pretty reliable.
Okay...
Sorry!
Someone suddenly took the day off
and I have to pick up her shift.
I see.
Sorry for not being able to talk about this.
No, don't worry about it.
Well, there's a simple test you need to pass to work here.
It's usually an interview.
They just want to know whether you can talk to your customers and carry food.
It's nothing difficult.
See ya.
I see.
You should be fine with carrying food,
but I don't know about talking to your customers...
Let's practice together.
That's what he says, but she has no idea he hasn't come up with anything yet.
Oh, so that's why we're practicing at our house.
I was really surprised when you brought Sae-chan over.
Okay, I've got it!
Leave it to me!
Sae-chan decided to go for a part-time job after all.
Of course I'll help!
Thank you, Miya-chan.
So what should I do?
Why don't you play the role of customer, Miya?
Okay.
Onii-chan, what about you?
Me?
I'll... hmm, let's see.
Ah, I know!
My Teacher and I
I'll be the instructor!
I'll play the role of instructor.
My Teacher and I
Huh?!
Now, call me "Instructor".
I-Instructor.
Instructor.
Instructor...
That's right.
Now that it's established, you're in for some rough training, so get ready!
It's just like you said, Miya.
Nakata-san's really afraid of strangers.
Yeah, that's right.
That's why I don't think she'll pass the test unless we take drastic measures.
Yeah, I guess.
So let's aim for success by training you!
Yeah, I'll help too!
Sae-chan, can you do it?
Um...
Huh?!
I-I'll try... I think...
Let's see...
Let's start by getting your voice loud enough for the customers to hear.
Yes, Senpa-
Instructor.
I have a friend, Umehara, whose family runs a sushi restaurant.
When he helps out at the restaurant, his dad tells him to say:
"Welcome!" loud and clear from the stomach.
I need to speak from the stomach?
Yeah.
So that you'll be able to speak loudly, let's start with exercises in expanding and contracting your stomach.
Huh?
Well?  You got it?
Um... I don't really understand.
Place your hand here.
Got it?
Yes.
Then try it.
H-Huh?
Excuse me for a bit.
It's just training.
Okay.
Okay, breathe in and expand your stomach.
Now breathe out and contract your stomach.
Your stomach didn't expand at all.
Okay, breathe in.
Instructor?
What's wrong?
Wait, Nii-nii?  Are you okay?!
In proper breathing, you don't just breathe in.
You also need to breathe out .
All right.  Next, we'll train you to carry food!
Y-Yes, Instructor!
Well, let's have you carry that cup of coffee to me.
Yes, Instructor.
H-Here you go.
Ow, hot, hot...
W-What should I do?
What's the matter?
Nii-nii, you pervert!
She was met with the sight of her brother taking his pants off in front of her friend.
Thanks for having me over today.
Be sure to come again!
Senpai, thank you very much.
Y-Yeah.
It's your fault, Onii-chan.
You did something that's easily misunderstood.
Yeah, but...
Miya-chan, you're so lucky.
You have a brother that's like an instructor...
Really?
I'm an only child.
The way my brother is, you can take him anytime.
Ah, I know!
It's been a while, so let's play some piggyback rock-paper-scissors!
You serious?
Piggyback rock-paper-scissors?
Yeah.
The loser has to piggyback the winner.
That's not much of an explanation.
You say "pineapple ice cream" if you win with paper,
TL Note: Basically, the word has to start with the same syllable as the
winning trick, hence "painaisu" for paper (paa) and "guratan" for rock (guu).
and "Gratin" if you win with rock.
The loser takes as many steps as the number of syllables.
I see.
It's fun!
The rules are that the winner chooses the word,
and you can't repeat a word that's already been used.
That sounds fun.
I know, right?
Let's do it!
Well, I guess I'll have to teach you a thing or two.
There you go again!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yay!
Onii-chan, you lost!
You suck.
Okay.  The loser, Onii-chan, has to piggyback Sae-chan.
Um, well...
You don't have to.
No, no!
The rules of piggyback rock-paper-scissors are absolute!
But...
All right!
Then I'll just have to go for it!
Now come!
E-Excuse me.
I won't lose next time.
Actually, the boy doesn't mind losing forever.
In fact, he wants to keep losing.
A-Am I heavy?
Hmm?  Not at all.
Uh, l-let's see...
I won with rock, so...
How about "glamorous body"?
Come on, from your stomach!
Now!
G-Glamorous body...
Louder!  Glamorous body!
Go!
Glamorous body!
By the time the slightly perverted phrase passed
from her lips to his ears, it had become much worse.
That was actually pretty loud.
Now, let's go.
Glamorous body!
Under the evening sky, the boy carried the girl on his back.
As summer ends and autumn begins, will the
wheels of destiny begin to spin for these two?
The two of them have yet to find out.
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
Anata no koto omou dake de
Just thinking about you
Watashi shiawase desu
Makes me so happy
Ippai oshaberi shitakute
I want to have long chats with you
Ima sugu ni
Right away
Itsumo futarikiri dattara
If only we could always be alone together
Ii no ni na
It would be so nice
Tsugi ni au made wa sukoshi oazuke tsurai kedo
It'll be hard to wait until the next time we can meet
Motto daisuki ni nareru hazu ne
But in the meantime I'll grow to love you even more
Nareru hazu ne
I'll love you even more
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
My Darling itsumo soba ni itai
My darling, I want to always be by your side
Zutto anata shika mienai wa
I'll never look at anyone but you
Daisuki yo
I love you
Preview
Next episode preview!
Senpai, you're drooling.
I-I'm not!
You look like you had the time of your life losing to a glamorous underclassman in rock-paper-scissors and piggybacking her.
Did I hit the mark?
Next episode: "Training".
Next Episode
Training
The days where I train Nakata-san continue.
By the way, who are you?
I'm Miya-chan and Nakata-san's classmate, Nanasaki Ai.
Senpai.