Two years ago, in December...
My childhood friend Junichi suddenly invited me to go shopping with him.
I was overjoyed and left the house thinking it was a date.
However, Junichi just wanted me to help him
choose a Christmas present for the girl he liked.
I was kinda disappointed...
I did have a lot of fun choosing the present though.
But it looked like things didn't go well for Junichi and the girl in the end.
When I learned about it later, I felt
as bad as if it had happened to me.
Back then, and even now...
My love for Junichi has always been one-sided.
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
UTW Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Translator: Ershin
Timer: Kusion
Typesetter: fnord
Stuff: ar
Graduation Ceremony
Ceremonial Hall
Sakurai!
You're gonna be late!
It's so cold...
What are you, a pill bug?
Why didn't my alarm go off?
Your alarm did go off, loud and clear!
Huh?  Really?
Yeah.
I'm glad you came to get me, Kanae-chan.
Geez, you're really troublesome.
At any rate, you're late way too often these days.
Oh no!  I forgot something!
I'm going back to get it!
Wait, I'm on cleaning duty today!
What do I do?  What do I do?!
Well, I'll fill in for you today.
Quick, go back and get it!
Really?
Okay!
Sakurai Rihoko Arc
Chapter 1
Memories
I don't have enough time to make it through the main gate.
All right!
Huh?
If I can't pull myself through... I'll push!
No way!
Huh?  What?!
I-I'm sorry!
I was just trying to take a shortcut!
I accidentally forgot something at home this morning, and...
Uh... I went back to get it...
I'm really sorry!
I'll come out right away!
Calm down, Rihoko.  It's me.
Huh?  Junichi?
Junichi, is that you?
Yeah.
Waah, Junichi!
What are you doing?
I'm... uh...
Don't tell me... you're stuck?
Bingo...
Then I guess I'll have to make a dash to the gate.
Best of luck to you.
Huh?!
No way!
We've been friends for so long, but who would've thought we'd part like this?
May you rest in peace, Rihoko!
No!  Don't abandon me!
I'm just kidding.
You jerk!
I'm sorry.
I'll get you out of there, so don't get so mad.
Relax your body and lie flat.
Whoa, wait.
What now?
Can you... see?
See what?
Um...
Pa... Pan...
Pan?
Come on now, you're thinking about pancakes at a time like this?
Can you see my panties?!
I can't.
I see...
Okay then.
Ready?  I'll pull now.
Okay.
I-Idiot!  Don't make noises like that!
But my chest got caught...
Huh?  You sure it wasn't your belly?
It's not!
Whatever, let's try again.
One, two!
I'm out!  Hooray!
A-Are you okay?
Geez... have you put on weight again?
What?!
That's why you couldn't get through.
No, I'm sure it's because I'm wearing a lot today!
I wonder if it's because of this coat.
Nope, it's because you eat too much.
I've gotta run!
Junichi?
Rihoko, you should hurry too.
So your PE uniform was what you forgot?
Yeah.
Wasn't Tachibana-kun kinda a jerk though?  Leaving you behind like that...
No, not at all.
If Junichi hadn't come for me, I'd probably spend the rest of my life stuck there.
Uh, I highly doubt that...
I've always made it through that hole before.
Maybe I really did get fatter recently.
Is it because I eat too much?
Maybe...
Hey, why don't you try the Air Diet?
Huh?  Air Diet?
Yeah, when you feel like eating something, you go like this...
And take in a deep breath of air while pretending you just ate it.
Ooh, I see.
Yup, I'll try it tomorrow!
Oh yeah, you also need to exercise after eating.
Exercise?
Here it comes, Hibiki!
Catch it like a puppy!
What's that supposed to mean?
Here I go!
Ah!  Sorry!
Watch out!
Are you okay?
Yes, it's okay!
Sorry!  Are you okay?
It's fine, yes.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I'm really sorry about that.
Don't worry, it wasn't harmed at all.
How nice.  They both have have great figures.
I guess exercise really is important.
I'll start doing that tomorrow too!
But why are you starting a diet again?
Didn't you say you were done with them?
Nope, it's because you eat too much.
Well... uh...
There's no real... reason.
So did Tachibana-kun say something to you?
Junichi has nothing to do with this.
Yeah, right.  It's written all over your face.
You're wrong...
Actually, I think I'll start today!
I'll slim down enough to fit through that hole!
If you weren't so late all the time, you wouldn't need that hole-
All right, I'm gonna do it!
Kanae-chan, do you want this?
I'm already full.
Oh, I know!
Hey, Umehara.
Boss, what's up?
This...
Thanks bud.
So how was it?
Now I understand why you kept recommending it.
So which girl did you like best?
Let's see...
That girl in the back with the pink bikini and short hair.
She's a little chubby...
That girl, huh?
Now that you mention it, doesn't she kinda look like Sakurai-san?
Huh?  You think so?!
Keep your voice down, boss.
Neither of you have submitted your Japanese History assignments yet.
Can you turn them in if you're done with them?
Yeah!  Right away!
Okay, I'd appreciate it.
Junichi!
Rihoko.
These are for me?
Yeah.
Well, they're kinda like a thank-you for this morning.
And I'm...
...gonna go on a diet!
Right.  And I've heard you say that so many times that I'll probably go deaf.
I'm gonna try really hard this time!
Yeah, right.
So you're giving me the treats
you originally made for yourself?
How did you know?
Sure, I'll take them.
They're a little beat up from this morning, but I'm pretty confident about them.
I'm sure they'll taste great since you made them, Rihoko.
Thank you.
Hey, Tachibana-kun.
Are you free this Sunday?
Huh?
Kanae-chan?
Sakurai and I were talking about doing some sports together.
Wanna join us?  Skating or something.
Huh?  When did we-
Skating?
Umehara-kun, wanna come too?
Oh, I'd love to.
Boss, you're coming too, right?
Uh...
Okay, it's decided!
Thanks!
Kanae-chan?
Well, see you on Sunday!
Why'd you ask them to go skating?
It's fine, it's fine.
Panda Cocoa
oolong tea
Ah, I'm sorry!
No worries.
So what are you getting?
I'm getting a Panda Cocoa.
That has a pretty addictive flavor.
But it has a lot of calories.
I wonder if it'll make me fat.
I think you'll be fine.
PERSISTENCE
YIELDS
RESULTS
Senpai, there's something I want to tell you-
Ooh, Rihocchi.  Good timing.
Huh?
Ah, it's the choux crème from the bakery at the train station!
Bingo.
That's Dazzling Custard.
And that's True Chocolate.
Wow!  They look delicious.
Nobody's gonna take them from you, so eat as much as you want.
Dig in.
I'll start with a custard one!
Here I go!
It's delicious!
Rihocchi, do you know the etymology for the word "choux crème"?
No, I don't.
In ancient Hebrew, "shook" stood for "love", and "lim" meant "charm".
Really?
It was originally a treat you'd give to
someone you like when proposing to them.
You'd do well to remember that.
Yes.
Rihocchi, your cheek.
Huh?
Not that side.  Your right cheek.
There's more.
Can I really have more?
Yeah.
You're a growing girl.
I guess I'll have a chocolate one this time.
By the way, what did you want to tell us earlier?
Ah, I've decided to go on a diet.
Rihocchi, you...
Ah!  I, uh...
Looks like it won't go well this time either.
Um... I'm starting tomorrow...
So having it today means I'm barely safe...
E-Excuse me!
Geez, she's such an innocent girl.
About the etymology for "choux crème".
Ah yes, about that.
Didn't the word come from the French "choux à la crème"?
Yes.  It means "cabbage with cream inside".
Rihocchi fell for it.
Poor girl.
Though, what's gonna happen to the Tea Club once we seniors graduate?
There's only the three of us.
I'm worried for the future of the club with just Rihocchi.
Actually, without other club members, this club'll have to disband.
The club is in danger.
Wait, you two!
I don't have to go to my part-time job today.
We haven't played billiards in a while, so how about it?
Sorry, Kaoru.
We have business to take care of today.
Huh?  What business?
I can wait for you guys if it's quick.
Nope.
Today's business won't be taken care of that easily.
Right, Umehara?
Yeah.
Huh?  What's that mean?
We men have our own problems to take care of.
You shouldn't pry in any further, Kaoru.
Let's go, Umehara.
Yeah.
Sorry, Tanamachi.
Weirdos.
Actually, something isn't right.
Hey, so what do you have in return for lending you that book?
Try to stay calm.
This is it!
This is a collection of drawings.
A treasure among treasures.  I was so surprised!
You're kidding!  This was something you found at the school library?
Yeah, that's exactly right.  This one right here-
Stop right there, boss!
Whoops, I accidentally raised my voice.
Rihoko?
Right before you begin your diet,
you hide where nobody can see you and have a choux crème.
You...
Well, you'll probably give up right away.
That's mean.
I'll definitely succeed this time!
Why are you going on a diet again?
Well... I...
Um...
Well, you should try harder since you said you'd do it.
I'll be rooting for you too.
It's been so long since the last time we walked home together.
Huh?  Really?
Walking past here brings back childhood memories.
Like that slide.
Hey, was it during kindergarten?
Huh?
Remember?  You used magic, and...
Become a princess.
Become a beautiful princess!
A princess, a princess!
Don't you remember?
You were trying to turn me into a princess.
I was?
Oh, you mean that.
Huh?  Was it really a princess?
Become a delicious meat bun!
A meat bun, a meat bun!
We often played here when we were kids, didn't we?
It brings back memories.
Yeah.  I agree.
Junichi, here I go!
Careful now!
What?
Onii-chan and Riho-chan?
Onii-chan, Riho-cha-
Miya.
My butt's stuck.
No, I gained weight!
Ah, must be because the towel's heavy.
Huh?
It didn't change very much.
I need to get rid of this...
All right, I'll do my best!
I-I'm so stiff...
Ow...
It's a lot harder than I thought.
Maybe I'll try for real starting tomorrow.
I should be well on time today.
Ah, I'm gonna be late again!
Why does staying in bed feel so good?
I'll be late if I don't use this.
Please don't get stuck...
Huh?
I got through...
I got through!
Rihoko should've been able to get through that this morning.
All I did yesterday was a few stretches!
Oh?  Really?
That's good.
Yeah!
I get the feeling my diet'll work this time!
Yep!
Kokoro ga kyunto
The area around my heart tightens
Sukoshi dake kyunto
Just a little bit
Shimetsukerareta nara
Since it's tightening like this
Hontou no koi na no kana
Could this be true love?
Hikaru shibafu no ue
Didn't we use to play around
Fuzakete nekoronda ne
And lie down on the sunlit grass?
Mujaki datta
We were so innocent
Osanakatta hibi
During our childhood days
Demo kokoro no oku de
But deep in my heart
Sodatte yuku kanjou wo
A feeling was growing
Sukoshi zutsu kizukihajimeteta
And I slowly came to realize it
Onaji toki wo sugoshita bun dake
The more time we spent together
Sunao ni narenakute
The less able I was to be honest
Toomawari shita
I did things indirectly
Kokoro de gyutto
My heart tightens
Tonari de sotto dakishimete
As you gently embrace me
Anata wo mitsumeteru yo
I can't take my eyes off you
Sore wa chiisa na koi no hajimari
That's the beginning of this small love of mine
Ima wa mada ienai kedo
I can't tell you this just yet
Anata ga suki da yo
But I love you
Preview
N-Next episode preview!
Amazing, Sakurai!
They're letting you do the preview!
Yeah, I'm apparently the protagonist.
By the way, you shouldn't use that hole in the fence too much.
Why, Kanae-chan?
I mean, you'll scratch your knees and get your clothes dirty.
As a girl, you can't be looking like that in the morning!
Oh, I see...
Next episode: "Assistance".
Next Episode
Assistance
I wonder if Junichi'll dislike me for that.
You really are troublesome.